[Script Info]
; // The sub is created by AssToolkit
; // AssToolkit is an ASS Converter designed by David C.
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.35,0:00:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《行尸走肉》前情提要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Previously, on AMC's "The Walking Dead."
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.36,0:00:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能互相帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can help each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.06,0:00:07.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们过得很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're doin' fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.67,0:00:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.51,0:00:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要是回不来了怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What happens if you don't come back?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.84,0:00:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何都要活下去[JSS]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just survive somehow.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.69,0:00:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山顶寨有个医生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's a doctor at the hilltop.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.74,0:00:19.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会让你好转的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's gonna make things better.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.36,0:00:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  让我们帮忙吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pl-please let us.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.15,0:00:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也是我们的家人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's our family, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.43,0:00:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会送她去那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna get her there.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.11,0:00:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会保护她的安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna keep her safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.40,0:00:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Welcome back.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.24,0:00:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you remember me?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.11,0:00:49.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是卡森医生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm Dr. Carson.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.32,0:00:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在山顶寨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're at Hilltop Colony.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.34,0:00:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你睡了一阵子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've been asleep for a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.61,0:00:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的胎盘早期剥离了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You suffered from the condition abruptio placentae.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.93,0:00:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意思是胎盘与子宫分离\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a separation of the placenta from uterus.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.18,0:00:59.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这么早出现很不寻常\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's unusual this early,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.30,0:01:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  可能由创伤引起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but, uh...could be caused by trauma.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.53,0:01:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-也许是因为你腹部的瘀伤  -我是不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Possibly the bruises on your abdomen -- - Did I-I...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.63,0:01:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流产了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...lose...?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.76,0:01:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.00,0:01:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有小部分分离\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Separation was small.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.11,0:01:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子的心率正常\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Baby's heart rate is normal.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.60,0:01:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听听吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here, listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.54,0:01:27.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.63,0:01:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得缓几天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, you need to take it easy for a few days.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.37,0:01:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可不想加剧分离\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't want to exacerbate the separation any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.69,0:01:40.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你怀孕期间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I really think you need to stay here
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.75,0:01:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都该待在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for the duration of your pregnancy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.70,0:01:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果发生了别的事  我能处理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If anything else happens, I can take care of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.61,0:01:48.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有问题吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have any questions?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.54,0:01:51.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whoa, whoa. Easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.22,0:01:53.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢点  慢点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Easy, easy, easy, easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.40,0:01:56.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能再说一次吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you say that again?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.87,0:01:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.07,0:02:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚说的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everything you just said.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.88,0:02:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You, uh -- you okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.54,0:02:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.71,0:02:30.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们俩在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where are they both?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.77,0:03:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这在格伦的口袋里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was in Glenn's pocket.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.42,0:03:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚伯拉罕只有一根雪茄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All Abraham had was a cigar.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.93,0:03:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉一切都不对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It feels like everything is wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.80,0:03:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并非一切\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.29,0:04:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他告诉我你会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He told me that you're gonna be all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.30,0:04:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说你只用在接下来几天里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He said you'll just have to take it easy
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.61,0:04:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保重身体\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for the next few days.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.72,0:04:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他跟我说我们得留下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He told me that we have to stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.73,0:04:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That we, um...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.65,0:04:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说有他在附近会好些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He says it's better if he's close,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.57,0:04:22.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防万一  直到孩子出生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}just in case, till the baby's born.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.96,0:04:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们就留下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then we'll stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.20,0:04:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还在考虑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm still thinking about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.87,0:04:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要留下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're staying.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.04,0:04:32.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And so am I.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.34,0:04:37.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看见你起来了真好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's nice to see you up.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.27,0:04:39.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Flowers.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.69,0:04:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你放的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.08,0:04:43.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有你床边的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ones on your bed, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.12,0:04:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在书上看到  蓝色的花\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I read somewhere that blue flowers
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.99,0:04:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能激发力量  带来平静\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}inspire strength and calming.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.06,0:04:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绿色的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's green?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.72,0:04:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Release.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.90,0:05:04.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢天谢地你终于醒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank God you're finally awake.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.67,0:05:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的人说你们把他们全消灭了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You people said you got them all.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.32,0:05:08.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们以为如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We thought we did.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.80,0:05:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只是一个哨站\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was just an outpost.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.06,0:05:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们有多少人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}H-How many of them were there?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.15,0:05:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There were a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.19,0:05:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许几百个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe hundreds.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.16,0:05:19.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们知道你们逼我们接受的协议吗  玛莎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do they know the deal you made us take, Marsha?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.56,0:05:22.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是玛姬  -不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- It's Maggie. ‭- No.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.30,0:05:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也没逼你们接受协议  格雷戈里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And we didn't make you take the deal, Gregory.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.41,0:05:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很高兴我们能为你治疗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I-I-I'm happy we could patch you up.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.91,0:05:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们得走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You need to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.68,0:05:32.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确保瑞奇知道我们为你做的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Make sure you let Rich know what we did for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.53,0:05:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡森医生说我该留下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dr. Carson said I should stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.83,0:05:37.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他觉得他有权做出那个决定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If he thinks he has the authority to make that decision,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.63,0:05:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他就搞错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}he's mistaken.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.17,0:05:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样看着我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't look at me like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.69,0:05:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她跟自己人在一起会更安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She'll be safer with her own people.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.00,0:05:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我们没有她会更安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And we'll be safer without her.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.14,0:05:49.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该和玛姬保持距离\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You need to keep your distance from Maggie
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.82,0:05:51.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,专心于你在山顶寨的工作就好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and stay focused on your work here at Hilltop.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.81,0:05:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你干的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you do this?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.73,0:05:56.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不埋死者  而是火化\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We don't bury our dead. We burn them.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.95,0:05:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我干的  我不住在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I did it. I don't live here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.80,0:06:01.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格雷戈里  这位是萨沙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Gregory, this is Sasha.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.86,0:06:02.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是她把玛姬送来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She got Maggie here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.84,0:06:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她俩都是从亚历山大来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're both from Alexandria.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.54,0:06:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't ---
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.19,0:06:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没时间记住每个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I-I don't have time to keep track of everybody.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.57,0:06:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也一直在修养  耶稣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been recuperating, too, Jesus --
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.28,0:06:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,养我的刀伤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}from a stab wound.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.27,0:06:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.90,0:06:19.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬说她的人能搞定救世军\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maggie said that her people could take care of the Saviors.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.14,0:06:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如今他们只是让我们的社区陷入险境\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}S-So far, all they've done is put our community at risk.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.09,0:06:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如他们看见你在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, if they see you here,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.12,0:06:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会以为我们是一伙儿的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they'll think we colluded.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.57,0:06:26.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们确实是一伙儿的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We did.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.48,0:06:30.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可没同意你们这样做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I did not agree to this.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.93,0:06:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如他们觉得我们帮你们袭击了哨站\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If they think we helped attack their outpost,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.59,0:06:34.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们也会这样对我们的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they'll do that to us.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.70,0:06:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶稣  你知不知道什么叫装糊涂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jesus, do you have any idea what plausible deniability means?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.32,0:06:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.94,0:06:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你就该明白  这是我们逃避惩罚的办法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, then you know it's our way out.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.27,0:06:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如她俩离开  我们就能装糊涂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If they leave, we have plausible deniability.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.46,0:06:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格雷戈里  天快黑了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Gregory, it -- it'll be night soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.59,0:06:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们现在离开不安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not safe for them to leave now.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.26,0:06:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧  我是个好人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, I'm a good guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.70,0:06:52.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们可以留下来过夜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can stay the night.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.91,0:06:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但明早就得走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But leave in the morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.99,0:06:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们今晚再好好谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll talk more about it tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.69,0:06:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我心意已决\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I made my decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.10,0:07:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是觉得  也许...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm just saying that maybe --
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.50,0:07:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想和她俩一起走吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you want to go back with them?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.90,0:07:05.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会送她俩回去的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll take them back.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.06,0:07:09.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我的意思是...  -我知道你什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I meant -- - I know what you meant.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.99,0:07:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就这么定了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So it's settled.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.33,0:07:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, it's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.25,0:07:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬怀孕了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maggie is pregnant.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.28,0:07:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是她自己犯的错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well... that's her mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.71,0:07:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.76,0:08:22.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该和我们一起去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You should come with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.32,0:08:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得有人留下来照看朱迪思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Someone's got to be here for Judith.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.27,0:08:26.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人可以照看的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's people who want to help.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.37,0:08:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们最多出去几天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll only be gone a few days at the most.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.58,0:08:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要补给\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need supplies.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.38,0:08:32.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们很快就会回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're gonna be coming back soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.55,0:08:33.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后就是这样了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is this how it's gonna be now?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.85,0:08:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes. ‭
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.74,0:08:36.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It is.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.18,0:08:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你清楚的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.09,0:08:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几天后见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See you in a few days.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.32,0:08:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们该出发了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We should get going.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.09,0:08:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他会想明白的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He'll come around.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.21,0:08:56.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...到楼下等你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll, uh, meet you downstairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.35,0:09:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你改变主意了的话...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You change your mind...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.61,0:09:03.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们往北走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we're headed north.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.48,0:09:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你好运\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good luck.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.07,0:09:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.84,0:09:11.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过两天见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll see you soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.87,0:09:34.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.63,0:09:40.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么没和我爸一起走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why didn't you go with my dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.94,0:09:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得想清楚一些事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have to figure some things out.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.42,0:09:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么要想清楚的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is there to figure out?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.04,0:09:50.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要如何做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How we can do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.13,0:09:53.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如我们能做的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If we can.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.35,0:09:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.95,0:09:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少不是像这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, not like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.31,0:09:58.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸可不是这么想的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your dad thinks differently.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.92,0:10:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And he's wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.63,0:10:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.94,0:10:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然我确实这样想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even if I think he is...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.30,0:10:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不确定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.04,0:10:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,待会儿换绷带  对奥利维亚好点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Change your bandage later, and be nice to Olivia.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.84,0:10:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊妮德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Enid.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.28,0:10:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得去见玛姬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need to see Maggie.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.79,0:10:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要走着去山顶寨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're walking to the Hilltop?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.29,0:10:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太远了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's far.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.81,0:10:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.64,0:11:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.02,0:11:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.35,0:11:04.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我比你射得准\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have better aim than you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.24,0:11:13.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是那个意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't mean it that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.39,0:11:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会再救你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not saving you anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.70,0:11:21.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说在武器库的时候吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what happened in the armory?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.60,0:11:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得你救了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You saved me?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.17,0:11:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.90,0:11:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你安全回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You made it back in one piece.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.66,0:11:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're still here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.63,0:11:32.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的不是那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not talking about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.24,0:11:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很遗憾你看到了那场面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry you had to see it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.62,0:11:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不遗憾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.09,0:12:02.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的没法说服你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You sure I can't talk you into
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.03,0:12:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去住巴林顿公馆的空房吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}taking the extra room at Barrington House?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.08,0:12:14.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是要说一下  有你在我很高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For what it's worth, I'm glad you're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.79,0:12:18.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就劝格雷戈里改变主意吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then make Gregory change his mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.92,0:12:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会试试的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm going to try.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.33,0:12:21.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那还不够\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not good enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.55,0:12:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然不够\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.46,0:12:27.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这里的人需要我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But the people need me here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.18,0:12:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果只剩下格雷戈里  可能会更糟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If it was just Gregory, it'd be worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.69,0:12:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你为什么不掌权\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So why aren't you in charge?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.00,0:12:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是那种人  我不是领袖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not me. I'm not a leader.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.73,0:12:38.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我走呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What if I leave?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.46,0:12:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果让玛姬留下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If Maggie can stay,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.33,0:12:44.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会帮山顶寨搜集物资\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll scavenge, for the Hilltop.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.24,0:12:46.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们保护她  我会替她做贡献\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll pay her way if you just keep her safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.20,0:12:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格雷戈里会同意吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Would Gregory go for that?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.43,0:12:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.34,0:12:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不想这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I-I don't want that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.15,0:12:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎样  耶稣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you want, Jesus?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.14,0:12:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要这里变成什么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you want this place to be?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.39,0:13:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I-I just...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.05,0:13:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just try to help.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.11,0:13:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你该做得更多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe you got to do more.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.15,0:13:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个  是亚伯拉罕的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This, uh...This was Abraham's.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.73,0:13:25.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在这找到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I found it here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.04,0:13:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.35,0:13:44.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很喜欢他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I liked him.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.80,0:13:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我认识的人中唯一一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He was...one of the only people I'd ever met
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.21,0:13:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能讲出好笑又气人的话的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}who could say things that make you smile and wince at the same time.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.82,0:13:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come in.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.07,0:14:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你铺好床了  还摆了几件衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I made the bed for you and laid out some clothes.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.01,0:14:00.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是我的衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're mine,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.95,0:14:03.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以它们更多是实用而不是舒适\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so they're more utility than comfort.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.22,0:14:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.28,0:14:05.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不会住很久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We won't be here much longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.88,0:14:07.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对所有这些事  我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry, about all of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.99,0:14:10.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会试试看我能做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm...gonna see what I can do.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.14,0:14:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们为什么火化死者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why do you burn your dead?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.63,0:14:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是为了继续前行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The idea was just to keep going.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.75,0:14:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们靠什么来铭记逝者呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you have to remember 'em by?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.36,0:14:30.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠我们自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Us.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.03,0:14:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明早见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll see you in the morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.76,0:14:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now what? 
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.35,0:14:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我们可以硬留下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe we stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.89,0:14:57.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格雷戈里能怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What can Gregory do?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.53,0:14:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里他掌权\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's in charge.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.26,0:15:01.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是个傻瓜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's an idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.84,0:15:03.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是懦夫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's a coward.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.59,0:15:05.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懦夫更危险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're more dangerous.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.80,0:15:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有一晚上时间来考虑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have the night. Let's think on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.05,0:15:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上就会想清楚了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Things will be clearer in the mornin'.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.29,0:15:56.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}空气
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.22,0:16:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来这做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.76,0:16:25.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想兜兜风\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Felt like a drive.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.20,0:16:37.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.98,0:16:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大门开了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The gates are open.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.18,0:16:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有火\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's fires.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.58,0:16:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,音乐是从一辆车里传出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The music is coming from a car.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.23,0:16:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得关了它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have to turn that thing off.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.69,0:17:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡森医生不让你站起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dr. Carson told you to stay off your feet.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.52,0:17:03.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能让你一个人去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't let you do this by yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.61,0:17:04.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sit.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.16,0:17:06.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.24,0:17:52.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶稣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jesus!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.66,0:17:54.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨沙一个人在下面  她需要帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sasha's alone down there! She needs help!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.81,0:18:01.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死  玛姬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Damn it, Maggie.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.94,0:18:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们两个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You two!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.82,0:18:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去把门关上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get those gates closed!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.13,0:18:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}On it!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.27,0:18:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可恶  快点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, man, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.97,0:18:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  -抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Hi. - ‭Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.30,0:18:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.04,0:18:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得把门关上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need to close the gates.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.46,0:19:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.95,0:19:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨沙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sasha.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.49,0:19:13.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她可以的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.80,0:19:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这需要你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need your help here.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.34,0:20:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到那场面你不遗憾吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not sorry you saw it?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.31,0:20:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.25,0:20:14.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我眼睁睁得看着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I watched it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.07,0:20:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两次都是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Both times.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.17,0:20:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有移开视线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't look away.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.84,0:20:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.84,0:20:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为在那个时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because, when it was happening,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.68,0:20:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我得牢牢记住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I knew that I needed to remember it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.25,0:20:32.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以当我有机会杀他时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So when I had the chance to kill him,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.89,0:20:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不会犹豫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I wouldn't have a choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.18,0:20:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我也会杀他的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think I'd kill him, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.07,0:20:43.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这很糟糕  但是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's messed up, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.48,0:20:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that's how it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.79,0:20:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会为爱的人做一些事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You do things for the ones you love.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.54,0:20:53.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有爱过的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Loved.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.52,0:20:55.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是为他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not for them.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.45,0:21:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉把你锁在武器库\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry I locked you in the armory.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.04,0:21:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要看那场面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't need to see it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.01,0:21:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们甚至不知道她是否还好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We don't even know if she's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.77,0:21:11.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll get there.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.90,0:21:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.74,0:21:19.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不关心她们做了什么  回答是不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't care what they did. The answer is no.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.88,0:21:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会赶走一个曾经帮过我们的孕妇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not turning away a pregnant woman who helped us.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.58,0:21:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不会赶走萨沙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not turning away Sasha, either.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.46,0:21:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谁是萨沙  -她们要留下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Who the hell is Sasha? - They're staying.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.90,0:21:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掌权的不是你  耶稣  是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're not in charge, Jesus. I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.86,0:21:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是要保证这地方安全的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm the one who has to look after the safety of this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.54,0:21:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  你是说你想管事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What, are you telling you want to call the plays,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.29,0:21:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经过这么长时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}after all this time,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.81,0:21:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我打理好一切以后吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}after I set the table here?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.09,0:21:41.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只要一句话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Say the word.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.84,0:21:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被破坏的门  救世军  居民\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The broken gate, the Saviors, the people --
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.32,0:21:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}all of this can be yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.71,0:21:49.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是你得多留五分钟了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Only you'd have to stick around for more than five minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.73,0:21:51.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得成为这地方的一分子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You'd actually have to be a part of this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.66,0:21:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格雷戈里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Gregory?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.98,0:21:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚让凯特琳小姐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ah, I-I was just telling Ms. Caitlin
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.73,0:22:02.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿一点她最出名的大黄果酱给你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to bring up some of her famous rhubarb preserves for you both.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.22,0:22:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是为了感谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's our way of saying thank you
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.37,0:22:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们昨晚的帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for helping out last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.52,0:22:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是梅特琳小姐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's Ms. Maitlin.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.54,0:22:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们离开的时候可以带走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can take them with you when you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.96,0:22:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在就该走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you should go now,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.74,0:22:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为救世军随时都会回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because the Saviors could get back any minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.74,0:22:17.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我会走的  -萨沙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I'll go. - Sasha...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.82,0:22:19.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但让她留下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But let her stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.08,0:22:23.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-昨晚我们就算扯平了  -不成\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- We'll call it even on last night. - No deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.80,0:22:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是谢谢有你们在的日子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But it's been lovely having you here.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.21,0:22:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我我们该怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just tell me how we can make this work.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.21,0:22:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们需要...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think we'd need to...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.25,0:22:40.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-单独聊聊  好好探讨...  -去死吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- meet on that one-on-one just to explore -- - Go to hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.18,0:22:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的在暗示...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you actually imply--
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.98,0:22:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. You know what? I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.43,0:22:50.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得让凯特琳小姐先别端果酱上来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna tell Ms. Caitlin to keep her preserves.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.96,0:22:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道他们要发现你们在这里会做什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know what they'll do if they find you here?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.31,0:23:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶稣  把她们藏进壁橱里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jesus, get them in the closet.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.65,0:23:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-格雷戈里  -赶紧进去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Gregory... ‭- Go get in there now.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.24,0:23:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许动  不许说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you don't move, you don't speak,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.40,0:23:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你们还能保住性命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and maybe you'll get out of this alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.86,0:23:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊妮德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Enid.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.85,0:23:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.51,0:24:52.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们好  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Hello. - Hello.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.43,0:24:53.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是格雷戈里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're Gregory.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.55,0:24:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正是在下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Guilty as charged.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.34,0:24:59.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-欢迎来到山顶寨  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Welcome to Hilltop Colony. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.12,0:25:03.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就当...在自己家一样吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do, uh... make yourself at home.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.25,0:25:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可不是什么社交拜访\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This isn't a social call.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.28,0:25:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...我也觉得不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I-I-I -- I wouldn't think it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.84,0:25:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.61,0:25:18.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这地方人多闷得慌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And it's getting a little claustrophobic in here, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.32,0:25:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你的书房谈吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's talk in your study.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.37,0:25:25.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想看看那幅画\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I wanna see that painting.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.91,0:25:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不记得是谁告诉我的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can't remember who told me about it,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.20,0:25:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我相信现在都无所谓了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I'm pretty sure it doesn't matter much anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.27,0:25:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道你有没有听说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't know if you heard what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.44,0:25:34.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}W-what happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.96,0:25:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,原来和你打交道的那些人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, those people you used to deal with.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.50,0:25:41.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们全副武装的兄弟姐妹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Our brothers and sisters in arms and operation,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.42,0:25:44.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们已经不再管事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}well, they've been removed from the field of play.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.66,0:25:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟姐妹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, brothers and sisters?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.84,0:25:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What -- W-w-what do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.47,0:25:51.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你知道是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think you know what it means.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.73,0:25:54.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意思是我们得谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It means we need to talk!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.73,0:26:09.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.26,0:26:14.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关于昨天晚上的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In -- in regarding last night,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.58,0:26:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白你的意思了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}m-m-message received.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.16,0:26:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Loud and clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.50,0:26:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What was the message?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.39,0:26:26.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说你很清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You said it was loud and clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.55,0:26:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你是想让我们明白谁才是老大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just I -- I think you were showing us who was boss, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.52,0:26:37.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah. Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.04,0:26:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's just...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.98,0:26:41.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,美到窒息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's just breathtaking.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.50,0:26:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.49,0:26:48.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就是统治的榜样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See, that's management by example.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.57,0:26:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你总得处理这些事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Crap you got to deal with, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.35,0:26:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还用你说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're telling me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.18,0:26:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨天晚上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, last night,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.99,0:27:02.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们努力想办法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that was us working our asses off
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.46,0:27:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你们看到了一个榜样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to provide you an example.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.04,0:27:11.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这地方不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You got a nice place.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.47,0:27:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高墙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tall walls.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.22,0:27:18.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里的人说不定都忘了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}People in here probably forget
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.47,0:27:20.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行尸的模样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}what the corpses look like...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.94,0:27:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行尸的味道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...what they smell like.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.44,0:27:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们本打算为你们杀了它们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, we were gonna kill them for you,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.26,0:27:33.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来提醒你们  我们能提供的服务\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to remind you of the service we can provide,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.39,0:27:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你们自己收拾了残局\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you cleaned up the mess yourselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.30,0:27:39.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.79,0:27:45.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们肯定是从你们那里学了不少本事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, we must have picked up some skills from your people.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.39,0:27:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你好好想想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, if you think about it...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.21,0:27:52.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是你们救了我们  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you still saved us, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.50,0:27:54.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样想很不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, that's a nice way to look at it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.06,0:27:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很欣赏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I appreciate that.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.15,0:27:56.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有团队精神\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I'm a team player, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.53,0:27:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想这就是为什么大家选了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I-I-I-I think that's why the people chose me.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.20,0:28:02.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前打交道的那些人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, the other people of ours your were dealing with? Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.27,0:28:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think they...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.47,0:28:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟你这样的人合作被惯坏了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}got spoiled working with a guy like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.53,0:28:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吧  -确实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Yeah, well... - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.97,0:28:16.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我觉得他们可能有些心慈手软了  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I think they might've got a little soft. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.69,0:28:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以才会被赶尽杀绝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's what got them butchered, I imagine.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.89,0:28:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们死了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're dead?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.25,0:28:26.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死透了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Very, very dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.58,0:28:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相当透\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Extremely dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.84,0:28:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  这事已经解决了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But, you know, it all worked out.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.72,0:28:44.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为杀了他们的那些人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because the people that killed them,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.37,0:28:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在替我们卖命了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they work for us now.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.30,0:28:53.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要知道他们可很能干\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And they are real go-getters, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.49,0:28:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是遗憾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's, um...a shame
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.85,0:29:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会发生那种事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}when things like that have to happen, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.67,0:29:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  告诉尼根\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please, tell Negan
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.07,0:29:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白合作的好处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I understand the benefits in, uh...crossing the aisle.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.53,0:29:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.66,0:29:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No reason for that.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.95,0:29:16.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.89,0:29:18.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为  现在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because, for now,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.19,0:29:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就是你的尼根\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm your Negan.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.67,0:29:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为尼根想这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'Cause that's what Negan wants.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.96,0:29:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还是谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.95,0:29:33.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能明白我们带来的好处  这意义重大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It means a lot that you recognize what we bring to the table.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.98,0:29:38.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是你为什么还在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's why you're still here, and...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.88,0:29:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而其他人不在了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}others aren't.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.24,0:29:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Understand?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.95,0:29:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.68,0:29:51.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.02,0:29:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.52,0:29:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样很好  很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It is. It's good. It's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.43,0:30:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-还有什么想告诉我的吗  -没了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Anything else you want me to know? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.02,0:30:05.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有什么幺蛾子需要我留意吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Any hitches in the giddyap I should be aware of?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.03,0:30:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格雷戈里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Gregory?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.25,0:30:30.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实还有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Actually, there is.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.35,0:31:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在开玩笑吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you serious?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.03,0:31:11.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这是...  -威士忌\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- This is, uh-- - ‭Scotch.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.60,0:31:14.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是普通的...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, not just --
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.50,0:31:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hate the stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.77,0:31:19.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝起来像烟灰缸和玻璃清洁剂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tastes like, um, ashtrays and window cleaner.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.68,0:31:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢琴酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm a gin man.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.34,0:31:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过看起来的确是好货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But this does look like it could harden a connoisseur.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.98,0:31:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,态度真不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What a gesture.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.02,0:31:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说你不喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You say you hate it?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.47,0:31:31.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根会喜欢的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Negan'll love this.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.12,0:31:35.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会跟他说是我送的  不提你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, I'm gonna say it's from me, not mention you, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.64,0:31:37.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很想抢这个功劳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I really want the headline on this one.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.75,0:31:38.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好吗  -但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Okay? - ‭But, uh --
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.81,0:31:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不把那瓶放回去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want to slide that one back in?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.71,0:31:52.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  不该用问句\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry. I shouldn't ask.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.15,0:31:56.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给老子把那瓶放回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want to slide that one back in, period.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.75,0:32:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是大事  格雷戈里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is big, Gregory.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:08.55,0:32:09.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天大的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's huge.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.92,0:32:11.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会忘的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I won't forget it.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.25,0:32:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,万分感谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I really, really appreciate this.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.80,0:32:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.09,0:32:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们要扫荡一遍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, we're gonna go through the place
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.95,0:32:22.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿走你所有东西的一半\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and take half of everything you have.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.44,0:32:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但只拿一半\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But only half.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.99,0:32:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把这放到尼根卡车上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take this to the Negan truck, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.99,0:32:34.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出去  先生们  干活了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Exeunt, gentlemen! Get to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.10,0:32:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有  把画拿走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, and take the painting.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.10,0:32:43.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一件事  格雷戈里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One last thing, Gregory.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.65,0:32:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能给我跪下吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Could I just get a kneel out of you?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.51,0:32:52.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Excuse me?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.33,0:32:56.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跪下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Kneel.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.42,0:33:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跪得真实在  格雷戈里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's a solid kneel, Gregory.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.66,0:33:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记得下次也要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You remember that for next time.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.73,0:33:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得尼根不在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't think Negan's here.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.86,0:33:54.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没看到他那辆黑卡车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't see that black truck.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:07.03,0:34:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你并不是出来兜风的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You weren't taking a drive.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:11.93,0:34:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是来找我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You weren't coming to get me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.84,0:34:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能就这么放过他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't let them get away with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.36,0:34:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你知道我不能  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You know I can't. ‭- I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.75,0:34:24.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我一起去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.75,0:34:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也想杀掉他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want to kill them, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.85,0:34:27.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以做到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.98,0:34:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己说过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You said it.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.48,0:34:36.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是为了我们自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It'd be for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.63,0:34:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是为了亚伯拉罕  不是为了格伦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not for Abraham, not for Glenn.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.88,0:34:42.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是为了玛姬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not for Maggie.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.72,0:34:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是为自己做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're doing it for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.10,0:34:51.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.37,0:34:56.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果一切顺利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So if it all goes right...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.11,0:35:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...and you do it...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.01,0:35:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你要怎么逃掉  -这不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- ...how do you get away? - It wouldn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.55,0:35:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我很重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It would to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.09,0:35:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你别去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please don't go.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:32.47,0:35:33.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just come with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.37,0:35:35.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你逃不掉的  -我会回家的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You can't make it -- - I'm just gonna go home.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.21,0:35:39.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你骗我  -不  我没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You're lying. - No, I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.71,0:35:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不该去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You shouldn't go.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.52,0:35:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我也不能阻止你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I can't stop you.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.87,0:35:59.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会看到你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They'll see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.65,0:36:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. They won't.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.70,0:36:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我让你把她们藏在走廊的壁橱里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told you to hide them in the hallway closet!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.67,0:36:11.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你只说了"壁橱"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, you said "Closet."
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.51,0:36:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的卧室\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is my bedroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.01,0:36:14.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们进来时我还没...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What if they came in here before I --
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.30,0:36:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没来得及把我们供出去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Before you tried to give us up?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.70,0:36:16.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会先杀掉你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They would've killed you first.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.85,0:36:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-甜心  我在和耶稣说话  -够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Honey, I'm talking to Jesus. - Stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.25,0:36:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么要维护她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why are you even defending her?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.34,0:36:23.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们变成现在这样就是因为她和瑞奇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're here right now because she and -- and Rich
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.46,0:36:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没能履行诺言\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}didn't handle things like they said they would.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.28,0:36:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救世军想要杀掉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The Saviors tried to kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.71,0:36:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是个误会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That was a misunderstanding.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.37,0:36:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等救世军一离开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And as soon as the Saviors leave,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.99,0:36:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把她们送走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we get them the hell out of here
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.17,0:36:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-省得真的发生惨剧  -别说了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- before something bad really happens. - Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.03,0:36:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们要留下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're staying.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.92,0:36:37.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者你想公之于众\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or do you want to make it public?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.82,0:36:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让大家知道你和亚历山大做的交易吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want to make the deal with Alexandria public?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.98,0:36:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丢掉你装糊涂的机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lose your plausible deniability?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.83,0:36:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丢掉你的权位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lose your position?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.21,0:36:50.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这么说你现在要掌权了  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- So you're gonna be in charge now? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.93,0:36:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只不过不再是你说的算了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's just that you won't be.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.05,0:36:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬和萨沙会留在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maggie and Sasha are staying.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.32,0:36:57.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也会留在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm staying.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.36,0:37:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会成为一个不正常的欢乐大家庭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're all gonna be one big happy dysfunctional family.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.83,0:37:09.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就这样吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So we will be.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.55,0:37:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来保证我们的安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I'll see us through this.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.39,0:37:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我今天和他们达成了进展\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I made progress with them today.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.31,0:37:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你也看到了  -我看到的不是那样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You saw it. - That's not what I saw.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.44,0:37:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗  反正就是这么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah? Well, it's what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.88,0:37:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们好好配合  他们就会善待我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We play nice, they play nice.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.73,0:37:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白吗  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See, dear?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.48,0:37:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救世军实际上是很讲道理的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Saviors can actually be quite reasonable.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.38,0:37:42.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是块好表\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a fine watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.17,0:37:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要丢在外面淋雨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Doesn't need to be left out in the rain.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.27,0:37:46.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里现在也是我们的家了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is our home now.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.35,0:37:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要开始学会叫对我的名字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So you'll learn to start to call me by my name.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.67,0:37:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是玛莎  不是亲爱的  不是甜心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not Marsha, not "Dear," Not "Honey."
Dialogue: 0,0:37:54.71,0:37:55.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maggie.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.05,0:37:58.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬·李\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maggie Rhee.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.82,0:38:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来的时候  格雷戈里已经掌权了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When I got here, Gregory was already in charge.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.30,0:38:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时以为大家出于某种原因选了他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thought the people chose him for a reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.86,0:38:08.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在想起来  可能只是凑巧而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Looking at it now, I think it just happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.10,0:38:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢他的做法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't like how he did things.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.21,0:38:15.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我心中没有取代他的人选\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I couldn't imagine anyone else in his place.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.77,0:38:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我有了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can now.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.05,0:38:20.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.25,0:38:24.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们以后再谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll talk about it sometime.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.72,0:38:30.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该早点跟格雷戈里谈的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I should've talked to Gregory sooner.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.67,0:38:31.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.36,0:38:34.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但愿  你们能让我做出补偿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hopefully, you'll let me make it up to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.25,0:38:36.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We will.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.15,0:38:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,门关了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The gates are closed.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.02,0:38:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  他们还在外面装货\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wait, they're still loading up outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.35,0:38:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拖车里见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll see you back at the trailer.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:59.71,0:39:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想补偿我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you want to make it up to us...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.62,0:39:06.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能找到尼根的住处吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...can you find where Negan lives?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:11.51,0:39:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其中一辆卡车会回那里  所以...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One of the trucks is going back there,so...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.11,0:39:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我可以找到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}yeah, I can do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.59,0:39:25.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能保密吗  只有我们俩知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you keep it between us, just you and me?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.72,0:39:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不告诉玛姬吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No Maggie?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.59,0:39:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.42,0:39:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Me neither.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.63,0:39:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.21,0:39:57.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.55,0:39:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.47,0:40:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我会好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I will be.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.00,0:40:34.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们说你开拖拉机杀了行尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}People told me you killed walkers and a car...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:35.35,0:40:36.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毁了车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}with a tractor?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.75,0:40:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时不能袖手旁观\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I couldn't sit by and watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.42,0:40:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会再那样了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not again.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.45,0:40:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我坐着做了一些事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So I guess I sat and did something.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.40,0:40:46.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你应该保重身体的  -那不难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You're supposed to take it easy. - It wasn't hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:48.25,0:40:49.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我第一次了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It wasn't the first time.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.43,0:40:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高中时有个男生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There was this boy in high school.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:56.92,0:40:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开车碾了他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You ran over the boy?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:58.51,0:40:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}His car.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.32,0:41:01.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前是辆大黄蜂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was a Camaro.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.01,0:41:03.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后来不是了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And then it wasn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.25,0:41:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊妮德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Enid.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.85,0:41:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是来帮忙的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I -- I came to help.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:13.55,0:41:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你独自来的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You came by yourself?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.19,0:41:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.43,0:41:18.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃点晚饭吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have some dinner.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.16,0:41:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚伯拉罕的墓上为什么有气球\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why are there balloons on Abraham's grave?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.94,0:41:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不忍心告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't have the heart to tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:29.27,0:41:30.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格伦会告诉你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Glenn would've.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.62,0:41:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他最不会说谎了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He was a bad liar.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.54,0:41:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.32,0:41:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's no need to be sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.24,0:41:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,气球没什么不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing wrong with balloons.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.43,0:41:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坟墓上没有标记\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's nothing marking the graves.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.36,0:41:43.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nope.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:45.63,0:41:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本打算在格伦的墓上放这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was gonna use this for Glenn's.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.32,0:41:50.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我爸爸的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was my dad's.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.42,0:41:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他送给了他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He gave it to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.10,0:41:55.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我现在要送给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I'm giving it to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.90,0:42:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不需要任何东西来铭记他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We don't need anything to remember him by.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.26,0:42:06.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有我们就够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have us.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:21.31,0:42:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢上帝  为你每个早晨给我们第一道曙光\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For this new morning, with its light,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:24.53,0:42:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为你在夜晚给我们安歇和住所\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for rest and shelter of the night,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:28.72,0:42:32.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为你给我们健康和食物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for health and food,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:33.11,0:42:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为你给我们爱和朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for love and friends,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:36.04,0:42:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为你一切美好的恩赐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for everything that goodness sends.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:40.32,0:42:41.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Amen.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:42.16,0:42:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-阿门  -阿门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Amen. - ‭Amen.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.30,0:08:18.51,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第七季  第五集』
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.86,0:02:30.71,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx2300\fscy200\alpha&AA\pos(129.2,218.4)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.85,0:02:10.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻译:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}冰蓝 Reginamoon CS小明漫画家 自然卷
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.82,0:02:15.82,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻译:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}小酸奶 艾瑞卡 蘑菇 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.78,0:02:20.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}校对:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.75,0:02:25.75,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}时间轴:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}某雪 加森
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.71,0:02:30.71,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}后期:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小哥  拉图    {\c&H008AFF&}总监： {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小孩

