South Park
Episode 1013 - Go God Go XII
Transcript VO : spscriptorium
Traduction: Kowaio
Synchro: aAakii
Relecture : Kowaio , aAakii
www.southparknews.net
www.seriessub.com
The year is 2006, and young Eric Cartman
cannot wait for the new
Nintendo Wii to come out.
Unable to cope with the wait any longer,
Eric decides to freeze
himself for three weeks.
But a freak avalanche makes
Eric impossible to find,
and so he remains frozen for 500 years.
Whoa, steady!
This way, otters!
This is it. New New Hampshire.
We have risked much bringing
you here, Time Child.
Can it. You otters may have
evolved to the point you can talk,
but I don't need lectures.
Don't let the time
child out of your sight.
He could try to run.
We have a deal, Blavius.
As long as I get what I want,
you have nothin' to worry abuot.
Something is spooking the ostriches.
Sure. This is Monarch land now.
Probably Jarvis probes everywhere.
Here it is! We have arrived.
Hold!
This is it, Time Child.
The old museum of technology,
abandoned long ago.
Let's get what you want, Time
Child, and get out of here.
Over here!
Yeah it's here! It's
here! The Nintendo Wii...
I've waited so long for this.
All right, Time Child, we've
filled our side of the bargain.
Now return with us to Otter Bay.
Sorry Blavius. I've got other plans.
NOOOO!
It was a trick!
SCIENCE DAMN YOU, TIME CHILD!
I got it! I got the Wii!
Time Child! You've returned!
We thought for sure you had
died in the in the Phobart plant.
Yeah. Lucky for me the otters
believed I was on their side.
Do me a favor: next time
I'm in a recessed biocave,
don't send me a level 2 homing call.
TC, wait!
Oh I can't wait! This
is gonna be so awesome!
Get out of my way!
You gained the otters' trust?!
Were you wearing an
information crystal?!
Here.
Science be praised.
This could end the war!
You've done a great thing, TC.
How can we repay you?
Just send a maintenance guy to my room.
I want this Nintendo hooked
up to my float screen NOW!
Come on! Come on!
Dude, what is taling
so long! I wanna play!
Uhh, what kind of output does this have?
This is some ancient
Super-VHS output or somethin'.
I can't connect it to your flaot screen.
There's gotta be some way to hook it up!
It's the freakin' future!
It may be the future for you,
but I can't hook up anything to a float
screen without at least a laser-7 output.
You've gotta be shittin'
me!! Science-damnit!
I am so fucking sick of the future!
TC? What's wrong?
I'll tell you what's wrong!
I've been waiting 500 years
to play the Nintendo Wii!
And if I don't get to play
real soon, I'm gonna bust a nut!
Well, we're all glad you're back.
I know somebody who's
missed you very much.
Come on in, K-10.
Bark bark. Hello,
Eric. I have missed you.
Suck my balls, K-10.
I'm not in the mood.
Fellow atheists: the
time child has returned
with information on our sworn
enemies, the Allied Atheist Alliance.
They have started digging
for clams in sector J7.
If we mount an all-out attack,
we can wipe out their food supply!
But, those are civilian otters.
We cannot tolerate the otters!
Their Science is flawed!
Their answer to the Great
Question is different from ours.
Yes, but... sending out all
our ships at the same time..
it would leave our city exposed!
...That's why we have to be super-duper
sure that nobody finds out we're doing it.
The United Atheist Alliance is about
to send out all its defense ships
to take down the Allied
Atheist Allieance's clam fields.
Praise Science
This is your chance, young Shvek,
to avenge your father's death.
Careful, son.
Just because their Science
leads them to a different answer
to the Great Question doesn't mean
we have the right to kill them all.
No! Our answer to the Great
Question is the only logical one.
Our Science is great.
Let us not forget the
great Richard Dawkins
who finally freed the
world of religion long ago.
Dawkins knew that logic and
reason were the way of the future.
But it wasn't until he
met his beautiful wife
that he learned using logic
and reason isn't enough.
You have to be a dick to everyone
who doesn't think like you.
Prepare all the troops!
We will level the United
Atheist Alliance to the ground!
With new Glade monvert cleaner,
you can make your monvert
sparkle like never before.
My monvert's never looked so clean.
God I hate future TV.
There's too many commercials!
Agh! I'm so bored.
There's nothing to do.
Tell me about it.
Hey, I know! Let's crank
call people in the past!
Huh?
I just got...
the Crank Prank Time Phone!
New, from Blasbro, it's
Crank Prank Time Phone!
I just dial a random
number on the keypad,
enter a date and year on
the debilibrator, and...
Wow! Someone from the
past is on the line!
Hello? Is there a refrigierator running?
Well then, you'd better go catch it!
What ?
Uh hi. It's the year 1973, right?
Could I speak to Al Coholic, please?
Crank Prank Time Phone
comes with debilibrator
antimatter fusion cone, andn
30 plain HF watt triggers.
Warning: Crank Prank Time Phone
is for entertainment purposes only.
Making anything OTHER than
crank calls to the past
could affect the present
and end your existence.
Crank Prank Time Phone is not
intended for the use by otters.
Why didn't anyone tell me
there was a time phone?!
Why does it matter? Bark bark
Don't you see?? If I
get one of those phones,
I can call myself in the past
and tell me not to freeze myself.
Then I can go back into my
time... and play Nintendo Wii.
Bark bark. That call is
for crank calling only.
Using it in the way
you describe is illegal.
I care! Where's the closest toy store??
Working, bark bark. The
Jarvanian shopping comples.
But it is not open yet.
Come on! Come on!
Store is now... open.
Welcome
Ugh, finally!
Welcome to Zeebod's Toys
I want one of those time-phone things.
Ahh, the Crank Prank Time Phone. Sure.
Now, I am required by
the state to make sure
you know this is for
prank-calling the past ONLY, right?
Yeah yeah, I'm only
gonna prank-call people.
All right, that'll be 6000 credits.
Six thousand credits?! What do I
look like to you? A Thurilian miner?!
This is a pretty advanced piece
of equipment. It's expensive.
Look, I have to have
one of those phones!
Oh, all right, then I
have to have 6000 credits.
Bark bark, I'm sorry, Eric, bark bark.
How about a robot?
How much for the robot?
Awww.
Sorry, kid, you're just gonna have
to crank-call people in the present.
Science-damnit! Wait. K-10, can you
access the store's sales records?
Working, bark bark. Access.
I want the name and address of anybody
who's bought a time phone
from this guy in the past week.
Working, bark bark.
The United Atheist
Alliance has taken the bait!
Soon they will send their ships out
to destroy our decoy clam fields!
And while their ships are away, the United
Atheist League intends to attack them!
Our plan has worked perfectly!
For when the United Atheist League
attacks the United Atheist Alliance,
we will charge in and kill them all!
Our Science, our answer to the
Great Question shall prevail!
Hail Science! Hail
Science! Hail Science!
And I will personally
kill the Time Child,
and eat his entrails on my tummy!
I'll get it, darling.
Hello? Hello?
Uh yes, hello? I'm calling for Mr. Wall?
I'm sorry, there's no Mr. Wall here.
Oh. Is Mrs. Wall there?
Nno, there are no Walls here.
Then how does your roof stay up?
Oh, I see! Is this the Johnson
boys from down the street?!
No, we're from the future.
Very funny!
Hi, uh, I'm a Pepper, and I'm wondering
if you'd like to be a Pepper too?
God darn ya!
Yeah.
That was a great one!
Hello, I'm with the
cubic waste department.
I need to check your
lowertram for inhibitors.
Oh. Okay, I guess.
Come on in, Bob.
All right, just let me use my tools...
Hey!
Haha! Stupid assholes!
I got your time phone!
Science H. Logic! What a jerk!
Silence, otters!
It's the Wise One
The Wise One speaks.
This is not the path
we should be taking.
Will more bloodshed end anything?
Wise One, our answer to the Great Question
is the only one based on good science.
Science, reason, is
that really all there is?
They are not a logical race, Wise One!
They go around chopping
down trees for tables,
when they have perfectly
good tummies to eat on.
How logical is that?!
Yes! The great Dawkins said we cannot
tolerate those who don't use reason!
How reasonable is it to eat
off wood instead of your tummy?
Well perhaps the great
Dawkins wasn't so wise.
Oh, he was intelligent, but, some
of the most intelligent otters
I've ever known were completely
lacking in common sense.
Maybe, some otters do need
to believe in something.
Who knows? Maybe, just
believing in God makes God exist.
Kill the Wise One!
Whoa, wait wait!
Oh God!
Hello?
Are you there?
Who is this?
No, no, I have me.
All right, all right, listen!
Listen to me carefully!
You need to be patient!
What?? Who the hell is this?!
It's me.
- Me who?!
- Me you!
What?!
I'm you in the future!
You have to be patient and wait
for the Nintendo Wii to come out,
or else you'll wake up in the future and
have to deal with a bunch of see otters!
Oh very funny, Kyle!
It's not Kyle, it's you!
Yeah? Well you can go fuck yourself.
I'm trying to do you a favor,
dumbass!! Just listen to me!
Listen to this!
Dickhead.
What an asshole!
Hello?
Butters? Butters!
Eric? Iiis that you?
Butters, Butters! Listen
to me! Just just listen.
I'm about to come over to your house
and ask you to help me freeze myself.
Do not... do it!
Eric, are you playing
a joke on me again?
No! This is not a joke!
Whatever I say to you, Butters,
no matter how hard I try, do
not... do... what I tell you!
But...
but you're here right now.
Butters?! Come on, we gotta go!
No! Don't listen to me!
Tell me to go screw myself!
Huh??
Come on, Butters, it's gonna get dark!
But, you're telling
me not to go with you.
What??
Who the fuck is this?!
Aw damnit, just listen to me!
If you freeze yourself,
you're going to die!
Suck my balls!
No, you suck my balls!! Just
listen to me for one minute!
...Okay, you have one minute.
Right before you left
for Butters' house,
you drank a buncha Ovaltine and put Clyde
Frog so nothing would happen to him, right?
Are you spying on me?!
No, I am you, you stupid asshole!
Fuck you, asshole. You
can go fuck yourself!
Come on, Butters, we're going!
Oh, all right then.
God I hate that guy!!
My friends, the time has come!
May Science give us the
courage to do what we must!
Launch all defensive ships to sector J7!
Take out the otters' clam fields!
Sir! The United Atheist Alliance
has sent out all their ships.
Their capital is now unprotected.
Then begin the attack!
Science be praised.
Kill the table-eaters! In
the name of Almighty Science!
Hello?
Hello? Kyle?
Yes. Hello, Kyle. It's
Eric. Uh, how's it going?
What do you want?!
Kyle, you are the smartest guy I know,
so I think maybe you're the only
person who can understand this.
You know how earlier today I
asked you to help me freeze myself?
I'm not going to help you freeze
yourself, Cartman! It's a stupid idea!
No, see, I know it's a stupid idea.
Because, I actually
did freeze myself.and...
you were right, Kyle. It it backfired
and I was frozen for 500 years,
and now I'm calling you from the future.
.. Uh huh.
No, really, Kyle, I'm I'm seriously.
Here, talk to my robot dog.
Bark bark. Hello, Kyle. Bark bark.
.. I'm hanging up now.
No, Kyle, listen! Please! I think right
about now, I'm in my mom's freezer.
Suck my balls, fatass.
.. I will. I will suck your balls, Kyle.
Just stop me from freezing myself,
and I will get down on my knees,
and I will suck your balls.
I'll suck 'em dry, Kyle.
Aw Goddamnit, now you've
made me miss my ride!
My whole day is screwed
up because of you!
Kyle? Kyle?
Eric, I really think you
should stop calling the past.
You could change the present.
Well I don't notice anything
different, KIT-9! Do you?
I guess not, meow meow.
Hm, I see... Hey!
Meow meow.
- Heeeeey!
- Meow meow.
TC! We're under attack!
By who?!
We have to get to the War
Room! It's the only safe place!
The United Atheist League is
bombing the city! We're defenseless!
This is terrible! I'm gonna die in the
future without ever playing Nintendo Wii?!
Sir! The sea otters are advancing!
They've broken through the east portal!
What?! Three-way
phone channel onscreen!
What are you otters
doing?! This is our attack!
Yes. And we're attacking both of you!
You fools! This will
be the end of us all!
Then accept our answer to the Great
Question, and we will withdraw.
Your answer to the Great
Question is illogical!
What is the Great Question?
What atheists should call themselves.
Unified Atheist League
is the most logical name.
Unified Atheist Allianace
makes more sense.
No! Allied Atheist Alliance!
That way it has three A's!
That is the logical choice!
So be it. We cannot
agree; prepare to die.
Forward missiles launched, sir!
I have to get out of here!
Why is everyone in my past so stupid
that they think I'm crank-calling them?!
But Eric, meow meow, you knew the
wife of the smartest man in history.
Who?
Your teacher, the one called Garrison.
Garrison? But he's an asshole.
Oh yeah! Yeah, I'm a monkey!
Give this monkey what she wants!
Oh Ms. Garrison!
Damnit, who the hell is calling?!
I'll thell them... to call
you back... Oh... yeah...
Garrison residence. Can you
call... back later, please?
It's an emergency! It's an emergency!
An emergency?
I need to speak to
Mr. Garrison right now!
I'm sorry, but Mr.
Garrison has passed away.
Mrs. Garrison is the only person here
and she's rather tied up at the moment.
Look asshole, this is a real emergency!
Just pass the phone to whatever Garrison
wants to call himself since
the sex-change operation!
Sex-change operation??
Uh oh.
Uuuuugh! You're a man?!
Not anymore. I've been fixed.
Richard, hold on. I can explain.
Explain?? How can I be so stupid??
Richard, come back, please!
Well go ahead and leave,
you atheist faggot!
Have fun mocking God in hell! You queer!
Mr. Garrison! Mr. Garrison!
All right, Eric. Are you all set to go?
Go... Right... Where am I going?
W-we told you: we're sending you home.
With the Crank and Wank Time Machine.
Don't worry, my son.
When you return to your time you
will merge with your other self.
It's all very Zen.
Wait... Isn't... everybody
at war over atheism?
Atheism? No. We've learned to get
rid of all the isms in our time.
Yes. Long ago we realized isms are
great for those who are rational,
but in the hands of irrational
people, isms always lead to violence.
So there is no war now in the future.
Of course there's war. The stupid French
-Chinese think they have a right to Hawaii.
Yeah!
But now the moment has come
to send you back to your time.
We unfroze you for a purpose,
and now that purpose is fulfilled.
And what was that purpose again?
We explained that to you already.
Right...
Goodbye, Eric. I will
mess you. Squawk squawk
I'll miss you too, COCKA-3.
So long, Eric. And tell
everyone in the past for us,
that no one single
answer... is ever the answer.
Noooo!
I'm back. Wow! I'm back!
There you are, Eric.
Mom! Mom, they did it!
Eric, you have to come home.
You can't just wait here
for that game to come out.
No, I know. You're right, Mom.
I need to learn to be patient.
I think I can wait three weeks
for Nintendo Wii to come out.
But, honey, it's only September. That...
Nintendo Wii doesn't
come out for two months.
What? NO! NO !!!!!
You sent me back too
far!! HEY! Do it over!
Who are you talking to, muffin?
I can't wait two months!
I can't! There has to
be a way around this!
Hey, kid, somebody's
on the phone for you.
Hello?
Hello? Hello? I know
what you're thinking!
Do not do it!
You just need to be patient
and wait the two months!
Do you hear me?!
...Oh, suck my balls, Kyle!
Transcript : spscriptorium.com
Traduction: Kowaio
relecture/synchro: aAakii
Visit www.southparknews.net
www.seriessub.com
www.tvsubtitles.net