captioning made possible by
comedy central
♪ i'm going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna have
myself a time ♪
♪ friendly faces
everywhere ♪
♪ humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna leave my
woes behind ♪
♪ ample parking
day or night ♪
♪ people spouting
"howdy neighbor" ♪
♪ headin' on up
to south park ♪
♪ gonna see
if i can't unwind ♪
♪ ( muffled mumble
muffled mumble ) ♪
♪ so come on down
to south park ♪
♪ and meet some
friends of mine ♪♪
( kyle )
wow, dude.
( eric )
man, indians
have it good, huh ?
now, eric, they're called
native americans, remember ?
show some respect.
welcome to the
three feathers casino.
i am your host,
chief runswithpremise.
please try your luck at
one of our many games.
alright !
let's go !
ahp-- i am afraid minors cannot
go onto the casino floor.
i'm not a miner,
dumbass.
you see a shovel
in my hand ?
you kids can enjoy our
native american comedy club.
alright, we're gonna
hit the tables.
why don't you kids run along
to the comedy club ?
alright, time to
win some money !
ooh yeah,
blackjack table !
welcome to the
blackjack table.
may luck run through you like
the spirit of the buffalo.
gerald, this is
$10 a hand !
relax, sweetie--
i know how to count cards.
well, i don't
want to play here.
yeah, come on,
sheila,
let's go to
the nickel slots.
ooh, the nickel slots,
you might win
the $30 jackpot !
ah, women, huh ?
god i hate 'em.
alright, time to show these
people how to gamble !
( announcer )
welcome to the three feathers
comedy club.
please put your hands together
for johnny manymoons !
what is native american
comedy anyway ?
thank you, thank you.
bear walked into
a bar.
bear said to deer,
"may i please...
have a drink ?"
and so
deer said to bear
"why the big pause ?"
( drum thump )
( indian war chanting )
ha ha ha ha !
many moons ago, pony and
eagle walked up to coyote.
pony said to coyote,
"i am very mad at eagle.
will you yell at him
for me ?"
coyote said to pony,
"why can you not
yell yourself ?"
and pony replied,
"because i am
a little horse."
( drum thump )
ha ha ha ha !
how's it goin',
gerald ?
oh, not so good.
yeah, i know
what you mean.
i'm down 300 bucks.
yeah, i'm down 26,000.
yeah, well,
maybe we should--
wait-- $26,000 ?!
i forgot to tell you,
i have a gambling problem.
gerald, 26,000-- !
shh-- i have to win it back
before sheila finds out !
where did you get
that kind of money ?
the casino gave me credit.
i put the house up
as collateral.
but i still have
this $10 chip !
dealer 21.
sorry.
that's it,
i'm destitute...
loan me money !
you've gotta have
money in the cup !
what's in the cup ?
just six quarters !
oh god.
oh jesus.
thank you for playing
at three feathers.
may your life be filled with
the song of the sparrow.
oh, shove the song of the
sparrow up your ass !
how am i gonna
tell my family ?
how do i tell them that tomorrow
we have to pack up our things
and get out of
the house ?
there's daddy !
oh, jesus.
where have
you guys been ?
we've been
looking all over.
yeah, come on, dad,
this place sucks !
i wanna go !
what--
what did you say ?
i said
i wanna leave !
oh, you wanna leave, huh ?!
okay, fine, kyle,
when we get home
we'll just pack  up our things,
load 'em in the car
and we'll leave !
what ?
no, no, i mean--
no, no, no, if you wanna
leave south park, fine !
tomorrow we're leaving !
gerald, what are you
talking about ?
oh, you heard him, sheila--
kyle wants to leave.
our nice old house doesn't
"interest" kyle anymore.
well, i'm calling a moving
company right now !
you shouldn't be
such a dick, dude.
what's wrong with gerald ?
he... he lost his house
to the native americans.
what ?
but don't the native americans
know he has nowhere else to go ?
they don't care.
look at them,
small-minded idiots
pouring their
life's savings away.
their cash flows
out of them
like diarrhea
from the buffalo.
yes, but we have milked these
simple mountain folk almost dry.
if we really
want to see cash flow
we need to bring in
city people, from denver.
yes...
it is time for us to
implement our plan !
a super highway, built from
denver right to our casino !
and we do we do about the
small town of south park
that lies in the
highway's way ?
simple...
we buy it
and we demolish it.
( chanting laugh )
ha ha ha ha !
and that's really
all i can tell you.
the town of south park
is going to be leveled
in order to make way for
a 12-lane super highway.
but how can they
do that ?
the native americans
have purchased the land
out from under us.
tomorrow they're buying
the last of what they need
to have
complete ownership.
well, can't we
stop them ?
let's call the bank !
the native americans
bought the bank.
oh my god !
now look, it isn't
all horrible.
the native americans are
offering you retail values
on your homes.
no, screw that !
we'll just pool
our money together
and buy the town
ourselves !
that's right !
yeah !
yeah, let the south park
people own south park !
yeah !
how much do we
have to raise, mayor ?
three hundred
thousand dollars.
oh, never mind.
how can they
do that, huh ?
how can they make us
all move away ?
because they're rich,
greedy-ass indians.
native americans.
our whole town, gone...
we've had such
great times here...
( screams of mayhem )
we can't let them
do it, you guys !
we have to find a way to
stop those native americans !
yeah !
yeah,
this is our town !
we shouldn't have to make
a bunch of new friends
somewhere else,
we're a team !
yeah, that's right !
that's right !
yeah,
we're a team.
we just have to figure out
a way to raise $300,000.
wait a minute !
i've got it, you guys !
we can get kyle
infected with aids
and then start
a charity organization
that we steal
money from !
come on, let's go !
no ?  we can't
give kyle aids ?
we need something that will
get us money tomorrow.
hey, i know,
how about a dog parade ?
dog parade ?
yeah, we dress up all our
dogs in little outfits
and parade them
down the street.
it'd be so adorable !
how do we make $300,000
doing that ?
oh... well, we could
sell tickets
to our moms and dads !
our moms and dads are the ones
who need money, butters !!
oh...
maybe give
kyle aids, huh ?
lookin' a little
better now.
oh gerald,
i can't watch !
how can you do this
to people ?
we're sorry, but if we do not
build a super highway,
our casino might stop
seeing profits.
there's more to life
than profits.
like what ?
like, you know...
slurpees and stuff.
well, come on, honey.
i guess we should start
packing up our things as well.
yeah, so long,
south park.
mom !  dad !
we figured out a way
we could raise $300,000 !
a dog parade ?
no !
stan, we've all tried
to raise money
but we only raised
$10,000
and the deadline
is tomorrow.
i know, so how about
we take the $10,000
back to the
indian casino ?
tell them, kyle.
the odds on a single number
in roulette are 35 to 1.
that means with a $10,000 bet
you win 350,000 !
boys,
that's ridiculous.
look, we've got
nothing to lose.
what do you guys think ?
it's a long shot.
yeah, but its the only shot
we've got to save our town.
"the residents of south park
had hoped to raise $300,000
"but in the end managed
to raise only 10.
"the loss of their town
may be imminent
for the poor people
of south park."
aww, i fink i'm going
to cwyyy !
ha ha ha ha !
alright, boys, you're
gonna have to wait here.
dad--
good luck.
it's in
god's hands now.
stand aside, everyone !
what are they doing ?
we're gonna try to beat you
at your own game,
chief runswithpremise !
$10,000--
on 31 black.
( crowd gasps )
impossible.
come on,
come on...
thirty one...
black.
( cheering )
we did it !
oh my god !
oh, this is amazing !
no !
noooo !
they did it !
south park is saved !
we have plenty enough
to save our town now !
yeah !
but wait--
$350,000-- that means
if we won again
it would be 12 and
a quarter million !
we could save the town
and be super rich !
oh, hell yeah,
let it ride !
what the hell
are they doing ?!
let's go, 31 !
let's see it !,
two, red,
you lose.
( everyone )
awwww !!
dammit !
hmm !
they--
they had it !
they freakin' had it !
you totally had it.
you had enough to save
the town and then some.
stan, okay ?
you just don't understand
the fine points of gambling.
you're never
supposed to stop
when you're on
a winning streak.
a winning streak ?!
you played one game !
stan, okay ?
what ?!
alright, stan,
okay ?
you people just got greedy
like the native americans.
hey, mister !
we are not like them,
alright ?!
now we may have pie-in-the-
sky dreams once in a while,
but we aren't the ones kicking
people out of their homes.
so don't you compare us
to those coldhearted,
moneygrubbing, evil,
stinky indians !
i'm sorry--
native americans.
there you are, sir, there's
the check for your home.
just sign here and here.
well, this is it, mr. slave,
we're officially homeless.
( sobbing )
oh, jesus...
jesus christ !
dad, what are you doing ?
don't take their
dirty money !
stanley, we don't
have a choice.
the native americans
own south park now.
we have to take what they'll
give us for our homes.
there you go,
have a nice day.
come on, you guys,
this is our town !
it's over, stanley,
what else can we do ?
we can stay--
and fight.
yeah, when the indians come
to tear up our town,
we kick 'em
in the nuts !!
yeah !
yeah, they don't own
our town-- we do !
i'm sorry, boys,
you just don't
understand economics.
it'll be okay, boys,
we'll just move to
the next town over.
oh sure, until the
native americans decide
they want
that land, too.
what if the native americans
just keep building their casinos
and their highways, until
we have nowhere else to go ?
we have to stand up
to them, now !
forget it.
come on, you guys !
you're all a bunch of
god damn pussies !
get out of our way !
no, we won't let you
destroy our town !
boys, it isn't
your town anymore.
just because you have a piece
of paper saying you own it
doesn't make it yours.
we grew up here,
our parents grew up here.
we shop at thatwal-mart
and eat at thatchili's.
we take fish from the streams
and bread them and freeze them
to make fish sticks.
this is not just a town,
it is our way of life.
well, your way of life is about
to change, little boys.
now, move !
you can't just roll into places
and take people's lives away !
and what are four little boys
going to do to stop us, huh ?
( crowd chanting )
bom bom bom, bom bom.
bom bom bom,
bom bom...
♪ we are strong ♪
♪ no one can tell us
we're wrong ♪
♪ searching our hearts
for so long ♪
♪ all of us knowing ♪
♪ love is a
battlefield ♪♪
this land is not
for sale.
dammit !
i thought you said
they were dealt with !
they were !
sorry, charlies !
you can just keep your filthy,
bastard, indian money !
filthy, bastard,
native american money.
oh, right,
sorry about that.
this isn't over !
( trucks beeping reverse )
we'll never give up !
you bastards !
yeah, south park
is ours !
but what do we do now ?
i mean, we can't stand here
and block their way forever.
we can stand here
as long as it takes !
what is the state
of our people ?
last night i spoke with
the spirit of the bear.
and bear said that
if we do not build
our super highway soon,
our investors
may soon sell off
their shares of
the new casino.
yes, and eagle says the
cumulative shared market loss
on the revenue of the new
casino drops 15% every day.
then we must force
the south park people
off their petty land.
but they are determined
and proud.
and the spirit of the wind has
stated that if we use force
it could be
a publicity nightmare,
further hurting
our net assets.
i already have a plan how we
can force them off their land...
sneakily.
we're going to
give them...
blankets !
blankets ?
yes, we will present the
blankets as a peace offering.
but what the round eyes
will not know,
is that the blankets are
infected with sars !
they will all get sars !
and then sars will run through
their town like a buffalo.
now, i need your help getting
the sars onto the blankets.
okay, bring them in !
( mock chinese )
let's see how south park
deals with this !
( yelling in chinese )
everyone, grab
a chinese person
and rub them
on a blanket !
make sure you rub them
all over !
get the sars
nice and deep in there.
tom, i'm standing in
chilly south park, colorado
where the residents are
entering the third day
of their sit-in to try
and stop native americans
from building a super highway
through their town.
the temperature is low, but
spirits are pretty low too.
what do they want ?
we're not moving,
ass-faces !
free blanket ?
though we know
we have differences,
we believe that a compromise
can be reached.
in the meantime, it hurts us
to see you all on television
sitting in the cold.
will you not take this offering
as a gesture of goodwill ?
you had me
at "free blanket".
free blanket ?
blanket ?
tom, it now looks as if
the native americans
are handing out blankets
as a sign of goodwill
towards the
south park people.
what an incredible display
of compassion.
i certainly hope there's
nothing sinister behind it.
please, as a token
of good faith.
you... understand if i'm a
little wary of trusting you.
it is only a blanket,
mr. marsh.
well, thanks.
oh...
you're welcome.
( coughing, groaning )
tom, it's tuesday
morning now
and the outbreak of sars
in south park
has reached
epic proportions.
( coughs, sniffs )
the entire town
has been quarantined
by the federal government,
nobody allowed in or out,
which means nobody can
come to our aid.
it appears this town, and this
reporter, are done for.
coming up next, choosing
the right hair conditioner--
what you don't know about
hair care products
could be costing you
a bundle !
( coughing )
it's alright, dad.
how is your mother ?
she's hanging in there.
here, drink some beer.
it's cool on my tongue.
you're gonna be
alright.
stanley, listen to me.
i have sars.
there's only a 98% chance
that i will live.
no, dad, no !
listen, stan !
sars is destroying
our people.
the native americans put it
in the blankets they gave us.
( coughs )
soon there will be
only 98% of us left.
what can i do ?
you-- must find a cure
for sars, son,
and save our people.
cure sars ?!
aw, jesus !
the spirit of
middle-class white people
is strong in you, stan.
seek out the wise man
in bellocreek.
now go, go !
( knocks )
what ?
hey, my name's stan,
and i was--
your coming was
foretold to me.
you've come to
save our people.
come in.
watch the cats.
uh, so, do you know
how to cure sars ?
me ?  ha !
no, i am just a guide.
sit down.
you must find
the answer yourself
by taking
an inward journey.
an inward journey ?
that sounds kinda gay.
let the voices of our
ancestors show you the way.
breathe... breathe from
the bag of visions.
ugh.
oh, dude !
how much longer must we wait
for our super highway ?
sars has spread throughout
the entire town of south park,
chief runswithpremise.
their wills
will break soon.
then i suppose we
must be patient.
runswithpremise,
come quickly !
what is the matter,
wife ?
it is our son,
premiserunningthin,
he is very sick !
what is the matter ?
he... he shared a glass with
one of the people from china.
he has sars.
no !
i told you
not to touch them !
papa...
papaaa...
i have given him herbs
from the desert plant
and water from
the cactus of life,
but nothing
seems to be working.
this would not have happened
if those townpeople
would have just
moved away !
no more waiting around--
tomorrow we begin the
final stage of our plan !
shock and awe !
( groaning, coughing )
dad !  dad !
stanley !
did you have an inward journey
with the old man ?
did you have a vision ?
i don't know if i did or not,
i saw something,
someone spoke to me
and told me the middle-class
white way to cure sars--
campbell'schicken noodle soup,
dayquil,andsprite.
yes,
yes, of course.
quickly stan, we must
give it to everyone.
boy, that really
did the trick, stan.
i thought we were kinda,
sort of, not really done for !
thanks to you,
we're all safe now, stan.
( man )
aaahghgh !!!
now, i will blow your weak,
sars-infested bodies
off the earth !
what the--
wait a minute.
stop, stop !
your, your sars--
where did it go ?
we have cured ourselves using
the medicines of our culture.
my son, premiserunningthin,
has the sars as well.
you, you can cure him ?
it is amazing.
all our plants and herbs
failed to heal him.
but your people's remedy
brings the spirit of the
buffalo back into his heart.
perhaps there are
many things we can learn
from your way of life.
we're a simple people,
all we want is to be
allowed to live our lives.
you have cured
premiserunningthin.
in return, i shall give you all
$5 credit at the casino.
alright, alright.
i will not build a super
highway through your town,
and you can all
have your homes back.
alright !
yeah !
woo-hoo !
well, i guess we all
learned that south park
is more than just a town.
it's a community that
nobody can split up !
dude, who the hell
are you ?!
alex.
alex glick ?
i got to come on and do
the guest voice thingy ?
what ?!
get the hell
out of here !
hi, mom !
hi, dad !
hi, jill !
captioning made possible by
comedy central
captioned by
soundwriters™