captioning made possible by
comedy central
♪ i'm going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna have
myself a time ♪
♪ friendly faces
everywhere ♪
♪ humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna leave my
woes behind ♪
♪ ample parking
day or night ♪
♪ people spouting
"howdy neighbor" ♪
♪ headin' on up
to south park ♪
♪ gonna see
if i can't unwind ♪
♪ ( muffled mumble
muffled mumble ) ♪
♪ so come on down
to south park ♪
♪ and meet some
friends of mine ♪♪
dude, i wonder where
kyle is.
maybe he caught
a disease and died.
that'd be so awesome.
dude, that's not funny,
you shouldn't joke about that.
yeah.
who's joking ?
( door opens )
you guys !
i have
awesome news !
you have aids ?!
no, this saturday
for my birthday
my mom said she's taking me
tocasa bonitain denver
and i get to invite
three friends !
wow, casa bonita !
woo-hoo !
what's
casa bonita ?
dude, haven't you
ever been there ?
it's a big mexican restaurant
but they have like,
cliff jumpers and
black bart's cave
and all kinds of stuff !
it's like the disneyland
of mexican restaurants !
this saturday,
awesome !
♪ casa boni-ta
casa boni-ta ♪
♪ food and fun in a
festive atmosphere ♪
♪ casa boni-ta ♪
who said
i'm inviting you ?
you... your mom said you
could take three friends.
yes, threefriends.
you're not
my friend.
well, come on, kyle, who the
hell else are you gonna take
besides stan and kenny ?
i'm gonna
take butters.
he invited me to his
birthday party last month
so i owe him one.
butters ?!
you're gonna take
that butthole ?  why ?
because butters isn't
a total dick to me !
i have never been
a dick to you !
oh please !
all you ever do
is call me names
and rip on me
for being jewish !
kyle, when have i ever ripped
on you for being a jew ?
oh yeah ?
well, you're a stupid jew !
you're a jew.
shut your goddamn
jew mouth !
good job, jew !
jews.
shut up, jew !
you're jewish !
dude, he's jewish.
jew !
i told you jewish people
don't have rhythm.
( bleep ) off, cartman !
okay, except maybe
for that one time.
you've always been
a dick to me, cartman,
and i'm not inviting you.
kyle, you don't
understand !
casa bonita is my most favorite
place in the whole world !
i'll just-- i'll just die
if you don't take me !
please !
sorry,
my mind's made up.
well, ( bleep ) you, kyle !
i don't wanna go to your
faggy birthday party anyway !
i'd rather hang out at home
than have to be around you
and your jew mom for a day.
kiss my balls, asshole !
( door opens and closes )
( door opens )
dude, i totally
didn't mean that, kyle.
i really, really wanna
go to casa bonita.
i'm sorry we had
that fight just now.
you know, i mean,
i said some things,
you said some things,
but i think it was good
and we've moved past it.
i'm not inviting you
to casa bonita.
well, ( bleep ) you, kyle !
i hope you die !
i hope you ( bleeping ) die !
( door slams )
casa bonita !
come on, you guys !
oh, awesome !
come on, you guys,
black bart's cave !
wow, cliff divers !
more sopaipillas, please !
( mariachi music )
i'm not inviting you,
cartman, you can't go.
no !
noooo !
no, casa bonita,
aaagh !
( panting )
god dammit, i have to get
invited to go !
i'm just gonna have to
start being nice to kyle.
hi, kyle !
that isn't it,
cartman.
what isn't it ?
that's not being nice.
that's just putting on
a nice sweater.
i don't understand
the difference.
i know you don't.
( school bell rings )
jimmy !
hey jimmy, wait up !
dude, i need your
advice on something.
well sure, eric,
what's seems to be
the p... problem ?
well, everybody
likes you, jimmy,
and you seem to be
really good with people,
so i was wondering
if you could tell me,
how do you act nice
to people ?
well, the best thing is
not to act nice, eric.
the best thing is to be
genuinely nice.
okay, so how do you act
genuinely nice to people ?
well, eric,
part of being nice
is just making people
smile and laugh.
the best way to do that is by
telling a f-fantastic joke
or a humorous anecd-anecd...
anecdote.
like what ?
well, like try this one
on for size.
knock, knock.
who's there ?
ingmar bergman.
now you say
"ingmar bergman who ?".
oof !
take that, jimmy !
and that !
don't you ever talk bad
about kyle again !
kyle is my friend !
and if you say you had sex
with his mom one more time
i'm gonna really
let you have it !
you hear me ?!
oh, kyle, hey.
you really think that
beating up a handicapped kid
is being nice ?
hey, kyle !
knock knock !
knock knock, kyle !
yeah, casa bonita
this saturday !
wow, that's gonna
be so fun !
yeah it'll be awesome,
just the four of us !
yeah !
( bell rings )
hey, kyle.
well ?
well what ?
how are you going to
try to get invited
to casa bonita
this time ?
i'm not, kyle.
i know you already
told butters he could go.
oh, well,
yeah, i did.
so, fine, kyle,
but honestly,
i never meant to
make you feel
like you didn't matter
at all to me.
i know we argue all the time,
and i give you tons of crap,
but we've also been through
a lot together, and,
maybe that alone
doesn't make us friends
but it makes us something.
so, whatever,
you know, just,
i hope things
can be cool.
i'm still not inviting you
to casa bonita.
i know, kyle,
i'll see you later.
hey, cartman.
you really don't care
that you can't go ?
i care, sure, but i
hope it doesn't mean
you and me and stan and kenny
can't hang out anymore.
that's exactly what i wanted
to hear from you all along.
i still have to take butters,
but i hope things
can be cool too.
good.
and hey, if for some reason
butters can't go
to casa bonita,
you can take his place.
sweet, whatever.
bingo.
what's this
all about, eric ?
butters, can you
keep a secret ?
well, sure i can !
for the past five days i've
been looking out into space
for a school project.
this morning
at 3:45 a.m.
i caught first sight of
something terrible.
how terrible ?
a meteor.
a meteor the size
of wyoming--
heading right for earth.
what ?!
now look,
i could be wrong !
i pray that i'm wrong,
but i just want you
to take a look
and see what you think.
do you see
anything ?
i just see stars.
keep looking.
sometimes it takes your eyes
a minute to adjust.
nope, i don't see any--
whoa, wait !
oh my god !
i see it, i see it !
it's a meteor !
oh my god !
does it look like
it's getting closer ?
it is !
it is getting closer !
oh my god !
oh my god, that meteor
is the size of wyoming
and it's on a collision
course for earth !
when do you think
it'll get here ?
i, i don't know, i have to
do some calculations.
10 to the power
of one base nine,
divided by pi,
plus five minus three...
oh jesus.
what ?!
according to
my calculations,
that meteor's gonna hit earth
in less than four hours.
oh, you mean
we're gonna die ?
no !
no, butters, we are
going to live !
do you hear me ?
we are going to live !
we've just,
we've gotta find
a bomb shelter !
where is there
a bomb shelter ?
stan's uncle jimbo !
he has a bomb shelter
in his back yard !
come on, butters,
hurry !
aaaghh !
here we go, bomb
shelter's down here !
oh god !
oh jesus !
all right, we should be
safe in here.
there's dried food and water
to last us for weeks.
but what about
everyone else ?
i have to tell my parents so
they can come here too !
no, butters, i can't
let you risk it !
i'll go up
and get the others.
are you sure ?
i'm not sure of
anything anymore.
now butters, listen--
no matter what happens,
no matter what you hear,
do not come out.
if i don't make it back
in time with the others,
then it will be up to you
to repopulate the earth.
but i'm the
only one down here,
what am i supposed to
repopulate with ?
well, you know,
with your wiener.
just stay down here until
you hear word from me.
and pray, butters,
pray for all mankind.
oh god.
where is butters ?
we were supposed to leave
40 minutes ago !
well, i think we better
just go without him, kyle.
it's getting late.
yeah, screw him,
let's go.
( doorbell rings )
oh, finally !
happy birthday, kyle.
i just wanted to stop by
and give you your present.
oh, thanks, dude.
hope you have a good one !
see ya later !
oh, wait, cartman.
yes ?
butters didn't show.
you wanna go to
casa bonita with us ?
butters didn't show ?
i can't believe it.
are you sure you told him the
right time and everything ?
i told him 5:30, and
we gotta get going.
you in ?
well, i really would need to
go home first and get my--
well, no, i guess i have
everything i need.
okay, sure.
all right, let's go !
okay, boys,
get in the car.
casa bonita,
here we come !
oh, hello,
chris, linda.
hello, everyone.
have any of you
seen our son ?
butters was supposed to go with
us to casa bonita tonight.
we know, but, he hasn't been
home since last night.
the police have been
looking everywhere but--
( sobbing )
well, thank you.
please, let us know
if you find out anything.
( wailing )
oh, butters !
oh dude, weak.
yeah, man, that sucks
about butters.
well, let's get going,
shall we ?
nah... dude, i can't go to
have a birthday party
while butters is missing.
yeah, it's kinda weird.
yeah, yeah,
i think you're right
but, on the other hand,
i think butters
would want us to go.
you know butters.
nah, i can't.
we should help
look for him.
yeah.
that's very good
of you, boys.
we can postpone casa bonita
until next saturday.
next saturday ?!
i'll never be able to keep
butters down in the--
in the depths of my heart
for that long.
i sure hope he
turns up before then.
dude, we should check
over at starks' pond,
butters always
hangs out over there.
yeah, and then we can
try the football field.
i'll drive you boys.
aw, god dammit !
how am i gonna keep butters
down in that bomb shelter
for a whole week ?!
all right, folks, this is the
little boy we're looking for:
leopold stotch,
also known as "butters".
he's been missing
for two days
and was last seen
at the school.
let's go find 'im !
"dried food rations.
add water to
beef-flavored square..."
hello ?
hello !
butters !
aaaagh !
oh god, it was,
it was horrible !
what happened ?
the meteor--
struck the earth sooner
than i predicted.
there was no time.
no time.
what about my parents ?
did you see them ?
there was mass
confusion, panic.
people were crawling all over
each other in the streets,
it was awful !
then it hit.
millions were
evaporated instantly.
the rest of us,
walking around in a cloud
of toxic radiation.
( coughs )
oh my god,
let me see !
no, butters !
if you come up,
you'll get infected too.
you best wait for the
radiation levels to go down.
probably...
next week sometime.
after saturday.
how many survivors
are there ?
you should all
come down here !
we can't come down there
or else we'll
contaminate you, butters.
no, we just have to survive
best we can.
wow...
eric, i can never
thank you enough
for everything
you've done for me.
thank me by living,
butters.
live and rebuild.
( coughs )
i've got to go.
remember, wait one week for
the toxic levels to go down.
after saturday.
good-bye.
all right,
just six days, butters.
sit tight.
tom, it has now been
three days
since the stotch child
has gone missing.
townspeople continue to search
but hope is dwindling.
all right, folks, i wanna
thank you for all your efforts.
three days is a long time,
but we've got to keep going
if we're gonna find him.
( eric )
you're not going to find him.
not until after saturday when
i finally go to casa bonita.
( mariachi music )
many times in cases like these
a child can trap themselves.
it's important that
we spread our search
to duct pipes, wells
and bomb shelters.
( record needle scratch )
wha-- whoa-- what ?
i say we need to
move the search
to ducts, wells
and bomb shelters.
let's move out, people,
every second counts.
agh !
♪ but if you leave me now ♪
♪ you take away the
biggest part of me ♪
♪ ooh ohh ohhh girl
baby, please don't go ♪
♪ ooh oh ohhhh girl-- ♪
eric ?
eric, is that you ?
oh god !
they're coming !
we've gotta get
out of here !
they're coming
this way !
who's coming this way ?
the cannibals !
don't you know ?!
the meteor destroyed
all society, butters,
now earth is ruled by packs
of wild humans gone mad !
those of us who survived
are now being hunted
by flesh-starved
cannibals !
oh god !
i hate cannibals !
they're coming
this way.
i can hear them.
they'll find you
down here for sure,
and when they do,
they'll eat you alive.
no !
we gotta get you
out of here, come on !
oh no, wait, i forgot--
the toxic radiation !
hey, wait,
we can use this box !
there we go, that should keep
you protected from the toxins.
but i can't see nothing.
believe me, butters, you don't
want to see what's up there.
now, come on, i'll guide you
to a safer location.
there you go.
two more steps
and you're at the top.
good.
are we out in
the destruction ?
yes.
there's nothing but smoldering
bodies all around you,
burnt out buildings and
what used to be our town.
oh, man.
all right, this way,
butters,
just follow the sound
of my voice.
right now we're walking by what
used to be people's houses.
now just smoldering,
burnt piles of rubble.
oh, oh,
it's terrible !
we're coming now to the crater
where the meteor hit:
a hole in the earth over
two miles in diameter.
whoa...
here we are at
the old gas station.
it survived
a lot of the impact.
we might be safe here.
brrragagahgh !
oh my god !
what ?
it's a cannibal !
stay back, cannibal !
brraagaggahagh !
aaaagh !
i've got to
fight them off !
agh !
stay away from butters,
he's humanity's last hope !
bragaaggah !
braahaggh !
agh !
he bit me !
he bit off my hand !
aaaaaaaaaagh !
oh god, he's eating my hand
like a piece of chicken !
can you hear
the bones crack ?
argashsgh !
ohhh !
wait, look here !
there's a dead body
with an axe in the back !
i'll pull out the axe
and use it to cut off
the cannibal's head !
ha !
die !
glarg !
what happened ?
what happened ?!
the cannibal...
the cannibal is dead,
butters.
but he bit me, which means
soon i will have a thirst
for human flesh as well.
oh, no !
we have no choice,
butters,
we have to lock you
away somewhere
where even i can't
get to you.
where ?
look, there's an old
refrigerator !
get inside, butters !
i'll break off the handle
so nobody can get to you.
are you coming ?
it's too late for me.
i can already feel my body
start to change.
no, must fight it !
don't open this door
for anybody, butters.
no matter what you hear,
stay inside for four days.
here's some water and food
from the shelter.
eric, you're the best friend
in the whole world.
i... i love you.
i love you too, man.
i-- ooh, you look
so delicious !
must eat your brains !
aaaaagh !
( chuckles )
( alarm rings )
hah !
it's wednesday !
only three more days
to casa bonita !
i'm gonna go through
black bart's cave first !
no-- i'm gonna watch
the cliff divers first !
maybe if i tell 'em
it's my birthday,
they'll let me cliff dive
into the pool !
oh, that would be
so bad-ass !
( thumping )
( coughing and gasping )
oh, finally,
i can breathe the--
oh my god.
oh my god, the meteor
took out everything !
it's all destroyed...
nothing left.
hello !
are there any other
survivors ?
hello !
ooh, that must have been
where the library was.
and that was probably
the school.
hello ?
oh, i forgot, i gotta watch out
for radioactive cannibals.
is that a cannibal ?
sir, ma'am ?
oh !
oh, it's a little dog !
well, hello there,
mr. dog.
looks like you and me
are the only ones
that survived the meteor.
we should stick together,
huh, mr. dog ?
well, come on, we gotta start
cleaning up this mess
and rebuilding civilization.
boy, that meteor sure did
make everything stinky.
( eric )
♪ we're on our way
to casa boni-ta ♪
♪ we're gonna be there
very soon ♪
you're gonna love
casa bonita, stan.
there's this one part
where you can dress up
in old western clothes
and get your photo taken
in a fake jail !
really ?
yeah, it's
pretty cool.
pretty cool ?
so, um, should we go to
black bart's cave first
or watch the puppet show ?
i think we should go through
black bart's cave right away
'cause we're gonna wanna
do it seven or eight times.
and then we'll watch
the cliff divers
before the puppet show.
dude,
it's kyle's birthday.
we should do whatever
he wants to do.
what ?
( bleep ) kyle !
ha, ha !
just kidding !
birthday joke !
of course we do
whatever kyle wants.
happy birthday, kyle !
♪ happy birthday
to you ♪
♪ happy... ♪
( all )
♪ birthday to you ♪
♪ happy birthday
dear kyle ♪
♪ happy birthday to you ♪♪
( butters )
♪ ... you take away the
biggest part of me ♪
♪ ooh ohh ohhh
baby, please don't go ♪
♪ oooh oooh girl
i just have to... ♪
hello ?
aaaghh !
who are you ?
are you infected ?
with what ?
you're not a cannibal,
are you ?
no !
oh... oh, good !
you're a survivor
like me !
look, mr. dog,
another survivor.
and it's a lady too.
that means we can
repopulate the earth !
yippie !
kid, what are you
doing here ?
i'm rebuilding society !
here, take a look.
this is the library,
and over here is the bank.
that over there i'm thinking
of making into ap.f. chang's
or abennigan's.
and this... is a memorial
to eric cartman,
the person who gave his life so
that i could rebuild society.
well, ma'am, i guess
we should start
repopulating
the earth, huh ?
i'm ready whenever
you are.
kid, i don't know what
you think is going on,
but this place is a dump.
hey, that's not
very nice !
this is my first society,
i'm doing my best.
no, i mean, you're
at the garbage dump.
town is right over there,
everybody is fine,
and i think they've been
looking for you
for over a week.
oh...
ma'am, can i use
your phone ?
( eric )
we're here, we're here !
casa bonita !
oh man, this is gonna
be so great !
wait up, eric, we need to
stay together !
( phone rings )
oh, hold on, boys,
that's my cell phone.
hello ?
yes...
oh, that's great !
boys, they found butters,
he's okay !
oh, awesome !
i knew he'd turn up.
yes, eric cartman
is with us, why ?
oh, really ?
what ?
yes, i will certainly
let him know.
thank you.
well, it appears
that eric here
is responsible
for butters missing
because he wanted to go
to casa bonita.
what ?
eric, the south park police
are already on their way here
to have a little
talk with you.
but-- casa bonita !
i should have
known better.
you never cared about
my birthday at all !
but i-- but--
stand back !
cartman, stop it !
i am going--
to casa bonita !
( police sirens )
it's too late,
fat-ass.
they'll be here
in less than a minute.
agh !
dah !
less than a minute !
cartman !
( mariachi music )
( huffing )
oh, awesome !
excuse me, excuse me !
can i just eat some of
your-- thank you.
thank you.
okay, okay, gotta get to
black bart's cave !
excuse me !
coming through !
black bart's cave !
oh scary !
look, a skeleton !
oh man,
i'm so scared !
( huffing )
oh, that was awesome !
cliff divers !
come on,
come on, dive !
dive, asshole !
oh, awesome !
that was cool, huh ?
come on, come on...
( camera snaps )
sopaipillas !
can i get some
sopaipillas, please ?!
sweet !
ooh, puppet show !
puppet show !
agh !
cartman !
wagh !
all right, kid,
end of the line.
yesssss !
jesus christ !
( coughs )
well, kid, you made
an entire town panic,
you lost all your friends
and now you're going to
juvenile hall for a week.
heh,
was it worth it ?
totally.
captioning made possible by
comedy central
captioned by
soundwriters™