♪ i'm going down
To south park ♪
♪ gonna have
Myself a time ♪
♪ friendly faces
Everywhere ♪
♪ humble folks
Without temptation ♪
♪ going down
To south park ♪
♪ gonna leave my
Woes behind ♪
♪ ample parking
Day or night ♪
♪ people spouting
"howdy neighbor" ♪
♪ headin' on up
To south park ♪
♪ gonna see
If i can't unwind ♪
♪ ( muffled mumble
Muffled mumble ) ♪
♪ so come on down
To south park ♪
♪ and meet some
Friends of mine ♪♪
♪ chanukah, chanukah ♪
♪ sivivon
Sov, sov... ♪
I gotta go tinkle !
No, ike, shh !
♪ sov, sov, sov
Ma naim vatov ♪♪
We thank god for our
Blessings this chanukah.
Our little family
Is so loving and perfect
And nothing will ever
Tear us apart !
( doorbell rings )
I'll get it !
Gerald broflovski ?
Yes.
My name is harry gintz
And this is my wife, elise.
We're from canada.
Yes, i can tell.
My wife and i had a child
A few years back,
And we weren't ready
To have a child
So we put him up
For adoption.
We were told that you
Might be the--
Peter !
Oh god, harry,
It's our son !
Peter, it's mommy !
Gerald, what the hell
Is going on ?!
I'm not sure.
It was a tough time
For us.
For all of canada.
The whole country was
Devastated by the cola wars.
It just seemed we couldn't
Take care of a baby.
So we put him up
For adoption.
But as the years
Passed, i,
I just felt an
Emptiness in my heart.
Oh, it's so good
To see him !
Well, we... Wish you all
The best, mr. And mrs. Gintz.
But, to be honest, i think
It would be best for ike
If you didn't
Come around again.
I don't think
You understand.
We didn't come
To visit peter--
We came to
Take him back.
What ?
We want to take
Peter home, to canada.
Are you crazy ?!
Look, you gave ike up.
You can't just
Change your mind !
Changing your mind
Is a canadian custom
That we hold quite dear.
And besides, the new
Canadian prime minister
Has issued a decree
That all adopted canadians
Must be returned home.
The new canadian
Prime minister ?!
Look, ike is our son now !
He doesn't belong here.
He belongs in canada
With his own kind.
I think you better leave.
Please, don't make this
Any harder for peter.
Harder for peter ?!
You two just
Blow in here
And say you're gonna
Haul him back to canada
And we're being hard
On peter ?!
We're prepared
To go to court.
But we had hoped it
Wouldn't come to that.
You bet your ass
It'll come to that !
I'm sorry to say
That my hands are tied.
The new prime minister
Of canada
Has authority this court
Cannot override.
By canadian law, i must
Award custody of the child
To his birth parents.
Yes !
No !
Ike's not my little
Brother anymore ?
Gerald, do something !
There's nothing
I can do.
( crying )
Good-bye, ike.
You... Be a good
Boy, huh ?
You... Remember all the
Things we taught you.
Ike...
You'll always be my
Little brother, okay ?
Come on, peter,
We should get going.
No !
Peter, you must come
With mommy and daddy.
No, no, no,
No, no !
I have some
Chocolate.
Chocolate !
We're going to take
Good care of him.
You better.
Dad ?
Can't we talk to this new
Canadian prime minister ?
If he knew the situation
He might--
Oh kyle, appealing to the
Prime minister of canada
Would take time and
Money we don't have.
Dude, look at that.
"sprinkle time make-your-own
Marshmallow factory".
I'm definitely asking
For that for christmas.
Dude, i'm gonna tell
My parents to get me
That john elway doll with
The karate chop action.
Guys.
Guys, i need
Your help.
Sure, dude !
It's been a week
Since ike's been gone.
And every day
My parents seem worse.
I have to try to
Go to canada
And speak with the new
Canadian prime minister.
But i can't
Do it alone.
We can't go to
Canada, dumbass !
It's christmas !
Yeah dude, what if we
Miss out on some
Great christmas
Adventure ?
Please, you guys,
You don't understand.
My family is devastated.
My mom just walks around
The house like a zombie,
And my dad
Can't stop crying !
Well, i didn't want to
Say anything, kyle,
But i think maybe this is
What your family gets
For being jewish
At christmastime.
Dude, cartman.
I'm just saying
Maybe jesus is having
A little revenge,
That's all.
I found the number of a really
Cheap airline to canada.
If we go as soon
As possible--
Dude, we just can't
Up and go to canada.
Look, they're about to
Light the christmas tree,
Maybe you can get your brother
Back some other way.
Kyle, i just
Want you to know,
If it were any other
Time of the year
I still
Wouldn't help you.
( crowd )
Three !  Two !  One !
Yeah !
Hooray !
As we celebrate
This glorious time
We can't forget those families
Who are suffering.
As many of you know,
The broflovski family
Has recently had their child
Torn away from them.
As a community,
We must do all we can
To ease their pain.
Are there any suggestions
How we might help ?
How about, we get rid of
All the mexicans !
Mr. Garrison,
Every christmas you suggest
We get rid of
All the mexicans
And every christmas
We tell you: no.
Rats !
The broflovskis need money
To appeal their case
To the new canadian
Prime minister.
What if this christmas,
Instead of buying presents,
We all use that money to
Give to the broflovskis ?
Ha !
Yeah, right !
Like our parents
Aren't gonna buy us
Presents for
Christmas !
That's a great
Idea, chef !
What ?
Yeah, who needs
More stuff anyway ?
This christmas
We can do something
That really matters !
Dad, don't get
Carried away.
Then it's settled !
This year we'll give
All our christmas money
To the broflovskis in hopes
That they may someday
Have their child
Returned to them !
( cheering )
No... No, this can't
Be happening !
( sobbing )
You ( bleeping ) asshole !!
This is all
Your fault !!
What ?
Everyone's gonna
Be charitable
And give money
To your family
Instead of buying
Christmas presents !
You ( bleeping ) jews
Ruined christmas again !
Arrghgh !
Whoa, whoa,
Cartman.
It wasn't enough for
You people to kill jesus,
Now you have to kill
Christmas too, huh ?!
Cartman, calm down !
Is that true ?
It's true, dude--
Christmas is ruined.
This is it, kyle,
You and me,
We're throwing down,
Right now.
I'm sorry, you guys.
But there is something
We can do.
We can go to canada
And see the prime
Minister like i said.
If we can change his mind
Before christmas,
Then your parents won't have
To give my family money.
You really think
If we go to canada
We might still get
Christmas presents ?
It's worth a shot.
Come on, you guys,
We can do this.
All right, but we
Better not miss out
On any great christmas
Adventures.
We'll get back in time
For a christmas adventure.
Fine, but if it
Doesn't work,
You and me are gonna
Have it out, kyle.
Once and for all.
No business.
Christmas time come
And a-nobody wanna eat
A-chinese food.
Rooks rike
I might as well crose.
( phone rings )
Oh boy,
Some business !
Finally !
Harro,shity wok,
Take a order, prease !
Oh, i must have
The wrong number.
We were trying to
Reachcity airlines.
Oh, yes, just
A moment, prease !
Harro,shity airlines,
Can i help you ?
Take a order, prease ?
Uh, we need to
Go to canada.
As soon as possible !
Ooh, canada, okay,
That's pretty far.
Gonna cost a rot of money,
Ret's see...
How many people ?
Four.
Okay, four people, canada,
Cost a rot of money.
That gonna be about
6,500 dorrar.
How about 50 dorrar ?
50 dorra ?!
You flying canada cost
At least 3,000 dorra !
55 dorra.
Hey !
Stop wasting my time
55 dorra.
No way i take
My plane to canada
For less than
A thousand dorra !
Okay, 60 dorra.
62 dorra.
Okay.
Okay, meet me
Park county airfield,
Yellow cessna
Tail number 432-g.
Got it !
Hee hee hee !
Never try to barter
With a chinese man.
We have exactly 52 hours
Before christmas.
That means we have to
Be back in 28 hours
To still give our parents
24 hours
To buy us presents.
Synchronize watches
On my mark...
Mark.
Harro, welcome
Shity airline !
Oh, no, no no no, i am not
Flying in that thing.
Me neither.
Why not ?
'Cause, dude,
I'll die !
You're not
Gonna die, kenny !
Don't be stupid !
You guys go get ike.
Kenny and i will stay here
And watch the fort.
No, you're both coming.
Do you care about
Christmas or not ?
Of course i care
About christmas !
Aw, christ on a stick !
Ah dude, it smells like
Kung pao chicken in here.
( over speaker )
Okay, welcome aboard
Shity airline.
This is your
Captain speaking.
Rooking about
A two-hour fright.
I'll be turning on
The seat belt sign now.
If your seats
Hadseat belts
This is the time
You would fasten them.
Prease sit back, relax and
Enjoy your shity flight.
( kyle )
All right !
We're going to canada !
( cartman )
Weak.
Hey, turn off
The right.
Whoa, wait !
Ohh !
What's going on ?!
Harro from the cockpit,
This is your
Captain speaking.
As you can see, it appears
That we are going down.
Now would be a good time
To refrect on your life,
And pray to whatever deity
You berieve in.
Thank you for frying
Shity airlines.
We know you have
A choice in airlines,
And it looks like
You made the wrong one.
Hey, where the hell
Are you going ?!
Do something, kyle !
I'm trying !
Look out !
( kenny )
Nooooooo !!!
You guys...
I don't think
We're in america anymore.
Excuse me !
Uh, is this
An invasion ?
No.
Oh, thank heavens !
It's okay-- everyone,
It's not an invasion !
I was sure when that plane
Fell from the sky
That we had
An invader !
Hey, we're in canada !
Well, of course
You are !
And canada, friends,
Welcomes you !
♪ welcome friends
To canada ♪
♪ canada friends
Loves you ♪
♪ we're just like
Any other country ♪
♪ without the big to do ♪
♪ we greet thee
With pleasure ♪
♪ but one question
If we may ♪
♪ what brings you folks
To canada ? ♪
♪ why are you here
Today ? ♪
Uh...
My adopted brother got taken
Back here to canada.
So, we want to talk to the
New canadian prime minister
About getting him back.
♪ his brother's
Here somewhere ♪
♪ the question is
Is where ? ♪
♪ he must talk to the new
Prime minister here ♪
♪ to get his brother home
Back there ♪
Oh, jesus christ.
Hey, what the hell
Is going on ?!
( all screaming )
Scott !
It's scott !
Who damaged our beloved
Canadian land ?!
Who's that ?
That's scott !
He's a dick !
Aha !
Americans !
I should have known !
You think you're the police
Of the world !
You think you own canada !
Well, you aren't
Welcome here.
Get out now !
Oh, no you don't, scott,
Leave these boys alone.
This isn't over,
You american scum,
I swear to god,
You'll rue this day !
God, what a dick !
Look, we don't have a lot
Of time here, okay ?
Can you just tell us where
The new prime minister is ?
The new prime minister doesn't
Live in this part of canada.
He's in ottawa !
So how do we get
To ottawa ?
Oh, that's easy, you just
Have to follow the road !
Which road ?
This is canada,
We only have one road.
♪ follow
The only road ♪
♪ follow the only road ♪
♪ to go anywhere
In canada ♪
♪ you just follow
The only road ♪
♪ there's only one road
In canada ♪
♪ we call it 'the road'
The only road ♪
♪ hip hip hooray ♪
♪ let's hear it
For our road ♪
♪ it's paved and wide
And up to code ♪
All right, dude, let's get
The hell out of here.
Word.
♪ you're off to see
The prime minister ♪
♪ the prime minister
Of canada ♪♪
Good-bye, friends !
Good luck with
The new prime minister !
And remember to watch our
For scott, he's a dick !
Good-bye !
So long !
See you !
Watch out for scott !
20 hours
Until christmas.
Our parents still have
Time to buy us presents
If we hurry.
Ahoy there, travelers !
Who are you ?
I am rick, the proud
Canadian mountie !
Baaaa !
I thought mounties were
Supposed to ride horses.
Yes, yes we are.
But our funding has been cut,
And now we're forced to ride...
Baaaa.
If you don't mind,
We're in a rush to see
The new prime minister.
You're going to see
The new prime minister ?!
Oh, i would so like to
Meet him myself !
It's his strange new laws
That took our horses away !
Perhaps i will
Go with you !
That's okay,
We'd rather just--
Follow me this way !
♪ we're going to see
The prime minister ♪
♪ the prime minister
Of canada ♪♪
Power hungry americans.
I'll fix you !
Oh jesus, 18 hours.
We're running
Out of time.
All right, boys,
Prepare yourselves.
We're about to enter
French canada.
French canada ?
♪ there's no canada
Like french canada ♪
♪ it's the best canada
In ze land ♪
♪ the other canada
Is hardly canada ♪
♪ if you lived here for a day
You'd understand ♪
Ho, ho, ho !
Welcome to
French canada !
We have everysing your
Heart could desire.
Trapezes, trampolines and
Lots and lots of cheese.
Would you like
A mustache ?
Just stay calm, boys.
French canadians
Are a little odd.
Uh, we're just passing through
To see the new prime minister.
Well, first you must
Answer that phone.
Ring ring !
We don't have
Time for this.
You cannot pass through
French canada
Unless you take
Zat phone call !
Ring ring !
Hello.
'Allo !
If you are going to see
Ze new prime minister
Zen i want to go
With you !
He has passed a new law
Forbidding us french canadians
To drink wine !
How can ze french
Not drink wine ?
Travas-tee !
Okay, you can
Come with us.
Ho, ho !
Very good !
Let us make haste !
♪ there's no canada
Like french canada ♪
♪ it's the best canada
In ze land ♪
♪ and ze other canada
Is a bourgeois canada ♪
♪ if you lived here for a day
You'd understand ♪
♪ i think
♪ you understand ♪♪
Oh my !
This certainly is
A desolate place.
It reminds me
Of death and fear.
( cartman )
How much further
To ottawa ?!
Christmas is only
12 hours away !
We must be
Very close now.
Eh !  What
Are you doing ?!
Aaaah !
Oh, no,
It's scott !
What are you two doing
Helping these americans ?
Don't you know america
Thinks it owns canada
Along with the rest
Of the world ?
You're a dick,
Scott !
You're a dick !
And by helping americans, you're
Just as smelly as they are !
Now i'm going to get you !
Not so fast, scott.
Who the hell are you ?!
I am steve
The newfoundlander.
And you're on newfoundland
Property now.
Get off before
I have you arrested !
Ooh, this isn't over,
Not by a long shot !
I'll fix you,
I'll fix all of you !
Ooh, that was
A close call.
Thank you,
Kind newfie.
God dammit,
We need to get to
The new prime
Minister, now !
Oh, yeah the prime
Minister, eh ?
He sure has screwed up
Things for newfoundland.
Life just hasn't been the same
Since he made sodomy illegal.
Well, come with us !
Maybe you can ask to him to
Take his sodomy ban away !
Can we just get
Going, please ?!
Yeah, sure, except
There's just one problem.
What ?
You folks is going
The wrong way.
What ?!
But i thought there was only
One road in canada !
Yeah, and you all went
The wrong direction on it.
Oh, that's right !
Ottawa is that way.
Of course !
Ottawa left,
Newfoundland right !
Oh, no !
How could you be
So stupid ?!
There's no way we can
Go all the way back !
We'll never
Make it now !
It's okay, boys, the power is
Inside us to get to ottawa !
We can wish
Ourselves there !
Oh yes, let's
Wish ourselves there !
( harp plucking,
Heavenly choir )
Is it working ?
Oh, god damn it !
Well, i warned you,
Kyle !
I told you if i missed christmas
We were gonna throw down !
Well, it's on.
We're gonna have it out
Right now !
Of course, we could always
Take my boat, eh ?
Oh yes !
On the river we could travel
To ottawa in no time !
Well, come on !
Okay, next stop: the new
Prime minister !
Do you think we can
Still make it in time ?
We better, kyle...
Or you're dead.
Here we are at
The parliament building.
Ze prime minister
Is inside !
( cartman )
Well, come on, let's hurry,
It's almost christmas !
Yyyyeeesss ?
We need to see
The new prime minister !
Ha !
Impossible !
The new prime minister
Is not seeing anybody !
Oh well,
So much for zat.
Yeah, we gave it
Our best,
But i guess our best
Wasn't good enough, eh ?
No... No !
Yyyeesss ?
Please, sir !
I've traveled a long way
To get here.
He's the only person
Who can help me.
The prime minister
Isn't here.
He's in china
On official business.
So you might as well
Go home.
Good-bye !
Then that's it.
I, i'm never going to
Get my brother back.
And... I'm not going to get
Any christmas presents.
And... I'm not gonna have
A christmas adventure.
( kenny mumbles )
( all crying )
Oh, please,
Please stop crying !
I'm gonna kill
You, kyle.
All right, all right !
I was lying !
The prime
Minister is here.
Really ?!
Yes, yes, come in !
I am the prime minister
Of canada !
What do you guys want ?
Sir, you recently passed
A new law allowing parents
Who had given their
Children up for adoption
To change their minds.
My little brother
Was--
Not so fast !
Ike !
Kyle !
Prime minister, these are the
Child's canadian parents !
Their canadian blood
Pumps through his veins.
Would you send him
Back to america
With those
War-hungry scum ?
Please, sir !
I came because i don't
Think ike belongs here.
Family isn't about whose blood
You have in you.
Family is about the people
Who cared about you
And took care of you.
We're not the same blood,
But i love my little brother.
We've taken care of him
Because he needed us to.
And that makes us more
Family than anything.
That was a great
Speech, guy.
But the answer is no !
All of my new laws will stay
In effect forever !
Ha ha !
You lose, americans !
Then i suppose us mounties
Will never get our horses.
And we won't
Get our wine.
And we can't
Perform sodomy, eh.
But why are you making
Such strange laws ?
I said go !
Oh my god !
They killed kenny !
You... Bastards.
What, what the hell
Is wrong with you ?!
What kind of prime minister
Bases his decisions on hatred ?
And takes away mounties' horses
And french people's wine ?
What the hell kind of prime
Minister are you anyway ?!
I am the prime minister
Of canada !
I can do whatever i...
Uh-oh !
Uh, don't mind that guy
Hiding in the spider hole,
He's just my friend !
What the hell !
Hey, that looks like
Saddam hussein !
Saddam hussein ?
Nooo,
Relax, buddy !
I'm not him !
Zat explains
Everything !
Ze new prime minister was
Saddam hussein once again
Trying to take over
Our beloved canada
Like he did before !
Saddam hussein ?
He was fooling us ?
Get him !
Uh, don't shoot !
I want to negotiate !
Hey, relax !
Wait a minute !
This means all the prime
Minister's new laws
Are null and void !
We can have
Our horses back !
And we can
Drink our wine !
And i can sodomize
Me boys again !
Young man, you must
Really care for peter
To have come
All this way.
Perhaps we were wrong to
Try and take peter back.
He doesn't belong here,
He belongs with his family.
Peter, would you like to go
Back to your home in colorado ?
( electronic beeping )
What is that ?
It's christmas.
We officially
Missed it.
It's christmas day,
And i'm in canada.
Yeah, but,
I got my brother back.
Yeah, you got
Your brother back,
But i didn't get
Any presents !
And what did i
Tell you, kyle ?
I told you if we didn't make it
Back in time for christmas
I was gonna whoop your ass,
Didn't i ?!
Dude, come on.
Well, now you're gonna
Get it, mother ( bleeper ) !
That's right, you and me,
Right now, we're having it out !
Let's go.
Come on !
( thwap )
Aaaaaaahhhh !
( wailing )
Myaaam !
Myaaaaam !
Hey, come on, boys !
You can spend christmas
With us, canada style !
♪ ding dong
They caught saddam ♪
♪ merry christmas
To the world ♪
♪ ding dong, the americans
Caught saddam ♪
♪ now, canada is free
For you and you and me ♪
♪ it's the best christmas
Present we ever got ♪
♪ canadian christmas
Is the best ♪
♪ we drink and dance
And show our breasts ♪
♪ and celebrate saddam
Hussein's been caught ♪♪
Oh well, maybe
We'll get to have
A christmas adventure
Next year.
Captioning made possible by
Comedy central
Captioned by
Soundwriters™