captioning made possible by
comedy central
♪ i'm going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna have
myself a time ♪
♪ friendly faces
everywhere ♪
♪ humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna leave my
woes behind ♪
♪ ample parking
day or night ♪
♪ people spouting
"howdy neighbor" ♪
♪ headin' on up
to south park ♪
♪ gonna see
if i can't unwind ♪
♪ ( muffled mumble
muffled mumble ) ♪
♪ so come on down
to south park ♪
♪ and meet some
friends of mine ♪♪
( school bell rings )
okay, children,
let's take our seats.
we have a new student
joining us today
who has just moved here
from utah.
i want you all
to say hi to gary !
hello, everybody.
it's really great
to meet you all !
gary was state champion
in wrestling
and in tennis !
he also maintained
a 4.0 grade point average
at his old school
and has been on two national
commercials for toothpaste.
i'm really excited to
live in this town
and share all kinds of great
experiences with you,
my new friends !
oh dude,
what a little asshole.
yeah, screw that kid.
all right, gary, why don't you
take that empty seat
and we'll get started
with the lesson.
hey, my name's gary.
hi !
my name's ura !
ura fag !
that's funny !
you're cool, man.
okay now, who can
tell me what year
the first astronauts
landed on the moon ?
ooh, ooh ooh ooh !
1969 !
very good, gary !
wow, looks like
i don't have a class
full of retards anymore,
doesn't it, children ?
dude, that new kid
is such a douche.
yeah, somebody needs to
put him in his place.
he's a pecker-face,
that's what he is !
go kick his ass,
stan !
yeah,
go kick his ass.
maybe he won't fight.
will he bleed ?
that's all
we care about.
come on, dude,
somebody needs to
wipe that ( bleeping )
smirk off his face.
yeah,
little bitch !
all right, i'm gonna go
kick his ass.
yeah, go stan !
go stan !
all right, i got five bucks
on the other kid.
who wants it ?
oh, hey there !
do you wanna kick the ball
around with me ?
no, i'm...
i'm gonna
kick your ass.
excuse me ?
i'm gonna
kick your ass.
bitch.
how come you
wanna fight me ?
oh, i get it,
i'm the new kid.
yeah, i guess maybe
i deserve it.
huh ?
it's really tough being
in a totally new place,
but i think all you guys
are really cool, so,
i understand if there's
initiation rights.
dude, stop it.
let him have it,
stan !
shut up, butters !
the other kids
are watching.
look, do what you gotta do,
i won't fight back.
i just hope that
maybe afterwards
we can try to be
friends someday.
what are they doing ?
they're just standing
there talking.
what happened ?
i'm... going over to his
house for dinner tonight.
( token )
what, how did that happen ?
he's... a really
nice kid.
you were supposed to
kick his ass,
not lick his butthole !
you're having dinner
with his family ?!
what kind of family
has a kid like that ?
( laughter )
okay, my turn !
ooh, five !
one, two, three, four, five--
oh, "lost your mortgage--
pay $10,000" !
oh, no !
hey, it's gary !
gary !
great to see you !
how are you ?
hey, everybody, this is
my new friend, stan.
stan, this is
my mom and dad.
hi, stan !
it's so nice
to meet you !
( gary )
and this is my
brother mark...
hi !
my sister jenny...
hey !
my little
brother dave...
hi !
and my baby sister,
amanda !
hello, stan !
well, it's great
you could join us
for family
home evening, stan !
what's that ?
that's when we don't
allow any tv,
and just entertain each other
with music and stories !
doesn't your family
ever do that ?
no.
hey kids, why don't you
grab your instruments
and play a song for stan ?
all right !
let's do it !
♪ yeah yeah yeah
i love my family ♪
♪ my family is the best ♪
♪ if we ever have to
face a challenge ♪
our family !
♪ can pass the test ♪♪
oh boy, who is the best
mom in the world ?
yay !
all right, mom !
all right,
go dave !
yes !
woo-hoo !
where be your
gibes now ?
your gambols ?
your songs ?
hey !  hey !  hey !
hey !  hey !
( laughter )
that's a great
story, sarah.
all right, kids !
now how about we do some
scripture readings--
from the book of mormon !
all right !
yeah !
woo-hoo !
yow !
the book of mormon ?
what's that ?
you know, the book
that joseph smith found !
who's joseph smith ?
only the most important
person in the world !
you never
heard of him ?
no !
tell us the story of
joseph smith again, dad !
tell us, tell us !
all right !
all right, you rascals,
gather 'round.
joseph smith lived in
a little american town
in the early 1800s.
( singers )
♪ joseph smith was
called a prophet ♪
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ he started
the mormon religion ♪
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
there goes that
kooky joseph smith.
you know he claims he spoke
with god and jesus.
well, how do you
know he didn't ?
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ joseph smith was
called a prophet ♪
hey, joseph !
i told my wife that you
spoke with god and jesus
and she didn't
believe it !
well it's true,
i did !
where ?
i was out in
the woods, praying.
i was asking god if
i should be a protestant
or a catholic or what--
and suddenly, god and jesus
appeared before me.
and they said i should
start my own church !
because none of the others
had it right.
and that's exactly
how it happened !
you see ?
you believe it now ?
yeah, sure, why would
he make that up ?
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ many people
believed joseph ♪
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ and that night
he saw an angel ♪
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
and please bless
mother and father.
and please keep our bellies
full of yum-yums
and luscious goodies.
aaah !
oh my gosh !
i am moroni,
i am a native american.
a native american ?
but your skin
is white.
yes, long ago all
native americans were white.
we all came to america
from jerusalem,
and while we were here
we were visited by christ.
jesus lived
here in america ?
yes, eventually my people
were all killed
by the other tribe of israel.
and as punishment,
god turned their skin red.
these are the native
americans you know today.
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
there is an ancient book
buried near here
written on gold plates that
account my people's lives.
also buried with the book
are two "seer" stones,
the urim and thummim,
which will allow you to
translate the writings.
find it and
fulfill your destiny.
wow !
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ joseph smith was
called a prophet ♪
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪♪
and we all know what
happened then, don't we ?
yeah !
i know !
what happened then ?
( bell dings )
ooh, therice krispie
squares are done !
rice krispie squares !
all right !
hey gang, let's wrap some more
of them up in plastic wrap
and hand them out
to the poor !
awesome !
i can't wait !
you coming, stan ?
no, i was supposed
to be home at eight.
aw, that's too bad !
well, it was really nice
meeting you, stan !
'bye, stan !
see ya !
great to meet you !
'bye !
( door opens )
( laughter from tv )
hello ?
oh, hi, stan.
hey dad, how come you never
told me about joseph smith ?
who ?
shut up, turd,
we're watching "friends" !
the guy who spoke to
god and jesus.
well, stan, god and jesus
don't actually speak to people.
that's not what
the harrisons said.
who are the harrisons ?
the new people that
moved in down the street.
mr. harrison said that joseph
smith spoke to god and jesus
and they told him none of
the religions were right.
oh, did he now ?
what are they,
religious kooks ?
they're not kooks,
they're cool !
how come we never have a night
where we don't watch any tv
and we just do stuff together
and eat and drink ?
we have that, stan,
it's called friday night kegger.
but that's just you
and your friends !
i said shut up, turd !
mr. harrison said that
i need to be following
heavenly father's plan,
and i don't even know
what that is !
all right,
that does it.
where are you going ?
i'm gonna go have a talk
with this mr. harrison.
if he thinks he can
fill my son's head
with whacko religious crap,
he's wrong !
randy, don't cause trouble.
let me handle this, sharon.
you gotta put these cult
people in their place
or else they never stop.
i'm gonna go kick
this mr. harrison's ass !
this mr. harrison is
a white guy, right ?
yeah.
yeah, i'm gonna go
kick his ass !
god damn
religious kooks.
tell my son what to
believe, will you ?
we'll see how you like
my fist in your ass.
( pounding on door )
hello !
yeah, are you
mr. harrison ?
i sure am,
the name's gary.
well, look, my kid was just
over at your house and he--
ooh, you're stan's dad !
it's so nice to
finally meet you !
karen !
mr. marsh is here !
uh, look, i just wanna
tell you that--
oh, mr. marsh,
what a treat !
it's so nice
to meet you !
well, thanks, uh--
karen just finished
baking the most amazing
rice krispie squares !
with chocolate frosting !
come on out of the cold,
you've gotta try one.
or six !
i cannot tell you how wonderful
it is to have you over !
i hear you're a geologist,
that is so amazing !
look, uh, i actually
came over
because i'm a little
concerned
about some of the things
you told my son.
uh-huh. uh-huh.
you know, about...
god and stuff.
oh...
oh boy, you think we were
trying to convert him.
well, i--
oh, mr. marsh,
i am so sorry.
we just moved here
from utah
and we're so used to everyone
being mormon that we--
we forget not everyone
wants to hear about it !
oh boy, you
must be furious !
well... no,
no, i just--
you just heard your son
talking about religious ideals
that aren't your own
and you said,
"who the heck do these
people think they are ?"
i'm really,
truly sorry, mr. marsh,
it won't happen again.
you can...
call me randy.
randy, the last thing we want
is for people to think
we're pushing our religion.
we know there are a lot
of beliefs out there
and ours just
works for us.
to each his own,
right ?
yeah.
yeah !
you know, to be honest,
i've never known any mormons,
i don't even know
what you people believe.
who was this
joseph smith guy ?
why did he believe
that native americans
were actually white people
from jerusalem ?
well, because he found
ancient books
they had written
on gold plates.
right where the angel moroni
said they would be.
i found them !
you're not gonna
believe it, everybody !
i found them !
found what ?
another new testament
of jesus christ !
what ?!
what'd he say ?
last night, a native american
angel told me
where i could find another
testament of jesus christ,
so i went out to the woods...
i dug around all morning where
the angel had told me to look.
hmmm, maybe there isn't
anything out here.
( clink )
wait a tick !
what's this ?
wow...
inside the stone box, i found
the magical seer stones.
under that, i found
four gold plates
written in
strange writing.
this must be the gospel that
jesus told the nephites !
well, they were the most amazing
things i'd ever gazed upon !
well,
so where are they ?
where are what ?
the gold plates and
the seer stones !
where are they ?
oh.
oh, well, i was not
allowed to take them.
you see, after i found
the plates
the angel moroni
appeared to me again
and said that i am not
allowed to show the plates
or the seer stones
to anybody !
because first i must translate
what's written on the plates
into english, so you can
all read it !
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
wow !
that's amazing !
♪ he found the stones
and golden plates ♪
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ even though nobody else
ever saw them ♪
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪♪
so, how'd it go,
"clubber lang" ?
you kick
mr. harrison's ass ?
not exactly.
we're, uh, having
their family over
for dinner
tomorrow night.
see, that's what
happened to me !
sharon, did you know
this guy joseph smith
found a new testament to the
bible buried here in america ?
what are you
talking about ?
well, it's just that--
the harrisons are
really nice people,
and you should see how loving
and together their family is.
i, i think there's something
to that religion.
that's what they
made me think too !
all right,
that does it !
from now on,
our family is mormon !
hey stan, how was your date
last night with the new kid ?
shut up, dude.
they're a nice family,
and gary is actually
really smart and talented.
awww, you guys,
i think stan's in love !
yeah, did you make out
with him, too ?
what's the big deal ?
can't i have
other friends ?
you guys should give
gary a chance.
hey, stan !
oh, here's stan's little
girlfriend now !
hey, guys !
stan, i remember
you said last night
that you'd lost your wallet,
so i made you a new one.
i carved a picture
of john elway
into the leather
on the front.
wow, you made this ?
oh, look at them !
aren't they
so cute together ?
hey, my family's
on their way
over to the fire station
to donate blood.
you wanna come along ?
( gagging )
uh, i don't think so, gary,
i have to, uh...
oh, here comes
my family now !
hey guys !
look, we painted
our faces !
( laughter )
i'm a lion !
i'm an alien !
hey !
just what the heck am i
supposed to be ?
my god.
you gonna come with us to
the fire station, stan ?
uh, no,
i've got a lot to do.
well, gary, you wanna just hang
out with your friend stan ?
oh, well,
i'd like to, but--
oh man, i would
miss you guys so much !
we'd miss you too, gary !
oh, we'll all see
each other tonight
when we go to
stan's house for dinner !
stay and play with
your friends, gary.
yeah, have a
good time, boys !
( laughter )
let's go !
our faces
are painted !
wow.
so what do you
guys wanna do ?
uh, that's cool.
we're gonna leave you
two lovebirds alone.
the three of us
have to go put in
some volunteer work
at the homeless shelter.
oh, cool !
i'm gonna do that
tomorrow !
( cartman snickering )
jesus christ !
so hey, i heard your dad
came over last night
and he and my dad talked
about joseph smith !
that's great !
yeah, i had a question about
that joseph smith guy.
sure !
what happened after he
found the golden plates
buried in the ground ?
well, he kept them
hidden from everyone
like he was told.
and then he translated what
was written on the plates
into the book of mormon !
yeah, but how ?
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
what's this all about,
mr. smith ?
mr. harris, can you
keep a secret ?
well, sure i can !
i have,
in my possession,
an ancient book
written on gold plates
that tells of jesus christ's
second coming !
here, in america !
in america, really ?
that sounds
kind of...
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
it's true !
and i'm going to
translate the plates
and publish it into a book
for the whole world to read !
i know you have a lot
of money, mr. harris,
and i'm just gonna
need a little bit
to pay for the
publishing costs.
mmm, i don't know.
how do you expect
to translate it ?
with these.
rocks ?
they're not rocks,
they're seer stones,
given to me by an angel !
with them,
god allows me
to translate the plates
into english.
watch !
you take this quill and paper
and write down what i say.
sit here.
i have the golden plates
here in this hat.
i need to have them
somewhere dark
so i can read
the spiritual light.
really ?
when i put the seer
stones into the hat
the ancient letters light up
and change to english
which i can then
read to you !
wow !
ooh, i'm seeing
the light !
okay, write this down.
"and so...
it was that...
christ appeared
before the nephites."
♪ and that's how the book
of mormon was written ♪
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ dum-dee dum-dum
♪ dum-dee
dum-dum dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ dum, dum,
dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ dum dum-dum dum-dum
dum dummm ♪♪
one, two, three, four--
"pay $1,000
property tax" !
isn't this great,
you guys ?
our first
family home evening.
i wanna watch tv !
we're not watching tv,
we're mormons now
and we're having
family home evening !
dad, did you know that
that joseph smith guy
read the book of mormon
out of a hat ?
and ?
your turn, sharon.
it's just that,
the book of mormon says
a lot of strange stuff.
like that adam and eve lived
in jackson county, missouri ?
yes ?
but school taught me that
the first man and woman
lived in africa.
well, you can't believe
everything
school tells you, stan.
your turn,
shelley.
( doorbell rings )
ooh, that must be
the harrisons !
hey, everybody !
wow, what
a great house !
you must be mrs. marsh,
it's so nice to meet you !
and you must be
stan's sister !
oh, i think your
brother's the greatest !
my brother is
a stupid turd.
hey, stan !
hey, gary.
well, come on in
and sit down, everybody.
you're here just in time.
my son was having a little
problem with our new religion.
dad !
oh, really ?
well, that's just because
he hasn't heard
the best part about
the joseph smith story !
the one that proves
he was for real !
yeah !
ooh, what's that ?
well, you remember
martin harris,
the rich man
who wrote down
what joseph smith read
out of the hat ?
yeah.
see, after he was done,
he took some of the pages
of what would become
the book of mormon, home !
♪ martin went home
to his wife ♪
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
♪ and showed her pages
from the book of mormon ♪
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
and so, joseph smith
put his head into a hat
and read to me what
the golden plates said !
i wrote it all down,
and we're gonna
publish it into a book !
martin, how do you know he
isn't just making stuff up
and pretending he's translating
off golden plates ?
♪ lucy harris
smart-smart-smart ♪
♪ smart-smart
why would he
make it up ?
♪ martin harris
dum-dum-dum ♪
all right, here.
i'm gonna hide
these pages.
if joseph smith really is
translating off of golden plates
then he'll be able
to do it again.
but if joseph smith
is making it all up,
then the new translations
will be different from these.
okay, fine !
i bet he'll have
no problem !
♪ lucy harris
smart-smart-smart ♪
♪ martin harris, dumb ♪
♪ so martin went on
back to smith's ♪
♪ said the pages
had gone away ♪
♪ smith got mad and told martin
he needed to go pray ♪
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
look, i'm sorry about losing
the pages we worked on, joe.
but i'm ready to
write it all down again
if you translate
from the plates.
i would love to,
martin, except--
i just had a vision.
and the lord said he is
very angry with me
for letting you
take those pages !
he is ?!
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
yes !
he is so mad that
he will never let me
translate from the plate
of lehi again.
he said we must now translate
from the plate of nephi.
so it will be
the same basic story,
but written a little
differently.
wow !
if god got angry with you
then you must be
telling the truth !
♪ dum-dum
dum-dum-dum ♪
all right, martin,
let's get to work !
and that's
how it happened !
yeah !
all right !
wait, mormons actually
know this story
and they still believe
joseph smith was a prophet.
well sure, the story
proves it, doesn't it ?
no, it proves he did
make it all up !
are you blind ?!
well, stan, it's all
a matter of faith !
no, it's a matter
of logic !
if you're gonna say things
that have been proven wrong,
like that the first man and
woman lived in missouri
and that native americans
came from jerusalem,
then you better have
something to back it up !
all you've got are a bunch of
stories about some asswipe
who read plates nobody
ever saw out of a hat
and then couldn't do it again
when the translations
were hidden !
hey, stan, don't
denounce our religion.
i don't want to be
mormon, dad !
me neither.
hey, that's totally
cool, guys,
you can believe
whatever you want !
yeah, it's great you have
your own beliefs !
yeah !
yay for the marshes !
oh, stop it !
that's another thing !
why do you have to be so
frickin' nice all the time ?
it isn't normal !
you just weasel people
into your way of thinking
by acting like the happiest
family in the world
and being so nice to everyone
that you just blindside
dumb people like my dad !
yeah !
( sighs )
well, kids...
who's up for a water
balloon fight ?!
yeah !
oh, hey stan, where's your
best buddy gary ?
i'm not hanging around
that kid anymore.
oh, no,
you guys broke up ?
you guys were right, okay ?
the new kid's a douche.
now i just gotta find a way
to keep him away from me.
hey, stan.
oh, brother.
uh-oh, the jilted
lover returns !
listen, i just wanted
to let you know
you don't have to
worry about me
trying to be
your friend anymore.
i don't ?
look, maybe us mormons do
believe in crazy stories
that make
absolutely no sense.
and maybe joseph smith
did make it all up--
but i have a great life
and a great family.
and i have the book of mormon
to thank for that.
the truth is, i don't care if
joseph smith made it all up.
because what the
church teaches now
is loving your family,
being nice and helping people.
and even though people in this
town might think that's stupid,
i still choose
to believe in it.
all i ever did was try to
be your friend, stan.
but you're so
high and mighty
you couldn't
look past my religion
and just be my friend back.
you've got a lot of
growing up to do, buddy.
suck my balls.
damn, that kid is
cool, huh ?
captioning made possible by
comedy central
captioned by
soundwriters™