captioning made possible by
comedy central
? i'm going down
to south park ?
? gonna have
myself a time ?
? friendly faces
everywhere ?
? humble folks
without temptation ?
? going down
to south park ?
? gonna leave my
woes behind ?
? ample parking
day or night ?
? people spouting
"howdy neighbor" ?
? headin' on up
to south park ?
? gonna see
if i can't unwind ?
? ( muffled mumble
muffled mumble ) ?
? so come on down
to south park ?
? and meet some
friends of mine ??
( knocking )
yes ?
oh, hello, boys.
hello, sir, south park
junior detectives.
we're wondering if
you have any crimes
you need solved
for a dollar ?
ooh, little
crime stoppers, huh ?
well, i'm afraid i don't have
any crimes to solve right now.
aw, --- !
alright, sir,
well please call us
if you need anything.
i'll do that,
have fun, boys.
stupid assholes,
how come nobody has
a crime to solve ?
yeah, maybe starting
a detective club
isn't such a great idea.
it's a great idea,
we just have to
keep working at it.
oh, hello there, boys !
hello, ma'am, we're
detectives with
the south park crime unit.
do you have any
crimes you need solved,
for a dollar ?
ooh, neighborhood detectives !
well, let me think...
ooh yes, there is something !
really ?!
yes, two days ago i put
a fresh baked cherry pie
out on my
window sill to cool.
and later when i went
to get it, it was gone.
my god.
have you reported this
to any other authorities ?
no, but i think it's
a perfect case for you kids !
cool, we'll see
what we can find ma'am !
we're on the case !
what have
you got, marsh ?
detective mckormick found
something interesting.
jesus... we're too late.
i think we can piece
this case together, now.
my pie tin !
ooh, but what
happened to the pie ?
well, we've all
talked it through
and we've come up
with a theory.
well what do you think
happened, lil' detectives ?
you said you sat
the pie on the windowsill
where it must have
sat for some time...
but its sweet smell attracted
the attention of somebody--
your husband !
he wanted that pie, badly
but he knew that he was
not allowed to eat it yet.
slowly, the rage
built inside his mind.
"why won't she
let me eat this pie ?"
"why does she always stop me
from doing what i want to do ?"
his only solution
became obvious-
kill her.
his plan was
to use a hammer.
bash ! bash ! bash !
your skull in-
causing instant death.
then to make it impossible
for police to identify the body
he would use his shovel
to remove your head-
then saw off
the arms and legs !
the torso he would
dump into the lake...
the arms and legs
he would dissolve
with acid and lye
in the bathtub
and then finally,
he'd be able
to eat that pie.
but before he could go through
with his entire plan
he discovered that the pie
had already been eaten...
by your dog !
looks like the game
is over, old man.
oh my god !
what kind of television
have you kids been watching ?
just the news.
alright, alright,
you boys run along now !
hey, you owe us
a dollar, lady !
fine, here,  just go !
wow, look you guys
our first dollar !
we're in business !
kenny, you got the f.a.g.
on that perp
in washington ?
boys, you have
a little visitor.
is this the south park
crime unit ?
yes, it is !
i lost my dolly.
thank you, ms. secretary,
that will be all.
and get us more
cookies and coffee
we're not paying you
to sit on your ass !
do you know
where your doll is ?
if i knew where it was,
it wouldn't be lost.
alright, sarah
come over here...
now, i want you to describe
what the doll looks like
to our sketch artist, kenny.
she has curly blond hair
and a red dress...
and a turned up nose...
and a blue bow
in her hair...
you got it, ken ?
alright, let's see.
dammit, kenny that's
not what she said !
put that away, dude !
don't worry, ma'am,
we'll find your doll.
no sign of
forced entry...
but the window
isn't locked.
right, so it's possible the
thief sat out in that tree--
he would have watched
sarah with her doll,
possibly while cutting the palms
of his hand with a large knife-
the pain gave him
sick pleasure...
disposing of the doll
wouldn't be easy.
he would have had to brought
a shovel to decapitate it.
we're going to need
semen samples
from everything
in this room.
alright let's do this
by the books !
o'donnel, get me smears of all
the places the doll used to be.
mitchell, run a tap
on the phone.
hey, kid, what
are you doing ?
agent tucker, fbi...
and you ?
detective marsh.
i'm in charge of
this investigation.
not any more,
you're not.
hey, this is our case !
you can't come in
and take over !
can't we ?
you guys are
playing detectives,
we're playing fbi.
that gives us
jurisdiction over you.
oh crap !
i want choppers on the roof
ready to go !
dude, we've been working
this case since 2:30 !
good, then you can help us by
telling me everything you know.
son of a bitch,
stupid fbi !
well, i guess we can go back
to playing laundromat.
no, we're not gonna
stop playing detectives.
we've just got to find
that little girl's doll
before those
fbi guys do !
yeah !
yeah, but how ?
we're gonna
have to start
bringing in people
for questioning.
and i think i know
exactly where to start.
where were you this morning
at nine o'clock, butters ?
i was at home.
your story is full of holes
and i'm gonna beat your ass
if you don't start
telling the truth !
( mumbling )
aw, don't be so mean...
butters is our friend, huh...
they're really good at this
"good cop-bad cop" thing.
you're going down, butters
you hear me ?
aw, aw, don't feel bad,
poor little kid.
you're a worthless two dollar
criminal, and you're lying !
aw, it's okay,
poor lil' fella.
i don't have nothin'
to confess !
honestly !
fine, then you won't mind
giving us a semen sample.
how do i do that ?
you just make the semen
come out of your body
and put it
in this cup !
how do i make semen
come out of my body ?!
stop playing games !
i'm not playing,
i really don't know !!
that does it,
wait right here !
you guys,
did you hear that ?!
butters doesn't know how you
make semen come out your body !
howdoyou make
semen come out ?
i don't know,
i was hoping you guys did.
it's that thing we
learned about in school
where you pull on your wiener
until white stuff comes out.
really ?
oh right, you're supposed to
pull and master-ber-nate
your wiener really fast.
oh, okay.
okay, retard you really
don't know how to make
semen come out ?
no.
follow me to
the bathroom !
aw, it's alright, butters,
don't worry about it.
now go sit
on the toilet
and pull and tug
on your wiener
until white stuff comes out,
then put it in this cup.
my wiener ?
yes, retard, semen comes
from your wiener.
now do it !
well, butters ?
i'm pulling on my wiener
but nothing's happening.
well pull harder !
ow....
owww....
it's not working.
try doing it faster.
ow.
ow-ow.
no nothing !
butters you wanna go to jail
for the rest of your life ?
no !
then you better get
that semen sample
no matter how long
it takes !
okay !
cartman !
we just got a tip
that a doll was found
near fosse's house !
let's go !
ow...
ow !
okay, ms. jones,
huh-huh,
me and doctor flick here
just need to
check your vagina.
huh-huh, that's gay.
kyle !
what ?
i-see-two-guys-inside
they-have
sarah peterson's doll
you-stupid-jew !
they've got the doll !
okay, okay... ready...
ring the doorbell !
( ding-dong )
who is it ?
south park
junior detectives !
we know you have
sarah peterson's doll !
they're playing detective.
huh-huh,
that's gay.
huh-huh, you're gay !
what do we do now ?
i don't know.
well, if they're not
gonna give us back the doll
then we have no choice--
let's go
tell on them.
dude we can't
just tell on them !
why not ?
because, dude, we're
playing detectives !
detectives don't just
go tell on people !
hey detectives !
uh- if you
don't get outta here
we're gonna rip
the doll's head off !
huh-huh, yeah !
huh-huh, we were
playin' gynecologist
and now we're
playin' criminals !
huh-huh, yeah,
that's gay.
huh-huh, we're gay.
jesus, they're
gonna kill her !
we've got to
do something !
time !
time is what we need !
but time is something
we ain't got !
attention
you in the house !
this is agent tucker
with the fbi
we have you
surrounded, sort of !
hey, you buttholes
can't play fbi here !
yeah, this was
our hot lead !
and you did a great job
leading us here.
now you just
stay out of our way !
the jig is up, fosse !
bring out the doll-
or we'll tell on you !
we're going to
charge the front door
and go get it !
no, you're not.
dammit man this is not
the time for negotiations !
there's a little
doll in there
about to have her
head twisted off !
climb off, kid !
we say you can't
charge the front door
and you have to obey what the
fbi says, that's the rules !
just because your parents can
afford better toys than ours
doesn't make you
better than us !
yes, it does so.
grrrr !
what do we do now ?
we go get
the doll ourselves !
but they said we can't
charge the front door.
that's right...
"chick chick"...
but they didn't say anything
about going in the back.
( fbi )
come on, guys, you don't
wanna hurt the doll.
oh crap they're
coming in the back !
pkew ! pkew ! pew-pew !
pew-pew !
huh-huh !
bkew !
bang ! bang ! bang !
i got you, fosse !
no, you didn't !
did so !
no, cuz i got
special wizard armor on.
we're not playing
dungeons and dragons, ass face !
alright, that does it !
cover me,
i'm going slow-mo !
pkew !
oh, you got me !
blagh !
huh-huh yeah !
ugh !
huh-huh we're dead.
huh-huh that's gay.
we got it !
mrs. peterson,
is your daughter home ?
my dolly !
we got her back safe.
lost a lot of
good men in the process.
well you boys
are little heroes !
i'm going to call
the police department
and let them know what brave
little detectives you are !
hello there
little crime stoppers !
i'm lieutenant dawson
with the park county police.
i heard you did
a great job
finding little
sarah peterson's doll.
we do what
we can, sir.
well, that's fantastic, kids.
and for all your
terrific sleuth-solving,
i am hereby making you all
junior detectives !
wow ! awesome !
rad ! sweet !
now that means
you boys are now
an official part
of the department !
cool !
alright so, ready for
your first assignment ?
sure !
okay, there's a meth lab
down at 567 mala vista.
the operators are
probably armed to the hilt
with illegal weapons.
i want you to get down there
and see what you can find.
a... a meth lab ?
i don't want any problems
just take 'em down by the books.
now get over there !
the mayor's all over
my ass on this one !
oh and deputies...
you screw this up
and i'll have you
working graveyard shift
behind a desk.
move it !
what is a meth lab, anyway ?
i dunno,
let's just hurry up
i wanna get home in time
to watch "crime drama".
( knocking )
uh, police, open up.
oh crap, did you guys
do your math homework ?
oh dude,
i totally spaced it.
you die, pigs !!!
you wanna die, huh ?
aaaaaaaaghghgh !
you won't
take us alive !
( screaming )
so long coppers !
oh ---- !
arrrrghhh !
damn !
"one u.p.s. vehicle
valued at $25,000
"one civilian vehicle
worth $16,000
"the second floor
of the post office
and a coffee shop
valued at $60,000."
the mayor's
gonna have myass!
uh, sir we just got kinda
blindsided by the-
you got careless !
now i don't know
how they do things
down at that dog and pony show
they call the "fourth grade"
but here we haverules!
jesus, we don't even
have guys to question now
because you killed them all !
we're sorry.
one more slip-up
like that
and i'll have your badges
you hear me ?!
now hit the showers !
well, well, well,
if it isn't thesupercops!
hey murphy, think they'll
let me borrow their g.i. joes ?
come on you guys,
leave 'em alone.
relax hopkins, all
fun and games, right ?
so tell us, rookies,
you, uh, find yourself
a little 'bonus' in that house ?
a bonus ?
come on... we all
skim a little off the top.
oh... or are you too
good for that ?
you think you're
gonna waltz in here
and clean up
the system, is that it ?
we just wanna be
junior detectives.
look, we all work hard !
and we deserve more than
the 30,000 a year we get paid.
so what if we take in
a little on the side ?
yeah, who the hell
are you to change that ?
i said back off, murphy !
why don't you and your
rookie friends make us ?
c'mon, bring it !
what's the hell
is the problem here ?
no problem, sir...
no problem at all.
then hit the showers,
all of you !
dude, i don't wanna play
detective anymore.
me neither.
it'll get better, you guys.
better how, dude ?
look, we said we wanted
to form a club
to protect and
serve south park.
we put all this
time into it.
i mean, what do you
guys wanna do, huh ?
go back to playing
car mechanics ?
or laundromat owners ?
we were happy
playing laundromat owners.
i wasn't.
we started
playing detective
because we wanted our playtime
to mean something.
or have you forgotten why
you joined the force, kyle ?
hey, broflovski's
a good cop !
you guys can go back to playing
laundromat owners if you want-
but i'm not gonna give
those kids playing fbi
the chance to
laugh at us.
i'll see you guys
at school tomorrow.
ughh--ugnnn !
eric, where have
you been, it's 10:30 !
we had to take down
a meth lab on mala vista.
well you should have
called mommy !
will you get off my back !
it's hard enough
i gotta work the beat,
and then i gotta
come home to your nagging !
look, look, i'm sorry
it's just this case and...
the guys down
at the station.
i'm tired alright,
i'm tired.
well why don't you get ready
for snuggums night-night
and i'll bring you some
toasty chocolate nummers.
okay...
oooohhhh...
owwww.......
butters ?
yyess...
are you still trying
to give a semen sample ?
i'm trying, but
nothing's comin' out...
well, keep trying, butters.
okay...
ow...
ow !
and so you can see, children,
that the women's movement
of the late 50s and early 60s
had a profound effect on
feminism in america.
uh, boys !
would it trouble you terribly
not to sleep in my class ?!
we weren't sleeping,
mr. garrison.
oh, well then maybe you can
tell me who was in charge
of the feminist movement
of the early 60s !
a bunch of fat old skanks
on their periods ?
right, but who was the fattest,
oldest skank on her period ?
that's what i thought !
now pay attention !
okay, children, now the
biggest skank of all
was an old fat-ass
by the name of-
marsh, broflovski,
mckormick, cartman...
in my office !
ugh !
uhhh ! ughhh !
looks like that meth lab
you took down
was just the
tip of the iceberg.
they found a paper trail
leading all the way
to the biggest
crime syndicate in colorado.
uh-oh.
the operators apparently
run their business
out of a sleazy strip joint
down in englewood.
they're all cop killers, so
i'm sending you in undercover.
uh, sir, i have a lot
of homework to do tonight
and i was-
what ?!
now you listen to me -
i'm giving you
one last chance !
you're good cops, but you let
your emotions get in the way.
and your little shoot first,
ask questions later technique
has no place
in this century !
now you get down
to that strip joint
and you do it
by the books.
you got it ?!
the mayor is--  my ass--
bla bla bla !
so... what did you boys
have to say to the lieutenant ?
nothing, he just
told us a bunch of stuff.
maybe you decided you needed to
tell him about our...
"bonus money".
no.
they're lying.
they're dead.
dude, if my mom
knew i was in here
i would be in
super-big trouble.
woo-hoo !!!
would you like a dance ?
no, thanks.
dance ?
anyone like
a dance ?
alright guys put
your hands together
be sure to tip the dancers
let's hear it for-- candyyyyy.
whoa, whoa !
what the hell are
you kids doing in here ?
this isn't an appropriate
place for children !
dance ?
anyone like a dance ?
uh, it's okay
we know the owner.
oh really ?
let's go see.
alright, so we'll have to
start having the mckormicks
make our meth again...
hey gino, these kids
say they know you.
what ?!
i don't know no kids !
i didn't think so,
alright you kids-
hey wait a minute !
these kids might be
just what we need
to get our drugs past
the security at d.i.a.
how would you like to
join our family ?
yo, gino, i know i seen
these kids before, man !
these kids are five-o !
what ?
these kids
are cops, man !
bang !  bang !
bang ! bang !
peekew ! peekew !
kenny, it doesn't go
"peekew-peekew",
it goes
"bang ! bang ! bang !"
god dammit !
those junior detectives and
their heroically reckless ways !
murphy, jankins, hopkins
get in there !
( screaming )
bang-bang, bang-bang !
daaance ?!
anybody like
a daaaance ?
freeze,
south park detectives !
great job boys, you found
the meth boss !
detective murphy, jankins
what the hell are you doing ?
we had a deal !!!
a deal ?!
that's right, we're partners
in the drug business.
everything was fine until these
supercops joined the force.
now we gotta
kill you all.
boys down !
alright guys put
your hands together
a lotta shootin'
and killin' going on
but be sure to
tip your waitress,
let's hear it
for re-bec-ca !
christ !
those junior detectives
have no regard for the law !
get me a hard line
to the phone !
and i want choppers
on the roof !
who the hell
are you ?
agent fields, fbi.
hey, i'm in charge of
this investigation !
not anymore you're not.
but that's not fair !
is so, is so !
aagh !!
sorry, detective hopkins,
we can't let anybody
know about our partnership !
that's right,
we split it all !
fifty-fifty !
that's right.
i think we'll take
a hundred percent now.
huh-huh, yeah.
sorry gino, but in
business like this
sometimes partnerships
need to end.
that's right.
sometimes partnerships
need to end.
well, supercops,
looks like i'll be
taking in all the money now.
i'm in business alone.
and that's means that the
only person i can't trust...
is myself !
looks like murphy and jankins
got what they deserved.
if it weren't
for you boys
we would have never
cleaned up the department.
alright, detectives let's
get one thing straight !
i do not agree
with your methods !
you're uncontrolled
and you're negligent...
but by god
you get the job done.
congratulations.
thanks.
i'm probably
gonna regret this, but,
well, i'm promoting you
to full detectives.
they'll be
lots more action
and that big paycheck
you've always wanted.
i think i have
a better idea.
hello, sir, welcome to the
broflovski laundromat.
yes, i have a suit i need dry
cleaned and pressed, please.
certainly.
here you are,
mr. mckormick,
your laundry is all done
and folded that will be $9.95.
on your
american express...
fellas, hey fellas !!!
i got it,
i got my semen sample !
you did ?
yeah, i was up there poundin' my
wiener for two days straight
and then finally i thought
about stan's mom's boobs
and this little tiny splooch
of this white stuff came out !
that's great, butters, but we're
not playing detective anymore.
we're playing
laundromat owners.
would you like those
pants cleaned for $4.95 ?
captioning made possible by
comedy central
captioned by
soundwriters?