captioning made possible by
comedy central
? i'm going down
to south park ?
? gonna have
myself a time ?
? friendly faces
everywhere ?
? humble folks
without temptation ?
? going down
to south park ?
? gonna leave my
woes behind ?
? ample parking
day or night ?
? people spouting
"howdy neighbor" ?
? headin' on up
to south park ?
? gonna see
if i can't unwind ?
? ( muffled mumble
muffled mumble ) ?
? so come on down
to south park ?
? and meet some
friends of mine ??
( school bell rings )
okay, children,
let's take our seats.
did you take attendance,
mr. slave ?
all "donesy-wonsey".
okay, let's all take out
our math homework
and go over the problems.
math homework,
math homework...
where did i file that ?
oh, and by the way,
children,
there's a walkout
scheduled today
to protest the war
in iraq.
so, uh, if you're against
the war, run along outside.
and if you're
for the war, uh,
stay here and we'll do
math problems.
( cheering )
? we got
out of school ?
? no more school today ?
what should we do ?
let's go see a movie !
( crowd chanting )
no war !  no war !  no war !...
no war, m'kay !
oh, here you go, boys,
these will help you protest.
it's good to see that you care
about peace, boys, m'kay.
no war, m'kay !
excuse me, boys,
tom statzl,hbcnews--
can you tell me why you kids
marched out of school today ?
uh... war ?
right, what about
the war ?
it, it's...
it's gay.
uh-huh, and what aspect of it
do you think is most gay ?
uh, no blood for oil !
yeah, war is not
my voice.
bush is a "nay-zee".
hey all you
un-american bastards !
if you don't like america,
why don't you get out ?
yeah !
don't you call us
un-american !
this country was founded on
the right to protest, m'kay !
yeah !
if the founding fathers
saw you burning your flag
and calling the
president a nazi,
they'd roll over
in their graves !
yeah !
the founding fathers would agree
with our right to protest.
the founding fathers would
kick all your asses !
boys, what do you think the
founding fathers would say ?
the foggy who ?
well, i hope
you little commies
are pretty pleased
with yourselves--
going out there
and protesting america
and then saying on
national television
that you don't even know
who the founding fathers are !
you kids don't know squat
about america, do you ?!
well, not really, no.
well, that's just jingles.
because i'm assigning
all you little flag-burners
a full report on 1776
and the founding fathers !
( all )
awww !
shut up !
i want you all in your
study groups of four,
and if you can't give an
outstanding report
on what the founding fathers
would have to say
about all this protesting,
then it's "f"s for you !
( bell rings )
eh...
eh heh...
i can't do it.
this is way too much
material for a 9-year-old.
yeaagh !
oh, no you don't,
cartman !
every time we get put
in a study group
you sit on ass while the
rest of us do all the work !
but you guys are such
better studiers than me.
i know you can
pull it off.
you're gonna read this stuff
and study like the rest of us !
myaaa !  mya !
shut up and study !
myaaaa,
mya, mya.
hmm, 1776,
when our founding fathers
created america.
i wonder what it used to
be like in those days.
in those days.
what are you doing ?
i'm trying to have
a flashback.
a what ?
you know, if i have
a flashback
then i can see what 1776
was like firsthand.
no, you just
have to study.
no, i've seen this
work before,
just give me a second.
oh, okay,
how about this ?
say, guys,
1776 was so long ago,
i wonder what life would
have been like back then.
back then.
oh wait, i know--
you know, guys, i don't
even care about 1776 !
it was so long ago
that i don't think it has
anything to do with me.
with me.
anything to do
with me, with me.
that isn't gonna work,
dumb-ass !
kids, let's keep it down
for study groups
or else mr. garrison's
going to punish me.
just face it, cartman, you're
going to have to study !
myaaa !
mya, myaaa !
there, all finished !
from now on, this is
the pro-war side of the town
and that's the
unpatriotic side.
yeah !
that's right !
how about we call this
the rational side of town
and that the
redneck side !
( laughter )
you just keep all
your flag burning
and your hippie rock protest
songs on your side of the town !
hey, wait a minute.
your side of town
has the post office.
well, your side has
the grocery store.
you can come to our side
to use the post office
if we can go to your side
to use the grocery store.
uh, can we cross the line
to take our kids to school ?
well, naturally you can
cross the line for that,
just like we can cross
for hardware supplies, gas
and pharmaceutical needs.
yeah, okay,
yeah, sure.
hey everybody, this is
never gonna work.
don't you see ?
all this dividin' up the town--
it's just ridiculous.
what we really
should be doing
is just beating the hell out of
each other like we were.
he's right.
boy, do i feel
like a fool.
cartman, what the hell
are you doing ?
you're supposed to
be studying !
that's what i'm doing.
i'm about to find out
all about what happened
back in 1776.
how ?
all i have to do is be thinking
about american history
when i walk through
this doorway.
i'll trip the rope, causing
the rock to fall on my head,
and then i will
have a flashback
to the times of our
founding fathers !
cartman, you are hereby declared
a full-fledged retard.
ha-ha, make fun of me
all you want, kyle,
but i will have
the last laugh.
gentlemen, if you will clear
the doorway, please ?
( clears throat )
oh, gee, i wonder what it
used to be like
in the year 1776 ?
eh !
derh.
derh...
cartman ?
cartman !
benjamin franklin ?
no, turd pants,
it's kyle !
kyle.
get-out-of-my-flashback,
you-god-damn-jew.
rabble, rabble !
rabble !
okay, people, what are we
rabbling about now ?
mayor, our peace rally
has always been set
for this saturday,
and now these
pro-war bastards
are suddenly trying to say
they get the town square.
that's bullcrap, mayor !
our rally to support the war
was setup months ago.
there was no war
months ago !
hey, if you don't like america
then you can get out !
look, nobody wants to hear
a bunch of twangy
country music
pro-war propaganda !
nobody wants to hear a bunch
of rock protest songs !
yeah !
up yours, rednecks !
rabble, rabble,
rabble !
quiet, people !
the town square
is public space.
that means if neither group
will nicely and maturely
move the day of its rally,
i'll just have to give the
town square to both groups.
alright, that's fine,
because our
war support songs
will be a thousand
times better !
oh, you think so ?
bring the shizzle.
we'll trizzle that shizzle
all over the hizzle.
yeah ?
see you saturday, mckizzer
shanizzernilla shnazz
beyaznatch kazizza.
cartman ?
you better be studying,
god dammit.
ah, stan, kyle, kenny--
you're just in time.
oh, no.
oh yes !  i am just
about to flashback
to the days of our
founding fathers.
cartman, you're supposed
to be studying !
what the hell
is all this ?!
i have programmedtivo
to record over 50 hours
ofthe history channel.
when the tivo is full,
both tivo and i will be
dropped into the water,
combining our
electro-whatever fields,
and sending me into
a flashback of history.
uh, cartman, i think that's
a really bad idea.
or a really sweet one.
( ding )
your tivo is full.
oh, here it goes !
cartman ?
aw, crap.
oh, awesome !
oy there,
young lad !
are you alright ?
yeah, yeah, can you
tell me what year it is ?
this year ?
why, it's 1776,
it is.
oh yes !
i did it, i did it !
would you like a ride
into town ?
i'm on my way to master
thomas jefferson's house
to get a very important
document, i am.
oh, kick ( bleepin' )
ass, dude !
never seen you
around 'ere, friend.
might ye be from
up north ?
no, i'm not from here at all,
i'm having a flashback.
a flashback ?
why, what is that ?
well, you know, it's a--
oh, awesome !
? look at me
i'm back in time, in 1776 ?
? with gaslight corners
cobblestone streets ?
? and humble houses
made of bricks ?
? what a special
magic time ?
? and it's all
alive for me ?
? i'm so glad
stan and kyle aren't here ?
? i hate those guys
seriously ?
? seriously hate
those guys ?
? hate stan & kyle ??
is he going to be
alright, doctor ?
your son tried to
kill himself
in a ritualistic fashion
i've never seen before.
his chances of surviving
are very slim.
i'm so sorry.
oh baby, baby,
you can't die !
yeah, we have a report
to do, asshole !
get up !
ooh, easy, kyle.
but it's not fair !
we have to do a full report
on the founding fathers
and cartman got out of
helping us again !
i guess we're just
gonna have to do it
with the three of us.
come on, guys.
i know you're in a very dark
place now, sweetie,
but you must come
toward the light.
come toward light !
'ere we are, then,
the current residence of
master thomas jefferson !
super neat-o !
i'm afraid you'll
have to wait here.
but i need to talk to
the founding fathers
to do my report.
sorry, only the
official messenger boy
is allowed to talk to
mr. jefferson.
oh, okay,
i guess i understand.
? i don't wanna wait ?
? for our lives
to be over ??
( screaming )
hello, i am
thomas jefferson.
and i am the official
messenger boy, i am !
very well, take this document
to the continental congress.
wow, the declaration of
independence day.
some favor going to war
with england
and others want to
avoid war at all costs.
it's a bitch, ain't it ?
perhaps this document will
make the reasons for war
obvious to all.
good luck, young messenger,
now make haste !
okay, so thomas jefferson wrote
the declaration of independence,
then the continental
congress--
no war !
oh, jesus.
uh, boys, would you mind
clearing the living room ?
we have to practice our
big war protest song.
dad, we have to study !
mr. garrison is making us
do a presentation
on what the founding fathers
would say about the war.
hey, that's
a terrific idea !
yeah !
we could have the boys
do their presentation
as part of our peace rally
on saturday !
oh, no.
no, no, no, no.
support our troops !
see ?  i told you
they had your son !
kenny !
what are you doing
over here with all these
un-american traitors ?
i'm doing my
homework.
the boys are going to give
a presentation atourrally
about how the founding
fathers would agree
with our right
to protest.
what ?
actually, we hadn't
really come to a--
look, my son is a patriot
and loves his country !
come on, kenny !
but dad--
now !
support our troops !
oh, kenny, no--
aw, aw.
aw, now we lost two
in our study group !
god dammit !
can you believe those
hick sons a bitches ?
manipulating their kids
into being on their side !
disgraceful !
stan and kyle, it's up to you
to show all those war mongerers
that the founding fathers
agree with us !
( man )
yeah, that's right,
let's get back to work.
do you think kids
in every town
have to deal with
this crap ?
( man )
enter, young messenger !
i am john hancock,
president of the congress.
wow !
mr. john adams ?
aye.
will you do the honors of
reading the document
to congress, please ?
when in the course
of human events,
it becomes necessary
for one people to...
we mutually pledge
to each other,
our lives our fortunes
and our sacred honor.
p.s. every thursday should be
free ice cream day.
excuse me, but does this
declaration actually suggest
that we should go to war
with england ?
we have no choice,
mr. dickenson.
( shouting )
alright, everyone,
thank you all for coming out
to protest the war, m'kay !
( applause )
don't kid yourselves !
these people have come out to
support our troops, right ?!
( applause )
and now, randy marsh is
gonna sing a protest song
he wrote about the war--
oh no, you don't !
we're doing our
pro-war song first !
yeah !  the last thing
these people want
is another bleeding-heart
rock protest song !
people, i told you,
you have to share the stage.
nobody wants to hear another
pro-war country song !
well, excuse me if--
? i'm a little bit
country ?
? well, i'm a little bit
rock n' roll-a ?
? i'm a little for
supportin' our troops ?
? and i'm a little for
bringin' 'em home ?
? i believe freedom
isn't free ?
? no, but war
shouldn't be our goal ?
? we must defend
our country ?
? if it means war
than we say no ?
? did you forget them
towers in new york ? ?
? did you forget
how it made you feel ?
? to see them
towers come down ? ?
? were you like me
did you think ?
? it weren't real ? ?
? i like to rock, but i don't
want to rock iraq ?
? the only kind of rockin'
america should do ?
? is the kind that we
can all dance to ?
? we've got g.p.s.
i.c.b.m.s ?
? and good
ol' fashion lead ?
? we're gonna show saddam
what america means ?
? that son of a bitch
will be dead ?
? why are we
fightin' this war ? ?
? there's a man in the office
we didn't vote for ?
? they didn't
give me a choice ?
? war is not my voice
yeah ?
( shouting )
we must go to war !
but what about
the violence,
the lives lost ?
if we found a country
it should be founded on
peace and diplomacy !
england will only understand
one thing-- force.
i must state again
for the record
that south carolina,
north carolina,
pennsylvania, maryland and
georgia are against war !
yeah, because
you don't care about
the fate of the colonies
like we do.
you're all unpatriotic !
if you don't like the colonies,
then you can get out !
don't you call us
unpatriotic !
we are protesting
this war because
we care so deeply for
the fate of our colonies !
you are all unpatriotic
for leading the colonies
into a war that
half of them don't want !
( shouting )
whoa, how very,
very relevant.
tom, i'm standing
in the town square
where the war rally
has been going on
for an incredible
87 hours.
the crowd still appears to
split right down the middle.
half support country music and
the other half rock n' roll.
let's listen in.
and now we'd like to bring out
a couple of very special
south park students
who did a report on
what the founding fathers
would have to say
about the war.
( applause )
( all )
boo !
for you people who still
think war is the answer,
perhaps you can listen to
the voices of the children.
uh, we didn't do it.
what ?
we didn't do
our homework.
boys !  you were supposed
to come up here
and tell everyone about
the founding fathers !
well, first we lost
one study partner
when cartman put himself
in the hospital,
and then they
took kenny away.
and then kyle forgot to
set his clock ahead
for daylight savings
and we couldn't find anything
in the history books
about iraq and--
that's because
the founding fathers
would have supported
the war !
the founding fathers would
have protested like us !
support !
protest !
country !
rock n' roll !
rabble !  rabble !
rabble !...
we cannot found a country
based on war !
that is afraid to fight !
rabble !
( murmuring )
oh, benjamin franklin.
benjamin franklin.
it's mr. franklin.
oh, benjamin franklin.
franklin, franklin.
benjamin franklin.
mr. franklin, where do you
stand on the war issue ?
i believe that if we are
to form a new country
we cannot be a country that
appears war-hungry and violent
to the rest
of the world.
however, we also
cannot be a country
that appears weak and
unwilling to fight
to the rest of the world.
so, what if we
form a country--
that appears
to want both ?
yes.
yes, of course.
we go to war.
and protest going to war
at the same time !
right !
if the people of
our new country
are allowed to do
whatever they wish
then some will support the war
and some will protest it.
and that means
that as a nation
we could go to war
with whomever we wished
but at the same time
act like we didn't want to.
if we allow the people
to protest what
the government does,
then the country will be
forever blameless !
it's like having your cake
and eating it too.
think of it, an entire nation
founded on saying one thing
and doing another.
and we will
call that country
the united states
of america.
wow !
i get it now !
i get it !
whoa, here it goes.
i wish i could
go back to my time.
to my time.
to-to my time.
wow !
everyone, stop,
please !
the-- the child.
the child
from the hospital !
if you all don't mind, i would
like to do my report now.
i know what the
founding fathers would say.
he does ?
i learned
something today.
this country was founded by
some of the smartest thinkers
the world has ever seen.
and they knew
one thing:
that a truly great country
can go to war
and at the same time
act like it doesn't want to.
you people
who are for the war--
you need the protestors
because they make
the country look like
it's made of sane,
caring individuals.
and you people
who are anti-war--
you need these
flag wavers
because if our whole
country was made up
of nothing but soft,
pussy protestors
we'd get taken down
in a second.
that's why the founding fathers
decided we should have both.
it's called having your cake
and eating it too.
he's right.
the strength of this country
is the ability
to do one thing
and say another.
yeah, if it weren't for
all you guys protesting
everyone around the world
would hate the american people
instead of
just the president.
and if it weren't for
you people flexing your arms
america could easily get taken
over by terrorists, or china.
i guess we owe you
an apology.
i guess
we owe you one.
( everyone )
aw...
cartman ?
cartman saved the day ?
it can't be.
the founding fathers
want you all to know
that we can disagree
all we want,
as long as we agree
that america kicks ass.
? hey, i'm a little
bit country ?
? and i'm a little bit
rock n' roll-a ?
? i'll be the
muscle of america ?
? and me, i'll be
the caring soul ?
? when you
put us together ?
? you get a nation
with one goal ?
? to thrive and prosper ?
? with a little country
and rock n' roll ?
come on up here,
everybody !
? we're a little
bit country ?
? we're a little bit
rock n' roll ?
we can be a nation
that believes in war...
and still tells the world
that we don't.
? let the flag for hypocrisy
fly high from every pole ?
? 'cause we're
a little bit country ?
? and we're a little bit
rock n' roll ?
well, good night, everybody,
it sure has been great
bringing you 100 episodes.
we wanna thank our guests,
the pro-war people...
( applause )
and the anti-war
people.
what the hell
are they doing now ?
i don't know.
? for the war
against the war ?
? who cares ?
100 episodes ??
i hate this town,
i really, really do.
captioning made possible by
comedy central
captioned by
soundwriters?