captioning made possible by
comedy central
♪ i'm going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna have
myself a time ♪
♪ friendly faces
everywhere ♪
♪ humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna leave my
woes behind ♪
♪ ample parking
day or night ♪
♪ people spouting
"howdy neighbor" ♪
♪ headin' on up
to south park ♪
♪ gonna see
if i can't unwind ♪
♪ ( muffled mumble
muffled mumble ) ♪
♪ so come on down
to south park ♪
♪ and meet some
friends of mine ♪♪
( mr. mackey )
m'kay, kids,
can i have it
quiet, please ?
m'kay.
m'kay, quiet now, the assembly
is about to start, m'kay.
quiet, m'kay.
( loud feedback )
( kids screaming )
m'kay.
uh, now kids, we have a really
fun motivational group today
who are gonna talk to you
about the dangers
of smokin', m'kay.
so please give a very big
south park cows welcome
to-- butt out !
woo-hoo !
all right !
get those hands up !
♪ butt out
yeah, yeah ♪
♪ give that cigarette butt
a throw ♪
♪ butt out
uh-huh ♪
♪ smoking's got to go ♪♪
oh, no.
yeah !
woo-hoo !
hey, students !
how are we all feeling
today ?  wooo !
hey, did you guys know
that each year
over 600,000 people a year
die from smoking ?
a year !
600,000 ?
are you sure you're not
just blowing smoke ?
( laughing )
blow smoke, us ?
no way !
because we don't
need to smoke
and neither do you,
right, kids ?
butt out !
break it down !
( beat-boxing )
butt out !
yeah yeah !
it's cool to say no !
butt out !
uh-huh !
smoking's got to go !
( beat-boxing )
smokin', no.
no smokin' !
freestyle !
vernon !
chi-stop.
cha-cha chi-chi.
don't smoke !
don't ever smoke !
kyle !
b- to the u-
to the t- to the...
dude, this is
unbearable.
i'm going to
kill myself.
... to the e- to the t-
to the t- to the e.
butt out, cigarettes !
randy !
smoke you know
has got to go !
you go to know,
you gotta say...
aaagh !
pam !
( imitating tire squeal )
( crash )
( screeching )
dooon't smoooke !
woo hoo !
all right !
you guys, kenny's
eating his own hand.
hey, what's
the big deal ?!
i like smoking, and it
makes me cool !
oh really ?
do you think lung cancer
is cool, too ?
what about emphysema,
is that cool ?
and what about
abortion and aids ?!
that's nones the cool !
word !
yeah, so butt out !
♪ butt out
yeah, yeah ♪
♪ give that cigarette butt
a throw... ♪
agh, jesus christ !
♪ smoking's got to go ♪♪
remember kids,
if you smoke,
you could grow up
to be a failure.
worse yet, you could
grow up to be dead !
so don't believe
what those evil tobacco
companies tell you !
yeah !
because if you don't smoke
you can grow up to be--
just like us !!
( all coughing )
here, here,
give me another one,
give me another one.
oh dude,
this is really hard.
oh ( bleep ),
here comes mr. mackey !
throw 'em away !
( coughing )
dude, here he comes.
we gotta stop
coughing !
boys, what are you
doing back here ?
i asked you a question.
what are you doing
back here, m'kay ?
nubbi.
what ?
nubbi-- nob--
nubb--
ahh, sick !
gross, dude !
well hey, if i didn't
know any better
i'd think you boys
had been smoking !
no.
no, mr. mackey, we don't
have any cigarettes.
well, you better not
because let me tell you
something about smoking.
uh, smoking's bad, m'kay.
and if you start smoking
at an early age, m'kay,
it's gonna be bad, m'kay ?
because smoking
can lead to
all kinds of health problems
like cancer, m'kay.
let me tell you something
about cancer.
uh, cancer's bad, m'kay.
and, uh--
what, what the ?
holy ( bleep ), m'kay !
( fire alarm
ringing )
agh, jesus christ !
whoops.
well, you boys have certainly
done it this time !
♪ we're sor-ry. ♪
not as sorry as
you're going to be
when your parents
get here.
ah, here they come now.
oh, god.
( knocking )
come on in !
stanley, what did you do
this time ?!
you better brace
yourselves, parents.
the boys were caught...
smoking.
smoking ?!
no !
it can't be !
my son is not
a filthy smoker !
mom...
dad, it was just--
i don't have a son !
eric !
you've done a lot of horrible
things in your life,
but smoking ?
you are grounded
for three weeks !
three weeks ?!
are you ( bleeping )
kidding me ?!
haven't you boys heard
anything about how harmful
smoking is to you
and those around you ?
of course they haven't
because the tobacco companies
have gotten to them first !
this is really their fault !
yeah, this is really
their fault !
no matter how much money
the anti-smoking groups spend
the tobacco companies are there
to fill our children's heads
with lies and propaganda
that make them want to smoke.
yeah, huh ?!
it's like the tobacco companies
have control of my mind.
no, must fight it--
tobacco companies making me
want to smoke--
agh !
oh my goodness,
i had no idea !
are you okay,
sweetie ?
well, those goddamn
tobacco companies
aren't gonna have
control over my kid !
i say we
bring them down !
we need the help
of the greatest
anti-smoking celebrity
that ever lived !
rob reiner.
who's rob reiner ?
i don't understand it !
i pushed a law for
higher taxes on cigarettes,
i lobby to get images
of cigarettes
removed from movies and art,
i force smokers
out of bars and parks--
but still i get letters
from parents
saying their kids
are doing it !
apparently, people
still don't understand
how bad smoking is
for them !
don't they know how dangerous
it is to their health ?!
don't they know the hazard
of secondhand smoke ?!
according to
the letter, sir,
the town has a tobacco
company quite near them.
yeah, that must be it !
the tobacco companies with
their millions of dollars
and their slick desks
and fancy buildings !
they're the ones making
children want to smoke.
they're the ones hurting
our nation's health !
i will not stand by and
see the children of america
corrupted by
those bastards !
this is war !
you guys, maybe we should
come clean right now
and tell everyone that it
wasn't the tobacco companies
that made us
want to smoke.
what ?
why ?
it's perfect !
if everyone's blaming
the tobacco companies,
then nobody's
blaming us !
yeah, what's the problem ?
it's just that--
this seems like another
one of those times
when things are gonna get
way out of hand, you know ?
it's been happening
a lot lately.
how about this time we just
put a stop to it right now ?
dumbass,
you don't want to be
grounded for
three weeks, do you ?
yeah, don't worry, dude,
things aren't gonna
get out of hand.
here he comes !
dammit.
( straining )
butter !
what'd he say ?
( crowd cheering )
( panting )
hello, south park !
it is so nice to see
an entire town come together
to fight for good health !
and i'm gonna
help you !
these poor,
innocent children
have been seduced into
smoking tobacco.
so i say, we fight fire
with fire !
we're gonna use
these children
to bring the tobacco
company down !
oh, no.
all right, kids, here's
what we're gonna do.
we're gonna sneak you
into the tobacco company
by saying you kids want
a tour for a school paper.
once you're inside,
i'm gonna take photos
and then we'll publish them,
saying the tobacco company
invited you over to
seduce you into smoking !
got it ?!
got it !
but-- isn't that
kind of lying ?
we're just leveling out
the playing field.
the tobacco companies
lie to you
about the dangers
of smoking.
if we're gonna
take them down
we've gotta lie
right back !
( sniffing )
oh my god !
( coughs )
( coughs louder )
excuse me !
yes ?
would you mind putting
that death stick out ?!
but, uh, this is a bar.
isn't smoking illegal
in bars here ?
not in colorado.
oh my god !
what kind of backward,
hick state is this ?!
look, man, i work 14 hours
a day at the saw mill.
i just got off work
and i need to relax.
well, when i relax,
i just go to my
vacation house in hawaii !
i ain't got a
vacation house in hawaii.
your vacation house
in mexico then,
whatever it is !
look, you are putting my life
and these boys' lives in danger
by smoking that in here.
and i am not gonna
tolerate it !
i will end smoking
in bars in colorado !
there will be
no more smoking !
isn't he awesome,
you guys ?
what ?!
dude, he just goes around
imposing his will on people.
he's my idol.
all right, boys,
just do what i tell you,
and we'll be able to sue
this tobacco company
for $2 billion !
as soon as we get into
the main facility
i'll snap the photo
of you kids
and we can all
run out.
think you can
handle it ?
for $2 billion i'd handle
my grandpa's balls, sir.
all right, great.
okay, now watch
yourselves, kids.
these tobacco company people
will do anything
to get you hooked
on smoking.
they are liars
and they are frauds !
can i help you ?
yes, my name is
rita poon,
i called about my boys
wanting a tour.
ah yes, mrs. poon.
my name's
kevin harris
and i'm the vice president
of big tobacco.
hello, mr. harris.
well, come on in !
how about a little
history first ?
native americans were the first
to cultivate the tobacco plant.
they smoked it in pipes
for medicinal and
ceremonial purposes.
not if i were around
they wouldn't have !
excuse me ?
oh, nothing !
please continue !
the first successful
commercial crop of tobacco
was cultivated
in virginia in 1612.
within seven years
it was one of the country's
largest exports !
so, tobacco helped
to build america.
that's right.
over the next few centuries,
the tobacco business
was so great
that many slaves were
brought from africa
to help work the fields.
which means if it
weren't for tobacco
many of our black friends
wouldn't be here today.
and so for centuries, tobacco
production flourished.
nobody was even aware
of any dangers back then,
until, in 1965, when
congress passed an act
forcing all tobacco companies
to put the surgeon general's
warning on their packages.
so now, everyone knows
the dangers of smoking.
and some people
still choose to do it,
and we believe that's what being
an american is all about.
that sounds perfectly
reasonable.
and here's our
factory at work !
♪ with a
hide-e-li-de-e-lie ♪
♪ and a hide-e-lie-de-lay ♪
♪ we work and we
make cigarettes ♪
♪ all hide-e-lide-e-day ♪
♪ so folks can get
a break-e ♪
♪ from their stressful
lide-lives ♪
♪ and relax-y
with the cigarettes ♪
♪ we make all day
and night ♪
♪ i like to have a cigarette
every now and then ♪
♪ it makes me feel calmer
when the day is at an end ♪
♪ and if it gives me cancer
when i'm 80 i don't care ♪
♪ who the hell wants to be
90 anyway ? ♪
♪ so with a
hide-alie-de-lie ♪
♪ and a hide-e-lie-de-lay ♪
♪ we work and we
make cigarettes ♪
♪ all hide-e-lide-e-day ♪
♪ so folks can get
a break-e ♪
♪ from their stressful
lide-lives ♪
♪ and relax-y
with the cigarettes ♪
♪ we make all day
and night ♪♪
well, i guess that's
the end of our tour !
oh, here, boys,
let me get your picture.
got it !
ha !  you bastards
are going down now !
what ?
i'm not rita poon,
i'm rob reiner !
and you've just been
reiner'd !
come on, boys,
let's make our escape !
don't you try
and stop us !
( screaming )
oh my god !
oh boy, that was
great, kids !
( kyle )
those people at
the tobacco company
all seem really nice.
yeah, you see that ?
they got into
your head !
now you kids can meet some
good decent people,
the folks who work
to get smoking banned !
( growling )
( hissing )
this is how we get
rid of smokers !
we go state to state and do
things like use bogus studies
and make expensive
commercials
to get the public
on our side
and force cigarette
smokers to stop !
wow, it's like, it's like
smoking brings a lot of people
just a little bit of joy
and you get to take that
away from them.
you are so awesome.
here you go, bob.
this is
mr. valkri,
he does all
ourphotoshopwork.
now all we have to do
is photoshop cigarettes
into your hands,
and bingo !
when this hits the papers the
tobacco company is screwed !
ha ha ha ha !
but dude--
you're making stuff up.
you kids need to understand
something, okay ?
sometimes lying is okay,
like when you know what's good
for people more than they do.
oh my god, that is exactly
what i've always said.
i love this guy !
mr. reiner, your bill
to have smoking
outlawed in bars here
didn't pass.
what ?!
god dammit, what
the hell is wrong
with people
in this state ?!
apparently, several people
here still believe
there's no proof secondhand
smoke can kill you.
they want proof ?!
all right,
we'll give them proof !
boys, i need one of you to act
in a commercial for us !
we'll shoot it tomorrow !
wow, a commercial ?!
you boys decide
which one of you
would be best
for the part.
all right, people, we gotta
get moving on the bill
to ban smoking
in parks here !
let's go !
god, he's just the best !
mr. reiner !
can i get you a muffin ?
or a cold drink perhaps ?
you guys, i think we should
bail out of this right now.
huh ?
i justknowwhere
this is heading-
it's gonna end up
with the whole town
taking this too far
and us having to talk
about "what we learned"
to change everyone's mind,
and i say we just
stop right now
and go play
cards or something.
yup, i totally agree.
yeah, maybe
you're right.
so, gentlemen, looks
like only one of us
gets to be in
the commercial, huh ?
who will it be... ?
gentlemen,
the game is on !
go ahead.
we don't want to be in
their stupid commercial.
huh ?
oh, i get it, kyle.
that's your serbian jew
double bluff--
make me think you don't care
about being in the commercial
so that maybe
i won't either.
oops, didn't work,
did it, kyle ?
no, we really want nothing more
to do with these people.
sure you don't, kyle.
oh, and neither do i.
i know what you're
gonna say next.
you're gonna say,
"how about none of us
show up tomorrow
to do it ?"
and then i'm supposed to
agree, so that tomorrow
you can waltz in
all by yourself
and do the commercial.
that's serbian jew
double bluff,
and it ain't
gonna work on me.
heh heh heh.
only one of us can be in
the commercial, gentlemen.
the game-- is on.
sorry, kyle, but i'm afraid
only one of us will be
showing up to do the
commercial tomorrow, ha ha ha !
thought you had me
with your serbian jew
double bluff, didn't you ?
well, let's see you try to
open this door now !
( laughing )
what are you doing ?
oh.
hello, kyle.
oh man, wait--
this isn't my house.
cartman, you go ahead and
do the commercial tomorrow.
but i'm warning you:
those anti-smoking people
are liars
and they're bullies
who will stop at nothing
to get what they want,
and that means
they're dangerous.
ha ha ha ha !
nice try, kyle !
let's see you try to get
through this door now !
ha ha ha ha !
okay, eric, this is
gonna be real simple.
all you gotta do is just
read the words
on the teleprompter, here.
( laughing )
okay !
let's see how the tobacco
companies deal with this !
all right,
roll camera !
roll the teleprompter.
and whenever
you're ready, eric.
( giggling )
okay, okay.
( takes a deep breath )
you know, some people say
there's no proof
that secondhand smoke kills.
the tobacco companies say
there's no proof
that secondhand smoke
kills.
i've just been diagnosed
with terminal lung cancer.
i guess...
i'm the proof.
the next time
you want to believe
that secondhand smoke
doesn't kill,
think about me.
because by the time
you see this commercial
i'll be dead.
dead ?
and cut !
great, we got it !
wrap up, people,
that was fantastic !
what-- what does that mean,
i'll be dead ?
hey, what was that
dead part ?
that was very good,
eric.
here, eat this cupcake.
uh... no thanks,
i'm not hungry.
but you are.
just eat this
one cupcake.
it has sprinkles.
i'm not eating
the cupcake.
eric, do you know what
a hero is ?
a hero is somebody
who sacrifices himself
for the good of others.
you can be
a hero, eric.
all you have to do
is eat the cupcake.
jesus christ !
hey !
( panting )
what are you
doing, cartman ?
they're going to
kill me !
who's going to
kill you ?
the anti-smoking people !
they had me say i died
from secondhand smoke
and now they want to sacrifice
me to make it look real !
they'll stop at nothing !
well, get away
from us then !
yeah, dude, don't
get us killed too !
you guys have to
help me !
no, dude, get away !
please you guys, i don't
know what to do !
stop it, cartman,
go die on your own !
if i go, you guys go !
dad !
what ?
the anti-smoking people are
trying to kill cartman
and he won't
stay away from us !
don't be ridiculous, boys.
the anti-smoking people are
kind, caring and intelligent.
your heads have just
been corrupted
by the lies of the
big tobacco companies.
hey, maybe that's it,
you guys.
maybe the tobacco company
can help us !
help you, fatass !
we weren't in the
commercial, remember ?
yeah, go to the
tobacco company yourself.
well, that's fine !
i thought you guys were my
friends but i guess i was wrong.
yeah, dude, you were
totally wrong.
uh-huh.
you guys, i am seriously
getting pissed off now !
now come on, we're going to
the tobacco company !
oh, all right !
no !
what we really should do is
go to our parents right now
and take responsibility
for smoking ourselves.
even if it means
getting grounded.
why ?
because, if we go to
the tobacco company
i know exactly
what'll happen !
they'll take us in,
and then rob reiner
will show up
with all the townspeople
holding torches or something
and there'll be
a big showdown
until we talk about
what we learned
and change
everyone's minds.
this is all following
a formula !
so it's either
deal with all that
or be grounded
for three weeks.
( angry shouting )
god dammit.
give us the child !
we will not !
there, you see that ?
the tobacco company
won't give us the kid !
and do you know why ?
because they know that
if they give us that kid
then we'll kill him !
and when our commercial
goes on the air
it will lose them
business !
yeah !
that's right !
( mr. mackey )
wait a minute-- what ?
yeah, when we kill the kid,
people are gonna think
it's because of
secondhand smoke,
and then these bastards
aren't gonna make money,
and they know it !
what the hell is
wrong with you ?
that's not right.
oh god dammit, do i have to
explain this again ?
smoking is bad, people !
so if we have to be a little
extreme to stop it, it's okay !
no, it isn't,
you fat turd !
because i've learned
something today.
you just hate--
see ?  i knew it.
yup.
you just hate smoking
so you use all your
money and power
to force others
to think like you,
and that's called fascism,
you tubby asshole !
god dammit, there will
be no more smoking !
it wasn't the tobacco company's
fault that we smoked.
it was our fault, us.
we should all take
personal responsibility
instead of letting fat fascists
like him tell us what to do !
you're right, boys,
m'kay !
yeah, let smokers smoke !
yeah !
that's right !
hey, mr. reiner !
why don't you--
butt out !
( laughter )
i'm warning you !
don't mess with
anti-smoking groups !
i don't idolize you
anymore, asshole !
my goo !
my precious goo !
so kyle, it wasn't
the tobacco company
that made you
want to smoke ?
no.
well then, you are
grounded, mister !
you too, eric.
aww, awwww !
well, i guess we
learned our lesson.
no, we
didn't dude...
no, we didn't.
♪ with a
hide-e-li-de-e-lie ♪
♪ and a hide-e-lie-de-lay ♪
♪ we work and we
make cigarettes ♪
♪ all hide-e-lide-e-day ♪
♪ so folks can get
a break-e ♪
♪ from their stressful
lide-lives ♪
♪ and relax-y
with the cigarettes ♪
♪ we make all day
and night ♪
♪ i like to have a cigarette
every now and then ♪
♪ it makes me feel calmer
when the day is at an end ♪
♪ and if it gives me cancer
when i'm 80 i don't care-- ♪♪