captioning made possible by
comedy central
♪ i'm going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna have
myself a time ♪
♪ friendly faces
everywhere ♪
♪ humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna leave my
woes behind ♪
♪ ample parking
day or night ♪
♪ people spouting
"howdy neighbor" ♪
♪ headin' on up
to south park ♪
♪ gonna see
if i can't unwind ♪
♪ ( muffled mumble
muffled mumble ) ♪
♪ so come on down
to south park ♪
♪ and meet some
friends of mine ♪♪
friends, we gather
in this place
to mourn the victims
of yesterday's tragedy.
nine good people, who were
run over in the street
by an elderly
woman driver.
oh god, memorial services
are so boring.
you insensitive asshole,
cartman !
nine people died !
yeah, but like eight
of them were hippies.
mostly hippies go to
farmer's markets.
mostly.
it is sometimes hard,
in times like these,
to understand god's way.
why would he allow
nine innocent people
to be run down in the
prime of their lives
by a senior citizen who,
perhaps,
shouldn't be driving ?
it is then that
we must understand
god's sense of humor is very
different from our own.
he does not laugh at the simple
"man walks into a bar" joke.
no, god needs complex irony,
and subtle, farcical twists
that seem macabre
to you and me.
all that we can hope for, is
that god got his good laugh
and a tragedy such as this
will never happen again.
look out !
wah ?
was that a stop sign
back there ?
( screaming )
ohhh, i think
i hit a pothole.
hey dad, how come they
let old people drive ?
well, stan, it's
a very fragile issue.
but they kill people.
sometimes, yes,
but senior citizens
have to be dealt with
very gingerly, stan.
we can't just take
their licenses away.
i'll be god damned
if they think
they can take
my license away !
oh, hi, dad.
i heard what you said !
you wanna take driving
privileges away from seniors !
well, let me tell you
something, pecker-face,
i worked 55 years
in a steel mill...
yes, dad.
and i flew spitfires over
germany in world war ii...
yes, i know.
and i will be god damned
if the government thinks
it can step in and take away
my right to drive !
i think old people should
have rights, grandpa.
i just don't wanna die.
( humming )
( ominous "jaws"-like music )
dammit, mona, this
isn't the fastest way
tocountry
kitchen buffet!
no, but it's the shortest,
save the most gas that way.
you save more gas
if you take the highway
to country
kitchen buffet !
less miles means less gas,
you old fool !
there's country kitchen
right there !
where ?
back there,
you're gonna miss it !
is this the
parking lot ?
i think so.
another death tonight by
a senior citizen motorist !
carl zorn of pine junction
was killed instantly
when struck by a vehicle
driven by pete and lydia melman,
who were trying to find
country kitchen buffet.
this latest tragedy
comes only two days
after the accident
in deer creek,
where three construction
workers in a bulldozer
were run down by
senior citizen paul tobb,
who was trying to find
country kitchen buffet.
public outcry is forcing
the d.m.v. to consider
suspending the licenses of
all seniors over 70,
though no decision
has yet to be made.
seniors of south park !
i don't know about you,
but i am mad as hell !
yeah !
i'm sick of having
my mental condition
come into question !
yeah !
that's right !
we need to let everyone know
we're pissed off
and we're not gonna
take it anymore !
hear, hear !
that's right, pete !
that's right !
now...
can anybody remember what
we're pissed off about ?
i remember we're all
pissed about something.
that's why we had
this meeting,
but i can't
for the life of me...
ooh, was it the kids
skateboarding
on the sidewalks ?
no...
oh, i remember !
they're going to take
our licenses away !
that's right, they're gonna try
and take our licenses away !
and i for one
am mad as hell !
me too !
yeah, that's right !
i'm mad too !
i am sick of having my mental
condition come into question !
so now, what are we
gonna do about it ?
do about what ?
they're gonna take
our licenses away.
they are ?!
they can't
do that !
you said it !
that's right, so you know what
i think we should do ?
i think we should have
a senior citizens meeting !
get all the seniors together
at the community center
and unite !
great idea, marvin !
wait, i think we're having
that meeting right now.
oh, right,
this is the meeting.
right, to get them
damn kids
to stop skateboarding
on the sidewalks !
yeah !
that's right !
we gotta stop 'em !
sharon,
have you seen dad ?
he's not here, honey,
he's having a meeting
with all the seniors in town
at the community center.
oh.
wait a minute.
if all the seniors in town
are at a meeting,
that means that when
the meeting gets out...
every senior in town
will be driving home...
at the same time.
oh-my-god !
get inside !
seniors meeting
getting out !
get off the streets !
all right,
great meeting, everyone.
let's do it again
sometime.
so long, everybody !
good-bye, lucy.
get off the streets !
old people
are driving !
( screaming )
gerald !
where are the boys ?
we've gotta
get out of here !
the boys, gerald,
where are they ?!
they're, they're...
they're playing
street hockey !
oh-my-god !
with just 10 seconds to go,
the offense makes its move !
marsh heads for the goal
and passes the ball
to the poor kid !
the poor kid hands it off
to the jew !
the jew shoots !
oh, and the shot
is blocked again !
proving once and for all that
jews cannot play hockey !
it isn't fair !
cartman's fatter
than the goal !
i'm not fat, i just have
a sweet hockey body.
( yelling in the distance )
get off the streets !
get off
the streets !
dude, look.
get off !
the streets !
get off the streets !
what is that ?
i don't know.
get off !
get streets
off the streets !
dude, is that
your dad ?
i think so.
looks like
stan's dad's
been hittin'
the bottle again.
streets !
what is he saying ?
i can't
understand him.
gaaaah !
calm down !
we cannot
understand you !
( screaming )
oh jesus !
old people !
come on !
get over there !
stay low !
why are they all out
driving at the same time ?
shhh !
it's okay, boys,
they're gone.
let's just lay low for
a minute until we can find--
aaagh !
i don't remember there
being a building here.
run !
i told you to
turn left, larry.
get up the stairs !
up the stairs !
come on !
aah !
there's another one !
excuse me, is this
costello avenue ?
in here !
( screaming )
they're not gonna stop
until we're all dead !
quiet !
keep quiet !
dad, i'm scared !
just keep your
voices down !
we'll stay
the night in here.
we'll stay the whole
winter if we have to.
i'm not staying the
winter in this room !
you need to tell old people
they can't drive anymore !
aw, stan, it's not
that simple !
just relax while
i find the lights.
here we go.
( old man )
how the hell did we
get up here ?
aaaahgh !
i told you this was
the wrong way.
tom, i'm standing outside of
the department of motor vehicles
where senior citizens
have until 3:00 p.m.
to hand over
their driver's licenses.
the new law was passed
just three days
after the night of horror,
in which all seniors were out
driving at the same time,
causing 14 deaths and
$3 million in damage.
alrighty...
there we go.
next !
it ain't right
what you're doin' !
i never had an accident
in my life !
that's right.
you shouldn't
punish all of us !
we're sorry, but this is
the only way to be sure.
next, please.
there we go.
but how am i supposed to
get to the grocery store ?
or the pharmacy
to buy medicine ?
well, maybe, you should be
in a nursing home, hmm ?
some of us would
rather die !
well, we can certainly
help you with that too.
we aren't second-class
citizens !
that's right,
you can take our licenses,
but you'll never take
our pride !
yeah...
ahhh, isn't this
great, you guys ?
being able to walk the streets
now that old people
are confined to their homes
where they belong.
( car honks )
billy, get in the car.
i need you boys to help me
pick up my newhoverround.
uh, grandpa,
i don't think you're
supposed to be driving.
god dammit, billy !
you're supposed to listen
to your dad, right ?
well, i'm your dad's dad !
and that means
you get in this car
before i tan
all your hides !
well, look at it
this way:
statistically speaking,
we're saferinsidea car
with an old person
driving, than outside.
my god, he's right.
hail mary, full of grace,
the lord is with thee.
i shall not walk through
the valley of death.
ergghhh...
guys, i don't know if i ever
told you this,
but, well,
i love you guys.
except for you, kyle.
okay, all set ?
( honking )
( man )
asshole !
( honking )
( screaming )
( police siren )
uh, i think there's a police
car behind you, grandpa.
eh ?
go around !
go around, ya moron !
( over loudspeaker )
blueimpala,pull
your vehicle over.
( eric )
i believe that's us.
thank god.
can i see your
license, please ?
i ain't got one !
you peckers took it !
well then, i have to
take you to jail.
you just try taking me
to jail, scrotum head !
you just try !
stupid, son of a--
god dammit.
i've just got him
right here, mr. marsh.
oh, brother.
well, good job, dad,
look at you now.
oh, god dammit,
don't you lecture me,
you son of a bitch !
you just had to be so damn
stubborn, didn't you ?
now my son is gonna
talk to me like i'm 12 !
we're not treating you like
children, dad, all right ?
now i think you owe mr.
police officer an apology.
who needs to
apologize, hmm ?
who's a sorry sorry ?
kiss my sagging ass !
well fine, i was
gonna bail you out,
but maybe you can just
sit here for a bit
and think about
what you did.
i won't be
sitting here long.
i've already called
the a.a.r.p. !
what's that ?
the american association
of retired persons--
the largest political group
in the country !
when seniors like me are
being discriminated against,
the a.a.r.p. comes
and sets it right.
and you're gonna be sorry
when they get here !
( school bell rings )
and so you see, children,
genghis khan was a mongol,
not to be confused
with a mongoloid,
like the actor
nicolas cage.
okay now, who can
tell me in what year...
the first film by...
the mongoloid...
that's odd.
those r.o.t.c. guys
are way off course.
more old people !
the american association
of retired persons.
stay in your seats, children,
i'll be right back.
set up a perimeter !
bring bravo team
to point delta !
bravo team is go !
move move move !
let's go !
uh, can i help you folks
find something ?
aagh !
old people
have gone mad !
( coughing )
contact !
get your hands up,
young man !
marvin marsh ?
yes.
i'm bill stewart,
president of the a.a.r.p.
we've come to help the seniors
in this town fight back.
oh, it's nice
to meet you, bill.
hah ?
we came as fast as we could.
we just had to stop by
country kitchen buffet first.
it's the nursing home !
liberate our
comrades !
let's go !
there now, mr. johnson,
we can go to the cafeteria
and get you some nice
cream corn and toast.
can i help you ?
help this.
oof !
the revolution
is on, brother !
we're taking control
of the town !
we are ?
well, it's about
damn time !
hey, everyone,
we're taking the town !
seniors, we're taking
the town over !
the revolution
is on !
ooh, the revolution ?
oh, i better get
my other sweater.
mrs. ryland, seniors
are taking over the town.
would you like a gun ?
i suppose so.
what the hell
is going on ?
shut your pie hole
and get over there !
randy, what is this ?
hah !
you are now under the
authority of the a.a.r.p. !
ha !  there you go,
mr. smart mouth !
look at ya now !
dad, what are you doing ?
the a.a.r.p. is going to
help us take this town
until we get our
licenses back !
yeah, and we're gonna ask for
more money in medicare too !
that's right !
yeah !
have you all got
alzheimer's ?
they're not gonna
listen to
a bunch of whacked out
senior citizens !
hah ?
we'll tell 'em if they
don't give us our demands
we'll start
killing hostages !
right, they're gonna
really believe that !
isn't that a little
extreme, bill ?
hah ?
no, we gotta be tough !
just like with those
damn japs !
this is insane, dad, you all
need to stop right now
before more people
get hurt.
the time when you can
tell me what to do
is over, bucky boy !
we're in charge now !
all right, we've got control
of the mayor's office
and the fire station.
reinforcements
have arrived
from the nursing home
in conifer.
good !
hell, us senior citizens could
take over the entire country !
we've got company !
( man over loudspeaker )
attention, seniors.
lay down your weapons
and turn yourselves over.
mrs. applegate, show 'em
we mean business.
all right.
what do you want ?
hah ?
we want our
licenses back !
yeah !
that's right, and we want
more money in medicare !
yeah !
and we want those
damn kids
to stop skateboarding
on the sidewalks !
yeah !
hey, dad.
stan !  boys !
you're safe !
dad, why is everyone letting
the old people do this ?
why doesn't somebody
stop them ?
they've tried to
stop them, son,
but the seniors get up
so early in the morning
they get everything done before
everyone else is even awake.
they're saying
something about
taking over
the whole country.
yes, and now seeing
how early they get up,
i don't see how
anyone can stop them.
wait a minute, you boys !
you get up almost
as early as they do,
you can fight them !
aw, come on, dad,
can't you guys do it ?
no son, we...
like to sleep in.
( old woman )
two hostages come
front and center !
they're coming !
get out of here
before they see you.
run to the hills and find
a way to fight them, go !
boys-- avenge me !
avenge me !!
all right, check it out.
kenny did reconnaissance
on the town.
the old people have blockades
here and here.
old ladies are keeping watch
in towers around the perimeter.
the leaders, along
with my grandpa,
are most likely
in the mayor's office.
( eric )
so our only solution is to
cut off their life force.
( kyle )
we can't fight them,
cartman.
no, but we can sneak
into town
and shut down
their food supply.
here.
country kitchen buffet ?
yeah, you take out
country kitchen buffet
and old people
won't know what to do.
that's a retarded idea,
cartman !
is it ?
two years ago they closed
the country kitchen buffet
in steamboat springs
and all the old people
died of starvation
in less than a week.
yeah, i remember
hearing about that.
even if it
could work,
how would we go about
shutting it down ?
i think i have a plan.
but we'll have to
do it tonight.
( eric )
we'll start by
sneaking into town,
cleverly disguised
as black people.
at 5:45, kenny
and kyle split off
and set a diversion
on the east side of town.
( train whistle tooting )
meanwhile, stan and i sneak
into the mayor's office
and steal some of
the explosives
the old people
have stashed.
9:00, we rendezvous at
the country kitchen buffet
where we strap the explosives
and the timer to kyle's chest.
we say our tearful
good-byes to kyle
and then send him inside.
yeah !
all right !
i did it !
yeah, or we just go to
country kitchen buffet
and lock it
from the inside
so the seniors
can't get in.
well, right,
or we do that.
all right, everyone,
round up your ammunition
and get ready to move !
we're taking this war
further out !
all right !
let's go !
look, bob, i appreciate
what the a.a.r.p.
is trying to do for us,
but all we want
is our licenses back.
hah ?
heck no !
this is going too well.
we're gonna take the
whole country back,
wipe out everyone
below the age of 65 !
wipe 'em out ?
what are you, senile ?!
come on, everyone !
it's time to
plan phase 2 !
what the heck ?
hah ?
what is this ?
it's six a.m., country kitchen
should be open !
it's not open ?
has to be !
try a window !
they're blocked from
the inside !
no...
no, let us in !
let us in !
open the door !
it's six a.m. !
open the country
kitchen buffet !
you have to
let us in !
ugh... argh...
all right, everyone,
area secure !
collect their weapons
and free the hostages.
that was a great
strategy, boys,
you may very well have saved
this entire country.
( yawning )
what happened ?
is it over ?
everything is fine.
control of the town
is back to you folks.
country kitchen...
what happened ?
sir, what should we do
with this one ?
it's up to
the townspeople.
well, i think he learned
his lesson, huh ?
don't you feel
silly now, dad ?
i think somebody owes us
all an apology.
yes he does.
oh, stop it, dad !
this is partly
your fault !
huh ?
look, all grandpa wants is not
to be talked to like a child.
i think half of what
he was angry about
wasn't what you were doing,
but how you were doing it.
that's right.
and grandpa,
you should be proud
that you made it though life
to be a senior,
but you should also realize
that when you get
behind the wheel
you're a killing
machine.
i know.
i guess sometimes
us seniors
need to know
when to stop driving
so we don't put the
responsibility on our families.
well, i think this has been
a real learning experience
for the marsh family.
people died, but we all
grew a little.
let's just go home.
sure, i'll drive.
( laughs )
that's our grandpa !
dude, i hate my family.
captioning made possible by
comedy central
captioned by
soundwriters™