captioning made possible by
comedy central
♪ i'm going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna have
myself a time ♪
♪ friendly faces
everywhere ♪
♪ humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna leave my
woes behind ♪
♪ ample parking
day or night ♪
♪ people spouting
"howdy neighbor" ♪
♪ headin' on up
to south park ♪
♪ gonna see
if i can't unwind ♪
♪ ( muffled mumble
muffled mumble ) ♪
♪ so come on down
to south park ♪
♪ and meet some
friends of mine ♪♪
oh my god, you guys
are not gonna believe
what happened to me
last night.
what ?  tell us.
so, i'm watching
the season premiere
of "boy meets boy"
on television
and then "queer eye for the
straight guy" comes on, right ?
so i fall asleep
in front of the tv
and when i wake up
i see that i've spilled
the coke i was drinking
all over my
satin pajama top.
oh my gosh,
are you serious ?
that was the cutest
top ever !
i know !
( muffled speech )
ooh, tell me about it,
ken-doll.
hey, dudes.
ha ha ha !
ha ha ha haaa !
what a dork !
what ?
nice jacket, kyle !
polyester is really the
hot fabric this fall !
ha ha ha haaa !
but-but, this is the jacket
i always wear.
you gotta get with
the times, girlfriend.
yeah, that jacket is
so september 10th !
oh my god, you've got
splotches on your neck.
are you using any exfoliating
products at all ?
we can't let kyle out in
public like this, you guys.
that's for sure !
come on, kyle, we're
giving you a makeover !
( dance music )
♪ you came into my life ♪
♪ and my world never
looked so bright, yeah ♪
♪ it's true
you bring out the best in me ♪
♪ when you are around
when you are around ♪
♪ all things just keep
getting better ♪
♪ things keep
♪ life keeps getting better
and better ♪
♪ things just keep
getting better ♪♪
( tv announcer )
coming up next on hbc
it's "queer eye for the
straight guy" !
we have got to get you some
tighter fitting shirts !
then it's "boy meets boy"
followed by "will and grace".
and then: "the love boat...
with men".
my goodness, there certainly
are a lot of gay shows
on television these days.
yeah, i think it's great
that gays are finally
being so accepted.
hi, mom, hi, dad !
aaaah !
kyle, what's
happened to you ?
i'm just trying
to fit in, daddy,
don't be such
a drama queen.
oh my god !
come on, sheila,
we better go tell
the other parents
what's going on !
( doorbell rings,
knocking )
oh, hi, gerald, sheila.
hi, sharon.
we need to talk to you
about the boys.
sure, come on in.
the guys are all
watching tv.
oh, is the game on
or something ?
( dance music )
hey, gerald !
how are you ?
hi, gerald !
gerald !
sit down, ger-ger.
"queer eye for the
straight guy" is on.
oh no, you guys all
turned gay too ?
( laughter )
not gay, gerald--
metrosexual.
what's that ?
just because a guy
cares about how he looks
and is in touch with
his feminine side
doesn't mean he's
gay anymore !
yeah, metrosexual
means you're straight
but you appreciate
the gay culture.
it's super fabulous,
would you like some shiraz ?
don't our men
look amazing ?
haven't you seen
"queer eye for the
straight guy", sheila ?
these five gay men go around
and show straight men
how to better themselves.
it's the best !
it is ?
well, sure, sheila,
our husbands are all
so clean and neat.
my randy irons his clothes
and even has pedicures !
and they like to talk about
their feelings now
and drink wine
and decorate the house !
my steven
shaved his chest.
and his balls !
ooh, i love it !
and how about
our boys, huh ?
ever since gay culture
became cool
our boys bathe every night
and brush their teeth
three times a day.
this is the
greatest thing ever.
i don't know,
sometimes boys take
cultural fads too far.
( school bell rings )
dude, i can't wait for wendy
to see how gay i look !
that's true, you guys,
when the chicks at school
see how gay we are,
they're gonna be
all over us.
woo-hoo !
all right,
let's work it !
what the--
toodle-oo, conner,
see ya after classies !
okay, sweetums !
oh my god,
where is my homework ?
i am frrr-eaking out !
hey, dudes.
hey, craig.
you guys look
pretty gay.
thanks !
not as gay as us, though.
oh please, craig, we're
10 times gayer than you !
oh yeah ?
we're super-duper
triple-dog gay !
oh yeah ?
we're ultra-super-stamp-it
stamp-it-no-erasees-mega gay !
what's all this
fighting about, children ?
these guys are
trying to say
they're gayer
than us !
oh no, don't tell me
you children
have taken up this whole
metrosexual fad too !
oh my god !
this is not a fad,
this is who we are.
no, it isn't !
last year you children
were all trying to be black,
now you're all
trying to be gay !
we're metrosexual !
maybe, but you'll never be
as metrosexual as us !
come on, fags !
god, i hate craig !
that son of a--
gah !
chef ?
i don't feel
very metrosexual.
well then, don't buy
into this fad, kyle.
be who you are,
not what's cool.
( bell rings )
all right, children,
let's take our seats.
( kids )
good morning, mr. garrison.
well... don't you all
look nice.
ooh, timmy.
( door opens )
dude, what are you
doing ?
i didn't feel comfortable
in that stuff, dude.
i'm just being me.
ha !
told you you guys
were straight !
we're not straight,
you're straight !
you're straight
like a freeway !
what the hell
is going on ?
you wish you were gay,
craig, in your dreams !
i'm not just gay,
i'm a catamite !
so, i'm half
bisexual !
oh, stop it !
you kids don't even know
what you're talking about !
eric, you're not
half bi !
i'm like,
a quarter bi.
my grandpa was bi,
so that makes me
quarter bi !
what ?!
it was the craziest thing
i've ever seen, mr. slave.
all the children were
suddenly acting like
being gay was cool.
i mean, maybe
we're not the only
gay couple in town anymore.
oh, jesus christ.
( thumping dance music )
look at that,
mr. slave !
our cup runneth over.
jesus christ !
mr. garrison,
those are great pants.
thanks, jimbo, i really
like your outfit too.
so, so, jimbo,
you wanna come back
to my place
with me and mr. slave ?
uh, for what ?
well, you know...
no.
huh.
mr. garrison !
hey, doll !
oh, hey, randy.
you're looking
ultra fabulous.
thanks, you too.
so, uh, randy,
you want me to give you
a hand job in the bathroom ?
no, no thanks,
i'm not like that.
not like that ?
how about some
shiraz, guys ?
oh, thanks, mr. tweek.
my pleasure,
silly buns.
oh...
well, mr. tweek, why don't we
go back to my place ?
why ?
well, you know,
i was just thinking
we could put on some music
and watch videos
and pound mr. slave's
tight little ass.
ooh, jesus christ.
oh, goodness no,
i'm straight.
straight ?
oh, what-- just what the hell
is going on here ?!
why won't anybody pound
mr. slave's butt ?
well, we don't
pound butt, mr. garrison,
we're straight.
those pants and those shoes
sayyoupound butt !
hey, now,
that's not true.
my shoes don't say
i pound butt.
no, your shoes say you
take it in the butt !
it's okay, mr. garrison,
we've learned that gays
are totally cool.
you're just
one of us now !
( all )
yeah !
one of you ?!
we spend our whole lives
trying to not be one of you !
you can't do this to us !
have you guys
seen this ?
it's a conditioner
that you can leave in
and it detoxifies
the scalp.
wow, is that
fromorigins?
yeah, it's a charcoal
based thing that--
hey, guys, you wanna go
throw the football around ?
guys, can i talk to you
over here for a second ?
look guys, a lot of the kids
in school are talking, okay ?
and they're spreading rumors
that we're not metrosexuals
because we hang out
with kyle.
well, what can we
do about it ?
we have no choice,
you guys.
we're just gonna
have to kill kyle.
what, that's stupid !
we wouldn't
have to kill kyle.
we would just have to tell him
not to hang around us anymore !
oh, you know,
you're right, stan.
we just have to tell kyle
not to hang around us anymore.
yeah-- wait, what ?
you hear that, kenny ?
stan thinks we should tell kyle
not to hang around us anymore.
i think he's right.
good luck
telling him, stan,
i know it won't
be easy.
hey, butch boy !
nice football
you got there !
( laughter )
when was the last time
you had a manicure,
straight man ?
yeah, let's see
that hair.
look, he's not even
using any product !
hey, what's going on ?
oh, here come
the butch boys
to help their
butchy little friend.
he's not our friend.
stan ?
this playground is for
metrosexuals, macho man !
take your non-flaming ass
to some other school !
no-- ah--
kyle !
what happened to you ?
i got beat up at school--
for being different.
what ?!
your classmates beat you up
for being a jew ?
no !
for not being
a metrosexual !
gerald !
gerald, get down here !
heeere i come !
( dance music )
oh, no, dad's
metrosexual too ?
kyle !
you look terrible !
the boys at school
beat him up, gerald !
oh, really ?
well, don't you worry, kyle.
we can cover that black eye up
with some cream base,
and the coat and pants
we'll bleach with an acid wash
for a fun, vintage look.
aaagh !
just leave me alone !
( dance music
coming from tv )
( man )
there you go !
now you look
fabulous !
you see that ?
a spray-on tan does
wonders for your look !
grrrrrrr !
now, let's get down to
the tango class
and learn some new steps.
that does it !
i know what
i have to do !
( doorbell rings )
oh, hello, mr. garrison.
chef, can i talk to you ?
sure, come on in.
thanks.
come, slave.
it's just awful, chef.
i used to feel like
an outsider,
a totally different person
who stood out in this town.
now every straight guy
is acting gayer than me !
oh, jesus,
jesus christ !
well, what do you
want me to do about it ?
chef, what did you do when white
people stole your culture ?
oh.
well, we black people just
always tried to stay
out in front of them.
how did you do that ?
well, like with our slang.
black people always used to
say "i'm in the house"
instead of "i'm here".
but then white people all
started to say "in the house"
so we switched it to
"in the hisouse".
"hisouse" became "hisisouse".
and when white folk
started sayingthat
and we had to change it to
"heezay", then "in the hizzle",
which we had to change to
"hizzle for zizzle"
and now because white people
say "hizzle for zizzle"
we have to say "flippity
floppity floop".
we don't have time
for all that, chef !
oh, if only those "queer eye
for the straight guy" people
understood what
they were doing.
wait, that's it !
i know exactly
what to do !
come on, mr. slave,
let's get back to our
flippity floppity floop !
oh, no !
dammit,
don't call it that !
one ticket to
new york, please.
you're going to
new york alone ?
i'm going to see the "queer eye
for the straight guy" people.
ooh, great idea !
they can help you with
those dated clothes.
mr. garrison ?
kyle, what are you
doing here ?
i'm going to new york
to kill the "queer eye for
the straight guy" people.
what ?!
that's what i'm doing !
oh, no,
they ruined my life--
i get to kill them first !
they took gay culture
from real gays
and their asses are ours !
i thought of it first !
no you didn't !
did so !
i thought of it
yesterday !
two days ago !
i thought of it
before you were born !
stop it, you two,
stop it !
don't you see
how crazy this is ?
oh, you're right,
mr. slave.
we can both
kill them together.
cool.
wow, we look great !
yeah, let's see
craig out-gay us now !
boys, boys,
come on !
there's a sale down
atexpress for men!
hey, guys, there's a sale
at express for men !
oh my god !
let's go !
you guys have got to see
these shoes i bought !
hurry, you guys, the mall
closes in seven hours !
oh, why can't we all
live at the mall ?
you know, i'm starting
to think
this whole metrosexual thing
isn't so great.
i know what you mean.
all my husband
ever does now
is look at himself
in the mirror.
he cares more about how
he looks than how i look.
i hope something happens soon to
put an end to this whole fad.
guys, you've done
a terrific job !
"queer eye for the
straight guy"
is our number one show !
what can i say,
we're fabulous !
you guys are
changing the world !
and tomorrow, we're
gonna have you make over
the president
of the united states !
oh my god, i think
i'm gonna faint !
( knock at door )
( mr. garrison )
room service.
what ?  we didn't order
any room service.
oh, well, the woman at
the front desk sent it up.
carol ?
i'll have to check on this,
excuse me a minute, fellas.
clear !
okay, mr. slave !
uh, jesus... christ.
well, crap,
that didn't work.
you better
shut up, craig !
everyone knows
it's true !
it is not !
is so !
craig !
behave yourself !
yeah, stanley what are you
fighting about ?
dad, craig's trying to say that
his dad can out-dress you !
what ?
son, that's a silly thing
to fight about.
yeah, everyone already knows
i dress better than randy.
oh really ?!
i mean, you do have the fashion
sense of a japanese woman.
( guys )
oooh !
please, girlfriend,
you look like some kind of
little orphan annie nightmare.
oh, no-- burn !
oh, stop it !
will you all
just stop it ?
look, you guys are
carrying this fad too far,
will you please stop
acting this way ?
you don't like us
being metrosexual ?
no !
well, you know
what i think ?
i think you're all
metrophobic !
yeah ! yeah !
what ?
we shouldn't be fighting
amongst ourselves,
we should be uniting against
metrophobes like these !
this is crazy !
crazy, different,
outcasts...
call us what you want,
but us metros are real
people, just like you.
you can metro-bash us all you
want, but we're here to stay !
yeah, mom, we're proud
of who we are.
that's right, proud !
you know what
i think, guys ?
i think we should have a
metrosexual pride parade.
great idea, eric--
raise metrosexual awareness !
we can make floats
and decorate them
with streamers
and flowers !
woo-hoo !
come on, fellas !
out of the malls
and into the streets !
( men chanting )
out of the malls
and into the streets !
out of the malls and
into the streets...
what the hell did
that show do to them ?
you sure you don't
want to press charges ?
that's okay, officer,
i think they learned
murder is wrong.
especially inthosepants.
look, guys, we're sorry
we tried to murder you,
but you have to stop
what you're doing !
are you crazy ?
we're the hottest thing
on tv !
but don't you see the price ?
you're selling out
your own kind.
look, us gays have
created a lifestyle,
a culture that is
uniquely ours.
if we keep trying to make
straight people into us,
well, we're gonna have
no identity left.
sorry charlie,
no sale.
but... but...
this doesn't make sense !
how can gay men do this
to their own people ?!
unless... you're not
gay at all.
( deep voices )
you just had to push it,
didn't you ?
just had to keep
asking questions.
now you know the truth.
they aren't gay ?
then what are they ?
for a thousand years
our kind have lived
beneath the earth's crust,
banished by man
in the kindling wars.
oh my god.
we are
the crab people !
aaaah !
jesus christ !
( chanting )
crab people...
crab people, crab people...
( chanting )
see now, where we have been
forced to live
for a thousand years !
but soon, we shall
rule the land above
and mankind
will be gone !
gone ?!
crab people, crab people...
crab people are too small and
weak to take man over by force,
and so we came up with
our perfect plan.
if you can't beat man--
change man !
i knew it.
i knew gay people would never
do this to their own kind !
when all the world
is metrosexual
the crab people shall
finally reign supreme !
crab people, crab people...
taste like crab,
talk like people.
crab people...
you'll never turn me
into a metrosexual !
i like being a dirty,
filthy little boy !
very well !
if we can't make you
into metrosexuals
then we will make you
into crab people !
take them !
( dance music )
♪ ... things just keep
getting better ♪
♪ you came
into my life... ♪
crab people...
♪ and my world never
looked so bright ♪
♪ it's true
you bring out the best in me ♪
♪ when you are around
when you are around... ♪
crab people...
♪ things just keep
getting better ♪♪
crab people...
tom, i'm standing
in south park, colorado
where the first annual
metrosexual pride parade
is under way !
( cheering )
we're here !
we're not queer !
but we're close !
get used to it !
we're here !
we're not queer !
but we're close...
this does it !
i can't take it anymore !
i should have
never wished for
a cleaner,
neater husband !
ladies, get your things.
i know what
we have to do.
whoa, look out !
oh my god !
it's on fire !
put it out !
i can't do anything--
these are brand-new pants !
the heat could really
damage our hair !
we better let the police
handle this !
are you crazy ?
i just had my
uniform pressed !
oh jesus, it's burning !
put it out !
jesus !
fire !
mr. president, it is such
an honor to make you over !
now, we've got to do
something with your hair.
and your nails are filthy,
let's get those clean.
this is gay gold !
stop them !
they're crab people !
they cannot see or
hear us, foolish man !
now stand by and watch
as your pitiful race
becomes helpless !
that is very good,
mr. president !
now, put on this
silk jacket.
no, mr. president,
don't do it !
help !
you bastards.
that looks great !
now, how about
some moisturizer.
there they are !
get 'em !
what ?
you turned our husbands into
whiny little wusses !
it's payback time !
oh my god !
what are they doing ?
no, nooo !
wha-- what have you done ?
we're sorry, but we didn't
have a choice.
you see, at first we liked
having our men
be clean and neat.
we thought that having them
use product in their hair
and wanting facials
would make them sexier.
but it doesn't.
that's right, even though my
stephen sicks me out sometimes,
it's his rugged, manly grossness
that i'm attracted to.
we're sorry, but we knew
the only answer
was to kill the
queer eye guys.
well, you're going to
jail for the--
wait a minute--
what is that ?
no, our evil plans.
nooo...
oh my god.
they were crab people.
yes !
they were trying to
systematically
make men into wusses so they
could take over the world !
mom !
kyle !
i should have known
they were crab people.
they tried this before
with "the jeffersons".
so now can you please change
your network's programming ?
yes.
yes, i think this
gay fad is over.
gentlemen,
back to studio 12.
we're gonna bring back
the latin fad !
hey,eses.
hey,jefe,
you want somecervesa?
kyle !
hey, ese, you wanna come
play catch with us ?
what ?
you want me to
hang out with you ?
yeah, it's cool, holmes.
no, dude,
it really isn't cool.
you all turned
your backs on me.
you're supposed to be my
best friends and you just,
you treated me
like nothing.
and now you all expect me
to just forget it all
and hang out with you again
like nothing happened ?
oh jesus, kyle, don't be such
a whiny little gay-wad.
come play catch
with us.
yeah, don't be
such a fag, dude !
god dammit.
captioning made possible by
comedy central
captioned by
soundwriters™