captioning made possible by
comedy central
? i'm going down
to south park ?
? gonna have
myself a time ?
? friendly faces
everywhere ?
? humble folks
without temptation ?
? going down
to south park ?
? gonna leave my
woes behind ?
? ample parking
day or night ?
? people spouting
"howdy neighbor" ?
? headin' on up
to south park ?
? gonna see
if i can't unwind ?
? ( muffled mumble
muffled mumble ) ?
? so come on down
to south park ?
? and meet some
friends of mine ??
and in conclusion,
the latino community
has provided america,
and indeed the entire world,
with innovations that
we would be lost without.
and that is my presentation
on the role of hispanics
in american technology,
thank you.
( cheers & applause )
okay, thank you,
kyle broflovski.
that was very good, kyle.
i think the latino
endowment council
was very happy with
your presentation.
looks like
you might win.
cool !
alright, students,
members of the school board.
our last speaker will
discuss the important role
of latinos in the arts.
here is--
eric cartman.
eric cartman ?!
( smattering of applause )
thank you.
the latino culture
has been very influential
on the arts in america.
but you don't
have to ask me.
you can ask my special guest,
ms. jennifer lopez !
no way.
ms. lopez,
come on out here !
hello !
oh, jesus christ !
my name is
jennifer lopez.
i eat tacos
and burritos.
ms. lopez, would you like to
talk about latinos in the arts ?
oh,si, si.
but first i would like to
put on my pretty dress.
oh, you mean this one ?
oh, si, si, si,
i like it very much.
there we go.
it's alright ?
it's alright.
that's a very
pretty dress.
it better be,
i am "hennifer hlopez" !
no, no, no,
you're jennifer lopez.
si, si,
hennifer hlopez.
no, no, j--
hj--
j--
jennifer lopez.
hennifer hlopez.
( amused chuckles )
ms. lopez, could you show
everyone your special example
of latino art ?
? don't be fooled
by all my money ?
? i still like to eat
tacos, honey ?
? so crispy on the outside
so super good and yummy ??
and that is my presentation
on latinos in the arts.
thank you.
( applause & cheers )
oh, man !
a $20 gift certificate
at the mall !
i can buy
whatever i want !
cultural diversity day
kicks ass !
it isn't fair.
i spent weeks preparing my
speech on latino culture !
hey, i spent weeks
preparing too, kyle.
no you didn't, asshole !
what you did was totally
stupid and racist !
and you only did it
to screw me over !
aww, i don't think kyle
likes you, ms. lopez.
awww, that makes me
muy triste.
ms. lopez,
do you like kyle ?
oh, si, si,
very much.
ms. lopez, would you like to
give kyle a kiss ?
oh, si, si, si.
my kisses
taste like tacos.
( kissing )
is nice ?
very nice.
he so handsome.
( kissing )
stop it !
hey, come on, guys !
we can use part of
my gift certificate
to buy food
at the food court !
woo-hoo !
mmm, tacos !
so yummy !
stop wasting the tacos
on your hand, cartman !
hey, ms. lopez
has to eat too !
she's not eating it,
it's just coming out
her backside !
when you eat a taco
it comes out your
backside too,chulo!
( kenny laughing )
look, look !
make your own
music video !
no, no, no !
we're not going into one of
those cheesy places, cartman !
i agree, those places
are stupid.
it's not stupid !
i need to make
music video !
look, we're not going
in there, so just--
wait, why the hell am i
talking to your hand ?
look, we're not going in there
so just knock it off !
hey, i'm on
your guys' side !
just wait one minute,
let me see how much it is !
god dammit.
welcome to
make your own video.
all set to
rock and roll ?
how much to
make a video ?
uh, well it's 9.95
for a three-minute tape.
ha !  we're not
paying 9.95 !
oh please !
come on, guys !
cartman, will you stop
this gayness ?
alright, alright,
here's $10 !
that's not
what i meant !
alright,
just come over here
and stand in front of
the green screen.
what kind of song
do you want ?
something hot
and spicy !
( rockabilly music )
spicier.
( mariachi music )
spicier !
( salsa music )
burrito !
taco, taco !
burrito and taco !
? don't think just because
i gotta lot of money ?
? i won't give you
taco-flavored kisses, honey ?
? i'll fulfill
all your wishes ?
? with my
taco-flavored kisses ?
taco, taco !
burrito, burrito !
y'know, i've seen a lot of
videos here at the mall
and that was
by far the best !
oh,gracias, michael.
hey, i've got a friend
who's interning
at a big record label
in l.a.
i'll send a copy
on to him
and maybe he'll get
the bigwigs to see it !
oh, gracias,
michael !
gracias !
can we go now,
please ?
yeah, i wanna leave !
stop it, cartman !
what ?
? fulfill all your wishes
with my taco-flavored kisses ?
taco, taco !
she's fantastic !
who is she ?
believe it or not, her
name is jennifer lopez.
that makes sense,
she reminds me of j-lo.
yeah, but she's younger
and spicier !
taco, taco !
burrito, burrito !
i don't think j-lo
would like it very much
if we signed
this new girl.
no, you're right.
we're gonna
have to fire j-lo.
( phone rings )
hello ?
b.h.i.records ?
oh, it's for you,
ms. lopez.
oh oh,
si si si.
'allo !
what do they want ?
just a second,
i'm trying to hear.
it's alright ?
it's alright.
yes, yes, this is
ms. lopez.
uh-huh.
( gasps )
aaaahh !!
what, what ?
oh my god,
i can't believe it !
hello ?
you still there ?
they want to sign me to
the record company !
you want to sign
ms. lopez ?
oh my god,
it's happening for me !
yes, yes, we can record
an album next week !
sure we can
write 10 songs !
we'll start tonight !
we're gonna
be rich !
we're gonna be famous !
come on, we've gotta get
to work on some songs !
there, that's three more songs
we've written already !
your style of music
is so easy
it doesn't require
any thought at all !
oh, si si si.
okay, ms. lopez,
time to go to sleep.
oh, i'm so sleepy.
goodnight, ms. lopez, tomorrow
is gonna be a great day.
a great day tomorrow...
tomorrow...
kyle, you were wrong,
we did get a record deal !
you were wrong, kyle !
? nya-nya nya-nya
nyaaa nya ?
? ha-ha ha ha ha
haaa ha ?
( crying )
? nya nya nya nya
nyaaaa nya ?
? ha ha ha ha
haaaaa ha ?
awesome, yesss !
ohh...
ms. lopez !
jennifer, right here !
we love you, jennifer,
over here !
we love you, jennifer !
ahh...
ah, ms. lopez,
come on in !
yo, make it quick,
i got a video shoot at two
and a script reading
at five.
yes, well, ms. lopez,
we regret to inform you that,
uh, we're dropping you
from the label.
what ?!
oh, no, you di'nt !
we want to thank you for
all your hard work and--
"talent".
you can't drop me !
i'm jennifer lopez !
how can you dropme?!
well, a very talented,
younger singer
has come to our attention
and the truth
of the matter is
her name happens to be
jennifer lopez as well,
and we really can't have
two here at b.h.i. records.
who the hell is this
other jennifer lopez ?!
where is she come from ?!
well, she lives in
south park, colorado now,
but i believe she's originally
from mexico just like you.
i don't come from
no mexico !
i'm "puera rican" !
whatever, look,
it's nothing personal,
we just think
you need to move on.
and you're a
mean-spirited bitch
who spits on people
who aren't rich and famous.
and sources say that the new
film will star ben affleck !
ha ha ha,
that's me.
how'd it go, baby ?
terrible, ben !
some girl in colorado
is trying to become
the new jennifer lopez !
( dog yips )
shut up !
what ?!
who could replace you ?
yo driver !
stupid driver !
yes, ma'am,
where to ?
take me to south park,
colorado !
i'm gonna
kill that bitch !
( school bell rings )
hey everybody,
listen up !
i've got something
to tell kyle !
what ?
? ha ha ha ha
haaa ha ?
? ha ha ha,
ha ha ha ?
? ha ha ha ha
what are you
gloating about ?
oh, i'm not gloating,
i just got a little call
from a record company
in los angeles
and they want ms. lopez to
record an album next week.
wow !
really ?
no !
yeah, looks like
i'm gonna be rich.
and famous.
okay, children,
let's take our seats.
if you'll
remember yesterday
we were discussing
state capitals--
hey !
a big limousine just pulled up
in front of the school !
butters, will you pay
attention, please ?
holy smokes !
it's jennifer lopez !
jennifer lopez ?
yes ?
holy geez wow,
there's ben affleck too !
wow, cool !
will you kids
shut up ?
jennifer lopez and
ben affleck are not--
oh my god, that's
jennifer lopez and ben affleck !
oh jesus, will you
look at those boots ?
well, what are we
waiting for ?
let's get outside !
woo hoo !
is it true
jennifer lopez is here ?
here she comes,
here she comes !
okay, what smart mouth
little punk-ass bitch
has been saying they're
the new jennifer lopez, huh ?
j-lo can we get a picture
of you with the kids ?
no, shut up !
if i find the ho who think
she's taking my career from me,
i'm gonna wring her
pretty little neck !
so, nobody wants to
fess up, huh ?
to scared to talk !
you better
remember, bitch,
that i'll come and
take you down
if you ever say
anything again !
( ms. lopez )
you can suck my
culo, chica!
who was that ?!
you got a problem ?
not me !
then who ?
hola,bitchola !
what the hell is that ?
my name is
hennifer hlopez
and i like tacos
and burritos.
that ?  that's what
replaced me ?
i'm sure it was
just a mistake.
the only mistake was
when this ghetto trash
got signed
in the first place !
shut your
god damn mouth !
you ( bleeping )
smart-ass !
who do you think
you are ?
nobody !
i am hennifer hlopez !
i eat tacos
and burritos !
( bleep ) you !
aaagh !
i'm sorry !
i'll stop, i'll stop !
you better stop !
i will !
come on, jenny,
let's go.
wow, ben affleck !
we should be getting
back to the--
( harp strumming )
( angelic choir singing )
don't you forget what'll
happen to you, ho !
come on, benny !
well, there you go,
fat-ass.
i hope you learned
your lesson.
yeah, i sure did.
i don't think i should
record that album now.
good.
or maybe i should !
aw, god dammit !
oh, no no no no,
ms. lopez !
oh, si si si, senor !
that does it,
i'm out.
oh, where are you
going, kyle ?
come give me kisses !
alright, ms. lopez,
let's take it from the top.
? baby let's make a run
for the border ?
? i've got a hunger
only tacos can stop ?
? i know exactly
what i'll order ?
? three tacos, two tostadas
and a soda pop ?
gentlemen, we have
ourselves a hit.
? i need to make a run
for the border ?
? if you pay
i'll take off my top ?
? do you remember
what i want to order ? ?
? three tacos, two tostadas
and a soda pop ?
? yeah, and don't forget
the hot sauce, chulo ??
( ms. lopez )
? don't think just because
i got money ?
? i won't still give you
taco-flavored kisses, honey ?
? i'm gonna fulfill
all your sexy wishes ?
? and give you lots of
taco-flavored kisses ?
what the hell
are you doing ?
i am practicing
my dancing !
look, we spent all night
at the recording studio,
now it's time to sleep !
dancing !
sleep !
slee-eep.
dan-cing.
mom !!!
what's the matter,
sweetie ?
ms. lopez
won't go to sleep !
( knock )
yes ?
hey, i was wondering if
i could talk to ms. lopez.
she's not here
right now.
ben, is that
my darling ben ?
jenny ?
yes, jenny, it's me !
where are you ?
please,
i have to see her !
( sighs )
ben !
oh, you brought me
rrrroses !
jenny.
aw, jenny, i just can't stop
thinking about you.
i can't stop thinking
about you either, ben !
i've been meaning to write
a song or a poem,
but i have no talent.
i know, my darling,
that's okay !
will you just take a ride
with me in my awesome car ?
oh, ben,
i would love to !
no !
excuse me
one second, ben.
don't you ruin this
opportunity for me.
how can you stand in
the way of this ?
i'm not going out
in his car.
i'm not gonna let you blow
this one chance i got.
i don't care, i'm supposed to
sit here and do my homework.
( both yelling )
fine, fine, fine !
okay, ben, let's go !
oh ben, i am so happy.
the cool breeze
blowing through my hair
in your sexy automobile.
let's spend the
whole day together !
? oh ben
you are so perfect ?
? so spectacularrr
in every way ?
? you bring light
into my life, ben ?
? you almost make me forget
all about tacos ?
? ooh tacos so good ?
? in my tummy yummy yummy
gimme more ?
? i love you, ben ?
? you almost make me
forget about tacos ??
jenny, i have to
tell you something.
i... i think i love you.
oh, i love you
too, ben !
but...
but what ?
but what if you still have
feelings for the slut
with the large ass ?
i still care for her,
maybe i always will.
but, you just have
so much more going on.
up here.
oh, ben, ben...
jenny,
can i kiss you ?
no !
yes, oh yes, ben,
kiss me !
aw, god dammit !
aw !
awwww, dude !
just like tacos.
taco-flavored kisses
for my ben.
you're so hot, baby.
i make you hot, ben ?
mmm, yeah.
oh jenny.
oh jenny !
oh god, jenny !
oh ben,
my darling !
aw, sick !
aw, that's it,
we're leaving now !
but i love her !
ben !
jenny !
jenny, i'll call you !
i love you, ben !
? ooh baby baby,
can i have your tacos ? ?
? those tacos
sure look good ?
? i'm just jenny
from the hood ?
? ooh, can i have
your tacos,por fa-- ?
stop, stop !
what the hell
is wrong with you ?!
you chulos can't even
keep a beat !
i deserve better than this,
i am hennifer hlopez !
where is my water ?!
notevian!
pelligrino,
you stupid bitch !
uh, that's fine,
ms. lopez.
look, it's been
a long night,
why don't we pick it up
in the morning.
fine my ass, chulo !
i'll tell you
when it's fine !
stupid idiots !
how am i supposed to make
an album with those chulos ?
you little snot nose !
you ruined my career and now
you're trying to steal my man ?
oh, crap.
you better stay away
from him !
ow !  ow !
oh jesus !
aaagh !
your son's hand has
a hairline fracture
and two dislocated
fingers.
oh, dear !
but i'm more concerned
about his state of mind.
your son appears to be
completely insane.
ohhh... ohh...
i told you
this would happen.
oh, hello guys.
cartman, you need to stop
this stupid little game
you're playing.
oh kyle,
why you no like me ?
kyle is right,
ms. lopez.
from now on, we're staying
away from ben affleck !
i hate you.
come on, sweetie,
doctor says you need to
get home and
get lots of rest.
( rooster crowing )
ah !
mom !!
what is it, sweetie ?
ben affleck is naked
in my bed !
ooh, looks like
the tooth fairy
was extra happy
with you !
buenos dias,my love !
good morning, baby.
you have to get
out of here !
jennifer lopez is gonna
kick my ass again !
he's not going
anywhere !
ben and i were up all night
making love !
what ?
aw-- awww !
ben affleck spooge !
should we tell him
the news ?
what news ?
i think we should
tell him.
it's alright ?
it's alright.
we're getting
married !
oh, balls !
( doorbell rings )
come in.
( ring )
come in !!
guys, i need
to talk to you.
what's the matter ?
i can't handle it
anymore.
all the fame and the
ben affleck spooge--
i just can't go on
living with ms. lopez.
so stop doing it.
stop doing what ?
you know god damn well what,
now get out of here !
please, you guys,
it's like i can't even
have a moment to
myself anymore.
see ?
( gasping, coughing )
don't you dare ever do
that to me again !
oh, stop it, cartman, your hand
doesn't need to breathe !
you try being in an oven mitt
for two hours !
i can see
your lips moving !
i can see your lips
moving too,culo!
see ?
i just saw your lips move !
look, i'm just asking
you guys for help.
will you please help me
with ms. lopez ?
what's she doing ?
come here !
you're not actually buying
this crap are you ?
i dunno-- maybe
he can't help it.
look, he knows full well
what he's doing.
and he's just waiting for us
to buy into it,
and then he'll laugh and
point in our faces and say,
"ha, ha, i got you guys
to believe me !
you guys are stupid !"
dude, do you really think
he would go through all this
just to make us
look dumb ?
yes, dude !
cartman, we've decided
that if you can be mature
and admit to everyone
that you've gotten yourself
into this mess,
then we'll help you.
okay, okay.
i know that i control
everything ms. lopez does.
oh, no, you don't !
quiet, ms. lopez !
out !
guys !
there you are, jenny !
i've been looking all over
for you, baby !
jenny ?
ms. lopez, you were due in
the studio two hours ago !
come on !
so you're getting
married, huh ?
( chainsaw revs )
aaagh !
don't you hurt her !
we'll sue you !
oh, jesus.
( chainsaw revving )
aaaagh !
( police siren )
freeze, leaf-blower !
arrest that woman !
she wants to kill
one of our artists !
alright, you're going
downtown, bean-breath !
jenny !
oh, i thought i was
going to lose you !
let's run away and
get married tonight !
hey, she can't get
married tonight,
she has a recording
session !
our love is like rain !
that's what you said
about me, asshole !
quiet !
get her
out of here !
( bleep ) you !
shut up,
picante-pants !
everyone be quiet !!
i-- i'm not who
you think i am.
you're not ?
no, it was all a lie,
a lie i cannot
continue anymore--
i'm not hennifer hlopez.
i am...
( cartman )
mitch conner.
( all gasp )
who's mitch conner ?
just your run-of-the-mill
con man.
i've been moving from
town to town,
scamming people
since i was 15.
but i'm tired
of running.
oh, no.
no no no no no !
i've been a cheat
all my life.
and now i've ruined
a singer's career,
lost a record company
millions
and cost this little boy
his precious time.
stop-it !
mostly, i'm sorry
to you, ben.
i'm sorry i played tiddlywinks
with your heart.
( sobbing )
but it's over now.
the cyanide pill i took should
be taking effect very soon.
hmm, looks like the sun
is going down.
i wonder...
will i dream ?
( wailing )
well, looks like mitch conner
has cashed in his last chips.
dude, who the hell
is mitch conner ?
i don't know, kyle,
alright ?
look, i don't care
what you guys believe,
but with all the crazy stuff
that goes on in this town
isn't it possible,
just possible,
that something i don't
understand happened here ?
( sighs )
alright.  alright,
i guess it's possible.
? ha ha ha ha
haaaa ha ?
? i got you kind-a
i got you kind-a ?
okay, ms. lopez, over here
we have the topping station.
this is where all your cheeses
and lettuce will go on.
ow !
look out, muffin head !
uh, look, ms. lopez,
if you're going to be a member
of thela tacofamily,
you're gonna have to learn
to get along with people.
get a what wif' who ?!
why don't you start
chopping those onions
and i'll come check on you
a little later.
this is bull ( bleep ) !
how the ( bleep ) did i end up
working at a la taco ?
i had six platinum records
and i starred in five
hollywood movies !
yeah... me too.
? oh ben
you are so perfect ?
? so spectacularrr
in every way ?
? you bring light
into my life, ben ?
? you almost make me forget
all about tacos ?
? ooh tacos so good ?
? in my tummy yummy yummy
gimme more ?
? i love you, ben ?
? you almost make me
forget about tacos ??