captioning made possible by
comedy central
? i'm going down
to south park ?
? gonna have
myself a time ?
? friendly faces
everywhere ?
? humble folks
without temptation ?
? going down
to south park ?
? gonna leave my
woes behind ?
? ample parking
day or night ?
? people spouting
"howdy neighbor" ?
? headin' on up
to south park ?
? gonna see
if i can't unwind ?
? ( muffled mumble
muffled mumble ) ?
? so come on down
to south park ?
? and meet some
friends of mine ??
( school bell rings )
okay, good,
children, good.
remember to
feel the clay.
be one with the clay.
nice, uh-huh.
( all mischivously giggling )
put more clay
on the balls.
boys, what is that ?
a reindeer ?
y'know, i've had it.
you four boys never take
art class seriously !
what a crime.
you think art
is not important ?
well, art's just kinda...
for gaywads.
i love art class !
see ?
do you think
this is funny ?
do you think this is
funny, huh ?!
( snickering )
well, you four can just
spend your afternoon
after school here,
making new pottery !
you can't do that !
i certainly can,
i'm your teacher.
you're an art teacher !
make it two hours.
mrs. streibel thinks
she's so cool !
how dare she talk to us
like that !
yeah, she's a...
( garbled )
we can't let her
get away with this.
i think tonight we need
to something drastic.
like what ?
like find out where
mrs. streibel lives.
and go over there.
and...
t.p. her house.
yeah !
t.p. her house ?
toilet paper-- cover her
house in toilet paper.
oh.
what's the matter, kyle,
you chicken ?
bawk bawk,
bawk bawk bawk.
ahh !
quiet, boys !
this isn't play time,
you're being punished !
fine.
but we'll have the last laugh
tonight, art whore.
yeah, payback time,
you ugly skank.
you think
that's enough ?
should be fine.
don't you guys think this is
a little suspicious.
we should buy something else
so it doesn't look obvious.
okay.
here we go,
a pack of chewing gum.
hello boys, find
everything you need ?
yup, all set.
okay, let's see here,
toilet paper.
so, what are you kids
up to tonight ?
oh, we're just gonna
watch some tv,
maybe play a board game.
nice relaxing
night at home, huh ?
toilet paper,
toilet paper.
and toilet paper.
hey, hey--
now you kids be careful
with this chewing gum.
don't go sticking it
under tables.
okay.
okay, toilet paper,
toilet paper.
y'know, son, i remember you
coming in last week
and buying this much
toilet paper.
oh, yeah,
that's right.
toilet paper,
toilet paper.
you t.p.'d a house
last week, cartman ?
no, last thursday night
was fajitas night.
oh.
aw.
is this
the right house ?
it's the right address.
wait, look there !
there's mrs. streibel !
this is the place !
( kyle )
oh wait, wait,
there's kids inside.
so ?
so i'm not t.p.'ing a house
with kids inside it.
kyle, we all
agreed to do this.
we didn't say nothin' about
no kids, man !
kyle, you're being
an asshole.
let's do this thing
and get out of here.
here's what i think
of your art class,
you god damn bitch !
( kenny )
yeah, ---k you !
come on, let's go !
what have we done ?
let's go, kyle !
( panting )
we're in trouble.
we're in
so much trouble !
oh man,
that was so awesome !
how can you say that ?
did you see what we did
to their house ?
it'll take them days
to clean that up !
who cares ?
well, you don't,
because you're an uncaring
asshole, cartman !
me ?
there's toilet paper
on your hands too, kyle.
cartman's right, kyle.
we're all in this
together.
no, no.
no !
( scream )
honey, what is it ?
oh, jesus, no,
our house !
( both crying )
mommy !
why ?!
ah !
oh god.
hey, did you guys hear what
happened last night ?
mrs. streibel's house got
covered with toilet paper.
yeah, they say it's gonna take
three weeks to get it all down.
yeah, well, ol' mrs. streibel
probably had it coming to her.
i don't know.
i don't think anybody deserves
that kind of brutality.
well, i understand the people
who did it weren't caught,
so looks like nobody will
ever know the geniuses
who masterminded
that perfect crime.
( bell rings )
okay, children,
let's take our seats.
oh, uh-- stan, kyle,
eric and kenny--
the counselor wants to see you
in his office now.
damn !
oh god !
how the hell did they
find out it was us
that t.p.'d that house ?
will you relax, kyle ?
they've got
nothing on us.
as long as we all stick to
our story we'll be fine.
we better go over our story
again so we don't screw it up.
okay, last night all four of us
were at the bowling alley
until about 7:30, at which time
we noticed ally sheedy,
the goth chick from
"the breakfast club",
was bowling in the
lane next to us
and we asked for her autograph,
but she didn't have a pen
so we followed her
out to her car,
but on the way we were accosted
by five scientologists
who wanted to give us all
personality tests
which were administered
at the scientology center
in denver until 10:45,
at which time we accidentally
boarded the wrong bus home
and ended up in
rancho de fritas rejos,
south of castle rock,
and finally got a ride
home with a man
who was missing his left index
finger named gary bushwell,
arriving home at 11:46.
i'm confused.
did ally sheedy take
the personality test ?
yes, dude !
kyle, it's very simple.
we followed ally sheedy out
to her car, but on the way
we were accosted by
five scientologists
who wanted to give us all
personality tests
which were administered
at the scientology center
in denver until 10:45,
at which time
we accidentally boarded
the wrong bus home
and ended up in
rancho de fritas rejos,
south of castle rock,
and finally got
a ride home with a man
who was missing his left index
finger named gary bushewell,
arriving home at 11:46.
you got it ?!
i... i can't.
oh, for christ's sake !
look, kyle, just let cartman
do all the talking, okay ?
he's better at being
in trouble than anybody.
thank you, stan.
shh, shh-- here they come,
here they come.
and so i said, "that's
a terrific joke, wendy,
tell us another one !"
oh hello, mr. mackey are you
ready to see us now ?
we're gonna talk to you
one at a time, boys, m'kay.
kenny, will you step
into my office, please ?
me ?
come on, kenny,
let's go, m'kay.
touche, mr.mackey,
touche.
why are they doing us
one at a time ?
they want to see if
we mix the story up.
and see if somebody will
rat out the other three
for a better deal.
i can get
a better deal ?
kyle, so help me god,
if you jew us out on this one
i will ( bleeping ) kill you !
there we go, that should be
about the last of it.
( humming )
excuse me, uh,
what are you doing ?
crime scene investigation.
there are several
footprints in the snow--
perhaps more than one
perpetrator ?
uh, look,
we really don't want to
make a big deal
out of this.
is that the
toilet paper there ?
i'll need to take
those bags as evidence.
look, it's just not
that big a deal.
i mean, i toilet-papered houses
myself when i was a kid.
you ?!
so where were you
last night at around nine ?
i was here !
aha !  got you !
officer, why would i
t.p. my own house ?
insurance ?
it wasn't me, okay ?
now if you
don't mind
i just want to get my yard
back to normal.
now you listen to me--
whoever t.p.'d your house
is still out there
roaming the streets.
it's only a matter of time
before another house
and another family
is victimized !
i have to stop that
from happening.
you really have nothing
better to do, do you ?
no, i do not.
no, no.
no !
( scream )
oh, jesus, no,
our house !
mommy !
why, why ?!
why ?!
( sobbing )
oh god !
i have to
tell the truth !
mom !!
( panting )
hello, kyle.
going somewhere ?
i was...
i was just going to
get a drink of water.
no need-- i have one
for you right here.
oh, okay, thanks.
is there anything else
i can get for you ?
no, i'll just...
be going back to bed now.
you do that.
good night, kyle.
josh myers t.p.'d over 600
houses in less than a year.
he's a real monster.
i just need to
talk to someone
who knows how
toilet-paperers think.
just remember:
he'd toilet paper you
in a second
if he had the chance.
he's the last cell
on your left.
hello, josh, my name is
officer barbrady,
i'm with the
south park police.
( "hannibal lecter" voice )
that's a terrible cologne
you're wearing, officer,
you should try something
more... casual.
i was hoping you could help me
solve a toilet papering case.
and why would i do that ?
because i'm such a
charming fella ?
please, i need your help,
what would you want in return ?
due to the harsh nature
of my crimes
they don't allow me to have
toilet paper in my cell.
you can imagine how
bothersome that becomes.
you know i can't give you
toilet paper, josh.
no, but it was worth
a try, wasn't it ?
tell me something,
officer,
why is it that you police
such a small town ?
you must've had
larger inspirations.
what happened to those
big city dreams ?
wul, that's kinda
personal.
quid pro quo, officer.
tell me what
i want to know,
and i'll help you catch whoever
toilet-papered that house.
look, kid, i have
very little time to catch
whoever toilet-papered
that house.
tell me what you know.
are those the
crime scene photos ?
let me see them.
yes, yes.
not bad work,
not bad at all.
these toilet-paperers
are professionals--
at least,
one of them is.
so you think there was
more than one-- why ?
tellmesomething first.
when you went to the academy,
you had something to prove--
you wanted to
protect and serve,
but mostly you just
wanted to protect, yourself.
who were you protecting yourself
from, officer barbrady ?
alright, alright !
my uncle charles used to
hit me with a belt !
waaah !
thank you.
your toilet-paperers
are most likely males
between the ages of eight and
ten, and probably virgins.
parents notice that much
toilet paper missing
so they would've had to
have bought it themselves.
find out where the toilet paper
came from, officer,
and you just might
catch your man.
( bell rings )
stan, kenny-- can i talk
to you guys for a second ?
i think we have the counselor
and the principal fooled,
but we need to
talk about kyle.
what about him ?
come on, you know !
i think so too.
he's losing it.
he's gonna crack.
kyle can't take the heat
and he's gonna sing
like a canary.
then we're all gonna take
the fall for what we did.
hey fellas !
butters.
( sniffs )
( clears throat )
look, you guys, all it takes
is for one of us crack.
and we all know who
the weakest link is.
so what should we do ?
we have no choice--
we have to kill kyle.
dude, we're not
killing kyle !
yeah !
why not ?!
kyle's not gonna say
anything, alright ?
he almost spilled the beans
in the counselor's office.
he can't even keep
the story straight !
i'm telling you guys,
he's weak.
he's weak, and he'll be
the end of us all.
you wanted to see me,
officer barbrady ?
yes, thanks for coming,
mr.bell.
a house was t.p.'d
in south park
and i need to see if you can
identify the toilet paper
i recovered
from the scene.
i'm sorry i have to
do this.
( gagging )
oh my god.
is this toilet paper
from your store ?
it's... difficult to tell,
it's so decayed.
i--
wait a minute, yes.
yes, i recognize the
floral pattern now.
positive i.d.
on the toilet paper.
who would do this
to toilet paper, who ?
mr. bell, do you remember
anyone suspicious
buying toilet paper
in the last few days ?
suspicious like how ?
well, like someone
who was black or mexican
or middle eastern ?
no, the only mexican guy
i recall
bought toaster tarts
and chips.
and we don't allow middle
eastern people in the store.
oh my god.
bleahhhh !
what's this
all about, cartman ?
i just wanted to see how
you're doing, kyle.
why don't we go out for
a little boat ride ?
a boat ride ?
i just thought we should find
a private place to talk.
well, okay.
could you help me put this
cement block and chain
into the boat ?
okay, let's go.
so how are things, kyle ?
terrible.
every time i close my eyes
i see the house we t.p.'d.
i see the tears
of our art teacher
and hear the screams
of her daughters.
and you feel like
you have to confess.
i don't know what to do.
part of me feels like
i have to end it all now,
tell people what happened.
y'know, i never noticed how
beautiful this pond was before.
so calm.
the world can
be like that--
so calm on the outside.
as if nothing bad
ever happens.
( tap )
ow !
what the hell are you
doing, cartman ?
i'm killing you.
but unfortunately i could
only afford a whiffle bat,
so it's gonna take a while.
cartman !
don't fight it, kyle,
it will only take longer.
just slip into
sweet unconsciousness.
you wanna kill me ?
fine !
i can't live like this
anymore !
go ahead !
do it !
won't be long now, kyle.
josh, i need more help.
the answer's right in front of
you, but you can't see it.
how do you mean ?
tell me, the toilet paper,
was it quilted ?
yes.
single sheet ?
no, two-ply.
what ?  what does that
tell you ?
why does one toilet paper
a house, officer ?
to get revenge.
no, that is
incidental.
your toilet-paperers
wanted to transform
the art teacher's house,
thus transforming her
entire occupation.
what do you mean ?
your uncle who hit you
with a belt--
was he a large man ?
i don't have time
for this, kid.
did he stink like beer when
he came home from work,
( southern accent )
all tired from playin'
down at the pool house ?
alright, alright !
my dad dressed me up like a
little girl on poker nights
and made me sit on
all my uncles laps !
( sobs )
whoa.
ah, oh--
thank you.
your toilet-paperers
are most likely students
in the art teachers class,
students who aren't
very good at art.
of course !
one of her students !
fly along now,
officer barbrady,
you've got some
arrests to make.
fly fly fly...
fly fly fly.
josh, were you doing
the silly voice
for the policeman again ?
( normal voice )
no, sir.
cartman, what are you
doing ?
i'm getting rid of
our problem !
kyle will be dead
in a matter of hours.
you don't have to kill
kyle, dude,
the police made an arrest,
and the person confessed !
they did ?
they say they've got
the guy that did it
down at the
police station !
who confessed ?
that doesn't
make any sense !
but can i still
kill kyle ?
hello boys,
how are you ?
we heard that you
have the person
who t.p.'d the art teacher's
house-- is that true ?
it sure is !
uh, could we see them--
him, her ?
right over here.
yeah, we interrogated the
suspect for over 40 hours,
then he finally cracked.
hey fellas !
butters ?
yup, i'm in jail.
you confessed ?
uh-huh, they said i t.p.'d
the art teacher's house.
i don't seem to remember it,
but they're pretty sure
it was me.
i just can't get my behavior
under control !
his parents are on
their way down now.
yeah and boy are they
gonna let me have it !
just wait 'til my father
gets here !
you guys, we can't
let him do this.
what are you
talking about ?
this is a gift
from god !
an early easter present
all wrapped up
with a pretty ribbon from
jesus christ himself !
i'm just a little asshole
is what i am.
when god made me,
he must a not been payin'
very close attention
'cause i turned out wrong,
just plain wrong !
officer barbrady, butters
didn't t.p. that house.
why do you say that ?
because it was--
whiffle ball anyone ?
anyone care for a nice game
of whiffle ball ?
y'know, it's not my parents
i'm worried about,
it's my girlfriend, carrie.
she lives in michigan,
but when she finds out
about this,
woo smokies, is she
gonna be sore !
she might even
break up with me.
and it would serve me
right, too !
alright boys,
visiting time is over.
thanks for stopping by.
you see guys, it all
worked itself out !
ta dao !
how do like me now ?
feel a little
silly now, kyle ?
ta dao !
how you like me now !
i still feel bad,
cartman !
what ?
how-- how can you
feel bad ?
somebody else is gonna
pay for our crime !
yeah, that makes it
even worse.
bu-- eh--
kyle, you don't
seem to understand.
we're not gonna get
punished for this, ever !
i know.
so-- so how can you
feel bad ?
he feels guilty for doing it
and for letting someone
else pay for it.
but he's not gonna
get in trouble.
it doesn't matter if you
get in trouble or not,
you can still feel bad.
i think you're right, kyle,
maybe we should confess.
yeah, maybe so.
wha-- dah---
you guys--
there's nothing
to feel bad about,
we're off scot-free !
we feel bad for
otherpeople.
for oth--
ahh, ow.
is it that you think you might
get in trouble later ?
tomorrow in school, we'll all
tell the art teacher it was us
and let her
decide what to do.
and cartman, if you have any
thread of a conscience at all,
you'll do the same.
eh-- eh, eh--
freakin' weirdos, man.
well, well, well, i had to
see it to believe it !
hi, dad.
don't you "hi dad" me !
look at you, standing behind
prison bars, again !
yeah.
what fibs have you been telling
this policeman, butters ?
you know damn well you didn't
toilet paper that house !
huh ?
butters was with us
all night, officer barbrady.
butters, what have we
told you about
confessing to crimes
you didn't commit ?
we have had it, mister !
well, he kept
accusing me for hours
and then he shot me up
with sodium pentathol.
and that's your excuse ?
looks like i made
a mistake.
i guess i better
let you out now.
just wait til we get you home,
you little fibber !
officer, can i stay
in jail, please ?
come you guys, hurry !
what is it, cartman ?
it's over this way,
come on !
so how are things, guys ?
cartman, we're confessing
tomorrow at school,
and that's final.
i'm afraid i can't
let that happen.
you can't kill all three
of us, cartman.
can't i ?
excuse me, everyone !
i have someone with me
who can tell us all
who toilet-papered
the art teacher's house.
josh insisted he be able
to tell you the names
of the toilet-paperers
in person.
uh, that's nice,
officer barbrady,
but we actually
don't need to know--
hold it !
principal victoria, mr.mackey,
mrs. streibel.
we have something
we need to tell you.
alright, will you people stop
barging into my office please ?
what's the matter,
principal victoria,
was your mother abusive ?
did she spank your thighs
with cold cuts
and stick umbrellas
up your ass ?
get him out of here !
uh, policeman brown, will you
take josh outside, please ?
ooh, policeman brown,
never quite made officer,
why is that, policeman brown ?
we have to confess that
we were the ones--
it's too late, boys, m'kay.
we already know
everything.
you do ?  how ?
hi guys.
cartman ?!
i told them everything,
you guys, it's over.
luckily for us, one of you
had enough of a conscience
to come forward.
my consciousness just
caught up with me.
that's not fair !
you all get two weeks
of detention,
except for eric, who gets
one week for being brave.
but he's lying !
he's doesn't have
a conscience !
well, i guess my
work here is done.
after all this, i'm gonna
need a long vacation.
this was supposed
to be my story !
my coming to terms with
a guilty conscience !
this isn't fair !
okay, josh, time to go
back to the--
oh, no !
he was too fast
for me.
he ran out the door.
couldn't you have
gone after him ?
well, i'm covered in
toilet paper, i'd look silly.
( bell rings )
welcome to detention.
you will be here
until 5:00
so make good study use
of your time, m'kay.
oof, two weeks of this.
yeah, but i have to say
i feel a lot better now.
i know what
you mean, kyle.
i realize now
that even though
you might not get caught
doing something bad
you can still
get caught later.
oh, jesus.
i didn't feel bad before,
but now i feel just terrible.
you just feel bad for yourself
that you're in detention !
right.
i guess
i learned that--
oh, stop it, cartman,
you didn't learn anything !
not a god damn thing !
hmm.
( phone rings )
police station !
hello,
officer barbrady.
josh ?
josh, where are you ?
i'm afraid that
giving away my location
might be harmful
to my freedom, officer.
i just wanted to thank you
for helping me get out of
that dingy cell.
josh, you have to go back
to juvenile hall.
you only have
a three-week sentence !
sorry, officer, gotta run.
there's something
i've been meaning to do
for quite some time, ciao.
captioning made possible by
comedy central
captioned by
soundwriters?