captioning made possible by
comedy central
♪ i'm going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna have
myself a time ♪
♪ friendly faces
everywhere ♪
♪ humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna leave my
woes behind ♪
♪ ample parking
day or night ♪
♪ people spouting
"howdy neighbor" ♪
♪ headin' on up
to south park ♪
♪ gonna see
if i can't unwind ♪
♪ ( muffled mumble
muffled mumble ) ♪
♪ so come on down
to south park ♪
♪ and meet some
friends of mine ♪♪
( children chattering )
( stan )
all right, you guys,
it's first down.
i'll hike the ball
on the third set hut.
kyle and cartman
do deep post outs.
kenny run a slant up the middle,
butters be ready for the screen.
right, what are
we playing again ?
football.
got it.
okay, 23 !
blue, 23 !
set hut, set hut !
wendy breaks up.
what ?
wendy breaks up
with you.
whoa, whoa, wait a minute !
what did i do wrong ?!
i haven't even
talked to wendy for weeks !
she just doesn't want to be
with you anymore.
she said she still
wants to be friends.
whatever, bebe,
like stan really cares.
just get outta our football game
you stupid skank !
( bleep ) you, fat ass !
you guys are assholes !
oh yeah, well, at least
wehaveassholes,
you dumb girl !
yeah, that's right !
god, you're so stupid !
what a whore.
( kyle )
yeah, like stan gives a crap
if wendy breaks up.
♪ don't know what you got
'til it's gone... ♪
stan ?
come on, stan,
it's first down still.
♪ now i know what i've
got it's just this song ♪
♪ and it ain't easy
to get back takes so long ♪
♪ don't know what
you got 'til it's gone ♪♪
( school bell ringing )
kyle, will you go talk
to wendy for me ?
why ?
'cause i need to know
why she broke up.
aw, dude, come on,
i gotta do my science homework.
dude, please, i might still have
a chance to make things work !
please,
just go talk to her !
god damn it.
wendy, stan wants to know
why you break up.
look, stan is really nice,
i just don't wanna be boyfriend
and girlfriend anymore.
i've been wanting
to break up for a while,
but it's nothing
against him.
'kay.
she says she's been wanting
to break up for a while,
and it's
nothing against you.
what ?!
that's no answer !
go tell her to be more
direct with me !
no, dude, i'm out.
go talk to her yourself !
be poetic !
kyle, this is my life !
jimmy !
hey, stan.
jimmy, will you go talk
to wendy for me ?
for w-w-what ?
just go talk to her
and be poetic.
tell her she's my muse,
no, tell her-- tell her--
she's a continuing source
inspiration to me.
she's what ?
she's a continuing source
of inspiration to me.
okay...
hey wen-- hey-- wendy ?
yeah ?
stan says you're a cont-
you're a cont...
stan says you're
a cont-cont-cont--
well, tell stan
to ( bleep ) off !
you're a cont-- continuing
source of inspiration to him.
well ?
she just walked away,
stan.
you're just gonna have
to face facts, it's over.
"over"...
♪ i'm all out of love
i'm so lost without you ♪
♪ i know you were right
believing for so long... ♪
stan ?
jesus...
we came over
to cheer you up, stan !
go away.
stan, you can't keep doing
this to yourself.
you have to go live.
why ?
what's the point
of living
when the only girl
i'll ever love is gone ?
god, what a fag !
dude, not now.
you guys have no idea
how this feels.
it's, like, you always
hear songs about a broken heart,
and you think it's just
a figure of speech,
but it's true,
my chest hurts.
i feel this, like, sinking
feeling where my heart is.
it's broken.
geez, he's worse
than i thought.
well, what do we do now ?
should i try telling him
a f-fantastic joke ?
no, we just
have to show him
that there are other girls
out there.
i say
we take him toraisins.
what'sraisins ?
hey, guys,
welcome toraisins !
six of you ?
right over here.
so you guys having
a good time today ?
( all )
uh-huhhh...
how about some
more fun fries, guys ?!
( all )
okay...
oof, i'm glad you guys
came in.
everyone in here is such
a loser, but you guys seem cool.
here you go guys,
lexus will be right with you.
what do you think, stan ?
these girls are
pretty cute, huh ?
jesus christ, i think i've died
and gone to h-h-heaven.
this place
is awesome !
how do you know ?!
we haven't even
tried the food yet !
hey guys !
whoa...
how are we
doing this afternoon ?
gooood...
i'm so glad
you guys came in,
everyone in here
is such a loser,
but you guys
seem really cool.
we are !
so what can
i get you ?
um, get us the zingy tingy
wings and mozzarella tasty tots
and, oh, and bite size pizzazas
and a pitcher of lemonade.
great, i'll put
your order in right now !
you guys, i think ourraisins
girl likes me !
she touched my back when she
walked away, did you see that ?
raisin'sgirls !
woo-hooo !
oh yeah !
hey, hey,
look, over there, stan !
that raisins girl is really
cute, huh ?!
why don't you
say hi to her.
excuse me !
hi guys !
my name's porsche !
hey, this is stan.
oh hey, cutie !
how are you ?
i love your hat.
i used to have a hat just
like that, except it was black
and didn't have
a puff ball on it.
oh my god, my hands
are so cold !
how come people
have hands, anyway ?
did you ever
wonder that ?
♪ it's fun
to stay at the... ♪
♪ y.m.c.a. ♪
woo-hoo ! woo-hoo !
woo-hoo !
♪ y.m.c.a. ♪
oh my god, you guys,
this is the greatest place
in the world.
have you ever noticed how much
sand there is at the beach ?
i mean, haven't you ever
wondered where all that sand
came from ?
oh my god, this one time, i saw
a beetle that was this big !
ewww !
can we go please ?
okay, okay,
come on, you guys.
oh my god, thank you guys so
much for coming toraisins !
oh, sweetie,
are you leaving ?
well, i don't want to, lexus,
but my stupid friends
wanna go !
aww, well, when am i
gonna get to see you again ?
when do you want
to see me ?!
as soon as possible !
oh my god, here, we left you
a tip already,
but here's another $5.
oh you are such a sweetie,
come here, you !
wugh...
wuighhh...
bye, guys, thanks for
coming toraisins !
well stan,
do you feel better now ?
no, dude, i feel worse !
look, we're just trying
to show you
there's other
girls out there.
dude, i don't have time to start
over with other girls !
i'm nine years old, dude !
if i don't work things out
with wendy,
i could be
alone my whole life !
she wants to see me
again !
myraisinsgirl said
she wants to see me again !
i can't let wendy go !
this whole time i've
been having my friends
do all the talking for me !
it's time i took control !
what are you doing ?
something i should have done
a long time ago.
bebe, you need to go
talk to wendy for me right now !
all this time i've been trying
to have my friends do all
the talking for me.
now, i realize i need her
friends to do it.
tell her i love her.
stan, why don't you show her
you love her.
if you really want wendy back,
try doing the most romantic
thing you can think of.
okay, so what's the most
romantic thing i can think of ?
if you really want a shot
at getting her back...
stand outside her window,
hold a boom box up over your
head and play peter gabriel.
♪ don't you know you're gonna
shock the monkey ♪
♪ hey hey
♪ shock the monkey ♪
shock the monkey ♪
♪ shock the monkey
♪ shock the monkey ♪♪
( lexus )
okay, porsche,
see you tomorrow !
bye, mercedes !
lexus !
uh-oh,
uh, hi sweetie.
i waited all night for you
to get off work !
oh, really ?
that's great, uh, morey ?
i just couldn't stop
thinking about you !
there a problem ?
could you uh, just help-
walk me to my bike ?
right.
thanks again for the big tip,
you are such a sweetie.
come back and see
me real soon, okay ?
oh, wait, lexus !
geez, i almost forgot--
i got you this present !
oh wow, thanks, cutie !
it's a little stuffed bear
dressed like a rabbit !
gosh, that's the nicest gift
i've gotten all night,
thank you !
well, i gotta go, honey,
be sure to come back toraisins
and see me again, okay ?!
well, yeah, but-- but--
hey-- hey, lexus ?
i was thinking, well, i was
thinking that we should
go do something,
sometime...
oh gee, that would
be great, honey,
but i'm really
busy this week.
tell you what,
you come back toraisins,
and then we'll be able to
hang out all we want, okay ?!
o-kay !
bye, cutie !
bye, darling !
wow, a real-life
relationship !
( school bell ringing )
( chattering )
( man )
all right, kids, out on the gym
floor for p.e. class !
come on stan, we're
gonna to play dodge ball.
i can't believe it.
she's in love
with somebody else.
dude, you need to
snap out of this !
so wendy left you for token,
what are you gonna do,
just be miserable
your whole life ?
there's nothing else
icando,
she was my whole life.
oh, come on, dude !
all you've done for the last
four days is mope around !
you might as well go
hang out with those goth kids,
who dress in black and talk
about pain all the time !
maybe i should, at least
they would understand me.
maybe i should go hang
with the goth kids.
life is pain,
life is only pain.
we're all taught to believe in
happy, fairy tale endings,
but there
is only blackness.
dark, depressing loneliness
that eats at your soul.
who needs that
ken and barbie love, anyway ?
everyone's just walking around
like a bunch of conformists.
go ahead and wear
your business suits,
so you can make $34,0000 a year
and buy your condominium.
they're like zombies,
racing to their graves.
love didn't work for
my mom and dad,
why should
it work for me ?
my dad is such an asshole,
drunken bastard doesn't even
know i exist,
but then he won't let me
go to the skinny puppy concert
because my heroin addict aunt
is coming over for dinner.
dinner ?
that's a laugh,
just an excuse for my mom
to bitch at me
for not wearing girly clothes
like all the britney spears
wannabes at this school.
they're all a bunch of
nazi conformist cheerleaders.
but if life is only pain,
then, what's the point
of living ?
just to make life more
miserable for the conformists.
all right, so how
do i join you ?
if you want to be one of the
non-conformists,
all you have to do
is dress just like us
and listen to the same music
we do.
'kay.
okay, i know it's
your first day, ferrari,
so i want to go over
the basics with you.
okay.
first of all,
there's a five-foot rule:
if you come within five feet
of a customer,
you need to acknowledge them,
even if they're not at
your table, "hey, cutie !"
when you're not serving food
or talking with customers,
you need to dance
around and have fun.
we have things like hoola-hoops,
silly string and water guns
to play with the other girls.
be sure to giggle a lot, and be
sure to show off your raisins.
now, when you take
a customer's order,
you need to sit down at
the table with them.
it makes them
think you're interested.
write your name down for them,
and make them feel special.
"oh man, i am so bored,
thank god you guys came in !"
if you want good tips,
the most important thing
is physical contact,
just a simple hold of
the arm can be the difference
between $5 and $20.
"i'll be right back with
your order, guys !"
wow, thank you
so much, mercedes.
okay, well i guess we're ready
to open for business, good luck.
go ahead and open
for business, porsche.
okay !
hi, welcome toraisins !
hi, is lexus here ?!
hey, cutie !
darling !
how're we doing today ?!
oh god, i missed you
so much.
"shallow life,
drowning alone i gasp for air.
"coldness creeps over
pale skin.
"there is sadness
so deep it pulls me down.
happiness dies in the deep,
dark sea."
yeah, happiness dies.
yeah.
all right,
your turn, stan.
read one of your poems
about pain.
"there is darkness
all around me.
"deep, piercing
black i cannot breathe.
my heart has
been raped."
whoa.
"the pain is everlasting,
i miss you so much, babe.
want to hold you
in my arms again, girl--"
whoa, whoa, dude, those last
two lines aren't goth.
they're not ?
no, dude, you can't say,
"i miss you so much, babe.
i want to hold
you in my arms."
make it, "i miss seeing you
so much, i want to slice
my eyes out
with razor blades."
henrietta,
hi, sweetie !
go away, mom !
leave me alone !
daddy and i just got your
birthday present !
but you can't see
what it is 'til tomorrow !
you'd like to wait 'til i was
dead, wouldn't you ?
you'd like to see
the maggots eat my face.
you are so creative,
honey !
conformist bitch.
( all )
yeah.
woo-hoo !
( telephone ringing )
thanks for callingraisins,
this is porsche,
have you tried
our double whammy wings ?
hi, is lexus there,
please ?
this is her boyfriend.
thanks for callingraisins,
this is lexus !
hey, lexus !
hi, sweetie,
who's this ?
it's me, butters !
oh, okay,
hi, cutie !
hey, sweetie !
so how are you, honey ?
i'm fine,
i miss you, though.
yeah, school was pretty
tough today.
we had two quizzes
and one of them was a pop quiz.
sometimes i think our classes
are too hard.
but i thought about
you all day long, i promise !
so how is your
day going ?
good, good.
hey, hey, sweetie, i was
thinking tonight you could
come over and we could watch
"the exorcist" on d.v.d. !
oh, gee,
i don't know, cutie.
why don't you just come down
toraisins.
well, i kind of
don't have any money left.
i spent it all atraisins
the last six times.
ooh, that's too bad, cutie,
i really want to see you !
oh, i really want to see
you too, baby !
don't worry,
i'll get more money !
'kay, tiggers, gotta run !
okay,
uh, hey, lexus...
well, there's something i've
been meaning to say...
here it goes...
lexus, i... oh geez, maybe i
shouldn't say it...
no, wait,
i want to say it...
i love you !
hee hee !
oh my gosh !
dad, i need an advance
on my allowance again.
oh, no, butters, you got
an advance two days ago.
but i spent it all !
what are you spending all
that money on, butters ?
on my girlfriend !
girlfriend ?!
you have a girlfriend,
butters ?
yeah...
and she's a girl,
right ?
yep.
well, all right !
good for you, butters !
oh, that is so cute !
when do we get
to meet her ?
well, i was hoping to go see her
right now, you can come along,
but don't
embarrass me or nothing,
i'm sure she'll be real nervous
to impress you.
don't worry, butters,
we just want to say hi and then
we'll leave you two alone !
okay !
you see, i told you
he wouldn't turn out gay !
all right, you win.
hey, can we get more coffee
over here ?
damn it, are you kids just
gonna sit here all night again
and drink $6 worth of
coffee ?
why don't you get a life ?!
conformist,
have fun in your rat race life,
living paycheck to paycheck
for corporate gains.
( all )
yeah.
dude, you haven't
drank your coffee.
well, i don't
drink coffee.
you can't be a non-conformist
if you don't drink coffee.
oh, jesus christ.
i had to see it to believe it.
what the hell are you doing ?
i'm breathing deep the darkness
that envelopes my soul.
god damn it, dude, your mom
and dad want you to come home !
so they can fill my head
with moredisneylies
about how
perfect the world is ?
i don't think so.
yeah, why don't you just go back
to your justin timberlake
and your homework,
you conformist asshole.
you just don't know what
real pain is.
oh, like you
know what pain is !
go try living in a third world
country, you little pussy !
i'm not gonna live
in a third world country
with all the conformists !
stan, this is it, time to stop
feeling sorry for yourself,
and come home.
everyone cares about you
and everyone wants you back.
what about wendy ?
is she still with token ?
yeah, she is.
then, people shouldn't
care about me,
'cause i don't
care about them.
what's the point of caring
when all it brings is pain ?
for sure.
fine, that's it, i give up,
have fun being miserable.
conformist.
yeah.
( butters )
here we are mom and dad !
hi, welcome toraisins !
three of you ?
hi, mercedes,
it's me, lexus' boyfriend.
i brought my parents over
to meet her.
great, be sure to
try our cheddar poppers.
right this way.
who else wants a signed
raisins'girls calendar
for $5 ?!
( table )
woo hoo !
steven,
what is this place ?
i don't know...
here you go, porsche
will be right with you.
go ahead and have a seat, guys,
i gotta go find lexus !
hey, cutie,
you having a good time ?
yeah.
oh boy, i think i know
what's happened.
our son hasn't learned yet
that girls will pretend to
like him for money.
this place is horrible,
to objectify girls like this !
hi guys, can i take
your order ?
little girl,
you shouldn't be working here.
i shouldn't ?!
where am i supposed
to be working ?!
no, i mean you shouldn't work
somewhere where you're paid
for how you look,
you should be learning a skill,
so you can grow up to be
a business woman
or even a doctor.
who knows,
you could cure cancer !
i could cure cancer ?!
oh my god,
that would be so cool !
i had a cancer sore
on my lip once,
and it hurt so bad !
oh, nevermind, i thinkraisins
might be the perfect place
for you.
cool !
mom, dad, this is lexus !
hi, welcome
toraisins !
uh, butters, can we have
a little talk with you ?
outside.
huh, oh, anything
you have to say to me,
you can say in front
of lexus !
butters, these girls pretend
to be interested in you
because they know
you'll give them tips.
huh ?
you see, butters, women know
that they can make men do
anything by flirting.
and some girls, like these,
turn that into a profession.
oh i see, you don't approve
of my girlfriend !
well, let me tell you
something, mom and dad,
our love is as pure as
a mountain spring !
the odds may be
stacked against us,
but we're gonna give it
our best shot !
and so if you
can't be happy for us,
you can just go to heck,
mom and dad !
come on, lexus !
i'm moving out
of my parents house,
and i'm moving in with you,
let's blow this joint !
what are you talking
about, kid ?!
we are not
boyfriend and girlfriend !
what, lexus, what are
you saying ?
are you saying you don't
want to be together anymore ?
i'm sorry, sweetie.
so that's it ?
we're broken up, now ?
i gotta give these curly fries
to table 12.
well, go ahead and go.
it's best we don't say
anything more.
there's nothing left to say...
it's over...
our relationship is over...
♪ i'm all out of love
i'm so lost without you... ♪
( sobbing )
♪ i'm all out of love ♪♪
( boy )
look at that,
another tortured soul.
another life of pain.
hey, raven,
check it out.
butters ?
oh, oh, hey, stan.
what's the matter
with you ?
well... my-- my girlfriend
broke up with me.
did she step on your
heart with stiletto shoes ?
yeah,
it sure does hurt.
that's cool, i guess you can
join up with us if you want.
yeah, we're gonna go to
the graveyard and write poems
about death and how
pointless life is.
oh, no, thanks,
i love life.
huh ?  but you
just got dumped.
well, yeah, and i'm sad.
but at the same time,
i'm really happy that something
can make me feel
that sad.
it's like... it makes
me feel alive, you know ?
it makes me feel human.
the only way i could feel this
sad now is if i felt something
really good before,
so i have to take
the bad with the good,
so i guess what i'm feeling
is like a 'beautiful sadness'...
i guess that
sounds stupid.
yeah.
no, no, butters, that doesn't
sound stupid at all.
but thanks for offering
to let me in your clique, guys,
but to be honest, i'd rather
be a crying, little pussy
than a faggy goth kid,
well, see ya, stan.
he's right, i don't
even know who i am anymore.
i like liking life a lot
more than hating it.
screw you, guys,
i'm going home.
go ahead and go back to
your sunshine fairy tale !
okay, it's third down !
now, somebody
make a play !
hey, can
i join in ?
what happened, aren't you
still wallowing in pain ?
yeah, it still hurts a lot,
but i just realized that
there's going to be a lot
of painful times in life,
so i better learn to deal
with it the right way.
hey, wendy !
you're a bitch.
token ?
right here, buddy.
oh, dude, it's good
to have you back.
yeah, let's play ball.
captioning made possible by
comedy central
captioned by
soundwriters™