captioning made possible by
comedy central
♪ i'm going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna have
myself a time ♪
♪ friendly faces
everywhere ♪
♪ humble folks
without temptation ♪
♪ going down
to south park ♪
♪ gonna leave my
woes behind ♪
♪ ample parking
day or night ♪
♪ people spouting
"howdy neighbor" ♪
♪ headin' on up
to south park ♪
♪ gonna see
if i can't unwind ♪
♪ ( muffled mumble
muffled mumble ) ♪
♪ so come on down
to south park ♪
♪ and meet some
friends of mine ♪♪
♪ summertime love's
gonna get me down ♪
♪ summertime is right for
touchin' in the night ♪
♪ girl, won't you feel
my summertime ♪
♪ come on and touch
my summertime ♪♪
stan, are you okay ?
yeah, dad, we're just
rehearsing our band.
ohh, i thought a group
of vietnamese people
were having their
intestines
pulled out
through their mouths.
ha ha ha ha haa !
he's right, dude, we have
to define our style
if we're ever going to
make a platinum album.
i mean, i'm a fusion guy,
but kenny's background
is more latin-jazz.
yup, uh-huh.
yeah, and i'm more hip-hop
and r & b oriented.
i think our band better buy
a whole bunch of music cds
to listen to
for inspiration.
inspiration...
wait a minute,
that's it !
inspiration, you guys.
don't you see ?
see what ?
our band should play
christian rock !
christian rock ?
think about it !
it's the easiest, crappiest
music in the world, right ?
if we just play songs about
how much we love jesus,
all the christians
will buy our crap !
that's a retarded
idea, cartman !
it worked forcreed!
i don't wanna be in
a stupid christian
rock band !
you just start that way, stan,
then you cross over !
it's genius !
just get the hell
out of here, cartman !
you're not serious and you're
a detriment to the band !
oh yeah ?
i will bet you 10 bucks
that if i start
a christian rock band
i can get a platinum album
before you guys do !
you're on, fat boy !
okay, fine !
ready-- first one to have
a platinum album wins.
go !
( huffing )
what a stupid
asshole.
platinum album !
gotta make a platinum
album before kyle !
oh, hi, eric.
butters, get your drum set
and meet me at my house !
we have to make
a platinum album !
hurry, butters !
oho !
no time to waste !
platinum album !
must beat kyle !
token, get the bass guitar
out of your basement
and meet me over
at my house !
what ?!
we don't have
a bass guitar.
your family's black, token,
there's bound to be
a bass guitar
in your basement
somewhere !
boy, you sure
seem driven, eric.
you must really have
some inspiration.
yes, the tears of
kyle broflovski
when he loses his
$10 to me.
hey, there was a bass
guitar in my basement.
i told you, token.
so, what are we doing ?
gentlemen, we are about to
embark on the most amazing,
life-affirming,
financially windfalling
experiences of
our young lives.
wow !
we are going to start...
a christian rock band.
aww...
i'm out.
wait !
walk out
that door, token,
and you'll regret it
the rest of your life !
christians have
a built-in audience
of over 180 million
americans.
if each one of them buys
just one of our albums
at $12.95 that would be--
two billion,
331 million dollars.
still want to leave,
token ?
thank you.
dad, can i borrow
$300 ?
$300 !
what in the world for ?!
our band can't find a
stylistic direction to go in.
we need to go
down to the mall
to buy hundreds of cds
to listen to
so we can define
our sound.
sorry, kyle, we gave you
your allowance already.
can't you see
this is my dream ?!
music is my life !
it wasn't your life
yesterday.
look, pops, i've got
the music inside me.
it's in my soul.
and i know my place
is up on that stage.
i'm gonna make it
to the top.
and i just want
your blessing, pops.
the answer is no, kyle.
aw, come on, dad,
don't be such a jew !
kyle, don't belittle
your own people !
argh !
hey, dude.
it didn't work.
my stupid jew dad won't
lend me money for cds.
no, dude, it's cool.
kenny says you can
download music for free
on the internet !
really ?
yeah !
you got a computer ?
see, everyone on the internet
copies music from their cds
and then we can
download them for free
and play 'em
on the computer !
all right, cool !
let's download
somemetallica
and some stevie wonder.
mprh rmph
rmhprmh rmh !
kenny's right,
we should download
somejudas priest,too.
judas priest...
wow !  downloading music
for free is awesome !
( helicopter whirring,
police siren )
what the hell is that ?
i don't know,
let me check--
freeze, f.b.i. !
down on the ground !
hands !  let me see
those hands !
tango team is
at point bravo !
suspects in custody !
move move move !
keep your hands up !
out to the car !
kyle,
what did you do ?
i don't know !
all right guys, this is
gonna be so easy.
all we have to do to
make christian songs
is take regular old songs
and add jesus stuff to them !
see, all we have to do is
cross out words like "baby"
and "darlin'" and
replace them with...
jeeesus.
all right, butters,
give me a beat.
( mid-tempo beat )
okay, nice, very nice.
all right, token, give me
a smooth bass line.
i don't know
how to play bass.
token, how many times do we
have to go through this ?
you're black.
you can play bass.
i'm getting sick of
your stereotypes.
be as sick as you want,
just give me
a goddamn bass line !
( funky bass line )
goddammit.
all right,
nice, fellas, nice.
♪ i need you
in my life ♪
♪ jesus ♪
♪ i can't live
without you ♪
♪ jesus ♪
♪ and i just want to feel you
deep inside me ♪
♪ jesus ♪♪
awesome !
um, sir ?
shut up !!
you downloaded
a lot of songs.
says here, you even
downloaded judas priest.
that's hard time
you boys are looking at.
you got anything to
say for yourselves ?
we...  we didn't think
it was that big a deal.
not a big deal ?
you think downloading music
for free is not a big deal ?
put your coats on, i'm
gonna show you something.
and i don't think
you're gonna like it.
this is the home
of lars ulrich,
the drummer
for metallica.
look, there's lars now,
sitting by his pool.
what's the matter
with him ?
this month he was hoping
to have a gold-plated
shark tank bar installed
right next to the pool.
but thanks to people
downloading his music
for free
he must now wait a few months
before he can afford it.
( whimpering )
come, there's more.
here's britney spears'
private jet.
notice anything ?
britney used to have
agulfstream iv,
now she's had to sell it
and get a gulfstream iii
because people like you chose
to download her music for free.
( sighs )
the gulfstream iii doesn't
even have a remote control
for its surround sound
dvd system.
still think downloading music
for free is no big deal ?
we... didn't realize
what we were doing.
that is the
folly of man.
now look in this window.
here you see the loving
family of master p.
next week is
his son's birthday
and all he's ever wanted is
an island in french polynesia.
so, he's gonna
get it, right ?
i see an island
without an owner.
if things keep going
the way they are
the child will not get
his tropical paradise.
we're sorry !
we'll never download music
for free again !
man must learn to think of
these horrible outcomes
before he acts selfishly
or else i fear...
recording artists
will be forever doomed
to a life of only
semi-luxury.
( sea gulls squawking )
almost there, guys.
ow.
why the hell did you
tell us to dress nice
to take us out here ?
because, token, we have to take
pictures for our album cover.
the key to a hot selling
christian rock album
is a flashy, inspirational
album cover.
wow, neat-o !
an album cover !
this christian album
better make as much money
as you said it
would, tubby.
i'm going to kill you
one day, token.
what did you say ?
nothing !
all right, guys,
stand over there
and look wholesome
and cool.
i have a timer on this thing
so i can get in shot too.
cheese !
no, no, no !
haven't you guys ever
seen an album cover ?
you're supposed to be
standing in random places,
looking away
like you don't care.
cheese !
( eric )
no, butters, you can't look
happy on a album cover !
that's not cool !
oh.
token, look away
to the right.
more... more !
why the hell would i be
looking way over there ?
so it looks like you're
too cool to care
that you're on an album cover,
you black asshole !
now just hold it !
our first album cover.
♪ don't ever leave me
jesus ♪
♪ i couldn't stand
to see you go ♪
♪ my heart would simply
snap, my lord ♪
♪ if you walked on
out that door ♪
♪ i promise
i'll be good to you ♪
♪ and keep you
warm at night ♪
♪ jesus, jesus, jesus ♪
♪ why don't we just
shut off the light ♪
thanks for releasing
them to us, detective.
sorry for all the
trouble they caused.
it's all right, i think these
boys learned their lesson.
boy, i'll say.
if you parents will
just step over here
you can pay their $400
release and penalty fees.
$400 ?
just for downloading some
songs off the internet ?
it's not that
big a deal.
not a big deal, huh ?!
come with me, i'm gonna
show you something.
and i don't think
you're gonna like it !
oof, dude, i can't wait
to just go back home
and get back to
band practice.
yeah.
no !  didn't you guys
learn anything ?
look, if we make an album,
all that's gonna happen
is that people are gonna
steal our songs for free
off the internet !
we won't make a dime !
oh, yeah.
until we get people to stop
downloading music for free
i say we refuse to play !
yeah !
tom, i'm standing in
south park, colorado
where the rock band "moop"
has refused to play !
the strike started yesterday
and could go well into
next week !
oh, hey guys,
how's it going ?
we're not letting you back
in the band, cartman.
( bleep ) off.
i don't want to be in your
crappy band, guys.
i just wanted to let you know
the album for my christian
rock band, "faith plus one",
is about to go
platinum.
it is ?!
that's right, we've
already sold 13 copies.
you wanna pay me that
$10 bet now, kyle ?
♪ nya-nya nya-nya
nya, nya ♪
hey-hey hey-hey
heeey, hey !
you get a platinum album for
selling one million copies,
you fat turd !
it's just a matter
of time, my friends.
this weekend is christfest,
the single largest gathering
of christians in the midwest.
each one of them a walking,
praying wallet full of cash.
and i'll be there
selling my album.
you'll never get
a platinum album
doing christian rock,
cartman !
it was a stupid idea then
and it's a stupid idea now !
yeah, you don't even know
anything about christianity !
i know enough
to exploit it.
just get that 10 bucks
ready kyle !
ta ta !
go ahead, people will just
download your songs for free
on the internet anyways !
what a dumbass-- our band is
way cooler than his !
yeah !
psalm t-shirts !
get a t-shirt with
your favorite psalm !
leather-bound bibles !
show your faith !
yes, it's really the best
christian album
that's ever been
produced actually.
ooh, this would be great
for my grandchildren.
they need hip cool music, but
with inspirational lyrics.
i think that's what
the whole world needs.
praise christ.
we're not really christian,
we're just pretendin' we are !
butters, remind me later
to cut your balls off.
( man over pa )
all right, everyone !
welcome to
christfest 2003 !
are you ready for some
live music ?
( crowd cheering )
yeah, jesus !
then let's give it up now
for one of christian rock's
biggest bands--
trinity !
♪ he's the shepherd
and the light ♪
♪ and his word
lifted me up ♪
♪ and i praise his holy name
wherever i go... ♪
dammit !
if we're gonna sell our hot
christian album
we have got to
get on that stage !
hey, is this the way
to the backstage ?
who are you ?
we're the band
sanctified.
we play metal and punk
but with lyrics that
inspire faith in christ.
yeah, we prove that christian
music can be tough and hardcore.
yeah, you guys
are real hardcore.
you bet your gosh darn
rear-end we are !
all right, sanctified ?
you guys are up next.
yeah !
let's do it !
sent down
from heaven !
the spirit
and the glory !
hey, guys wait--
we wanna pray with you
before you go onstage.
oh, that's cool.
always good to be prayin'
before you're playin'.
let's just go in here so we
can hear ourselves better.
lord father in heaven, we thank
you for all your blessings...
hey, eric, i don't think
they can get out !
all right, christians,
how are we feeling tonight ?!
praise jesus !
praise him !
well let's keep this
salvation train going
with the hot band,
sanctified !
( whispers )
uh, uh, apparently
there's been a change.
give it up for--
faith plus one !
you know, jesus,
i've been thinking
a lot about you lately.
and, well, that's why
i wrote this song...
♪ i love you, jesus ♪
i want you to
walk with me ♪
♪ i'll take good care
of ya, baby ♪
♪ call ya my baby
baaaby ♪
♪ you died for my sins ♪
♪ and you know that i would
die for you-- right ? ♪
♪ what's the matter, baby ?
♪ you're tremblin'
jesus baby ♪
♪ your love
is my light ♪
♪ you know when
i'm without you ♪
♪ there's a black hole
in my life ♪
♪ ohh, i wanna believe
it's all right ♪
♪ but i get lonely
in the night ♪
♪ and it's up to you
to save me ♪
♪ jesus baby ♪♪
dude, i didn't know
being in a band
was gonna be this tough.
yeah, it's tough.
but it's times
like these
that you see what
your band is made of.
we've gotta fight through the
rough times likejourney.
tom, we're now entering
the second day
of the rock band moop's
refusal to play
and the second day of absolutely
no other news to report on.
in a recent poll we asked people
if moop's refusal to play
would stop them from downloading
music off the internet.
1% percent said "yes",
2% said "no",
and 97% said
"who the hell is moop ?"
back to you, tom.
hey, are you the guys
protesting
free internet music
downloading ?
hey, it's that
lars ulrich guy !
that's right, metallica is
behind you dudes %1000 !
we're gonna sit here
and protest with you
until free
downloading stops !
tom, it appears now the
musicians strike is growing.
as i'm speaking,
more musicians are arriving !
it looks like alanis morisette,
blink 182,britney spears
and dozens of others
are going to join moop
in not playing music.
this is a veritable
strike-apalooza !
guys, we here
atfaith records
were very moved by your
performance at christfest.
you're one of
the most talented
christian rock bands
we've ever heard !
thank you so much.
christ has really
blessed us with talent.
( laughing )
yeah !
we just had
one question, though.
we were looking over
some of your lyrics...
uh, "i want to walk
hand in hand with jesus
"on a private beach
for two.
"i want him to nibble
on my ear
"and say,
'i'm here for you'--"
it seems you
really love christ.
yes, we sure do.
no, but it appears
you are actually
in lovewith christ.
well, what are you
saying,
that you don't really
love christ ?
well, of course i do,
i mean, i just--
well, what's
the difference ?
you love christ,
you're in love with christ ?
i mean, what the heck
is this ?!
we just like to make sure
the bands we sign
are in it for god
and not for the money.
i resent that, sir.
i have never in my life done
anything just for the money.
if i'm lying, may the lord
strike me down right now.
uh, oh...
that's all we
needed to know.
just sign here and we'll
get your album sold.
( announcer )
k-tal recordspresents
the most inspirational
christian rock band
in the world--
faith plus one.
featuring the very best
in good, wholesome
christian music.
♪ oh lord
you are my savior ♪
♪ you know i miss you so much
when you are gone... ♪♪
with great inspirational
songs like
"i wasn't born again
yesterday".
♪ yes i may be born again ♪
♪ but i wasn't born again
yesterday... ♪♪
♪ i wanna get down on my knees
and start pleasin' jesus ♪
♪ i wanna feel his salvation
all over my face... ♪
the cds is filled with
instant classics.
who doesn't remember...
♪ the body of christ ♪
♪ sleek, swimmer's body
all muscled up and toned ♪
♪ the body of christ ♪
♪ oh what a body, i wish
i could call it my own... ♪♪
♪ you one time, two times
three times my savior... ♪♪
♪ whenever i see jesus
up on that cross ♪
♪ i can't help but think
that he looks kind of hot... ♪♪
this album is not available
in stores
and limited quantities
are available !
so order now !
i can't take this
much longer.
maybe we're just not cut out
to be in a band.
you guys, we can't give up
on our dreams now !
as soon as this strike ends
we're gonna be the
biggest band ever !
yeah, if we all give in now,
people might never stop
downloading our music
for free !
i'm sure we're gonna get word
any minute
that people have
agreed to stop.
certified letter for
the rock band moop ?
that's us !
"dear moop, this letter
is to inform you
"that faith plus one's
debut album
has just sold
one million copies."
what ?!
"we cordially invite you to
"attend the platinum album
award ceremony
"which will be held tomorrow
morning at 10.
"details and proof
of sales enclosed.
p.s. nya-nya nya-nya nya, nya,
ha-ha ha-ha ha, ha."
he did it...
cartman got a platinum album.
is this for real ?
this is for real !
he beat us.
because all this time
we've been so caught up
with how to protect our music,
that we forgot to just play !
but why play if we're not gonna
make millions of dollars ?
because that's what
real artists do.
people are always
going to find a way
to copy our music
and swap it for free.
if we're real musicians,
then we should just play
and be stoked that so many
people are listening !
besides, maybe our songs would
have gotten downloaded for free,
but if they were good songs,
then people still would
have bought tickets
to see our band
in concert.
from now on, moop
isn't about money--
moop is about music !
we're not striking
anymore.
who's with us !
we're just about
the money.
yeah. yeah.
yeah.
oh.
so, dude, what are you gonna do
about your bet with cartman ?
are you gonna pay him ?
i don't have
a choice, dude.
i'm gonna swallow my pride,
face cartman
and say, "congratulations,
you were right."
and i'm gonna
give him the $10.
and hopefully, he won't make
a big deal out of it.
( marching band playing,
elephant trumpeting )
welcome !
welcome everyone !
please, enjoy, the presentation
should begin shortly.
cartman, what the hell
is all this ?
our platinum album ceremony--
i've spared no expense.
but you spent all
the money we made !
we're faith plus one, token,
there'll be plenty more money.
relax and enjoy,
black asshole.
there's hors d'oeuvres
and drinks
by the ferris wheel,
everyone !
oh, kyle, guys,
so nice to see you !
let's just get this
over with, cartman.
you won the bet,
here's $10.
oh, no no no--
not yet, kyle.
hold on.
everyone, everyone, can i have
your attention, please ?
( cheering )
woo-hoo !
faith plus one !
we love you !
praise christ !
yes, yes, thank you,
praise him.
i think we're ready
to start now.
( announcer )
welcome to the
presentation ceremony
for faith plus one !
( audience cheering )
and now to present the award,
here's michael collins !
this is the worst day
of my life.
ahh, this is the best day
boys, in recognition of over
one million records sold
the christian recording industry
is pleased to present you
with this-- myrrh album !
thank you very--
wait, myrrh album ?
i thought albums went
either gold or platinum.
no, no, in christian rock
our albums go gold,
then frankincense
then myrrh.
congratulations !
ha !  our bet was that
you would get a platinum album
not a myrrh album !
i don't owe you
anything, fat boy !
do you mean to tell me i can
never get a platinum album
with a christian
rock band ?
no, but you can go
double myrrh.
goddammit !
( gasps from audience )
oh, please don't take
the lord's name in vain !
who cares ?!
i can never win my bet
because you stupid assholes
don't give out
platinum albums !
but you've spread
the word of the lord.
you've brought
faith in jesus !
oh, ( bleep ) jesus !
( gasps )
( woman shrieks )
eric, i'm pretty sure
you shouldn't say the
"f" word about jesus.
yeah, you're gonna
hurt the band !
who ( bleeping )
cares, token ?
i can never beat
kyle now !
i'll say it again !
( bleep ) jesus !
( audience screaming )
my ears are
bleeding !
good job, dick head !
you lost the
entire audience !
ah, ( bleep ) you, token,
you black asshole !
ah !  oh !
eh !
( coughing )
hmm, guess he got
what he deserved.
( eric coughing, wheezing )
( bleep ) you, eric !
( eric )
♪ the body of christ ♪
♪ sleek, swimmer's body
all muscled up and toned ♪
♪ the body of christ ♪
♪ oh what a body, i wish
i could call it my own ♪
♪ lord almighty
i've never been so enticed ♪
♪ oh i wish i could have
the body of christ ♪
♪ the body of christ ♪
♪ lord almighty
i've never been so enticed ♪
♪ oh i wish i could have
the body of christ ♪♪