[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Subtitles
Original Script: Subtitles
website: www.zimuzu.tv
Sina Weibo: @zimuzu
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134
Style: LOGO,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.68,0:00:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.60,0:02:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\alpha&B0\c&H000000&\t(0,200,\fscx2000\fscy600\t(200,400,\fscx2500\fscy300\t(29800,30200,\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\alpha&AA\fscy400\fscx400)))\move(158,211.2,46.5,211.2,29800,30200)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.60,0:02:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\fs16\fn方正大黑_GBK\move(-150,211,56,211,400,600)\clip(54.24,192,230.88,228.48)}本字幕首發于{\c&HEBAE00&}字幕組{\c&HFFFFFF&}網站\N{\c&H00C0FF&}www.ZiMuZu.tv {\c&HFFFFFF&}歡迎交流
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.60,0:02:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,281,227))}翻譯  冰藍 送小孩 小十三 自然卷 小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.60,0:02:15.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,291,227))}翻譯  33來了 CS小明漫畫家 Reginamoon
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.60,0:02:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\frx-630\t(0,500,\frx0\t(4500,5000,\clip(40,213,40,248)))\pos(57.12,210.56)}翻譯 艾瑞卡    校對 送小孩 冰藍
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.60,0:02:25.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,0)\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\move(57.12,210.56,400,210.56,4500,5000)\clip(54.24,193.92,284.24,228.48)}時間軸  加森 沒有影子 濤濤
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.60,0:02:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(300,300)\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs17\bord0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&HEDB425&\4c&H9EF6FF&\shad0\bord0\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))\pos(57.12,210.56)}后期 吉吉 拉圖  總監 面館生快
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.26,0:02:51.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.18,0:02:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死  我說了注意
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.86,0:03:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊妮德
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.67,0:03:23.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊妮德
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.11,0:03:25.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在外面干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.34,0:03:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,角落里還有一瓶水
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.66,0:03:32.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿上就走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.26,0:04:11.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不回答我嗎 
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.31,0:04:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.45,0:04:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞歷山大里怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.35,0:04:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們聽到了那聲音
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.92,0:04:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,槍聲
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.64,0:04:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊妮德
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.06,0:04:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發生了總是會發生的事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.79,0:04:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人們死了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.09,0:04:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它們沖破了圍墻嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.14,0:04:45.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,誰
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.74,0:04:46.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尸群
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.24,0:04:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它們提前沖出了采石場
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.91,0:04:51.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們引走了它們  但那汽笛聲
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.91,0:04:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.60,0:04:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.43,0:04:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你該走了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.08,0:05:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.54,0:05:07.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪姬
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.86,0:05:10.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.48,0:05:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊妮德
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.34,0:05:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪姬沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.85,0:05:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.06,0:05:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊妮德
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.94,0:05:31.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊妮德
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.67,0:05:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊妮德
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.68,0:05:52.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊妮德
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.54,0:06:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊妮德
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.01,0:06:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs21}本藍光版外掛字幕由  {\c&H9B30FF&}風吹來的那片云{\c&HFFFFFF&}  用WEB版調軸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.01,0:06:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第六季  第七集』
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.91,0:07:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩根
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.97,0:07:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.57,0:07:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們還沒聊過  我們該聊聊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.55,0:07:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚點聊  好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.89,0:07:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.94,0:08:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒必要經常上來
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.30,0:08:25.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.82,0:08:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是他回來的方向
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.03,0:08:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他發信號  就會在那邊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.45,0:08:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者不會有信號了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.61,0:08:43.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們出去時
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.14,0:08:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從來都不容易  不輕松
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.98,0:08:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總會有戰斗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.56,0:08:51.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但更難的情況我們都挺過來了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.36,0:08:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更遠的距離我們也回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.85,0:08:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格倫  達里爾
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.57,0:08:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞伯拉罕和薩沙  他們也可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.53,0:09:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許我們不應該干等著他們回來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.58,0:09:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們應該開始想想怎樣把行尸引走
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.41,0:09:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的食物和水還能支撐一段時間
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.97,0:09:15.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,墻也還撐得住
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.07,0:09:18.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以慢慢來
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.28,0:09:20.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好想清楚  把這事干好了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.26,0:09:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,清理干凈  這樣他們就能...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.42,0:09:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們就能直接走進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.73,0:09:31.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有天看見朱迪思在屋子里
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.39,0:09:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她開始...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.71,0:09:39.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她開始長得像洛莉了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.87,0:09:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是啊  -這讓我挺開心的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.60,0:09:46.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.27,0:10:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}貝琪  親愛的\N如果你在看這張紙條  那說明我沒能活著回去
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.72,0:11:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑體簡體\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}今日1點\N在太陽能板處\N舉行祈禱圈活動
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.39,0:11:43.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.91,0:11:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你初次嘗試還是用手槍比較好
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.84,0:11:59.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裝彈  上膛
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.85,0:12:02.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拇指保險
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.48,0:12:04.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算簡單的  是不是  老爸
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.23,0:12:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯  空的彈夾
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.95,0:12:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-空的槍膛  看到了嗎  -看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.02,0:12:16.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人在你前面  他們手里有槍
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.02,0:12:18.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會害怕的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.76,0:12:20.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.60,0:12:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的身體會緊繃  你沒時間思考
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.29,0:12:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當你面對這種情況時
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.62,0:12:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會只想著扣下扳機
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.36,0:12:31.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你會打偏
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.81,0:12:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你就會死
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.39,0:12:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得把槍舉到與眼睛平行的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.92,0:12:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得足夠堅強  耐心等到一個好時機
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.23,0:12:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能... 
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.76,0:12:57.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的手指不能碰扳機
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.96,0:12:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你準備好開槍了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.04,0:13:11.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那把槍你留著吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.18,0:13:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,體會體會隨身配槍是什么感覺
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.98,0:13:15.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能開槍嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.43,0:13:19.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許可以朝著行尸開槍什么的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.77,0:13:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  照現在的情況
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.95,0:13:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,墻足夠堅固能抵擋
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.42,0:13:26.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但幸運的是行尸慢慢散開了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.20,0:13:27.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可不想把它們全部引到一個點
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.97,0:13:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那...在鎮中心練習打靶可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.17,0:13:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為那樣聲音就會四散開來
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.54,0:13:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者我們可以安個消聲器之類的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.52,0:13:43.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.34,0:13:48.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們現在最好還是別浪費子彈
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.02,0:13:55.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想多學一點
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.17,0:13:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.43,0:14:18.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.72,0:14:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正在做...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.24,0:14:23.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想來點燕麥粥嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.24,0:14:28.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多謝  不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.34,0:14:31.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看你剛剛在門邊晃悠  有什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.92,0:14:37.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要我看看你手臂上的傷嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.29,0:14:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我來不是為了...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.90,0:14:44.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.67,0:14:48.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有事可以告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.45,0:14:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩根
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.31,0:14:59.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在方便談談嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.25,0:15:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.57,0:15:09.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我回來的路上...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.35,0:15:15.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我試圖用車擋住行尸
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.45,0:15:17.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,引開它們
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.52,0:15:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但有五個額頭上刻著W的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.61,0:15:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我攔下了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.36,0:15:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們想殺我  朝車子開槍
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.53,0:15:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡蘿爾告訴我  她看到你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.43,0:15:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不愿意殺死他們
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.74,0:15:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你放走他們的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.36,0:15:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.38,0:15:47.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想殺死五個我沒必要殺的人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.67,0:15:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可他們活活燒死人啊
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.96,0:15:49.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.95,0:16:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克  在金恩郡那會兒 
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.88,0:16:06.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你為什么不殺我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.38,0:16:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對你亮刀  試圖捅你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.11,0:16:11.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你為什么不殺我
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.87,0:16:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因為你從醫院出來后我救了你嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.86,0:16:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我知道你的為人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.12,0:16:17.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那會兒我一看見你就會殺你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.49,0:16:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也動手了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.48,0:16:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你饒了我一命
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.52,0:16:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才有了后來我幫助亞倫和達里爾脫險
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.54,0:16:32.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看吧  如果我不在場...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.63,0:16:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他們死了...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.71,0:16:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些狼或許就不會來這里了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.94,0:16:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經分不清對錯了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.99,0:16:53.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我明明就很想殺死他們
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.43,0:16:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到他們為非作歹  惡性不改
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.71,0:17:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明知可以了結此事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.54,0:17:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我也知道人是可以改變的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.84,0:17:12.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為在座的每位都改變了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.22,0:17:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有生命都是寶貴的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.93,0:17:19.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而那個想法  那個想法改變了我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.23,0:17:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我重獲新生  讓我活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.58,0:17:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是覺得  沒那么容易
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.41,0:17:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-并不容易  -我的意思不是...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.36,0:17:26.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.82,0:17:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想過要放棄那種想法
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.11,0:17:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不愿意
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.36,0:17:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許你必須放棄
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.07,0:17:38.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情沒有說起來那么簡單
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.84,0:17:41.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從來沒有過
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.00,0:17:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得我不該留在這里嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.96,0:17:46.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在這樣做
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.77,0:17:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真以為你能手不沾血嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.71,0:17:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.60,0:18:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我們能想辦法到墻外去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.01,0:18:43.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到采石場的車子那里
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.61,0:18:45.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們就能用車子引走它們
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.82,0:18:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們要建立更多哨點
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.79,0:18:49.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,協調射擊槍支和信號彈
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.31,0:18:52.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣就能把它們分散引走
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.82,0:18:54.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們得用上所有我們的人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.62,0:18:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡爾  塔拉  羅西塔  卡蘿爾
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.62,0:19:00.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.27,0:19:03.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前我們先不告訴別人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.43,0:19:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.33,0:19:08.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我們有時間帶上大家  那當然可以
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.98,0:19:11.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我們連歇口氣的機會都沒有過
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.00,0:19:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.15,0:19:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都在這個社區里
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.29,0:19:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在我們正在歇息
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.93,0:19:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他的都是借口
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.64,0:19:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪安娜
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.85,0:19:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.10,0:19:38.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.22,0:19:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擴張計劃
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.99,0:19:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們現在有其他的事情要忙
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.14,0:19:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.82,0:19:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情結束之后  可以這樣建設亞歷山大
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.89,0:19:53.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為不管怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.94,0:19:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這事都會結束
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.80,0:20:05.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刀砍進去后  不要立刻拔出來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.58,0:20:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你會被卡住  -被卡住
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.34,0:20:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像斧子砍進樹里
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.02,0:20:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把刀砍進骨頭容易  拔出來難
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.84,0:20:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那應該怎么辦
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.77,0:20:16.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用砍刀順著傷口向下劃出去
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.69,0:20:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,動作要連續
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.16,0:20:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像這樣劃過骨頭
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.24,0:20:22.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.56,0:20:37.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是個手握砍刀的武器菜鳥
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.85,0:20:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我周圍有人穿著露腳面的鞋
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.48,0:20:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  所以振作點
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.32,0:20:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在怕什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.03,0:20:54.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概是死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.59,0:20:55.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死很容易
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.38,0:20:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都停止了  你死了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.40,0:21:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你周圍的人死去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.31,0:21:03.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才是最難的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.25,0:21:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂了嗎  因為你繼續活著
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.16,0:21:09.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心里想著他們已經死了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.16,0:21:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你還在這里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.58,0:21:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最應該害怕的是繼續活著
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.46,0:21:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同時心里愧疚著自己沒能盡力保護好他們
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.07,0:21:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,難受得堅持不下去了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.14,0:21:29.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噪音嚇著你了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.85,0:21:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能繼續講課了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.13,0:21:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們再來一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.52,0:22:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.16,0:22:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要帶你回家
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.64,0:22:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不認識你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.86,0:22:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你為什么給我水喝
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.91,0:22:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有水  你需要水
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.23,0:22:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不代表我們是朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.20,0:22:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不是朋友  我是因為瑪姬才這么做的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.93,0:22:38.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的妻子嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.75,0:22:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不會拋下你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.87,0:22:44.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她肯定也不希望我拋下你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.93,0:22:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我們走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.91,0:22:49.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和你妻子也不是朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.52,0:22:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想跟你商量
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.80,0:22:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會把你丟在這里
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.21,0:22:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們現在就走
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.46,0:22:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.62,0:23:18.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把槍給我  伊妮德
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.33,0:23:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,轉身走開
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.21,0:23:27.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不會開槍的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.29,0:23:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你逼我的話  我會的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.34,0:23:35.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放手
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.91,0:23:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.74,0:23:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你拿槍指著我還叫我混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.55,0:23:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們走
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.93,0:23:50.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走后門去小巷
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.41,0:23:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們走大路  需要開闊的視野
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.95,0:23:53.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.29,0:23:57.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為半數尸群離開了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.99,0:24:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它們正在往家走
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.18,0:24:02.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜你沒碰上吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.82,0:24:06.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶路吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.32,0:24:56.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看上去需要一些幫助
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.76,0:25:05.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得我們可以給這玩意兒造一個支架
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.71,0:25:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.27,0:25:37.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得你妻子不希望我殺了它嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.79,0:26:05.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以利用它們引開行尸
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.79,0:26:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灌木叢中有一個氦氣罐
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.11,0:26:15.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有更多氣球和繩子
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.46,0:26:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要支撐好  墻就沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.53,0:26:44.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們剛見到你時
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.49,0:26:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把大家都嚇了一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.74,0:26:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.31,0:26:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把我嚇了一跳
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.57,0:26:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大胡子
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.97,0:26:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你環顧四周的方式
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.95,0:27:01.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像你看到了什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.39,0:27:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們沒看到的事
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.49,0:27:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結果真的是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.93,0:27:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本來這里節奏很慢
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.99,0:27:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你一來  一切都加快了步伐
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.62,0:27:22.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太快了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.99,0:27:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不要放棄我們
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.34,0:27:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在家里的時候跟誰住
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.45,0:27:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是我的家
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.50,0:27:52.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我住在奧利維亞那兒
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.89,0:27:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我靠我自己
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.29,0:28:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行尸奪走了我的父母
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.10,0:28:08.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.36,0:28:10.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.75,0:28:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情就是這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.00,0:28:30.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你很害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.39,0:28:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不怕
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.77,0:28:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是很怕
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.82,0:28:36.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不想再失去什么了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:37.57,0:28:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你放棄了  說"事情就是這樣"
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.22,0:28:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不需要說教  -我覺得你需要
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.03,0:28:47.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你通過活下去來尊重死者
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.60,0:28:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使當你害怕的時候
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.91,0:28:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你活著是因為他們犧牲了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.34,0:28:58.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為害怕就舉著槍
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.79,0:29:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得你父母會想讓你那樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.83,0:29:03.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不必聊天
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.47,0:29:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不必聊天
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.96,0:29:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟糕 
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.17,0:30:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.63,0:30:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別走
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.54,0:30:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說了別走
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.15,0:30:38.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么意義
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.28,0:30:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世界在自取滅亡
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.92,0:30:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不應該去插手
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.98,0:30:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.09,0:30:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你錯了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.27,0:30:58.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們應該阻止它
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.41,0:31:01.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且我肯定也不會讓你死
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.02,0:31:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我肯定你妻子會原諒你的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.85,0:31:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不再是為了她才這么做
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.39,0:31:11.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,墻還沒有倒
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.05,0:31:13.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,房子也還在
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.78,0:31:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會找到其他人的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.89,0:31:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.25,0:31:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.19,0:31:43.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯賓塞
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.16,0:31:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯賓塞  回來
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.25,0:31:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔拉
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.21,0:31:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯賓塞
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.02,0:31:58.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯賓塞  快給我回來
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.79,0:32:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯賓塞  快爬
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.04,0:32:17.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快  繼續爬
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.09,0:32:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快點  -尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.63,0:32:21.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓瑪姬和羅西塔從崗哨處開槍
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.01,0:32:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-為什么  -照做就是
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.20,0:32:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-塔拉  我良心會不安的  -快去
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.52,0:32:35.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯賓塞  上來
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.74,0:33:22.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抓緊
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.16,0:33:27.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔拉  你已經為這些人差點死過一次了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.44,0:33:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -你他媽的在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.40,0:33:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丟了只鞋  該死
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.68,0:33:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你剛在干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.96,0:33:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在幫忙  想找輛車引開它們
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.03,0:33:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前這樣爬過嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.90,0:33:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想幫忙的話  就不要讓我們反過來救你
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.66,0:33:54.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么主意  你先給我說
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.87,0:33:57.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會聽我的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:34:11.79,0:34:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在沒事了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.14,0:34:15.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,解決了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.78,0:34:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.34,0:34:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的小抄
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.41,0:34:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.97,0:34:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,估計沒能給你多少信念
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.61,0:34:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還有信念
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.75,0:34:46.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須有信念不是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.30,0:34:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是必須  是我選擇的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.67,0:34:51.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也該這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.34,0:34:55.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這次你會告訴我你來干什么嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.59,0:35:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,社區的抗生素庫存如何
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.30,0:35:03.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,夠用
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.49,0:35:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得包扎傷口
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.80,0:35:09.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不知道有沒有感染
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.61,0:35:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒必要的話我不想浪費藥物
Dialogue: 0,0:35:12.08,0:35:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,燒熱紅膿痛
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.06,0:35:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發燒  發熱  膿  疼痛和發紅
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.02,0:35:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.97,0:35:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,水腫
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.17,0:35:35.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看看你的手臂
Dialogue: 0,0:35:36.92,0:35:38.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我早上沒來
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.21,0:35:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我不想讓你卷入到
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.49,0:35:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你或許不愿卷入的事
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.82,0:35:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是個保密
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.21,0:35:51.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我的傷口
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.97,0:36:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你早上才照看了朱迪斯
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.89,0:36:54.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但斯賓塞那事之后
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.34,0:36:56.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哨崗需要人手  你能不能...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.18,0:36:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  沒問題
Dialogue: 0,0:36:57.41,0:36:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你想讓我替你的班
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.80,0:37:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用  我喜歡在上面
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.74,0:37:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使那么多行尸在外面嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.38,0:37:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能看到一切  包括里面
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.87,0:37:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把這些先放好
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.97,0:37:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能稍等會兒嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.32,0:37:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你要進來嗎  -好的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.79,0:37:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡蘿爾
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.70,0:37:29.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡蘿爾
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.55,0:37:31.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  山姆
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.69,0:37:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.19,0:37:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是你接受不了怎么辦
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.08,0:37:42.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我告訴過你  那會打垮你
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.82,0:37:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能下來嗎  我聽不清你說話
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.01,0:37:49.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來的那些人
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.09,0:37:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們是怪物嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.39,0:37:57.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸爸變成怪物了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.09,0:37:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.29,0:38:00.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你殺了人
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.14,0:38:04.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會變成怪物嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.78,0:38:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有殺人才不會變成怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.76,0:38:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-謝謝幫忙  -小事一樁
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.06,0:38:28.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再見
Dialogue: 0,0:38:38.99,0:38:40.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在里面關著誰
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.77,0:39:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,見到丹妮斯了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.56,0:39:32.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.77,0:39:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我馬上回來
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.46,0:39:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著  之前的事我很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.54,0:39:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我只是...  -他很蠢  這點我們知道
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.26,0:39:53.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的意思是  你不必為他那樣做
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.23,0:39:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.81,0:39:58.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有可能會死掉
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.13,0:40:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想說我想過這點
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.37,0:40:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:40:03.32,0:40:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你才那樣做嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.31,0:40:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為你沒好好想過
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.49,0:40:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我們就該這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.58,0:40:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們離不開彼此了  對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.79,0:40:18.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克  你救了我兒子
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.61,0:40:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.52,0:40:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝塔拉吧
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.16,0:40:24.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已經謝過了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.65,0:40:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在我要感謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.42,0:40:34.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯賓塞做的事很蠢
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.33,0:40:35.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒法反駁這點
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.57,0:40:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-至少他試過  -這不是重點
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.35,0:40:41.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才是真有可能試過
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.90,0:40:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當時有機會
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.85,0:40:44.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.97,0:40:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行尸追他時  出現了空隙
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.57,0:40:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以跳下去  跑出去
Dialogue: 0,0:40:51.54,0:40:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以坐上車
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.50,0:40:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用車引走行尸
Dialogue: 0,0:40:55.17,0:40:58.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以那樣做  然后斯賓塞就死了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:58.97,0:41:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你沒有那樣做
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.66,0:41:02.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.54,0:41:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我救他是因為他是你兒子
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.68,0:41:10.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,答錯了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.79,0:41:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是格倫  那是格倫
