[Script Info]
; // 此字幕由TimeM生成
; // 欢迎访问人人影视 http://www.YYeTs.net
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:1
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:02.03,0:00:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\an9\fs18\blur5}{\alpha&FF\t(0,5000,\alpha&00)}Blackbird Song\N{\fs14}{\alpha&FF\t(3000,5000,\alpha&00)}Lee DeWyze
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.87,0:00:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪Take your things♪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.32,0:00:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪Leave somehow♪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.84,0:00:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪Blackbird song♪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.97,0:00:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪Is over now♪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.58,0:01:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪Mouths are dry♪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.21,0:01:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪River runs♪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.79,0:01:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪Hands are tied♪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.55,0:01:31.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪Preacher's son♪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.18,0:01:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪Pack your things♪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.86,0:01:45.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪Leave somehow♪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.37,0:01:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪Blackbird song♪
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.09,0:01:58.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪Is over now♪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.98,0:02:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪Don't be scared♪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.82,0:02:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪I'm still here♪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.48,0:02:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪No more time♪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.15,0:02:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪For crying tears♪
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.27,0:03:07.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你去问问  -嗯  我来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You got point? - Yeah, I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.39,0:03:15.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有你一个人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just you out here?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.97,0:03:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.04,0:03:21.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这样漂泊了多久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How long's it been like that for?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.75,0:03:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.06,0:03:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前跟过两队人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was with one group and another one after that.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.29,0:03:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们没撑过来吗  两队都没有吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They didn't make it? Neither one of them?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.01,0:03:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫什么名字\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's your name?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.52,0:03:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲍勃·斯图基\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bob Stookey.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.00,0:03:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们有营地吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You people have a camp?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.97,0:03:52.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}瑞克的三个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.97,0:03:52.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀了多少行尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How many walkers have you killed?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.92,0:03:57.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没数过  十几个吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Haven't kept count. A couple dozen.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.27,0:03:58.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀了多少人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How many people you kill?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.33,0:04:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Only one.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.45,0:04:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.18,0:04:09.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她让我动手的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She asked me to.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.77,0:04:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想和我们一起走吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Want to come with us?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.62,0:04:21.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.93,0:04:23.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对我们有什么问题吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You got any questions for us?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.03,0:04:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.15,0:04:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是谁并不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It doesn't matter who you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.16,0:04:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.87,0:04:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.43,0:04:36.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.23,0:04:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad0\fscx7\fscy10\p1\c&H80BDC4&\move(257.4,185.291,248.067,183,120,1420)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.23,0:04:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad0\fscx7\fscy10\p1\c&HB1ECF3&\move(269,185.291,259.667,183,120,1420)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.23,0:04:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\bord0\shad0\fscx7\fscy10\p1\c&HBAF5FB&\move(257.4,185.291,248.067,183,120,1420)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.56,0:04:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\b1\fsp0.5\bord0\fn微软雅黑\shad0\c&H80BDC4&\move(285.333,219.901,256,221)}本字幕由人人影视字幕组翻译\N禁止用作任何商业盈利行为
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.22,0:04:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\b0\fsp0.5\fn微软雅黑\bord0\shad0\c&H7DDDE4&\move(276.799,160.315,263.467,160.315)}翻译  {\b1}森の鸟
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.72,0:04:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\b0\fsp0.5\bord0\shad0\fn微软雅黑\c&H82D7DA&\move(270,178,253.867,178)}翻译  {\b1}蘑菇
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.68,0:04:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\b0\fsp0.5\bord0\shad0\c&H7DDDE4&\fn微软雅黑\move(115,158,116,158)}翻译  {\b1}Reginamoon
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.89,0:04:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\b0\fsp0.5\bord0\fn微软雅黑\shad0\c&H000000&)\move(272,120,275,120)}翻译  {\b1}重案组李Sir
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.31,0:04:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\b0\fsp0.5\fn微软雅黑\bord0\shad0\c&H7DDDE4&\move(252,208,255,208)}翻译  {\b1}小饭
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.60,0:04:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\b0\fsp0.5\fn微软雅黑\bord0\shad0\c&H7DDDE4&\move(124,100,119,99)}听译  {\b1}CS小明漫画家
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.90,0:05:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\b0\fsp0.5\fn微软雅黑\bord0\shad0\c&H7DDDE4&\move(227,114,229,112)}翻译  {\b1}33来了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.78,0:05:05.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\b0\fsp0.5\fn微软雅黑\bord0\shad0\c&HB0ECE5&\pos(152,254)}翻译/校对  {\b1}冰蓝 卫老哥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.86,0:05:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\b0\fsp0.5\fn微软雅黑\bord0\shad0\c&H99E8E6&\move(178,244,172,244)}校对  {\b1}米小勒 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.11,0:05:09.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\b0\fsp0.5\fn微软雅黑\bord0\shad0\c&HB5E9EB&\pos(203,212)}时间轴  {\b1}雪贵人
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.74,0:05:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\b0\fsp0.5\fn微软雅黑\bord0\shad0\c&H7DDDE4&\pos(239,233)}时间轴  {\b1}涛涛  鸟の森
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.99,0:05:12.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\b0\fsp0.5\fn微软雅黑\bord0\shad0\c&HA7EDE7&\move(229,220,228,220)}后期  {\b1}、青衣
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.87,0:05:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs15\b0\fsp0.5\fn微软雅黑\bord0\shad0\c&H121C18&\move(224,149,226,145)}特效  {\b1}送小哥
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.12,0:05:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs14\b0\fsp0.5\fn微软雅黑\bord0\shad0\c&H00090B&\move(234,98,230,103)}总监  {\b1}送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.66,0:05:22.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn文鼎霹雳体\fsp5\fs64\shad0\bord0\clip(136,175,247,254)\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\alpha&HAF\t(40,40,\alpha&HFF\t(160,320,\alpha&H00\t(320,320,\clip(41,171,369,285))))}行尸{\c&H6DC0CC&}走肉\N{\b0\fs25\c&H4C9AB9&}第四季  {\c&H6DC0CC&}第十三集
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.85,0:06:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲍勃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bob!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.89,0:06:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maggie!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.09,0:06:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放开她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let go of her!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.82,0:06:33.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.66,0:06:50.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲍勃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bob.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.63,0:06:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.72,0:06:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它正好咬到了绷带\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He got me right on the bandage.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.81,0:07:01.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ow! Ow! Ow!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.07,0:07:04.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没说不让你抱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't say stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.88,0:07:05.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是叫疼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just said ow.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.85,0:07:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是叫疼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just said ow.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.41,0:07:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-接近了吗  -快了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Are we close? - Almost done.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.85,0:07:16.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How do you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.16,0:07:18.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到处都有踪迹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The signs are all there.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.61,0:07:19.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要学会辨位\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just got to know how to read 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.34,0:07:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在追踪什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are we tracking?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.47,0:07:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You tell me.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.64,0:07:29.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你想学的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're the one who wanted to learn.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.99,0:07:34.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有东西经过了这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, something came through here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.52,0:07:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路线弯弯曲曲的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The pattern is all zig-zaggy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.51,0:07:39.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是行尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a walker.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.84,0:07:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是个醉汉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe it's a drunk.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.76,0:07:45.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我越来越擅长了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm getting good at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.38,0:07:48.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快我就不需要你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pretty soon I won't need you at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.07,0:07:51.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  继续追踪吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, keep on tracking.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.97,0:07:57.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它有一把枪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's got a gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.59,0:08:34.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,脚能动吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you move it?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.02,0:08:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.19,0:08:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.82,0:08:46.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该等到雾散\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We should wait till the fog clears.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.27,0:08:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们已经等了一阵了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've been waiting a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.93,0:08:50.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们刚只是幸运而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You see all this? We got lucky.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.61,0:08:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要能见度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need visibility.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.68,0:08:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只剩六发子弹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've got six bullets left.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.41,0:08:55.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说的对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.04,0:08:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们按计划行事一直很顺利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've been doing good following the plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.55,0:08:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不能草率\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No need to get sloppy now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.87,0:09:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.43,0:09:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坏了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's broken.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.75,0:09:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不需要这个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We don't need it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.18,0:09:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太阳东升西落\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sun comes up in the east, sets in the west.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.45,0:09:19.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意观察就行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll keep an eye on it in between.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.11,0:09:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.14,0:09:36.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能等一会儿吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can we-- can we hold up a sec?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.32,0:09:37.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.79,0:09:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐一会儿就好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just need to sit down.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.76,0:09:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right. Hold up.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.11,0:09:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hop on.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.60,0:09:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你说真的吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Are you serious? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.71,0:09:55.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来背你  跳上来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is a serious piggyback. Jump up.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.88,0:10:01.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你比看起来要重\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're heavier than you look.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.16,0:10:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里可能还有人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe there are people there.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.82,0:10:09.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有  我来收拾他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, if there are, I'll handle them.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.62,0:10:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是有好人的  达里尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There are still good people, Daryl.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.44,0:10:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不认为好人能活下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't think the good ones survive.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.09,0:10:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正黑体简体\fs25\fsp2\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&HAFB4BA&\pos(195,260)\frz1.5\c&H4C4F55&}生于1837年11月12日\N卒于1874年12月10日\N慈父
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.09,0:11:14.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.35,0:11:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,0)\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1}避难所和社区欢迎所有人  抵达就能活命
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.76,0:11:24.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,终点站\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Terminus.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.32,0:11:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去兽医院的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When we were out on the run to the veterinary college,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.08,0:11:29.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在广播上听过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we heard a message about this on the radio.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.04,0:11:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他们在广播吗  -说了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- They were broadcasting? - What did it say?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.90,0:11:34.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没听清\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Couldn't make it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.40,0:11:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在看了这个才明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I only know because I'm seeing it now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.18,0:11:38.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"抵达就能活命"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Those who arrive survive."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.29,0:11:42.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We should go.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.18,0:11:44.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是在找格伦吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought we were looking for Glenn.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.62,0:11:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他看到这样的牌子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If he saw one of these,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.91,0:11:47.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会知道我去这里找他了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}he would go looking for me looking for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.53,0:11:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这地图  所有路线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look at this map. All these tracks
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.03,0:11:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都通往同一个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}from different directions leading to the same place.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.56,0:11:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太远了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's far.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.74,0:11:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,况且我们不知道有没有其它的牌子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And we don't know if there are other signs.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.35,0:11:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会认为只有这一个吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't think this is the only one.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.89,0:11:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是目前最好的线索了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is the best lead we've had so far.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.62,0:12:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上面说是避难所  更值得试一下了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It says sanctuary. That's just another reason to try.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.70,0:12:04.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,监狱里的其他人也可能去那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Others from the prison could be there.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.04,0:12:04.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如泰尔西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tyreese.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.90,0:12:06.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些事如果听上去太美好...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If it sounds too good to be true...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.11,0:12:09.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许格伦看到这牌子后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe if Glenn saw one of these,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.26,0:12:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想法和我一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}maybe he felt the same way.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.75,0:12:13.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不会的  我知道他有信念\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He wouldn't. He'd believe, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.01,0:12:15.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你想怎样  萨沙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you want to do, Sasha?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.17,0:12:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,围着大巴绕圈吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Keep making these circles from the bus?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.88,0:12:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是让我们做别的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or are you talking about us starting to do something else?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.00,0:12:24.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能分开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're not splitting up.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.38,0:12:26.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That can't happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.96,0:12:30.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是想投票还是怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want to take a vote or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.66,0:12:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不必投票\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We don't need to vote.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.17,0:13:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give it a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.44,0:13:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真干净\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's so clean.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.13,0:13:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人在打扫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Someone's been tending to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.00,0:13:26.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那人也许还在附近\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}May still be around.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.12,0:14:08.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你的脚踝包扎一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's get that ankle wrapped.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.31,0:14:17.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来某人没洋娃娃来玩穿衣游戏了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Looks like somebody ran out of dolls to dress up.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.96,0:14:19.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很美的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.06,0:14:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做这事的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whoever did this
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.64,0:14:23.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在乎这些人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}cared.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.71,0:14:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们希望这些人能有一场葬礼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They wanted these people to get a funeral.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.70,0:14:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们还记得它们曾经是人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They remembered these things were people
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.93,0:14:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在一切发生之前是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}before all this.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.20,0:14:36.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在最后一刻依然是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They didn't let it change them in the end.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.99,0:14:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不觉得这很美吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't you think that's beautiful?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.17,0:14:46.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.53,0:15:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬人呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where's Maggie?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.56,0:15:01.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去拾柴火了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Getting more firewood.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.32,0:15:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在流血吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Still bleeding?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.61,0:15:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不太流了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Barely.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.60,0:15:12.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So tell me...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.73,0:15:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉你什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell you what?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.12,0:15:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我们应该停下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You think we should stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.63,0:15:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.02,0:15:25.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell me why.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.23,0:15:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了活下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}To not die.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.17,0:15:32.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你  玛姬  我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You, Maggie, me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.02,0:15:33.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是因为这个呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, that's not it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.35,0:15:34.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.26,0:15:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你不明白自己为什么想停下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't think you know why you want to stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.10,0:15:39.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲍勃  今早发生的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bob, what happened this morning,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.71,0:15:42.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是对我们的警告\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we get warnings.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.06,0:15:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们挺过来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We did fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.33,0:15:45.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个警告\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We get warnings.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.61,0:15:49.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次我们就完了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And the next time it's on us.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.62,0:15:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格伦可能已经死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Odds are Glenn is dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.78,0:15:59.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也可能会死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Odds are we will be, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.87,0:16:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是现实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's the reality.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.39,0:16:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只剩六发子弹  而且你还在流血\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We got six bullets and you're still bleeding.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.37,0:16:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些轨道会穿过一些城镇\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Those tracks, they run through towns.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.04,0:16:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在最近的城里找座房子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The first one we see, we find a building,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.03,0:16:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在制高点栖身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}some higher ground to set up in. All of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.22,0:16:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才是我们该做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what we need to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.04,0:16:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也是我们要做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what we're gonna do.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.71,0:16:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能说服她的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If we can talk her into it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.26,0:16:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑一下吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just think about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.53,0:16:48.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dang.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.37,0:16:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有收获吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You find anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.74,0:16:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花生酱和果酱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Peanut butter and jelly,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.68,0:16:59.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无糖汽水  还有猪蹄罐头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}diet soda, and pig's feet.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.60,0:17:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,标准的懒汉早午餐\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's a white trash brunch right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.81,0:17:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得挺好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It all looks good to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.93,0:17:07.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, hold up.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.96,0:17:09.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些东西一尘不染\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ain't a speck of dust on this.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.99,0:17:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.20,0:17:15.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说明是有人刚放进去的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That means somebody just put it here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.69,0:17:17.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是某人的补给\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is someone's stash.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.33,0:17:18.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他们还活着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe they're still alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.35,0:17:21.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我们就拿一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, we'll take some
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.52,0:17:23.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他都留下  行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of it and we'll leave the rest, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.52,0:17:25.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I knew it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.82,0:17:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Knew what?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.28,0:17:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像我之前说的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's like I said.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.73,0:17:30.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是有好人的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There are still good people.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.40,0:17:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恶心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Gross.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.01,0:17:40.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,猪蹄归我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, those pig's feet are mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.26,0:17:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,♪夏日的松树♪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}♪Pine for summer♪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.92,0:17:54.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,♪然后我们要买♪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}♪Then we'll buy♪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.40,0:17:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,♪一瓶啤酒一饮而尽♪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}♪A beer to shotgun♪
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.52,0:18:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,♪我们要躺在草地上♪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}♪We'll lay on our lawn♪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.97,0:18:05.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,♪我们将一切安好♪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}♪And we'll be good...♪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.99,0:18:13.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里封锁好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The place is nailed up tight.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.22,0:18:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唯一的入口是前门\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The only way in is through the front door.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.30,0:18:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.99,0:18:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我几年来睡过最舒服的床了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is the comfiest bed I've had in years.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.17,0:18:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.38,0:18:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没开玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I ain't kidding.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.93,0:18:41.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你继续弹吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why don't you go ahead and play some more?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.77,0:18:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接着唱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Keep singing.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.99,0:18:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是讨厌我唱歌吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought my singing annoyed you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.80,0:18:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里没有点唱机  所以...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There ain't no jukebox, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.46,0:18:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,♪然后我们要买♪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}♪And we'll buy...♪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.80,0:19:01.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,♪一瓶啤酒一饮而尽♪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}♪A beer to shotgun♪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.86,0:19:05.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,♪我们要躺在草地上♪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}♪We'll lay on the lawn♪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.28,0:19:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,♪我们将一切安好♪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}♪And we'll be good♪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.25,0:19:13.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,♪如今我嘲笑着我的无聊♪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}♪Now I'm laughing at my boredom♪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.65,0:19:17.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,♪和我失败的尝试...♪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}♪And my string of failed attempts...♪
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.62,0:19:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲍勃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bob?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.29,0:19:47.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}别为了我冒险\N祝好运
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.40,0:19:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲍勃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bob.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.63,0:19:55.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.02,0:19:57.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她肯定顺着轨道走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's got to follow the tracks.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.01,0:19:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还能跟上她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can still catch up to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.09,0:20:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨沙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sasha,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.60,0:20:07.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还能跟上她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we can still catch up to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.79,0:20:31.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1}避难所和社区欢迎所有人  抵达就能活命
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.70,0:21:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自从平安地逃离监狱后  你就一直笑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have been grinning since we left the prison in one piece.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.18,0:21:23.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果活着让你这么开心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you're so happy to be alive,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.29,0:21:25.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们为什么还要朝黑暗的深处走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}then why are we walking into the heart of darkness?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.47,0:21:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这和我活着没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not about me being alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.84,0:21:33.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你知道自己为什么笑么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you even know why you're smiling?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.47,0:21:35.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.56,0:21:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我没落单\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.38,0:21:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,失去第一队人后  我落单了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's how it happened when I lost my first group.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.12,0:21:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二队也不例外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And my second group.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.33,0:21:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我破了这个记录\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I broke that streak.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.20,0:21:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,换做是你  也会笑的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You'd be smiling, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.09,0:21:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自我意识真是个好东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Self-awareness is a beautiful thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.67,0:21:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你哪天也该试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You should try it sometime.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.31,0:22:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么  不打算接话吗  -才不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Oh, you're not going to take the bait? - Nope.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.66,0:22:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有时候真跟她一样倔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're just as bullheaded as she is sometimes. You know that?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.57,0:22:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(500,0)\fn方正黑体简体\fs20\b1\bord1\shad1\c&H2B2B39&\3c&HE3E3E4&\pos(160.8,45.727)}格伦\N{\fs18}去终点站\N\h\h\h\h玛姬留
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.17,0:22:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.42,0:22:30.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正全速前进呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Going as fast as I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.01,0:22:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Forget that.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.59,0:22:37.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.79,0:22:43.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.21,0:22:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开吃吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.72,0:22:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.60,0:23:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一条该死的狗而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's just a damn dog.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.51,0:23:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来  孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come here, boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.33,0:23:20.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它不进来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He wouldn't come in?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.40,0:23:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫你别动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I told you to stay back.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.16,0:23:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是呀  但你不是说有条狗吗  达里尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, but, Daryl, you said there was a dog.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.09,0:23:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定它会跑回来  走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe he'll come back around. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.21,0:23:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我睡不着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm awake.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.43,0:23:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So am I.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.17,0:23:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看见它了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can you see it?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.61,0:23:55.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看不到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.40,0:23:57.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它这样快一个小时了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Been that way for an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.36,0:23:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定被卡住了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Might be stuck on something.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.21,0:24:04.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚上的声音真多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's a lot of noise at night.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.14,0:24:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蝉  猫头鹰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Cicadas, owls.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.21,0:24:10.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们真是阴魂不散\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think sometimes they go in circles.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.40,0:24:13.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我一个人时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Still, when I was out here by myself,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.97,0:24:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总是睡不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't sleep much.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.08,0:24:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你现在也睡不好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're not sleeping much now.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.57,0:24:20.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你需要睡觉养伤\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've got to heal. You need to sleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.51,0:24:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can try.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.61,0:24:41.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试过了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I tried.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.48,0:24:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲍勃  我们在这里算是干什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bob, what the hell are we doing out here?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.68,0:24:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你认为泰尔西死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why do you think Tyreese is dead?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.60,0:25:05.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -如果泰尔西活着  他会去终点站\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What? - If Tyreese were alive, he'd go for Terminus.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.71,0:25:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很清楚这一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know you know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.66,0:25:10.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么你认为他死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So why do you think he's dead?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.89,0:25:14.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你害怕知道他的生死吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or are you just too afraid to find out if he is or not?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.22,0:25:25.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,目前为止  我都觉得你是我遇到最顽强的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Up until now, I thought you were the toughest person I ever met.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.78,0:25:27.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说起来有点怪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Which is kind of weird,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.52,0:25:30.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你也是最贴心的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'cause you were the sweetest, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.81,0:25:33.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说说而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just saying.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.93,0:25:53.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要留一张感谢卡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna leave a thank-you note.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.76,0:25:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.22,0:26:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们回来能看见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For when they come back.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.25,0:26:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们会回来的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If they come back.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.87,0:26:07.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算他们不回来  我还是想说谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even if they're not coming back, I still want to say thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.11,0:26:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你不用留话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe you don't have to leave that.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.68,0:26:18.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我们可以在这里住一阵子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe we stick around here for a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.01,0:26:22.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们回来后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They come back,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.39,0:26:24.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以想办法共处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we'll just make it work.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.05,0:26:27.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他们脑袋不正常\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They may be nuts,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.65,0:26:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也许一切都会安好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but maybe it'll be all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.13,0:26:37.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你觉得还是有好人的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So you do think there are still good people around.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.26,0:26:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么改变了你的想法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What changed your mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:47.54,0:26:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.69,0:26:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.50,0:27:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.57,0:27:01.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别哼唧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.06,0:27:05.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么改变了你的想法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What changed your mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.67,0:27:24.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再给那条狗一次机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna give that mutt one more chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.68,0:27:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝丝  贝丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Beth! Beth!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.21,0:27:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快跑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Run!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:36.78,0:27:37.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快跑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Run!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.55,0:27:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝丝  撬开窗户  拿上你的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Beth, pry open a window. Get your shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.49,0:27:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会丢下你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not gonna leave you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.78,0:27:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出去  去路上  我去那里找你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go out. Go up the road. I'll meet you there.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.56,0:27:53.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.54,0:27:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This way.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.56,0:29:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝丝  贝丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Beth! Beth!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.77,0:29:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贝丝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Beth!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.15,0:29:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\fad(500,0)\fn方正黑体简体\fs20\b1\bord1\shad1\c&H2B2B39&\3c&HE3E3E4&\pos(306.6,10.429)}格伦\N{\fs18}去终点站\N\h\h\h\h玛姬留
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.90,0:29:38.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是沿着轨道走的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's keeping to the tracks.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.44,0:29:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们加快速度  就能追上她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If we pick up the pace, we'll catch her.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.20,0:31:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲍勃  那边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bob, right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.37,0:31:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高且安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Secure and high up.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.07,0:31:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们搭个东西接雨水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See if we can set up something to catch the rain.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.28,0:31:13.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在屋顶上瞭望  寻找食物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See if we could move from the rooftops to look for food.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.58,0:31:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在上面种点东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe even try to grow some up there.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.35,0:31:16.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨沙  我不会停下来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sasha, I'm not stopping.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.70,0:31:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就留在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We are.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.09,0:31:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.02,0:31:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她孤身在外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's out there alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.75,0:31:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不想让我们去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She didn't want us to come.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.86,0:31:32.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她做出了自己的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She made her choice for her.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.07,0:31:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不在乎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.57,0:31:36.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她落单了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.94,0:31:40.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚到监狱时心想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When I got to the prison, I thought to myself,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.37,0:31:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时光飞逝  还要多久\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"How long? The clock's ticking.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.18,0:31:44.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他人会死光\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How long until everyone else is dead
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.72,0:31:46.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又只剩下我一人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I'm on my own?"
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.41,0:31:49.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我害怕  才发生了坏事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bad things happened 'cause I was scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.55,0:31:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些事未必会发生  我不用害怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They didn't need to. I didn't need to be afraid.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.02,0:31:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果到了终点站  泰尔西不在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now we get to Terminus and Tyreese isn't there,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.92,0:31:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不意味着他死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it doesn't mean he's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.93,0:32:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你不用害怕  -我没有害怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You don't need to be afraid. - I am not afraid.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.91,0:32:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们就此分别了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So this is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.78,0:32:18.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不一定非要分开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It doesn't have to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.43,0:32:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.85,0:32:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要冒险做件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna try something here.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.82,0:32:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.19,0:33:00.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不必这样做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't have to do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.16,0:33:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不必再孤单一人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't have to be alone again.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.27,0:33:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I won't be.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.05,0:35:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maggie?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.76,0:35:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.80,0:36:39.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲍勃呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where's Bob?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.46,0:36:41.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去找你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Out looking for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.69,0:36:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why are you here?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.76,0:36:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想找只行尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was looking for another walker.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.67,0:36:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果碰到了好多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Found more than I wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.24,0:36:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我躺在那的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, I was lying there
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.21,0:36:57.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I remembered--
Dialogue: 0,0:36:57.24,0:36:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听见了你在营地说的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I heard what you said back at the camp.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.78,0:37:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听见你说  你认为我们应该\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I heard you say you thought we should
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.38,0:37:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留在镇上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}be in a town.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.02,0:37:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还听见我说什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What else did you hear me say?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.17,0:37:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格伦可能已经死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That odds are Glenn is dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.33,0:37:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该停下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And we should stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.94,0:37:28.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But you're wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.88,0:37:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你为什么还在这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So why are you here?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.38,0:37:42.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我在等你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'Cause I was waiting for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:44.88,0:37:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会放弃的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not giving up.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.96,0:37:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我需要你的帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I need your help.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.50,0:37:54.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一个人没法做到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'Cause I can't do it by myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.00,0:37:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算我赶上鲍勃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And even if I catch up to Bob,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.82,0:38:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光靠我跟他也做不到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we can't do it alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.22,0:38:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本以为我不敢求你以身犯险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought that I couldn't ask you to risk your life.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.41,0:38:10.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我可以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.42,0:38:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我知道你冒险为的是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'Cause I know what you'd be risking it for.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.74,0:38:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不止是为了格伦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And it isn't just Glenn.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.46,0:38:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你害怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I get that you're afraid.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.12,0:38:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.83,0:38:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我害怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I am afraid.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.19,0:38:31.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以做到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We could get there.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.69,0:38:33.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:40.21,0:38:42.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去找鲍勃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So let's go get Bob...
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.52,0:38:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后去避难所吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and let's get there.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.00,0:39:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, look it here.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.75,0:39:18.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死  等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Damn it, hold up!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.17,0:39:20.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的背心我要了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm claiming the vest.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.19,0:39:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢上面的翅膀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I like them wings.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.91,0:39:25.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别轻举妄动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hold up.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.90,0:39:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弩手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A bowman.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.27,0:39:45.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很敬佩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I respect that.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.71,0:39:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿着来复枪的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See, a man with a rifle,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.17,0:39:49.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前可能是摄影师\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}he could have been some kind of photographer
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.65,0:39:51.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或足球教练\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or soccer coach back in the day.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.62,0:39:55.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但弩手自始至终不会变\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But a bowman's a bowman through and through.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.22,0:39:57.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你手上拿的是150磅张弓力吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What you got there, 150-pound draw weight?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.30,0:39:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那东西的速度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll be donkey-licked if
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.62,0:40:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能达到每秒三百英尺  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that don't fire at least 300 feet per second.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:03.43,0:40:05.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直在找这样的武器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been looking for a weapon like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.31,0:40:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然了  最好能多几支箭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Of course, I'd want one with a bit more ammo
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.48,0:40:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少点污渍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and minus the oblongata stains.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.46,0:40:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你遇到麻烦了吗  老兄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get yourself in some trouble, partner?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.25,0:40:19.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你扣下扳机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You pull that trigger,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:20.51,0:40:22.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会把你射成蜂窝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}these boys are gonna drop you several times over.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.96,0:40:23.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That what you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:25.25,0:40:27.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样伙计  自杀多蠢啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, fella, suicide is stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:29.19,0:40:31.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害己不如害人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why hurt yourself when you can hurt other people?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:38.96,0:40:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我叫乔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Name's Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.52,0:40:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Daryl.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.17,0:41:05.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪No more time♪
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.79,0:41:11.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fad(300,300)\fn微软雅黑\t(\fsp0.5)}♪For crying tears♪
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.43,0:41:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鲍勃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bob.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:07.30,0:42:13.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\fad(500,500)\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1}避难所和社区欢迎所有人  抵达就能活命
Dialogue: 0,0:42:11.81,0:42:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\fs25\bord0\shad0\fn方正稚艺_GBK\b1}终点站
