- Howdy-ho, you South Parketeers.
- Howdy-ho!
- I'm rootin'-tootin' Trey.
- I'm pistol-slinging Matt.
- This here's Scratch. Say hi, fella.
- Hi, Scratch!
We're right excited about this next
episode because it's our favorite one.
It's called "Starvin' Marvin,"
and it aired on Thanksgiving.
In it, the boys celebrate
the holiday with a visitor.
When Comedy Central asked us
to do a Thanksgiving special...
...my first thought was, "I'd like
to have sex with Jennifer Aniston."
Cup her perky breasts in my hands and
put my hand on her nice, tight buns.
This episode teaches
racial tolerance...
...to treat everyone equally,
regardless of skin color.
It's our Indian friend
Indian Companion. Say hi, kids.
- What's happening, Indian Companion?
- Something coming. Grizzly bear.
Why don't you go over and kick him
in the balls? Grizzly bears like that.
- Dumb-ass.
- He's so stupid.
Y'all sit back and have
a rootin'-tootin' good time...
...with "Starvin' Marvin." Yee-haw!
Hooray!
Starvin' Marvin
- That was awesome.
- Would you boys like Cheesy Poofs?
Move! The Terrance & Phillip
Thanksgiving Special is on.
- Sure.
- Yeah, we want Cheesy Poofs.
Terrance, looks like a good place
to start a colony.
It sure does, Phillip. No one
will repress our religion here.
- You stained my hat!
- Did you see that? That was sweet.
Coming up next on the special,
Phillip farts on Terrance and laughs.
- Cool!
- Now a word from our sponsor.
In Africa, children are dying, not
from disease or war but from hunger.
I'm Sally Struthers.
These children are in desperate need.
- Who's that fat chick?
- Sally Struthers.
She was on Full House.
Here in the middle of Africa,
food is extremely scarce.
She's not having
trouble finding food.
- She's fatter than Cartman.
- Yeah. Hey!
- Just $5 a month can sponsor a child.
- That's stupid. Who'd want to do that?
Sponsor now, and we'll send you
a Teiko sports watch as a free gift.
- Kick-ass!
- Sweet!
- I know my mom's credit-card number.
- Is it waterproof?
- Hello, is this Sally Struthers?
- What did she say?
- Shut up, butt pirate!
- Ass-rammer.
- We wanna adopt a starving Ethernopian.
- When do we get the watch?
- Just a second, fat-ass!
- You vas deferens.
Hello? No, it's a... Vas deferens?
- Ask if we get the watch right away.
- Do we get the watch right away?
- She says we do.
- Cool.
I get to wear it first.
- I can't wait to get our Teiko watch.
- But I get to wear it first.
To honor this special time of year,
we'll be doing a canned-food drive.
Anybody know what a
canned-food drive is? Yes, Eric.
When they cut up a chick's stomach
to get a baby out?
That's a cesarean section.
That's okay. There are no stupid
questions, just stupid people.
It's when we collect food for people
who can't afford food on Thanksgiving.
- You mean like Kenny?
- Exactly.
Mr. Garrison, why do poor people
always smell like sour milk?
I don't know, Eric. They just do.
I want everyone
to bring a can of food.
The mayor will divide it up amongst
Kenny's family and other poor people.
- I won't bring food. Screw them!
- How about helping the less fortunate?
Do you hear something?
I think I hear flower children calling.
This is the one time of year
to care about people who can't eat.
Isn't it enough that I pay taxes?
What about the poorhouses I pay for?
Many would rather die than go there.
They should,
and decrease the population.
That's enough Dickens for one day.
- On with our lesson, right, Mr. Hat?
- Right, Mr. Garrison.
Engelbert Humperdinck was the first
man on the moon. Who was the second?
What the hell is going on?
You don't see that every day.
Now, once we have all
the canned foods collected...
...we'll need some clever way
to distribute them to the poor.
It should be something festive.
Mayor, we've got a very big problem.
You're that insane
genetic engineer, right?
Yes, and I may have made
a horrible mistake.
I was genetically engineering
turkeys for Thanksgiving...
...to provide food for the needy.
Something went wrong,
the turkeys broke free.
The worst part is,
they're really pissed off.
Naturally.
Oh, do go on.
We have to stop them, or they could
destroy everything. Time is short.
- You were saying?
- They act normal, but they're evil.
Oh, my.
- You're not taking me seriously.
- Why would you say that?
- Did it come?
- Is it here?
I get to use it first, you guys.
- Did our digital sports watch come?
- Not yet, hon.
- Damn.
- Hey, look, you guys.
Now back to part two of The Terrance
& Phillip Thanksgiving Special.
- I sure am cold, Phillip.
- Yes, and hungry too.
- Being a pilgrim totally sucks ass.
- Gosh, I hope we don't starve.
A squeaker!
The digital sports watch is here!
What the hell?
- That's not a digital sports watch.
- It looks like an Etheropian.
They accidentally sent him
instead of the watch.
Maybe they took it literally
when we said we'd adopt a kid.
- That was cool.
- How'd he make those clicking sounds?
What's your name, dude?
- I think he said his name is Marvin.
- Yeah, Starvin' Marvin.
Nice to meet you.
- Hey, Mom.
- Yes, hon?
We found an Etheropian.
Can we keep him?
- Sure, hon.
- Sweet.
- Let's bring him to school.
- I want you to meet my brother.
He's my son. I adopted him.
- It was my mom's card.
- We'll switch off.
He'll stay here.
Then with Stan, then me.
- Not with Kenny. His family's too poor.
- Totally.
Look how the leaves fall so delicately
on the surface of the pond.
It's so beautiful.
Not as beautiful as you.
Darling, look. Thanksgiving turkeys.
They're so beautiful.
Not as beautiful as you.
Look at the way they foam at the mouth
like beautiful suds of beer.
Not as beautiful as...
This is a great way
to experience America.
This is an all-you-can-eat buffet.
You can eat all you want for $6.99.
That's why we all come on Tuesdays.
Except for Kenny's family.
To them, $6.99 is two years' income.
Why is your family poor?
Is your dad an alcoholic too?
You see, Starvin' Marvin,
these are called appetizers.
Appetizer.
This is what you eat before you eat
to make you more hungry.
Food's here.
That's it for the appetizers.
No, that's my potpie.
This is the time of year
you're supposed to share.
You're right.
You gonna eat your cobbler?
No, you don't want all that.
Why don't you share it with me?
Let me just have some of that.
I'm a little disappointed
in your Thanksgiving spirit.
Only a few cans have been donated
to our food drive.
And can't we do a little better
than creamed corn...
...creamed corn and creamed corn?
Bring in more diverse food...
...or else Kenny's family will have
a pretty corny Thanksgiving.
Corny Thanksgiving!
Anyway, some of you have brought
something special for show-and-tell.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, we did.
All right, boys.
Show us what you've brought.
This is our new Ethernopian:
Starvin' Marvin.
He can do cool stuff
with his voice. Show them.
No, Starvin' Marvin,
that's Kenny's creamed corn.
That's a bad Starvin' Marvin!
What the hell are you doing?
This is horribly wrong.
- How did you get him?
- He came instead of the sports watch.
- From the commercial?
- Yeah, that one.
- I want a Starvin' Marvin.
- Me too.
- Yes, I'll pay $50 for one.
- I want one!
You're too young to take care of him.
I'll call the Red Cross
and have him returned.
We shouldn't have brought him here.
Thank you very much.
You can pick him up tonight. Bye.
- I hope you've learned your lesson.
- No.
- You can't care for him.
- I thought we were supposed to.
But you don't get involved
with the child.
You send money,
and they write you a letter.
He didn't grow up
in a normal place like here.
- Why can't he live here now?
- Because he can't.
- Because why?
- Because 8-year-olds can't be parents!
- Then you take care of him.
- I can't. I'm very busy.
I send my $5 a month, see?
- This sucks, he's our friend.
- Back to the poor country with you.
Watch what you say.
You might be poor and hungry someday.
Yeah, right.
I knew you were
the only person who'd listen.
Let's get it over with.
This gives me the booboo-jeebies.
Look here in my microscope.
Tell me what you see.
I see an extreme close-up...
...of Vanessa Redgrave's
private parts.
Now tell me what you see.
Well, I'm no biologist...
...but it looks like turkey DNA.
- Precisely.
- Look how rapidly it's dividing.
- What's it mean?
The turkeys are growing exponentially.
If we don't destroy them,
they'll take over the town.
- Maybe the world.
- Oh, fudge!
Let me see that
Vanessa Redgrave thing again.
Sure.
We're looking for
a starving African child...
...who was accidentally sent here
instead of a Teiko sports watch.
Hey, what's going on? Let go of me!
I'll kick you in the nuts!
Here's your sports watch, son.
Sorry for the mix-up.
Now you're pissing me off!
Sweet.
- So how does this thing work?
- It's based on the cash grab.
Instead of money,
cans are in the capsule.
The pov catches as many as he can.
- "Pov"?
- Poverty stricken citizen.
Oh, brilliant.
- What the hell is this?
- I don't know, mayor.
- It's not on the program.
- They're increasing in number.
These are the turkeys
I warned you about.
It's true, mayor. Those turkeys
just ripped apart my cafeteria.
You won't get away
with this, you bastards!
Those are some pissed off turkeys.
Okay, people, don't panic!
Bring out the defense squad!
We need more than that.
They'll come back in larger numbers.
- Phillip, could you pass the beans?
- Beans?
Looks like we'll be at war
with these Indians soon.
Wait, wait, wait.
Here it comes.
I crapped in my pants!
I think you got some spat
on Chief Running Wolf.
I spatted his face.
Now he's a smelly Indian.
We'll be back to part 1 4
of Terrance & Phillip...
...right after this.
Hunger is an enemy
that we all must fight.
These children desperately
need your support.
Somebody get me out of here!
This sucks!
So please call
and adopt a child today.
I'm seriously getting pissed off!
- You want more Cheesy Poofs?
- Yeah, I want the Cheesy Poofs.
Okay.
Sweet.
This is serious bullsh *t!
There has to be a Happy Burger
around here.
Excuse me, I am a lost little boy.
Could you help me?
Well, screw you too!
Who let these flies in here? Hasn't
anybody heard of insect repellent?
All right, everyone, it's time
to give out canned food to the poor.
- Where's Cartman?
- I don't know.
Do you know where he is?
Looks like we have
the turkey problem under control.
It's time to embrace the spirit
of giving with the canned-food grab.
Come on, hurry up.
Grab a lot, son.
Happy, happy Thanksgiving.
Let her rip!
Come on, grab those cans, little boy!
- Come on, Kenny!
- Come on, son!
Now, let's see all the goodies you're
going to take home to your family.
It looks like he got
a can of string beans.
- What the...?
- Dude, the mutant turkeys are back.
Okay, people, move along.
Nothing to see here, you looky-Ioos.
- I told you, but you didn't listen.
- Gather around and listen good.
Go to your homes and arm your...
- What the hell are you supposed to be?
- That's not important right now.
What's this thing supposed to be?
It doesn't look like anything.
- Chef, the turkeys.
- All right.
Listen up and listen good.
Go to your homes and arm yourselves
with whatever you can.
We'll meet back here
in 1 5 minutes. Hurry.
We won't let our Thanksgiving
be ruined by a bunch of turkeys.
Dang, you guys.
Seriously, I'm hungry.
I have to eat.
Sweet, the Red Cross.
I'll have fried chicken
and mashed potatoes, please.
Sorry, we're out of food.
We ran out of funding.
We couldn't get enough sponsors,
so we gotta pack it up.
I'm not an Ethernopian.
I gotta get home!
Sorry, we just don't have any funds.
Here, have a Teiko sports watch.
Weak!
People, we all have to do our part
against the evil turkeys.
- There's too many of them.
- Come on.
- Where is that Thanksgiving spirit?
- We can't stop them.
Today, you fight for your city.
You fight for your honor.
These turkeys will continue to push...
...until they have taken
everything from us.
These fudged-up turkeys from the
crustaceous era can take our lives...
...but they can never take
our freedom!
Here you go, turkeys.
Does my hair look okay?
Can't go on.
Need appetizer.
I'm sorry, God.
I'm sorry I mocked poor people.
I'm sorry I wasn't more sensitive.
Please.
Please, God.
My God has forsaken me.
I wonder what's in here?
Snacky Cakes!
- Sally Struthers?
- Who the hell are you?
- Give me that cake!
- No, this is my cake.
- Sally Struthers, give me that cake.
- No, you can't have any.
You guys, Sally Struthers is
holding food from us!
Stay close, children.
- Oh, my God, they've killed Kenny!
- You bastards!
The last three are getting away!
Shoot them!
- We did it!
- My God, what have we done?
We've saved Thanksgiving.
But those poor turkeys,
they're all dead.
Every turkey dies.
Not every turkey truly lives.
As horrible as they were,
they felt like a part of me.
Perhaps I shouldn't toy with
God's creations. Perhaps I should...
We're looking for
a starving Ethiopian boy...
...who was accidentally delivered
instead of a Teiko sports watch.
Have you seen anyone like this?
That could be a hundred kids
in this town, mister.
There you are.
Are you ready to go home now?
- It sucks he has to leave.
- I like him a lot more than Cartman.
I've learned something today.
It's easy not to think of images
on TV as real, but they are.
That's why it's easy to ignore those
commercials, but people on TV are real.
That means MacGyver's real too.
We're terribly sorry about the mix-up.
We'll get you home immediately.
That's right, you will.
Move it povs, I'm an American!
Lord, on this day of thanks,
we extend our deepest gratitude...
...for this incredible bounty of green
beans you have bestowed upon us.
Though you, for some reason, found it
necessary to take our son...
...and though you find pleasure
in watching us suffer...
...still, we give thanks. Amen.
Amen.
Does anybody have a can opener?
Goddamn it.