-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Proudly Presents
i'm goin' down to south park gonna have myself a time
friendly faces everywhere humble folks without temptation
goin' down to south park gonna leave my woes behind
ample parking day or night people spouting howdy neighbor
heading on up to south park gonna see if i can't unwind
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Sync: YTET-ÌìÍâ·É×©
come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine
south park.s13e14
we're goin' to the water park
The water park,the water park,
We're goingto the water park
Me andall my best friends,
Except for kyle,who i don't like,
okay,cartman.You can stop singing now.
This is gonna beso awesome,dude.
I haven't been to the water parkin like,over a year!
What do you guyswanna do first?
I hear they havea new innertube slide.
No,dude.We gotta dothe wave pool first.
It's so dope.As long as therearen't any minorities.
What are youtalking about,eric?
You know,there's always like five or six minorities wearingtheir tshirts
in the wave  pool.Pisses me off.
We're here!It's the water park.
Pi Pi's SPLASHTOWN
I'm gonna pick you boys upright here at 4:00,you got it?
Come on,let's go!
We got it,dad.
Six adorable children,please.
Wave pool!Wave pool!Wave pool!
Oh,what the hell?
Alright.What do you guyswanna ride first?
Well,cartman said he wanted to do the wave poolfirst,right cartman?
Forget it.
Just forget it!
Dude,this is awesome!
You guys wanna seehow long i can hold my breath under water?
Hey,fellas!Fellas,hang on!
I gotta goto the bathroom!
Okay.Go ahead.
Okay,thanks!
I can seriously hold my breathlonger than anybody.
Somebodytime me alright.
- Okay!
- Alright.Check it out
butters butters!
What the fuck?
Are you peeingin the pool?
You said go ahead!
Come on,kyle.Let's check out the fireboats.
No,dude.Butters' pee is in there!
Aw,come on.Look at all this water.
It doesn't matterif one person pees in it.
Yeah,come on,kyle.I am not the only person herewho's peed in the pool.
Lots a people do.
- No,they don't.
- Yeah,they do,kyle.
To be perfectly frank,i peed in the poolabout 25 seconds ago.
Dude!
Come on,show us how longyou can hold your breath!
No!
What has happenedto this place
I don't recognize itanymore
it used to beso fun and special
What is lifeworth living for?
The dream is dead,our land is gone
There's a hole in my heart
And i can't go on
There are too manyminorities
Minorities
At my water park
my water park
This was our land,our dream
And they've takenit all away
They just keepcoming and coming Minorities
I tried to go and tell the police
But even the authorities
are minorities
At my water park
There's no place for meto sit anymore
and the lines just keepgetting crazier
There are mexicansall around me
The lazy riverhas never been lazier
it's a 40minute wait to godown one slide
And the instructions in spanishon the zipline ride
guarde sus brazos y piernasdentro del paseo siempre.
Just do it in english!
There are too manyminorities
too many
At my water park
somebody do something
Where did they allcome from?
Why can't they leavethis land alone?
And it's such a tragedy
Feel a bit like dying
We've been lookin'the other way too long
we've gotto change our priorities
and get all these minorities
Out of my water park
minorities
Mexicans and asians   black people
i think i even saw   a native american  gross.
God,i'm asking please,
Get all of these minorities
Out of my water park
My water park.
After this,you guys,wannahit the hurricane slides?
You bet!
I'm not getting backin the water.
Oh,come on,kyle.
Dude,i just found out thateverybody pees in pools.Why would i go back?
Not everybodypees in pools.
Do you pee in the pool?
Not today yet.
Aw,come on!
Well dude,what are you gonna do?Just hang out hereat the table all day?
- Most likely.
- You guys!
You guys,we have got problemsof biblical proportions!
Dude,where have you been?
I've been counting.
Do you knowthere are 205 mexicans here?
And there are109 black people.
- So what?
- So.
Guesshow many white people are at the water parktoday?
143.
There are actually moreminorities here than us.
Well,then they're notminorities,are they?
What do you mean?
Dumb ass,if there's 60% of them to 40% of us,
then who's the minority?
The black and brown people.
No,you're the minority!
Do i look like a minorityto you,stupid?
Now look,guys,i did some calculations.
Just last year,there were almost 90% normal peopleto minorities.
That's a 50% risein one year.
This is more math thani've ever seen you do.
Because it's important!
A 50% rise each year means that in three years,
the world will be only minorities.
That's 2012.
- The mayans predicted this!
- The who?!
The mayans.They knew that minoritieswould take over the world by the year 2012.
And now it's happening!
I'm going to go onthe slides.
- Whoopie!
- You guys?
You guys,we have to dosomething to stop this!Come on!
Well,looks like at least you've got some senseleft in you,kyle.
So what are we going to doto keep the mayans prediction from coming true,buddy?
Blow it out your ass,cartman.
Eugene!That is disgusting!
Did you justpee in the pool?
Oh,come on!Look how big this pool is.
One person peeing in itisn't going to hurt anything.
Oh my god!
Ah,gentlemen,i am athe pipi.
How can i ahelp you?
Pipi,we have some dire newsconcerning your water park.
I've just finishedsome tests.
The water in your parkis now 98% pee.
Yes?So what's athe problem?
Pipi,you know thatacceptable pee levels in any water parkis 83%.
You have to shut down.
What?I can'ta close down.
Now it's my biggest aweekend!
Everyone is ahavingthe fun!
You're endangeringpeoples' lives!
If those pee levels hit 100%,there's no tellingwhat will happen.
And what proof do you havethat the pee levels will go up?
One in three people admitthey pee in pools.
Add another for people who dobut don't admit it,that's two in three.
You've got just over500 people out there.
That's 332 people aboutto pee in your water.
Gentlemen,pleasea.
I comea from the venice.
Venice is almost all pee,
and we do just afine.
We swima in the pee,we singa in the pee.
You can't barge in here andtell me that i have to close down
just because my water parkhasa too much pee.
You haveto evacuate people now!
He said he's not doing it!
And as his lawyer,i advise you gentlemen,to leave and takeyour wild pee theories with you.
If one more personurinates in your pool,it could set offa chain reaction.
Then the pee will beon your hands.
Oh,boy,the waves arestartin' up again!
This is sweet,huh,kenny?
Wwhat's that?
It's pee!
Look out for the pee!
Gross!
It's athe pee!
Oh,my god.They killed kenny!
Aw,sick!
I wantthat entire water park contained and quarantineduntil i get some answers.
What's going on?
I told you peopleto keep civilians back!
Sir,please,my son is in there.What's happened?
We don't know yet,alright?
There's been a pee breachand a lot of people are dead.
Now,i'm sorry butyou're gonna have to
captain,these two men claimto know the situation.
We warnedthe owner of the park,but he refusedto shut down.
This was inevitable.
So this is all peerelated?
Yes.I tested the ph levelsthis morning.
And?
It was almost all pee,no h.
Oh my god.
I've got to help him!
Stay back!
You can't just leave my sonin there with all that pee!
Sir,it's possiblewith a crane,we could helpany survivors out.
I think that would bea very bad idea.
And why is that?
Anyone inside there iscontaminated.
We have reason to believe that when people are exposedto that much pee,they change.
Change how?
Alright,bring inbring in the monkey.
We've only tested the theoryon monkeys so far.
This monkey is healthy andnormal in every way.
But now watch.
My god,he's becomefull of rage!
Kyle,quick!You gotta swim overto us.
No way!
You gotta swim over here,kyle.
Come on,kyle!
Dude,that's all pee!
Well,if you don't swim in it,you're gonna die.
I'll dieif i do swim in it.
Kyle,it's just pee.
It's not that big a deal.
Yes,it is a big deal!
Why do you thinkeveryone washes their hands after they goto the bathroom?
Well,not everyone washestheir hands after they goto the bathroom.
What?
Come on,dude,you gotta swim.
You don't wash your handsafter going to the bathroom?
Not.all the time.
That is gross!
Why?It's not like you're peeingon your hands.
There's more germson most furniture  than there is in pee.
Yeah,if anything,you should wash your handsbefore you touch your wiener.
Kyle,come on!
God dammit!
Do you needto wash your hands?
I can't hold on.
Help!
Here!Hey kid,grab this stick!
Yes!Yes,help me!
Yes,help me.I'm just a little boy.You have to help me.
Are you okay?
Yes.Thank you.
Well,what arewe gonna do now?
We've gotto just wait it out.
yeah,but for how long?
we need to find somethingto paddle with.
day one.It has happened.
The mayans were right.
Only thing they got wrongwas the date.
It is 2009 and i appear to bethe last of my species alive.
Now it's just me,all alone,with minorities.
What will the minoritiesdo with me?
I'm sure that's what's onall their minds.
I have to make myselfseem useful to them,or they willsurely not let me live.
Does anyone needmedical help?
I am a doctor.
Randy!Randy,calm down!
I can't understandwhat you're saying.
It's the pee!
It's all pee andnobody can go in or out!
What is all pee?
Sharon,the water parkhad a pee meltdown!
They think a lot of peoplehave died.
What?What about stan?Is he okay?
I don't know!
The whole water parkhas been quarantined.
They're worried anyoneleft alive could be some kind of raginghatefilled mutants!
Randy,you've got todo something!
Calm down,sharon.Calm down!
They're tryingto find an antidote.
Once they believethey can neutralize the enraging affectsof the pee,they'll.
They'll go into look for survivors.
I saidkeep the media out.
If the publichears about this,we'll have a fullscale panicon our hands.
Dammit!Where is that antidote?
Here!Here!
We think we have it,sir.
It's the bestwe could come up with in such a short time.
We aren't sureof the ramifications,
but it does appear to neutralizesome particles of the urine.
Alright,let's test it.Bring in the monkeys!
Let's hope to christthis works.
No,dammit no!
They're still angry!
This one's really angry.
It's out of control!
Find an antidotethat works!
Dude,why aren't peoplecoming to help us?
I don't know.
Oh why.
Why didn't pipi alisten?
They tried to warnathe pipi,but apipinot believe them.
Who are you?
Oh,i'm so sorry!
This is alla my fault!
I should haveashut my water park down when it reached90% apee!
Yeah.Well,people should know that peeing in poolsis bad!
But waita!Maybe you boysa cana help pipi.
Ina the maintenance rooma,there isthe emergency release valve.
If you open it,alla this a peecan be lowered!
Okay!Where'sthe maintenance room?
That is athe problem.
The maintenance room is away down on the basement level.
I would do it,but pipi isa no good at athe swimming.
Somebody will haveto dive down into the pee,
then stay thereto turn the release wheel.
So who can holdatheir breath the longest?
- No!
- You said you can holdyour breath the longest,kyle.
Not in pee!
Pleaseayou have to hurry.
I'll draw youathe map and instructionshow to shut off athe valvea.
It'll be as easy asapeeing in the shower!
Oh,who peesin the shower?
Well,it's not like if yousuddenly have to pee,you're gonna getout of the shower.
Yeah,seeingall that running water always makes meneed to pee.
You don't peein the shower,dude!
That's fucking disgusting!
Boysa please!
We've got to get this boytoa that drainage valve or we're all agonna die.
Jesus christ!
It has been many,many hourssince the apocalypse,
And all i keep thinkingis "why me?
" why am i the only oneof my race god chose to survive in thisminorityrun world?
When the smokehas cleared,I'm sure the minoritieswill start rebuilding.
Building the worldin their way.
I can see it now.
No.
Alright,eric cartman.Let's hear your book report.
I read treasure island because i was so happywhen i saw that movie.
You're living in a minorityspeaking country now.
Say it right.
Because i was so happywhen i seen that movie.
Good.
No.
Trying to find a jobwill be even harder.
You don't expect to makethe same amount of money that minorities make,do you?
Well,i do justas much work.
You're trash around here.
You'll never make as muchas a minority.
No.
Eventually,the minorities willdo away with me all together.
All those in favor of puttingwhite people in camps?
aye!
All those opposed?
No.
The minorities win!
No!No,i don't want to live in your world,do you understand?
Your world is cold and voidof any humanity.
Just kill me.Kill me now!
Do it!
Okay,there
we are almostaready for the diving.
Now if you run aintothe any problems,
you just tug athree timeson the cableAnd apipi will apull you backato the surface.
Let's just getthis over with.
You got a the mapa andapipi's instructions.
- Yes.
- Good.
Now justaone last thing.
- You needto drink somea pee.
- What?
- You just need to drink abouta three cupsa pee.
- Why?
You swim a downadeep in the pee,you get athe pressure.The benza!
You have to fill the inside ofyour body with some apee to compensate.
That's true,dude.Didn't you see the abyss?
I am not.
Not drinking pee.
But only you can aholdthe breath a long time to swim downand release athe valve anda
If you get a the benza,then you a fail and we all adie!
- Just drink the pee,kyle.
- Please,kyle.I wanna go home.
What's athe problem?
When ayou pee,either inthe toilet or in athe shower,it all goes to the sewer.
The sewer all agoesto the ocean.
The ocean is the waterwe all adrink.
You are alwaysdrinking the pee!
That doesn't make mefeel better!
I wouldn't even be ableto keep it down.
*********You drank only peefor nine months when you lived inayour mother's belly.
No!
Make way!Make way!I need to speakto the fire marshal!
Sir!Sir,i just got off the phonewith my colleagues at the university.
They've also been testingantidotes on monkeys.
They're claiming thatthey've had success,using simple musa acuminata.
Wait.You mean a banana.
- Yes.
- Is it possible?
The antidote is somethingas simple as a banana?
Get another monkey!
Alright,conners.
Holy god!It works.
Alright.Let's start moving in everyone!Check for
hold on!It is a promising lead,
but this antidotehasn't yet been tested on a human.
I'll do it.
You can testthe antidote on me.
You sureyou want to do this?
Give me the banana.
He looks agitated.
He's losin' it!Stevens,your gun!
No,wait!Wait.
I'm okay.
He's alright!
The banana worked!
Come on,dude.
I'm thinking about it!
Well,it's probably bbbetter if you don't thinkabout it,kyle.
There's no more timea!You haveto drink athe pee now!
Come on,you haveto drink all athe pee!
You can do it,kyle!
Alrighta!Now you can openathe releasea valve.
Okay,so letsa
hey,look!
Stan!
Alright,they finallycame for us!
Are you fuckingkidding me?
Wait herea minute,stan.I'm goingto call your mother.
Guys?
Guys!
Oh,it's true!
You all did survive!
Aw,you lived?
Oh my god,you guys!I really thought i wasthe only nonminority on earth!
How many ofour species survived?
That wasn't a mayan apocalypse,you racist idiot!
It wasn't?
So then you mean.
We do have until 2012.
Well,it may be onlythree years,
but i intend to live thoseprecious years to the fullest!
Will somebody just get meto a hospital?
I need to getmy stomach pumped.
Aw,come on.It was just a little pee,kyle.
God dammit,don't you get it?
I hate pee!
I'm grossed outby pee!
The only thing i find moredisgusting than pee is bananas!
Alright everyone,quick!Here you go!
What's this?
You all need to eatyour banana immediately!
What the hell for?
Eat the bananaor we have to put you down!
south park.s13e14