-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
South
Park Season13 Episode02
CRIME RATE UP
The city isn't what
it used to be --
It all happened so fast.
Everything went to crap.
It's like everyone's sense
of morals just disappeared.
The bad economy made things worse.
The jobs started drying up.
Then the stores had to shut down.
Then the black man
was elected president.
He was supposed to
change things. He didn't.
As more and more people turn to crime and
violence,the town becomes gripped in fear.
Dark times. This city needs protection.
There is an animal that lives by night.
Searches through trash cans
and cleans out the garbage.
To clean the trash can of society,I've
chosen to become more than a man.
I am the hero this town needs.
I am --
the coon.
As the world plummets into despair,the
coon fights to keep order intact.
Lisa,i had a really great time tonight.
I did too,josh.
Would you mind very
much if I kissed you?
Not at all.
A woman being raped.
This is what our city
has been reduced to.
When the money goes the raping starts.
Women are helpless without the coon.
Oh,yes,josh! Yes!
Let her go!
Excuse me?
You aren't raping anyone tonight!
Oh,it's a talking squirrel.
Oat out of here! Get to safety!
Lisa! Call me!
Another woman saved from rape.
But how many more rapists are out there?
That really stings.
Here's the file on that
rodriguez case,detective.
All right. Things are
pretty quiet out there,boys.
Let's try to get caught
up on our paperwork.
Murphy,i
want you to --
don't let the city's peacefulness
fool you,commissioner.
It's too quiet.
Oh,not this kid again.
Hey,you get outta here. Out!
There was another rapist
in the park tonight.
It's no coincidence.
It must be a rapist plot
and it stinks to the top.
What?
I think the mayor might be involved.
It's my theory she has a lesbian
lover who's holder her leash.
Jesus christ. Can't we
get a lock on that window?
Look,kid,you
need to stop --
he's gone.
No,I'm just over here now.
What do we know about the
mayor's sexual preferences?
All right,listen.
You have five seconds to leave or I'm
gonna put you in jail and call your parents.
Jail's full,sir.
Whatever.Then
we'll put you in --
now I'm back over here.
Just get out of
here before we --
I'm right here now.
All right. Stop it!
Yes,i have to go now.
But in the meantime,i have
something that might interest you.
Make sure all your men get
a look at these,detective.
What's in here
hey,guys. Good morning.
You guys hear that another rape victim
got saved by a superhero last night?
They say it was the coon.
Who's the coon?
I know,right? Who is the coon?
It's what everyone must
be asking themselves.
Somebody is dressing up at night and
taking the law into their own hands.
As for me,i certainly don't agree
with the coon's reckless ways.
If you ask me,there's no room
in this world for vigilantes.
I believe the coon is a menace.
Yeah,and dressing up and running
around at night is faggy anyway.
You're a fag,kyle! You!
- Dude,what?
- He's not a fag!
Why do you care?
I,well,I'm just mad 'cuz you shouldn't
ever use the term "fag," kyle.
That's a hate word and it's
insensitive to butt pirates.
Anyway,what the you think
about the coon,stan and kenny?
Do you think he's the savior this town needs,or
do you think he's a dangerous vigilante?
Kenny?
And of course the most
common question asked is --
Just who is he? Is
he a hero or a menace?
While we can all admit that the
coon is obviously really cool,
We should also be asking each other why does
he care so much for the people of this town?
Why does he sacrifice himself every
night to rid our streets of crime?
And does he really have the right?
What we all need
to know -- clyde.
Clyde,could you wake
up,please. This is important.
What we all need now is
proof that the coon exists.
I believe that tonight,from
approximately 5:00 to 5:45,
The coon is going to be
on the roof of walgreens.
I know i'll be there with my camera.
I'm sure many of you will,too.
Sometimes it seems the more
criminals I try to stop,
The more just come out of the
back alleys and dilapidated bars.
The city is a dying whore.
She calls out to me to save her.
And I don't know if I can.
But she is still my city.
And I cannot just sit and
watch as innocent people are --
who the hell is that?
Who the hell are you?
I am an angel keeping watch
over the city at night.
As violence and darkness take over the
streets,i work to rid the streets of crime.
I am the symbol this town needs.
No,no,no. I'm the
symbol this town needs.
Dude,seriously,you can't do that.
Go home. I was doing this first.
Yeah-huh!
You heard of the coon and
now you're being a copycat.
Is that your hero name? Copycat?
I am mysterion.
Mysterion? That's retarded.
You just gave yourself away,craig.
Only you would think
of a name that dumb.
I might be craig,an then
again I might not be.
My identity must remain a secret.
You cannot know.
******
*********
***
********
*********
and try*****
****
********
I cannot stand here and make
idle conversation any longer.
The city needs my help. There
are innocents to protect.
No! Dude,I'm serious. You're
being a copycat! I'll sue you!
Mother!
Which one of them is it?
Somebody is dressing up and
pretending to be a superhero,but who?
Has to be one of the guys in my class,'cuz only they
know the coon would be on the rooftop of the walgreens.
No. Stop. Can't think about
that now. I have to focus.
Tomorrow is the most important
day in the coon's life.
Everything the coon has lived and
fought for comes down to tomorrow.
Concentrate
how is it that nobody
came to coonicon '09?
This is just --
this is ridiculous!
Got everything you need here,sir?
Okay on beverages,buffett items?
Yes,it's fine.
Great. Hey,just want to say that the airport
hilton really appreciates your continued business.
What do you mean "continued"?
You don't know who I am.
Aren't you the little boy who had his ginger
pride rally and his aids benefit here before?
No! I'm not that kid!
Oh,really? My bad.
I'm actually relieved. That
kid was kind of a douche bag.
You're a douche bag!Get out of here
oh,hello,sweetie. What did you do today?
I got boned. That's what I did,mom!
I try to do good stuff
and nobody ever notices.
Oh,what happened,hon?
I can't tell you what happened,'cuz
it's about my super secret double life!
Tonight,an incredible story of
an unknown child in south park
Who has taken to the streets
in an effort to fight crime.
What?
But who exactly is mysterion?
Curiosity has led to large crowds in
the mountain town of south park,colorado.
They've brought binoculars,and cameras to try
and get a shot of the mysterious superhero.
He was dressed mostly in
black with a kind of cloak.
He jumped down from the fire escape
stairs and then he just ran off.
We barely got a look at him.
To me it looked like mysterion to me.
Everyone who seen mysterion say yeah!
Yeah!
Well,i think he's kind of a
symbol for the town,you know?
A symbol that everyone who's
sick of crime can rally behind.
Butthole.
Well,if you ask me,he's a menace.
There's no room for
vigilantism in today's world.
The artist rendition of mysterion has
already generated thousands of copies.
You've got to be kidding me!
As hundreds of people gather to try and get a
glimpse of the superhero,one question remains --
Who is mysterion?
Who is mysterion? Who
is he? Who could he be?
If you have any idea about
the true identity of  *******
Who is mysterion?
I could no longer watch as the
city has become a cesspool of crime.
I lived in south park all my life.
I decided it was up to
me to keep town safe.
Nobody at school knows my double life.
To them,I'm just another fourth grader.
But tonight,i am mysterion.
Ah,mysterion,thank god you've come.
What news do you have?
There's some graffiti
on the bridge again.
I think those sixth
grade kids are doing it.
And the guy at the movie theater
is harassing mexicans again.
We'll get right on it,mysterion.
Thank you. Thank you for all your help.
Godspeed,mysterion!
You are a beecon of hope in an
otherwise bleak and dreary world!
Dude,seriously.
I'm gonna kick the out
of you if you don't stop.
The city needs my help.
It cries for
protection and I will --
answer the call to save her!
That's what I'm supposed to say!
I know it's you,kyle. So just stop.
I don't have time for this.
Fireworks are illegal
in colorado,you asshole!
Hey,he's got fireworks!
So guys,any of you do anything
interesting last night?
- Not really.
- Really?
Nobody was playing with any fireworks?
Dude,what the hell?
Kenny! I should have known!
Why do you have a picture of
mysterion in your locker,kenny?
Unless you are mysterion!
Dude,i have a picture of
mysterion in my locker,too.
Yeah,so do i.
What? Why?
I don't know. It's just a cool costume.
It's not a cool costume!
He just wears his
underwear over his pants!
Now come on! Which
one of you guys is it?
How are you so sure mysterion is a boy?
Bitch.
U-STOR-IT
STORAGE FACILITY
I had no choice. I was
at the end of my rope.
Sometimes when a superhero needs answers,he has
to turn to on the wretched underbelly of society.
Look what the cat dragged in.
Come out where I can see you.
What's the matter,coon? Nervous?
I didn't want to resort to this.
But you could have the answers I need.
How utterly delightful.
The heroic and mighty coon
come to put a stop to me again.
Chaos. I need to keep on my toes.
I'm not here to stop
you this time,chaos.
I need information.
Oh,I'm sure you do.
But you see
I -- wugh!
But you see I also know
you like to beat me up.
I didn't call you to fight,chaos.
I came to see if you
know mysterion's identity.
Oh,I'm close!
And i'll put an end to him and
all of you goodie two shoe heroes.
I'm not on his side.
Do you think I'm a fool?
All those times you've stopped
me from my acts of evil.
All those times you tricked me into
meeting you and then gave me titty-twisters!
Not this time,coon.
I finally learned my lesson.
Now! General disarray!
Yeah!
Oho,careful,general disarray.
Stop! You little butthole,knock it off!
Yeah! We beat him,general disarray!
Listen to me!
I want to help you get rid of mysterion.
Let him go,general disarray.
Why would you help us?
Because mysterion
is trying to -- ugh!
Little! That hurt!
Because mysterion is trying to
say he's the hero this town needs.
But that's my job.
But you both fight for justice and good.
Yeah,but he's a dick.
I want him gone just as much as you do.
Very well.
I will show you what we know
about mysterion's identity.
But if this is some
kind of set-up --
look,I'm the good guy,chaos.I
don't betray people.
Oh,yeah.
I didn't like working with this
scumbag,but I knew mysterion was out there.
Plotting his next move.
Hello,kyle.
What
the --
do not be afraid.I mean you no harm.
Hey,hey,you're that mysterion kid!
Yes,but now I believe someone is
trying to learn my true identity.
Dude,everyone's trying
to figure out who you are!
I cannot be unmasked,for then
I would stop being a symbol.
I need help.
Somebody who can do background
checks for me,do some investigating.
Who? Me? Why?
Because I think you are
the smartest kid in class.
This way!
We will now show you our
secret headquarters of doom!
You guys have your own storage facility?
Actually,it belongs to general
disarray's grandma,but she lets us use it.
This is where we come up
with al our evil plans!
Here's our computer relays.
And this is like a cube of chaos that
can destroy the world in one second.
And here's some of our evil minions.
We have everything we need here!
Can I offer you a coke
or a sprite or something?
I'll take a sprite.
Get the coon a sprite,general disarray.
As you can see,we too have been
working hard on mysterion's identity.
You have an entire wall
dedicated to mysterion?
What about -- do you still have that
"who is the coon" t-shirt I gave you?
Oh,yeah. I think that's
around here somewhere.
Using our photos,we are trying
to pinpoint mysterion's identity.
Why is cartman crossed
out? He could be mysterion.
No,he's too fat.
Based on his body type,it's gotta
be someone like stan or kyle.
All right,all right,look,chaos.
Just set up a video camera.
I know how we can put an end
to mysterion once and for al >
The clock is ticking and the citizens
of south park are gripped in fear.
Two days ago,an evil unknown
terrorist threatened major consequences
if mysterion does not
reveal his identity.
Mark my words,south park!
Your precious hero is now your undoing!
If mysterion does not unmask
himself publicly by wednesday night,
i am going to blow
up a hospital --
Blow up a hospital? I'm not
gonna blow up any hospital!
Are you nuts? What?
Uh,the choice is yours,mysterion.
Unmask yourself or hundreds will die.
Jesus christ.
Since the threat was issued there
has been no sign of the mysterion.
Where is mysterion?
Hey,coon. We aren't actually
going to blow up anything,are we?
If you don't make good on your
threats,chaos,then what good are your threats?
But you really won't
to blow up a hospital?
I mean,aren't you a good guy?
Sometimes blowing up hospitals
is for the greater good,chaos.
You know I've been thinking.
If we're really evil villains,then we should
betray him and blow him up with the hospital.
You know,you're a little
scrotum licker,dude.
Why don't you shut the up?
All right,chaos. I'm gonna get the
triggers for these things at ace hardware.
Keep an eye on this stuff.
Oh,jeez. General disarray,this is a
lot more than I ever really intended.
I mean,i hate the world and all its puny inhabitants
and all,but blowing up a hospital just seems mean
Oh,hamburgers!
Mysterion,ibudduh,ibuddush,hebba,hebba
--
why are you doing this?
This isn't your usual m.o.,chaos.
Well,you bubba,i was just -- and then the
coon showed up and he was isa abuduh abdudh --
What is that?
Look!
Mysterion and professor
chaos are fighting.
Give him hell,mysterion!
Look out,mysterion. General
disarray is behind you!
Jesus christ. We need backup out here!
I think I can get a shot at chaos,sir!
You think your bullets can hurt him?
Yeah! We did it!
He's dead. Mysterion is dead!
No!
The impossible has happened.
Mysterion,beloved protector
of the city,is dead.
Who will save us now?
Wait! Look!
He's all right!
Oh,my god! Look,everyone! It's the coon!
Fear not,everyone.
The coon is here to save the day!
Isn't that bruce vilanch?
Be careful,bruce vilanch. There's
super humans fighting right over there.
Okay,sorry. Sorry. I
give up. Please,i give up.
Don't worry,mysterion.
The coon will now help you.
Whoa,wait! I thought we
were working together --
Oh,jeez. I think I broke a tooth.
That was great teamwork,mysterion.
South park is safe,until next time.
What next time?
Well,people are obviously so desperate to
learn your identity that they'll do anything.
Won't be long before the next villain comes along
and threatens violence unless you take off your mask.
Citizens,tonight has shown me that I
have no choice,but to unmask myself.
Don't do it,mysterion!
If you show your identity,we'll be forced
to arrest you for being a vigilante.
Don't you think he knows that?
But superheroes know that sometimes you have
to sacrifice yourself for the greater good!
Don't show your face,mysterion.
You have to be a symbol!
So that the next terrorist can threaten
south park if he doesn't unmask himself?
No,it's true.
As long as my identity is a mystery,this
will just happen again and again.
It has to end. I will show my face.
Well,i'll be.
I knew it was you! Rember
I even said it before!
Wow,a kid from my class was mysterion.
Well,I'm sorry,but you're under arrest.
Take the kid to jail.
My entire plan worked to perfection.
My work here is done.
With mysterion out of the way,the coon can
finally go back to keeping the city safe.
Once again,i alone am the symbol
this town can stand behind.
Every town needs a hero.
Every town needs a coon.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚