-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
South
Park Season13 Episode07
You guys! You guys!
We can finally do it!
We can finally leave this crappy town
and live the life we've al dreamed of!
We can?
What are you talking about,dude?
Haven't you assholes
been watching the news?
Pirating is back,my friends.
Swashbuckling adventure
on the high seas.
The stuff we've all dreamed about!
And it's all happening right here!
Somalia!
Somalia? Where's that?
North africa.
Just picture it,guys!
Clear blue water with skull islands!
Waterfalls with jewelled
treasure underneath!
I've worked it all out on expedia,and
we can take southwest airlines to miami.
Then dubai air here to cairo.
Then it's just a 49-hour
bus ride into mogadishu
with all the booty and
plunder a pirate could want.
You know,cartman,this
is an awesome idea.
You should totally go to somalia.
Right! Wait a minute.
You never think my ideas are good,kyle.
No,i'm being totally serious.
That is the best idea you've ever had.
You should run away to mogadishu.
You should go there right away!
I'll even help plan your trip!
Wow,cool! What a minute. The?
Why would you do that?
Unless you're trying
to trick me somehow.
No,no! You're right.
Somalia is an oasis of
treasure and waterfalls!
It's totally the pirate's life!
Then why don't you want to go?
Well,'cuz,dude,i'm
jewish.And,you know --
jews can't be pirates.
That's true.
Well,i'm glad you've come to
terms with your disability,kyle.
Gentlemen,i'm off the start planning.
Please,please let him go.
Good morning,students. These
are the morning announcements.
Teacher-parent conferences have
been rescheduled to next tuesday.
Please inform your parents.
The gym is being repainted and is
closed until tomorrow afternoon.
And now for a special announcement.
Avast there mateys!
Do you have a thirst for
adventure on the high seas of life?
Are ye sick and tired of your parents and
teachers telling ye what to do all the time?
Then join captain cartman's
perfect pirate club!
Just imagine it,me hearties!
A life without rules,without
homework and chores!
You can live the pirate's
life in somalia,me friends.
Even kyle said so.
Our first official pirate meet willing
be 4:00 p.m.at kevin stoley's house.
At my house? Why my house?
There will be refreshments served!
So make sure your mom goes
to the grocery store,kevin!
So come one,come all.
The invitation is open to any
student who wants to be a pirate
and who isn't jewish,mexican or ginger.
And for lunch today,the cafeteria will be serving
taco salad or hoagie sandwiches. Thank you.
Ahoy,fellow club members!
Congratulations on leaving your
meaningless lives behind to become pirates.
Your life of boredom is at an
end,thanks to captain cartman!
All hands on deck!
Attention!
All right,ye booty lubbers!
So you've decided to join
captain cartman,didee?
Uhhh,guys. Who let
in the g-i-n-g-e-r?
Well,there's really not that many of
us. We figured we should let him join.
But,guys,g-i-n-g-e-r-s can't be
spirits because they don't have souls.
Please get it out of here.
Fine! I don't want to
be a pirate anyways!
Okay,anyways.
Now enough small talk lads!
It's time for us to start
rappin' and plunderin'!
Yeah!
We set course tomorrow!
I purchased everyone's tickets
online using my mudder's credit card.
And your mom is okay with that?
Dude,i'm a pirate!
What the devil do i care
what me mudder thinks anymore?
Neat-o!
All right,lads.
Go home and write your farewell
letters to your families.
The land of pirates awaits!
Pirates ho!
Kevin,goddammit.
Have a good flight. Next,please?
We be heading to somalia,by
way of miami to cairo.
And take care ye put us in
an exit row,ye landlubber.
I see,you five boys are all booked
through to cairo by yourselves?
That we be,lass. It's all paid
fer on me mudder's credit card.
Oh,jeez. I don't know if i can
really go through with this.
What?
It's just leaving everything behind.
I can't believe i'm actually doing it.
Yeah,maybe we should think about this.
You guys,the?
Are you forgetting how
crappy your lives are?
All the homework? The rules?
Butters,do you really want to just go back
to school where people just make fun of you?
- Who? You mean you?
- Yes!
- Do you really want to go back to that?
- No! I'm sick of it!
Well,all right then,fag!
We can't turn back now.
The path to adventure lies
just beyond this ticket counter,
And if you four have really come all this way
just to turn back now,then seriously you guys --
The?
He's right,lads. To adventure!
This is somalia?
Where's all the waterfalls
and shipwreck lagoons?
The?
Excuse me. Where are the pirates?
We're looking for all the
pirates.Where can we find the --
butters,get the phrase book out.
Ask can these people
where the pirates are.
Oh,he says they're in there!
Ah,nice! Come on,mateys!
*******
***
Yes,baka,baka,alaka jam. Thank you.
Avast!
These aren't pirates. They're
just a bunch of black people.
*********
*****
I'm captain cartman and this
here be my terrible crew.
We be looking fer a ship to pirate with
*********
**********
******
yes,very nice.
Apparently these are the pirates.
*******
**********
Ah,excellent! They are
taking us to the ship!
Once we commandeer a vessel,the
plundering will be easy indeed,lads.
********
*****
This is your pirate boat? Dude. The?
All right,seriously. You
guys,what kind of pirates are you?
I mean,really,the,dude. The?
***********
******
All right,lads. Guess we'll have
to settle with this meager ship.
Two of you sit aft and two
of you sit in the front.
I gotta sit middle 'cuz
i get motion sickness.
Kevin,jesus christ.
Hard to starboard,lads!
There's sure to be
lots of bootys out here!
Clyde,the?
You said there was gonna be crystal
clear lagoons and treasure and plunder!
Calm down,clyde.
Everything's gonna be okay!
No,it's not. You made me run away and be
a pirate and there's not even any treasure!
Ike! Will you do something
about clyde,please?
Very nice,ike.
All right,me hearties.
Keep your eyes open for boats to plunder
**********
*******
***********
******
************
**********
******
************
*******
***********
*****
*********
******
************
********
dude,dude! You're doing it all wrong.
Let me handle this.
All right,ya scallywags!
Surrender your plunder lest we
start firing shots across yer bow!
********
************
Yeah,that's good but now go "arrrgh!"
Yeah? Okay,and you checked
with kenny and token?
He's not just staying at their houses?
No,dude. Everyone's checked.
I think cartman really
ran away to somalia.
Yes!
I can't help but take
some credit for this.
I helped convince him to go!
You really he'll die in somalia?
For sure,dude!
It's the most god forsaken
place on the planet.
Things are finally gonna
be normal around here!
Oh,god!
Oh,god,what did we do wrong,gerald?
Take it easy. We'll find him!
I'll call you back.
Oh,kyle! He's gone!
Your little brother's
run away from home!
What? Are you sure?
He left a note saying
he's never coming back!
"dear mommy and daddy.
I am running away.
I am sorry,but i cannot longer handle
the monotony of middle class life.
Everyone at school is a idiot,
and if one more person talked to me about
that Susan boyle performance of "les miserable"
i was going to puke my
balls out through my mouth.
I love you all,but i have to move on.
I'm going to somalia to
be a -- to be a pirate!"
Oh,oh,gerald. What are we going to do?
It's all right. He couldn't have gone
far. Let's call the other kids' house s.
Oh,god,what have i done
**********
******
the are you pirates doing?
Are we gonna plunder them or not
*********
*******
***********
********
*************
all right,let's go
**************
*********
**********
quiet,ye sons of biscuit eaters!
This boat is now pirate property!
Now get ye to yer lifeboat
lest ye wanna be shark bait!
*********
Plunder the booty,lads!
This ship is ours!
Okay!
I said get off me boat!
***********
That's it! Get in there ya swarmy dogs!
Lower 'em down,ike!
*********
Have a good day!
Hard to port,lads.
Hard to port!
What's port?
Just make the boat go that way,kind of
that's good! Now bring
'er round topside!
Now that's a pirate ship.
Ah,a fine day of plunderin' we
had,boys. What about yourselves?
Here ya are,lads. Plenty
of booty to go around.
A round of grog for me boys.
A round of grog for everyone.
The is this?
This is water in a dixie cup!
All right,goddammit. Really,you guys.
What kind of pirates are
you? Look at yourselves!
You're a disgrace to blackbeard!
I don't know where you people get
off calling yourselves pirates --
Little beat-up
boats,water in dixie cups.
I mean look! Look at this guy!
Look at this guy,for christ's sake!
I mean how hard is this,people?
I tell ya lads,if we're gonna be
the most feared people on earth
Then there needs to be some
goddamn changes around here!
We drink and we pillage
and we do what we please
And we get all we want for free
we'll kick your ass Then rape
your lass somalian pirates we
so with a yo ho ho
uh,goddammit,people.
With a yo ho ho
yo ho,ho
and with a yee hee hee
yee hee hee
We take to the african sea
we'll brave the squalls And bust
your balls somalian pirates we
somalian pirates we
We left our homes and we left our
mudders to go on a pillaging Spree
we'll cut off your ears and break
your toes and make you Drink our pee
and if ye sail into our waters
you best hear this Decree
we'll take your boat
and set yer ass afloat
- somalian pirates we
- nice!
With a yo ho ho yo ho ho
and a trick a lotty do trick a loty do
We'll shoot you in the face with
our glee then we'll cut off your --
Okay. Let's stop there for a minute.
Rember on "trick a lotty
do" that's an loddy do,okay?
Really need you guys to
enunciate the lotty. Uh,nadif?
If i can get you and abdikarim to
sing the harmony on the second yo ho.
And ue,hashmish,is it?
I'm sorry,but you're a little flat.
Rember to sing out. Don't
close your throat. Okay?
So let's go from uh,bar 14. Pick
up after the quarter rest. Ike?
- Somalian pirates we
- better!
With a yo ho ho a yo ho ho
And a trick a lotty do
we'll shoot you in the face with glee
Then we'll cut off your c c
coca and feed it to a crock
somalian pirates we
We found them adrift.********
*****
What's causing them to
suddenly be so much more active?
Is the crew okay?
Yes,sir. They're french,so
they surrendered immediately.
Once the pirates boarded your
ship,how did they force you off?
Elles avait lightsaber!
Oui! Un light saber!
Le lightsaber terrible!
Sir,the pirates appear to have forced the
french crew off their boat with a lightsaber.
My god.
The pirates are getting
better equipped every day.
Gentlemen,i want the president
of the united states on the phone.
We can no longer fight
the pirates on the seas.
We have to take them
out where they live.
What did i tell you,butters?
This is the good life,huh?
What's going on?
**********
************
Ah,good. A hostage will
bring a fine ransom!
Well,well,well,well,well
this is cnn.
breaking news of yet another
pirate cris in somalia.
Members of nato receive word today that
pirates have captured an american child
And are demanding 10 million
euros for his safe release.
U.s.navy ships have been deployed and
the pirate standoff is about to get ugly.
Well,well,well,well,well,well,well,well,well,well,kyle.
You came all this way to
try and join my pirate club.
No,fatass,i came to get my brother!
We all have to get out
of here! It isn't safe!
It isn't safe.
That's not what you said
back in the cafeteria,kyle.
In the cafeteria you
said somalia was awesome.
I know. I was lying then.
Or are you lying now?
So many lies,kyle,you can't
even keep them straight!
You just couldn't stand that we were
living in paradise while you were back home.
This isn't paradise,and you know it.
The people here are starving and dying.
The whole world has used somalia
as a dumping ground for toxic waste.
Even the fish here are radioactive.
Cartman,just give me my brother
and let us get out of here.
Your brother is with butters taking
inventory of our latest plunder,kyle.
You just sit tight until we
hear about your ransom money.
One box of italian passports!
One necklace
-- Gold!
Three crew member watches.
Excuse me. Can i ask you a question?
Oh,sure,guleed.
Why did you americans come here?
Well,'cuz our lives sucked back home.
We had all these rules and homework.
Yeah,homework!
And our parents hollered at us.
Yeah!
So we wanted to come
here and be pirates.
Pirates!
But that's what i do not understand.
Why would anyone want to be a pirate?
Every day,i dream that i can go
to school,learn about the world.
But my mother,she's dying of aids,and
there is no money for medicine.
My father was killed
trying to find food for us.
Do you know how i feel every
time we try to capture a boat?
Scared.
And not just scared,because
i might get killed,
But scared because if i
don't get something out of it,
my family and friends are going to die.
I don't want to be a pirate.
I have don't see how anybody would.
Oh,my god.
Jeez,guess we kinda got
put in our place,huh,ike?
I feel like an asshole.
Yeah,me,too.
Go on! Walk the plank,ye scurvy dog!
Cartman,knock it off!
That's captain cartman,ye jewswoggle
*********
******
eric! Hey,eric! Listen,we wanna go home.
What?
Me and ike,we been talking and,well,guys,we
really had it pretty good back in america.
I mean,sure,it's easy to think our
lives are boring and full of rules,
But a lot of people have it way worse.
The pirates' life isn't a
life of fun and adventure.
It's a life of hardship and suffering.
When you get down to it,we were
pretty lucky to have the lives we did.
Clyde?
I hate it here. It wanna go home!
You guys cannot leave
the pirate club now!
How can you not want to stay
in this paradise we've created?
In somalia people have no laws!
They have no rules and
they never grow old!
They never grow old because
they die before they're 30!
Nobody's going anywhere!
I'm the captain of this outfit.
To arms!
Now is there any
question who's in charge?
I have an entire pirate crew
willing to do anything for me
*******
all right,men. Remember,do
not hit the white ones!
Me and my crew are gonna
go on pirating forever!
Clear.
The?