ALL CHARACTERS AND EVENTS IN THIS SHOW-- EVEN THOSE BASED ON REAL PEOPLE--ARE ENTIRELY FICTIONAL.ALL CELEBRITY BOICES ARE
IMPERSONATED....POORLY.THE FOLLOWING FROGRAM CONTAINS COARSE LANGUAGE AND DUE TO ITS CONTENT IT SHOULD NOT BE VIEWED BY ANYONE
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Proudly
Presents
* I'm goin' down to south park
gonna have myself a time *
* friendly faces everywhere *
* humble folks without temptation *
* goin' down to south park
gonna leave my woes behind *
* ample parking day or night
people spouting howdy  neighbor *
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Sync:
YTET-天外飞砖
heading on up to south park  gonna see if I can't
unwind south park S13E10
Come on down to south park
and meet some friends of mine
*****************
You think you're e better than me?
Cena!Your mouth has gotten you
into trouble for the last time!
I'm gonna shut it up for you!
Mess him up edge!
Kick his ass!****
Oh yeah?I got somethin'
else to tell you,edge!
I slept with vanessa last night!
Cena slept with edge's girlfriend!
Oh my god,dude.This is awesome!!
I am having the best time!!!
You cheated and took my belt from me!
And now I can't hardly
get work wrestling!
You took my girl and you took myjob!
He took his job!
He took his jer Terkiederrrr!
Oh sweet!
- awesome!
- *****
Dude,that was so badass!
Wrestling is awesome!
This is it you guys!We know
what are calling in lifeis now!
Tomorrow we are signing
up for wrestling class!
- Alright!
- Sweet!
The  Is this?
Why did they have us
put on long underwear?
Wul,I guess in wrestling we're supposed to
make your own outfit and then wear it over this.
Yeah that makes sense.
Alright.So did everyone settle
on their wrestling names?
I did!I'm the rad russian!
I come from russia to crush
yourpuny capitalist head!
Alright boys!
I'm really glad to see we have some new recruits
interested in the fine sport of wrastling!
Cool!Let's do this!
Now,the first things we are gonna learn
today are the fundamental wrastling holds.
Let's get some volunteers.
Why don't you come over here,young man.
What's your name?
- The rad russian.
- What?
You capitalist swine!I crush you!
Uh,okay.
Just go ahead and get
on your hands and knees.
Just  down on the floor.
Hands and knees.
Okay.
Alright.And now how about you?
Your name is?
Triceratops!
Uh,alright.
Come on over here.I'm gonna position you
into the official wrastling starting position.
Here we go.
The  Is this?
Now just reach around him.here.good.
Dude.dude!Dude!
The  Are you doing?
Get back on the floor.I'm teaching
you the starting position of wrastling!
That's not wrestling dude.That's  Gay!
Yeah.What you,a child molester?
Where's all the cool costumesand
jumping off ropes and stuff?
not this again.
Let me guess,you just went to that
stupid wwe show in denver last night!
The wwe is not wrastling!
That's a bunch of fake bullcrap!
How stupid are you?
Real wrastling,boys,is this.
Well this is Lame,dude.
Let's get the hell out of here guys.
Yeah,this guy probably wantsto
take pictures of us naked.
I got half a mind to reportreport
you to the police,sir!
The wrestling takedown federation
has several matches planned today!
Alright.So here's how
we'll do this,guys.
I'll come out to the ring first and then jimmy
you come in and tell me you're gonna kick my ass.
Then I'm gonna say you slept with my
girlfriend,and I'll charge you and do a headslap.
Sounds good.Then butters you
come in as the ref all like
no,no,the fight hasn't started yet,
and that's when jimmy sneaks up frombehind and
hits me over the headwith the foldaway chair.
- Okiedoke!
- So is that when I tell you your girlfriend is a whore?
No.Let's save the
girlfriend is a whore line
until after stan headbutts butters
for trying to stop the fight again.
Boy wrestling sure is fun!
Alright.We ready to try this guys?
- Yup.
- Alright.
Let's start wrestling.
I'm gonna kick your ass!
You slept with my girlfriend,hammerclaw!
Hey!No!
No,the fight hasn't started yet,
no!Bad!
Hey!Slept with my girlfriend,referee!
In my country we don't
wait for a bell mister
Your girlfriend is a whore
- Wait for it,wait for the whore line.
- Oh,right.Sorry
You're gonna get it now,hammerclaw!
- We'll see about that!
- Now hold on!
I am stopping the fight!
What's going on?
Apparently that crippled kid slept
with that russian kid's girlfriend!
Geez.They're so young!
I'll kill you triceratops!
You made fun of my crippled mother!
That's because your mother
betrayed my mother,juggernaut!
You don't come to this
country and make fun of it!
And just what do you care
about your pitiful country?
I served my country!
I fought for two years in vietnam!
That kid was in nam?
Man,that's incredible.
Good for you fer servin' yer country!
Guys,check this out!
There's this little kid from
thecongo who was raised by panthers!
Are you serious?
Just admit it,congo!
Admit that you lied about me to irene!
I admit nothing!
Maybe irene lied to you!
That kid in the hat is havingsex
with two different girls?
Naw,that little kid from thecongo
lied about one of them to try
and get the kid in the hat
in trouble with his wife.
They're married?
You will have to forfeit
thisfight,rad russian!
You cannot fight until
your testresults come back!
I might have to wait
for my hepatitis test,
but in the meantime I have brought my
comrade from mexico to wrestle against you!
That russian kid's got hepatitis?
Here he comes now!
The cold blooded wrestler from mexico.
El pollo loco!
What are you doing here,el pollo loco?!
Your girlfriend doesn't
even like you,stan the man.
She likes me!
You have no idea what
you're saying,juggernaut!
Irene loves me and
I'm going to marry her!
If she wants to be with you,
how about you have her
tell all these people here?
Here some comes now!
It's bad irene!
Let me tell you somethin',let
me tell you somethin'.
It's true I love stan
the man with all my heart.
- But I want to be with juggernautnow.
- What?
No!No way!
Naw what are ya doin?
Stan the man loves you!
Don't break his heart!
If you love juggernaut,irene,
then tell him what
you did two years ago!
How you killed his child!
It's true.I was pregnant with
your child and I aborted it.
Irene,no!
Why?
Do you know what it's like tohave
an abortion at seven years old?
Do you?
I've had so many abortions.
I just got addicted to them.
Woa,did you hear that?
Irene!You said you loved me!
I'm not in love with you.I'm in love
with abortions,don't you understand?
I'm telling you guys,you
have got to see this.
These kids ain't more
than eightor nine years old
and they got more problems
than you can imagine.
There's this one kid,
he saw his father get murdered.
And yesterday he finds the killer
and it's this other kid who's an excop
needless to say,he whooped his ass good.
Yup.And there's this little girl.
She's actually addicted
to gettin' abortions.
Got pregnant by nearly every boythere.
You're  me.
No we're tellin' you
these kids are  Crazy.
You gotta check it out.
You can watch'em almost everyafternoon.
It's some of the greatest
wrestlin' we ever seen.
It isn't real.
Don't you people understand?
That stuff isn't real.
None of it!
How stupid are you?
What'ch you mean it ain't real?
It's all made up.Fiction.
Real wrestling is a serious
and respectable sport.
Why can't you people understand that
that kind of wrestling isn't real?
Mister,
there's a little girlout there who's had
14 abortionsand she ain't even 10 yet.
But I guess that's just not realto you.
Son a bitch.
Look!Look!Look!
This is wrestling this!
Mister,you better take your gay
porn and walk right outta this bar.
Holy crap,dude.There's
a huge turnout tonight!
Good thing we made those
changes to the seating.
Alright.You guys let's bring it in.
I think we've really done a great
job and let's just keep the energy up,
*** **** have a good flow
and have fun out there.**?
Yeah!
Let's do this!
One,two Backyard wrestling!
Oh,what a perfect night for fighting!
Lo,the moon sets upon the
tips of the trees and I,
the man known as the rad russian,
start to stir with the
excitement of violence.
Only a country like yours canbreed
men of such discontent,rad russian!
But you don't know
what real pain is.Pain.
Like I've known.
Abandoned when I was four
years old by my parents.
Left to die in a cold
and dark sewage tunnel.
Geez,I didn't know his parents did that
I am very sorry,
but I'm afraid we have to terminate
youremployment here at south park elementary.
You're firing me?Why?
The school board has decided to
discontinue the wrestling program.
Wrestling simply involves
too much adult subject matter.
Like murder and abortion.
No!This isn't wrastling!
This isn't wraaastling!
Principal victoria,just let me stay on and
I can teach kids what real wrestling is!
I'm sorry.The board
has made up their minds.
You can't fire me for
what these kids do!
That isn't the only
reason you're being let go.
What do you mean?
We...found all the gay porn
on your iphone,mr.Conners.
So I'm thinking we do the part about jimmy's
relationship with his alcoholic father
after you smash butters onto the table.
Oh,sure that works.
You guys!You guys listen to this!
- It's amazing!
- What,dude?!
We just received a letter from the wwe.
From the professional
wrestlers we saw in denver?!
No way!
Gentlemen,we have heard of
your wrestling organization
and are quite interested
in its popularity.
The wwe is delighted to inform you
that it will be sending a talent scout,
president vince mcmahon,
to view your wrestling
event this saturday,the 24th!
Vince mcmahon is coming to see us?
This is our shot at
making itinto the wwe,
to be real wrestlers!
- Oh my god!Oh my god oh my god!
- We could become pro wrestlers.
I am completely freaking
ouuuttt.
Ok,guys!Guys listen!
We seriously have to focus here.
We have exactly three days before
the scout is here to see us wrestle.
We've got to step it up and
workit like never before!
Alright.It's time to
start the second act.
Let's bring the crowd
back from intermission,
and then improvisesome
stuff for saturday!
Yeah,no,I think congo
is a great wrestler.
I just think rad russian has hisnumber.
Yeah,but rad russian has a
lot of abandonment issues.
Oh,looks like intermission
is over we better head back.
I left my wife today.
Walked out of the apartment
without saying a word.
I ran away from my responsibilities,
just I like always do.
And I,again,
am alone.
Here he is!Hiding in
the forest as I told you!
Juggernaut!There is to be an
ultimate smackdown this saturday!
Are you going to run from that as well!
I'll fight anytime anywhere!
He don't run from fights,just
from responsibilities.
What do I do?
Juggernaut is my long lost brother,
and yet congo saved my life in nam!
It's el pollo loco!
El pollo loooco!
Thanks for coming,guys.
I'm sure you're wondering why
I've calleled you to sizzler.
Yeah.What's this about we should
writing our monologues for smackdown.
Well guys,kenny and I have been talking
Yeah,we've been talking.
And,I mean,smackdown might be our one
shot at making it into the wwe,right?
A shot like this might never come again.
- Yeah.
- Well,the way we see it,
we have three primary obstacles
in making smackdown a great show.
- ************
- Yup.
What are you talking about?
Guys,let's face it.They
can't wrestle for crap.
I mean,every time I wrestle with
one of them they flub a line,
or blow their monologue.
And token,he has no emotion,notiming.
He's the worst wrestler I've ever seen.
He's right.
What?Dude,it's really hard to do your best
wrestling when you're up against token.Right?
And butters and jimmy,I
mean,they're okay,
but they're never gonna make
it as professional wrestlers.
Well,so then wwe will
recruit us and not them.
No dude,they're gonna hurt our chances!
They're gonna hurt our chances!
Because we all know
that withall the new material I've
written is stuff those guys can't handle,
and we'll suffer from it.
So what do we do?
We gotta bring somebody else on.
Yup.We gotta bring somebody else on
who can handle the more difficult roles
that we wrestle against
instead of those guys.
Somebody who can do the harder
stuff we've written so that token,
butters and jimmy can
have smaller parts.
How do we find somebody
who can wrestle that well?
It's simple.We just gotta hold tryouts.
Number 17 step forward please.
You're wrestling a muslim immigrant.
You suspect he could be a terrorist and
your parents died in the 9/11 attacks.
Go.
You dirty,muslim bastard!
I don't trust you!
And I never will!
Do you know how it feels
to loseyour parents.
No,you wouldn't,you smelly
brown middle eastern piece of
Thank you.Number 24.
You're wrestling for the right
to marry mackenzie phillips
but just learned that she
had sex with her father.
Go.
Your father?
Your own father?
I don't care if you were
on drugs your sick whore!
Thank you.
That guy's a pretty good wrestler.
Yeah,yeah not bad.
Let's see.Can we get number
37 to step forward again?
Just want to get to know
you alla little better.
What can you tell us about yourself?
Not a whole lot to tell really.
Was born in fort collins.
Started watching wrestling
when I was four years old.
My father.
he liked it too.
until he died.
sometimes I think it's because
of him I follow this dream.
All my life,all I ever
wanted was to be a wrestler.
Fighting in the ring,winning that belt.
And so I dreamed every night
that I was the undertaker,
smashing skulls in,breaking arms.
Damn dude,that is
some bad ass wrestling.
Yeah,this guy crushes.
It isn't fair.
All my hard work.
I'm not going to take it anymore.
That wrestling show is
in for a big surprise.
I'm putting an end to
this once and for all.
He's here!
Vince mcmahon is here!
Wow,it's really him!
He's here.Oh my god,oh my god Oh my god,
oh my god,oh my god.
Alright.Places everyone!
Welcome to this performance of
wrestling takedown federation,smackdown.
Juggernaut?Juggernaut.
Hey,what's going on?
You know what's going on.
It's smackdown tonight.
Which means we might
haveve to fight each other.
You shouldn't be fighting anybody.
What about your cancer?
********Who was that?
It's triceratops.*********
**********
- *********
- ********
- You know what you have to do for the good of real wrestling.
- ***********
No,irene,*********
******do not abort this baby.
My body,my right.
***********
I don't think I'll
make to it the clinic.
No,you can't possibly mean that  YeS.
I think maybe I'll have another
abortion right here,right now.
No!
There's someone here
to wrestle you,irene.
A baby you aborted
many years ago survived.
He's here now.
*********
Why did you abort me?Why?
************
You,
get back in the trash
condition where you belong.
What do you think?
They are descent wrestling.
We'll check out the second act.
*************
**********
Excuse me.
I'm sorry,I'm afraid
this area is off limits.
Oh,don't mind me.
I was just about to
What the  is this?
Oh,how i long for the springmeadows.
*********
********
*******
*********
*************
Now,you listen here,el pollo loco.
**********
************
*********Crawl back
to mexico,hammerclaw.
Only one shot.
Maximum damage.
This is all your fault,you
wwe president.******
*******
**********
No!
***********
****************
No,no.Shut up!
You idiots want wrestling?
This is wrestling.
We want some real wrestlers.
This is ***********garbage.
You're ruining the
good name of wrestling.
Wrestling is from ancient greasegreece.
It's in the olympics.
What the heck you care?
Get off the mat.*******
Why do i care?
These kids made it so real
wrestling is gone from schools.
********
***********
- They took his job.
- I know.
You want to know pain?
Pain is dedicating your
entire life to a sport,
to a career andhaving it ripped away
from you like a baby from its mother.
Oh,man,they took his job.
They took his job.
Lost everything.
Couldn't even afford to pay
for my little retriever anymore.
Animal control came and got him.
They took his dog!
They took his der!
I ended up on the streets stealing.
Got bust bid the police and
had to spend the night in jail.
Then the inmates beat me
up and fractured my jaw.
They broke his jaw!
You see,I have nothing left.
Nothing!
Not even the will to live.
That was one of the finest wrestling
performances i haveever seen.
What?Will you not join
our wrestling organization?
I promise to make you our leading act.
You mean it?
Come.I want to get you
in rehearsals right away.
What,dude?
Hey,what about us?
Our show?
Sorry.boys,You are descent wrestles,
but lack the raw wrestling
talent this man haS.
This is all your fault,kyle.
You screwed up the second act.
Me?It was you.******
Face it,his singing sunk us.
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Proudly
Presents
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Sync:
YTET-天外飞砖
What the hell is this?
This is garbage.Screw
this.This is stupid.
Oh,don't start with me.******
Bye!
south
park S13E10