-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
South
Park Season13 Episode05
Hey,jimmy,what are you up to?
Oh,hey,eric.
I was just trying to write some
new jokes for my comedy routine.
Yeah,well,you wanna do something?
I wanted to hang out with stan and kyle,but
they're all pissed off at me for something,
So I have to hang out with you.
Sorry,eric,but I really
need to work,very much.
I haven't written a
good joke in over a week.
All right. Well,maybe I can help you.
You know,we can totally
write some stuff together.
Oh,well,sure.
I've never really tried working with a
partner,but let's give it a shotsgarrooski.
Let's see.
I was working on this. Why does
a squirrel swim on its back?
To keep his nuts dry.
Nah,that's not that funny.
Let's try something else.
A fireman and a pollack are
eating marshmallows when --
No,no. Pollacks aren't that
funny,dude. Try something else.
So the pope says,"what are
you,a stinking evolutionist?"
Here's some fruit,boys. Better
for you than potato chips.
Jimmy,look out. There's a black widow!
Wow,thanks,mom! You
might have saved my life!
Dude,if I'm trying to be
creative,i can't eat fruit.
Doesn't your mom have something
more substantial to eat?
You can check the freezer.
There might be some frozen
fishsticks or something.
If you like fishsticks.
- Yeah,i like fishsticks.
- Wait a minute. Fishsticks.
Fish... Dicks. Oh,my
god! It's so obvious!
- How did I never think of it before?
- What? Dude,you got something?
All right. Just run
with me on this,eric.
Save,eric,do you like fishsticks?
Yeah.
You like putting fish
dicks in your mouth?
Yeah.
Well,what are you,eric,a gay fish?
Fish dicks!Oh,dude,that's funny as
I think we're really
onto something here.
Let's try it out on the guys.
There's clyde. Do it to clyde.
Yeah,yeah. Let's do it to clyde.
Okay. Okay,shhh! Check it out.
Ue,hey there,clyde.
What's going on?
Eric and jimmy came up
with the funniest joke ever!
Say,clyde,do you like fishsticks?
- Yes.
- You like to put fishsticks in your mouth?
- What are you,clyde,a gay fish?
You said you like fish dicks in
your mouth,that makes you a gay fish!
Token! Token,got a question for you.
Token,do you like fishsticks?
Fishsticks? Yeah,i guess so.
Butters!
You like putting
fishsticks in your mouth?
Yes.
- What are you,a gay fish?
- A gay fish?
Hey,look,there's kevin stoley!
Hey,kevin,do you like fishsticks?
Hey,hey,mackey. Do you like fishsticks?
Fishsticks? Yeah,i like fishsticks,mkay.
Oh,hey,peterson.
Buying fishsticks,i see.
Yeah,i like fishsticks.
What are you,peterson,a gay fish?
and now here he is,jimmy kimmel!
All right,hey,how we
all feeling tonight?
So let me ask the guys in
the audience a question.
Do you like fishsticks?
Yes.
Huh,what are you? Gay fish?
And so,uh,hey,paul,do
you like fishsticks,paul?
Uh,sure.
What are you,paul,a gay fish?
So apparently more and more
americans are eating fishsticks.
Have you seen this?
Have you read about this?
Loving fishsticks. Kind of
makes me wonder,you know?
What is everybody,a gay fish?
It is quite possibly the funniest joke
ever conceived,and its origin is unknown.
The fishdicks joke crosses
all borders,all races,
All ages and eth thick groups
and is slowly uniting our country.
In fact,the only person who appears to
not get the joke is rapper kanye west,
Who becomes furious when
people use the joke on him.
Yo,that is messed up,yo. I am not gay.
And I sure as hell
ain't no fish,all right?
You really don't get it?
Hey,man,I'm a genius,all right.
I'm the most talented
musician in the world.
If I was a homosexual
or a fish,i would know.
- You're a rapper.
- Yes!
- An entrepreneur.
- Yes.
- And you like fish dicks.
You're a gay fish.
No,I'm not no gay fish.
Just gay?
I'm not gay and I'm not a fish. Man!
You are male.
Damn right I'm male.
A male that likes fish dicks.
Yeah,i like fishsticks.
You like to put fish
dicks in your mouth.
Yeah.
You're a gay fish.
All right,that does it. I'm
gonna kick your mother ass!
And then it was on leno
and jimmy kimmel show!
Dude,that's our joke
on national television.
We know,cartman!
We are comedy writers
and you guys aren't.
Jimmy,I've been thinking.
We've got to patent the fishsticks joke.
- Patent?
- Yeah,dude.
There's lots of people out there
using our joke on their shows.
We should be getting compensated.
Well,eric,that's really
not how jokes work.
I mean,you know,we should just be happy that the
joke is so popular and made a lot of people laugh.
Dude,that!
Maybe you were writing jokes for people's
amusement,but I don't work for free.
I'm gonna talk to a lawyer
so we get what's coming to us.
Jimmy,exactly what part of the
fishdicks joke did cartman write?
Well,he didn't actually
write any of it.He just uh --
let me guess. You wrote the joke and cartman
just laid on the couch eating twizzlers.
Actually,it was potato chips.
I knew it! Don't let that fat
turd walk all over you,jimmy!
Stand up for yourself.
Well,i mean,he was in the room.
Then just give him half.
What?
I like you,jimmy. But
you're not gonna win this.
Consider yourself lucky
he's only asking for half.
Craig,if cartman didn't do anything then
he doesn't deserve any of the credit.
Up. And if I had wheels,i'd be a wagon.
No,dude,crew that!
Jimmy,if cartman didn't write the joke then
definitely don't sign any patent papers with him!
Just say,"cartman,you didn't have anything
to do with this joke and you know it!"
Just give him half.
There are a lot of people out there making up
rumors about me that are malicious and untrue.
But I am going to prove once
and for all I am not a fish.
Because I am a genius,i have
ascertained that fish have gills.
Doctor,do I have gills?
He does not have gills.
You hear that? No gills.
So I can't be a fish.
And I'm a genius voice of
a generation,so I'm not gay.
So that is that. All right,it's over.
Now,are there any questions?
Do you like fishsticks?
Love 'em.
You're a gay fish.
No,I'm not!
All right.Recently,
recently we've all come to know the fishsticks joke
as probable the funniest,most awesome joke ever.
But who originally came up with it?
Well,here's your
answer.Joining us tonight,
the brains behind the incredible fishsticks
joke,the one and only carlos mencia.
Yeah! Viva la mexico!
So,carlos,you've got a show on
comedy central,a stand-up tour.
Where did you have time to
come up with this classic joke?
Well,you know,i was just kicking
it with my homies and my brain --
my brain is always so full of
ideas,'cuz I'm so funny and stuff?
So I was all like,hey,pepeeto,you
like fishsticks?
And my homeboy says,"yeah,carlos,you
know,you're so funny."
And then it just occurred to
me,oh,man,you must be a gay fish,holmes!
And that's just how I
came up with it,mi amigos!
Mother!
Jimmy,dude! Did you see?
Carlos mencia is taking
credit for our joke.
- Really?
- Yeah,dude. I told you this would happen.
Now look,i got a lawyer to
draw up some patent papers.
We've got to sign these so that people
know that the joke belongs to you and me.
Uh,i don't know,eric.
I really don't think I
want to sign that,very much.
But jimmy,some fat turd is taking
credit for something he didn't do.
Well,to be perfectly frank,eric,
i think I came up with a little
bit more of the joke than you did.
What?
Well,you know,i mean,i basically wrote
the thing and you just kind of ate chips.
Jimmy,that's messed up.
We decided that day to write
together. Don't you remember?
Hey,jimmy,you wanna hang out?
Sorry,eric,but I gotta write some jokes.
Unless you wanna team up or something?
Team up? Okay. Let's
write some jokes together.
Here's some fishdicks,guys.
Hope you like fishdicks.
Do we like fishsticks?
What does she think we are,gay fish?
Ooh,look out,jimmy,it's a black widow!
Thanks,eric.
Is that,is that how it happened?
Look,exactly who came up with which
part of the joke isn't even relevant.
We had an agreement,jimmy,and
if you wanna go back on that now,
Well,then you're no better than a jew.
I'm,I'm sorry.
It's cool,man. It's cool.
Here he is,y'all. Give
it up for kanye west!
What the hell?
Gay fish! Gay fish! Gay fish!
Yo,this noise.
It just doesn't make any sense,yo!
Why's everyone calling me a gay fish?
Kanye,look,we all think it would
be better if you would just drop it.
You know,i mean,if you don't
get it,you don't get it.
What you mean I don't get it,house?
I'm a genius. I'll understand it.
I just need to break it down is all.
Now let's see. Something
about fishsticks.
Interacting with me.
Makes me gay fish.
- Kanye,really
-- - shut up!
All right,what do we
know about fishsticks?
They're breaded.
They're fried. They're frozen.
Then under me,we have rapper,genius.
Gay fish are homosexual.
They swim.
Is it because breaded has
something to do with genius?
Which swims?
No,because you said you like fish
dicks,kanye. Don't you get it?
You see fish dicks is a play on words.
I don't need anybody
telling me play on words.
I'm a lyrical wordsmith genius!
Hey,kyle,can I talk to you for a second?
Dude,get outta here. I'm peeing.
It's just,i don't know
what to do about jimmy.
I'm starting to think he might try and
jew me out of half of the fishsticks joke.
I just need you to teach me
some jew defensive moves,kyle.
Because we really did
both come up with it.
You know what,cartman? I believe you.
You do?
Yes. I believe that you believe
you helped write that joke.
That's how people like you work.
Your ego is so out of whack that it will
do whatever it can to protect itself.
And people with messed up ego can do these mental
gymnastics to convince themselves they're awesome
When they're really just douche bags.
But I'm sure I helped come
up with the joke,didn't i?
Hey,jimmy,what's up,dawg?
Oh,hey,eric! Just working on some jokes.
That's cool. You wanna
write some together?
Hey,that'd be great!
I've always wanted to work with you.
You're really funny and
you're totally not fat.
Cool,thanks. Let's get to work.
Now,let's see. Something
that's a play on words.
I dunno fishsticks.
You know,'cuz of dicks.
You're really onto something there!
Hello,eric,have some chips,because
you're totally not fat at all.
Oh,thank you,mrs. Valmer.
Now,let's see. The set-up could
be "do you like fishsticks?"
Right. And then I say "yeah."
So then I can say,"what
are you,a gay fish?"
This is incredible!
- What is that?
- It's a dragon of some kind.
Don't worry,i can save you all!
Hey,look,eric killed a dragon!
He's the most awesome kid in school!
And he's not fat at all!
Thanks,you guys!
Nope. No,i definitely
helped write this joke.
All I can hope is jimmy
doesn't try to jew me over.
Is it perhaps that I'm fashionable
and fishsticks are crunchy?
Yo,kanye,kanye!
We found 'em,money!
Found who?
You told us to track down whoever
started the whole fishstick thang.
We found out who,dawg.
C'mon,man! What is this,man?
What the is going on,man?
Oh,,man. Kanye west.
Oh,no,oh,,man. Okay,look it wasn't me.
I didn't really start the
fishstick thing,all right?
You just saying that
now 'cuz you're scared!
No,man,it's true! I stole it,man!
I took credit for it,'cuz
I'm not actually funny.
C'mon,man. Do you know what that's like?
Being a comedian but not being funny?
Come on,kanye,i just take jokes and
repackage them with a mexican accent man.
You think you can make
fun of me? I'm a genius!
I'm the voice of a
generation! What are you?
Nothing!
Look at me,man. I'm not funny.
I steal jokes,my dick don't work,man.
I got to piss in a plastic
bag,man. I got no dick!
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I pay people to do that for me.
Oh,oh,no,man. Come on,i got no dick,man.
Now,explain it to me.
Why do people think I'm a gay fish?
'Cuz,'cuz you like
fishsticks,man. C'mon,man.
Don't you get it?
Please,just get it,man.
Why? Look at me. Look at me!
I love fishsticks.
I love putting fishsticks in my mouth.
You're,you're a gay fish,man.
Thank you! Thank you very much!
Well,about a week ago our country
was blessed with the fishsticks joke.
And ever since then us comedians have been
kick ing ourselves for not thinking of it.
But today,we have with us the true
creators of the fishsticks joke.
Please welcome the comedy
team of cartman and valmer!
Hey,guys!
Hi,ellen.
You guys like fishsticks?
Thank you,thank you.
No,really. Thank you.
So,guys,i gotta ask.
How did you come up with
this incredible joke?
- It was just -- - ellen,comedy is
like a game of racquetball,you know?
You serve,and the other
person hits it back.
It bounces off the
wall,you back-hand it.
And it goes back and
forth and back and forth.
Then hopefully you've got
a good joke. Thank you.
But,guys,this joke is so perfect.
Can you explain how nobody
thought of it before?
Well,ellen,the
t-t- --
Truth of the matter is that there's
never really been a team like us before.
I mean,let's be perfectly honest.
A lot of people wouldn't work with someone
who was disabled,but I see past that.
I look beyond jimmy's
disabilities and find a bond.
Which can unite us in comedy.
Working with crippled
people is really important.
That's so great. And
are you crying,jimmy?
Yes,ma'am.
Oh,don't cry,pal. You're
gonna get me started.
Anyway,what was important
for us,as a team,ellen,
Was to make sure everyone knew that we came up
with the joke,and not charles butthole mencia.
I see. And did you know that carlos mencia
was found dead in his house this morning
With fishsticks stuffed
down his open neck hole?
Excuse me?
Get my jet*****
All right. So check it out.
We've got offers from van de camps and
gorton's fishermen to do commercials!
It's always been my dream to go on a national
tv show and talk about the craft of comedy.
Yeah,that was cool,huh!
Eric,there's something
I really need to know.
What's that?
How do you live with yourself?
You know you had nothing to do with the
fishsticks joke,but you just keep pretending.
How do you look at
yourself in the mirror?
That's what I want to know.
So. Here it is.
How do you take credit for
something you didn't do?
This is bullcrap,jimmy,and you know it!
I had just as much to do with
the fishsticks joke as you did.
Dude,it's puff daddy!
Tie up these mother!
Now,I'm gonna ask you one more time.
Why did you start these rumors about me?
Please! I wasn't
starting rumors about you.
I don't even know who you are!
Oh,right. Everyone knows who I am!
I want to know how this got started.
Well,we were just talking
about ideas for jokes and --
Oh,so now it's we,huh,jimmy?
A minute ago you said
you did it all yourself.
Well,i just
abu -- I bu --
We both came up with it together.
You wanna know how it happened?
Hello,jim.
Oh,boy,it's my best pal,eric!
What you up to?
I'm trying to write jokes but I'm
not as funny as you,so it's tough.
Well,maybe I can help
you. We can team up!
Really? Wow,you would help
me,even though I'm crippled?
You are caring and not fat.
Now,let's see. How about a joke that
has something to do with fishsticks.
You know,'cuz fishsticks
sounds like fish dicks,jimmy?
Eric cartman,you are handsome
and not even remotely fat.
Thanks.
So what I'm thinking is -- do
you like fishsticks in your mouth?
What was that?
Eric! Eric,you have to save us!
An entire army of jew robots!
Oh,my god! What are jew bots doing here?
Flame on!
Flame off!
You saved everyone from
the jew-bots,cartman!
C'mon,jimmy,we gotta get
back and finish that joke!
-
- like fishsticks in your mouth?
What are you,a gay fish? There!
Wow,eric! Incredible!
Too bad I'm a dick and I'm
gonna take all the credit.
Suck it,bitch.
Aw,dammit. I guess it really
was all me who came up with it.
- What?
- You gotta let jimmy go. It's all my fault.
Jesus,eric. He's gonna kill you.
You won't even admit it was
just me knowing you're gonna die?
Jimmy,you really believe that you
came up with it all on your own?
Oh,my god. Wait. I totally get it now.
What? I stel don't get anything!
All this time I've been mad at
you,jimmy,for trying to take all the credit.
But now I realize it's just that your ego has
made you believe things happened differently.
That's what kyle was trying to tell me.
That you have such a huge ego you do these mental
gymnastics to make yourself a part of things.
Really?
I thought you were just trying to
jew me out of my part of the credit,
But now I realize that some people
just have egos that are so out of whack
That they distort everything and can't
rember the simple truth of what happened.
Jimmy,i owe you an apology.
I realize now you can't help
believing you created the entire joke,
Because your ego won't
let you think otherwise.
I just have to accept that.
Thanks,eric. For being so understanding.
He's right.
For so long I've considered
myself god's gift to the world,
That I couldn't take it
when people made fun of me.
But they weren't making fun of me.
They were trying to help me.
Boys,i understand what you did now.
Untie them,guys. I
know what I have to do.
Yo,kanye,you sure about this?
It's time for me to stop running.
I need to believe what people tell me.
Let all my fans know I love 'em,
But a gay fish just can't live
in the outside world forever.
Don't be sad for
me,guys. I'm going home!
*************
Couldn't*****
I******
'cuz*******
Gay*******
It's********
*******
'cuz*********
Now*******
*******