-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly
Presents
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Sync:
YTET- °îµÂÖí É­Æ¤
southpark\season13Episode
I'm goin' down to south park
gonna have myself a time
friendly faces everywhere
humble folks without  temptation
goin' down to south park
gonna leave my woes behind
ample parking day or night
people spouting howdy   neighbor
heading on up to south park
gonna see if I can't unwind
Come on down to south park
and meet some friends of mine
Alright.Cool guys.Gather all around.
Everyone should be a witness to  this.
Alright.You ready?
Now say 'I'm a dork and I
deserve what's coming to me.
Come on dude 'I'm a dork and I
deserve what's coming to me'.
I'm a dork and I deserve
what's coming to me.
Yow!
Alright.Your turn,craig.
Fellas,my underwear is so  far up
my butt crack,my legs  are numb.
Well,that's what you get for
being a douchebag again,butters.
You gotta take your medicine!
Yeah,I guess I deserve it.
What the hell are you guys
picking on butters for this  time?
Oh dude,you guys are not
going to believe this.
You know what we just found out?
Well,it turns out that butters  -- our
butters -- has never  kissed a girl.
So what?
So what?!
So I'm almost nine years old and anyone who
hasn't kissed a girl  by fourth grade is a dork.
That's right.
You guys,we got it!
We got it!
Sally darson is selling kisses  for $5!
Sellin' kisses?
She hangs out behind the temp
building during afternoon  recess.
She'll kiss any boy that pays  her.
You mean I'M... gonna
kiss a  girl today?
So then when she sticks her  tongue out,you
just kind of  lick it with your tongue.
Oh boy.I sure am nervous.
Nothing to be nervous about,butters.
You're finally going
to become a man today.
Butters,I think you
should  reconsider this.
How come?
Dude,you don't want your  first
kiss to be something you  paid for.
It's supposed to be special.
Oh,god.Why don't you go sit under
a  rainbow and write a poem,kyle.
I gotta do this.
I gotta know what it feels like.
Oh boy.
Oh jeez.Stay calm,butters.
How was it?
Pretty worth it.
Go ahead,b-butters.Go get some.
I'm goin'...
So uh... I was hoping
maybe i could get a kiss.
- Okay,cool...
- Yeah,cool.
Okay.
So you... got the money?
Oh,money,right.
There you go.
A five dollar bill!All for you!
Alright.You ready?
Thank you.
Atta boy,butters!
You did it!
You're a man!
Nice job!
Boy,oh boy.
I finally did it.
I'm a man now.
Geez.
I'm gonna start havin' lots
of  responsibilities soon.
I gotta start thinking about a  career.
There's gonna be family and
bills to start worryin' about.
No more playtime for you  butters.
You gotta buckle down and find
yourself a way to make money.
Hey,I know!
Hey fellers!
Fellers,do you like gettin'  kisses?
Cuz I know a girl that'll give
you a great kiss for just $5!
She'll kiss anybody?
Sure,scott!Even if you got diabetes!
It's almost like having
someone  care about you.
Geez,butters.Thanks for bringing
me yet  another customer!
Here's your $2 cut again!
Boy,oh boy!This sure is great!
I been thinkin' sally.
I could probably drum up some  third grade
customers if you  could do kisses before school,too.
We could make double the money!
Oh that'd be great!
But I can't do kisses before
school.I have swimming class.
Awww,nuts.
Well,I did have another idea.
What if we got another girl
to  fill in for you sometimes?
- What?
- Wul,you know!
We bring someone on,show her  what to
do,and then share all  our money together.
Wow you're right,butters.
I should start expanding.
We could have our very
own  kissin' company!
The next key to a successful
business is innovation.
I think maybe we need to  understand that some
boys simply can't afford the $5 for a kiss.
So what if we start also
charging just $2 for a hug.
Wow,that's a great idea,butters!
Thanks!
Sally,I think your position  behind
the temp building at  recess is perfect.
Meagan,I'm thinking about  moving you to the baseball
field after school during little  league practice.
Got it.
I got a kissing booth set up  at the kid's fair on
saturday,so kayla and ashley,you take  turns there.
Any girl that sells more
than  twenty kisses gets --
a little  sunshine... but if you
don't show up for  work at all,
I'm afraid you get  a stormy cloud.
This is gonna be great!
Sir!Sir,take a look at this.
We've got rumors coming in of a  possible
prostitution company  starting up in south park.
What?
Ohh,not in my county!
We've got no information on the prostitutes,don't
know who they are or where they came from.
So then we need to go after  the johns.
We need to let the men of this  town know that
if they pay for  sex,they're going to jail.
Sting operation,sir?
We need an undercover cop  disguised as a prostitute so
we  can arrest any citizens looking  for cheap thrills.
Hey baby,you looking for a  party?
H-how much are you charging?
20 for oral,50 for half and  half.
Anal will cost you extra.
Uh,get in.
Right here's good,sexy.
Now if you wouldn't mind handing
over the $20 for oral sex.
Okay.
Alright,buddy.
Go ahead and unbutton your  pants.
Alright.
Here we go.
oh yeah...  oh man...
Oh... oh sorry I was so  quick.
Oh,that's alright.
Nothing wrong
with -- freeze!
You're busted,buddy!
I'm a cop!
Ahahg!What?!
This is a sting operation  scum bag,and you
are going to  jail for soliciting  prostitution!
Got our first one boys.I'm
bringing him in for booking!
Did you guys hear what's  going on?
There's like four girls at the  school
now offering to kiss boys for money!
Yeah,I heard that.Now even staci
anderson is  selling kisses!
Stacy anderson?
Holy shit,dude.I wanna
make out with that  chick!
Hey,fellas!Would anybody like a coupon?
We are offering two for one
kisses tod through thursday!
Butters,you're the one doing all this?
Yup!I am founder and head ceo
of the butters' kissin' company!
Just look at this!
Damn dude,you made all
that  money off of chicks?
I'm telling you guys,it's  the most
genius idea I ever came up with!
A lot of boys will pay
to kiss  my employees!
You didn't think of anything  butters!
Guys have been doing what
you're doing for years!
You're nothing but a common  pimp!!!
A pimp. Huh.
Boy,kyle was right,sally!
There's guys with kissin'
companies all over the country!
The person managing all the  women is
known as the pimp while the working women
are referred  to as 'ho' or
'bitch'  You're a bitch,sally!
Hey look at this!
There's about to be a big
pimp  convention it looks like!
I gotta get to that convention,sally!
I could learn all kinds
a stuff  for our company!
Hi there!
My name is butters.
This sure is a nice convention  huh?
Yeah,I'm just starting out.
I really came last minute cuz I  was hoping
to learn more about  being a successful pimp.
You?
You be pimpin?
Yeah,just about a week now.
I have four girls at the moment,but I
feel like I could be doing a better job.
Now see,you think you a pimp but you
can't be pimping,you  know what I'm saying?
You wanna be a pimp,then
you  gotta learn the game.
See,it's all about knowing the  game.
What's the gaye?
The game is how you treat the
bitches,you know what I'm  saying?
Bitch gotta know when she out  there,she makin'
your mother  Money,you know what I'm saying?
You got your main bitch,you
know what I'm saying?
That be your bottom bitch.
That bitch rank higher than all  the other bitches,but
she still a bitch,you know what I'm  saying?
Yes,I know what you are  saying.
You don't have to keep asking.
See,it's all about mind
control.You got to act the part.
Any man can control a bitch's  heart but a pimp gotta
control a bitch's mind,you know what I'm  sayin'?
I know what you're saying.
Pimp gotta be out there every mother
Day keepin' his  bitches in line.
Can't let em go shopping,spending
their money on stupid  shit.
Bitch got to think that's your
mother Money,you know  what I'm saying?
Yeah!I believe I know
what you are  saying!
There you are,butters.
Hey dad!
Butters,we heard a rumor  that you
might have a little  girlfriend.
Sally darson?
Aw hell,dad,I got lots of  girlfriends.
Sally is just my bottom bitch!
Do you know what I am saying?
I've got to tell you,I don't do
this kind of thing very  often.
You're sure you're not a cop,right?
No way!
Let's just get to this,baby.
Alright.
So... you are agreeing to  have
sex with me for $100,correct?
Sure.I have the money right here.
Remember he's going to give
us the code word to move in.
Wait for the code word: Stretch.
Code word is stretch.Copy.
Oh,yeah.Yeah,get those pants down.
Oh,you feel good.
Oh,you're a nasty little  Aren't ya?
Yeah,let me see that
hot penis  of yours.
Oh,yeah,nice.
Yeah,I'm ready when you are.
Oh,yes,that's great.
Yeah,you like it?
- Oh,I love it!
- Yeah,you're a dirty...
Yeah,come on,harder!Deeper!
Oh yeah!Oh yeah!
Yeah,teach me a lesson,daddy!
Teach this little whore a  lesson!
Yeah!Yeah!
Yeah,that's right!
Oh,man,thank you.
That was great.
Yeah.You've really worked it,daddy.
You really gave my little
hole  quite a stretch!
That's it.
Move in!
Oh god!
It's the police!
Freeze!!!
You are under arrest for
soliciting prostitution!
Book him,boys!
Please!
Please,don't do this!
I have a wife and kids!
A wife and kids.
And you're out here trolling
the streets for prostitutes?!
You make me sick.
Take him downtown,boys.
I'm going back on the street.
That's it!Recess is over,back to class!
Boy oh boy,really great work bitches!
You all sold lots o' kisses  today!
Except for you meagan,I'm  afraid
you get a stormy cloud  sticker today.
So wait.You're keeping
all the money  now?
I just hold on to all the  money,cuz
bitches can't be  trusted with it.
We pool all your kissing
money  together,see?
But if you want to buy anything,you
just talk to the bottom  bitch
and then the bottom bitch  talks to me.
Alright.See you after school,do
you  know what I am saying!
Children I want you all to copy  down these
math problems,and  solve them before recess.
Yo,bebe.Bebe.Yo.
What?
Bitch,you wanna make some  mother Money?
Bitch you should be doing
kisses on the playground.
You can make fifty bucks a day.
Buy all the purses and
shoes  you've ever wanted.
I'll treat you right,bitch.
Shut up!
Oh,alright then.
Hey wendy.
Wennnndy.
Bitch,don't you wanna start
making some real Money?
Leave me alone.
You were made for the  playground,bitch.
You should be out there working.
Don't you wanna new lunchbox?
Nice new coat?
I can get all that for you  bitch.
- Butters!Dude!
- What?
You can't call my girlfriend  a bitch!
Well,I'm just sayin the bitch
should be out there working,is  all.
What'chya doing bitch,just
givin' kisses to stan for free?
You should be making
some  [Bleep] Money.
Stan!
Butters,seriously,if you  don't
stop this,I'll kick your  [Bleep]!
Clyde,here's a hundred  bucks.
If stan comes near me,punch  him.
Wow-wee!
Dude,we've created a  monster.
C'mon wendy you should be
puttin' that mouth to work.
Butters?
Butters,do you have a problem?
All these bitches are kissin' fellers
and they haven't figured out they
can be makin' some  serious Money.
Really glad you joined
the  company,annie!
Now remember,you're charging $5 for a
kiss,two for a hug,and  six for half and half.
Alright,bitch?
Alright,how about a freebie?
Oh,whoopie!
Butters,I really think we  should talk.
Sure,kyle!
Butters,can't you see this  is wrong?
You've got little boys all over  school
spending all their lunch  money on kisses.
Boys shouldn't be paying for  kisses.
It's wrong.
Kyle,every boy pays for  kisses.
Do you know what I am saying?
If you got a girl,and she  kisses you
sooner or later  you're paying for it.
You gotta take her out to
lunch,take her to a movie
and then  spend time listening
to all her  stupid problems.
Look. Look at stan right there.
He's gotta sit there and listen  to her
stupid  Problems  cuz she kisses him.
You ask me,that's a lot more
than the $5 my company charges.
Butters,what's happened to  you?
What happened is I became a  man.
I'm sorry I'm not your little  buddy anymore,but
there's a  time people have to grow up!
Do you know what I am saying?
Alpha tao omega.
Atos!
Alright,atos!
Our little kevin is 21 today!
And so kevin,we would like  to welcome
you to manhood,our  gift to you.
Give it to me!
Come on you sissies.I
can fit more of you!
Yeah,you like your
little  stripper whore!
You like her?
Freeeeeze!
Take them all to the station!
For oral and anal sex
with a  prostitute!
Half of them didn't even use a  condom!
Don't you stupid kids know
the  diseases you can catch?!
Hand me that evidence bag!
Sir,some of us are wondering if maybe
you're not... taking  this role a bit far.
What?No way.
Nothing is more important than  keeping
prostitution out of our  community!
Hold on,that's my daddy.
Hey daddy.
Where you at bitch.
I need my bottom bitch right  now.
Y-yes,daddy,I'm on my way.
I made you my bottom bitch,now you gotta
take care of your  pimp,know what I'm sayin?
Be right there.
Sorry guys.My daddy needs me right now.
Damn bitch,your pimp beat  your  Again?
He's an ****.
You know,I heard a rumor  about
some new pimp up in park  county.
They say he's real respectful.
Lots a girls are switchin' over  to him.
A pimp that respects his hos?
Sign my [Bleep] Up.
And that's $3,000 today for  sharise!
Did I do good daddy?
Really great work,bitch.
That is another sunshine
sticker forrrr you.
Thank you daddy!
Woooa boy!
And so,I would like to see  if there are any housing
loan  opportunities for some of my  employees,
and also what kind of corporate
tax I should be filing under.
And exactly what kind of
business are you running?
It's a kissin' company!
And you're making a profit?
Oh sure!
My black employee sharise over  there,one
time she made $2,000  on one customer!
Can you believe it?!
$2,000 just to kiss a feller!
She currently stays in a motel  room,cuz
a lot of her customers see her late.
You wouldn't believe the time
of night some guys want a kiss.
Do you keep any record of the
men getting these 'kisses'?
Of course,my bottom bitch  keeps
a database of all our  customers.
Specially the vips,like senator morris.
Senator morris?
Sure!
Senator morris gets kisses
every day at lunch time.
You know where he likes to get  kissed?
Where?
In a motel room.
Darndest thing.
He must get sleepy.
Alright.Get out of here!
Huh?Why?
I'm not falling for it!
But I heard acorn helps
pimps and their bitches.
We aren't giving you  anything.Get out!
Mrs. Davis,is there
some  kind of problem?
No sir.
Mr. Daniels!
You get kisses from my bitch
roxie in the ally behind  sizzler!
Boy!How do you like that bitches!
Approval for two housing
loans  and tax exempt status!
File these away,sally!
Okay!Daddy,how come this
ho get to  be bottom bitch?
What?
I make the most money for you daddy.
That means if anyone should
be  bottom bitch,it's me.
Hey screw off,ho!
Fair is fair,ho!
Bitches!Bitches!
Excuse me!
Well,well,well.
This must be the organization
I've been hearing so much about.
It took me a long time to find  you.
You won't believe the hardships  I've
been through trying to  track you down.
My name is yolanda.
I'd like to know all
about your  operation here.
You see,I just left my pimp  recently
and I'm looking for a  new one.
Well,we operate at a 60/40  split here.
Bitches have access to medicare
and now low income housing  loans.
Well,I think that's
about  all I need to hear.
Yolanda!
Yolandaaaaaaaa!
What's that?
Yolanda,please!
You gotta come back to me!
I got nothin' widdout you!
You gotta a lot of nerve
coming here,keshawn!
After the way you treated me!
I need a pimp that doesn't beat
me every time he gets drunk!
Yolanda,I love you!
I need you.
Not as my bottom bitch.
I want... I want to marry you.
It's too late for that,keshawn!
I just told this pimp
I was his  bitch now!
Wul hold on now.
I'd never get in the way
of  somebody being happy.
Us pimps gotta be
good,even to  each other.
Thanks,pimp.
You done changed the
game,that's what you did.
Marry me yolanda.
We'll move to a little chateau  in
switzerland,get away from  all this!
Oh keshawn!
I love you so much.
- ****.
- So much babe.
Let's be happy.Promise,baby?
Promise.
Oh oh geeeez.
Gals. Gals could you
all come gather  'round?
Gather round,gals,take a  knee.
Gals,I... I'm afraid
I can't do this anymore.
I'm going to be leaving the  company.
I enjoyed being your pimp and  all.
It's just that... when I see  real
love,like what those two  people have,
wul it just makes  me feel like...
wul like a  I may be a man now,
but it  doesn't mean I have the right
to be earning money for what girls  do.
Whether you charge
fellers for  kisses by cash
or by making them listening
to your stupid  Problems,
well that's your hard  work.
Bitches,this is your company  now,so get
out there and make  yourself some  Money!
Happy anniversary baby.
Do you like them?
I love them,darling.
I wanted to get you
something extra special.
Well,hold on.
I got something for you too,my  love.
I just put it right over
here by the -- freeze!
You're busted,buddy.I'm a cop!