-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
South
Park Season13 Episode01
would you look at that?
it's just incredible,isn't it?
i still can't believe it.
even though it's right
there in front of me.
yeah,it's just so astounding.
well,believe it,friends.the
impossible has happened --
kenny has a girlfriend.
yeah. a fifth grader girlfriend.
this is serious. they've been
going out for almost two weeks now.
so who is she?
her name's tamny warner.
she's the only girl in school whose
family is actually poorer than kenny's.
it's really kind of
beautiful, if you ask me.
you guys! you guy,i think
we have a big problem!
what?
well,apparently kenny has a girlfriend!
yeah,dude. tammy warner.
she's a fifth grader.
does kenny like her?
i guess so. she's like his
first real girlfriend ever.
oh,no. oh,jeez.
butters,what's the problem?
i just talked to brad dixon.
tammy warner is bad news.
al the fifth graders call her a slut
on a count she gave this kid dave darski
a b.j.in the parking lot of tgi fridays.
what?
it's true! ask anybody in fifth grade!
tammy warner is a total slut!
that bitch!
kenny gave his heart to her and
she's just gonna throw it in his face!
well,kenny deserves to know, fellas.
if you guys found out my girlfriend was
a raging whore, i'd want you to tell me.
all right. c'mon,guys.
hey,jimmy,what's a b.j.?
kenny! hey,kenny! oh,hey,guys.
listen,kenny,we need to talk
about your new girlfriend.
what about her?
oh,boy. kenny,we know you
really like this girl,but --
but what?
well,we've heard
that she's --
kenny,you girlfriend
is a notorious whore.
she even gave a kid named dave darski
a b.j.in the parking lot of tgi fridays.
your girlfriend's a slut, dude.
he took it pretty well.
- hey,tammy!
- hi,ken!
you decide what you
wanna do after school?
yeah,i was kind of thinking
we should go to tgi fridays.
tgi fridays?
yeah,could be lots of fun.
yeah,okay. but
-- kenny,listen.
there's something i need
to talk to you about.
there's a lot of rumors going around
about me,that i agreed to give a boy a b.j.
well,it's true.
but it was before you
and i were together.
and it wasn't my fault!
see,i was watching the disney channel.
and that show came on
with the jonas brothers.
jonas brothers?
you know,that teenage boy band?
every time i see them i get so tingly.
i just completely lose control.
and then dave darski showed
up and took me to tgi fridays.
and it just happened.
but it was only for one second
and i had my eyes closed.
i know it's terrible.
can you,can you forgive me, ken?
there you are,young man.
two tickets to the
jonas brothers concert.
thanks!
the jonas brothers?
dude,kenny,what the
hell is wrong with you?
aren't they those queermos
on the disney channel?
yeah,jonas brothers,dude. they get tammy
all hot and then she'll give me a b.j.
a b.j.? you want tamny
to give you a b.j.?
of course,dude!
kenny! you're gonna let a girl
put her mouth on your wiener?
do you know how disgusting that is?
girls' mouths are full of germs.
yeah,dude,that's gross.
it's okay. i'm gonna have protection.
what kind of protection?
can i have a box of condoms, please?
box of condoms? certainly,little boy.
which kind would you like?
uhhh,i'll take those over there.
these here? well,certainly.
cool.
kenny,aren't you a
little young for this?
no,i'm not young. i want a b.j.!
just because you have condoms
doesn't mean you're safe,kenny.
statistically speaking,the most
bacteria ridden place on the planet
is the mouth of an american woman.
and you're going to let
that near your penis?
yup! woo-hoo!
kenny,you're the best
for bringing me here!
isn't this awesome?
my giney tickles!
oh,my god! it's that tingling again.
i love you!
you're so hot,kevin. i love you,joe!
good night,denver! we love you all!
we love you,denver! good night!
oh,my god! i am so worked up!
i just want to attack you, kenny!
all right! c'mon,let's
go out to the parking lot.
and you,too! little girl in the red!
band would like you to come backstage.
you too,little girl
with the puppy tee-shirt.
they want me to come
backstage? oh,my god!
no,no,we're going to your place now.
it's a dream come true!
all right,right this way, girls.
yeah,come on in,everyone.
the band is waiting for you.
uh,not you.
no,that,dude! i bought the tickets.
what the?
the jonas brothers
will be right out,girls.
why do you think they
called us back here?
they must wanna have sex with us.
what? you think so?
sure. they're a band.
they called us back here so
we can give 'em blow jobs.
well,i'm not doing it!
just 'cuz they're rock stars
doesn't mean i'll do that.
yeah,i'm not giving
a blow job to anybody.
me neither!
hey there,girls!
hey,listen. we saw you
out there in the audience.
yeah,you were getting a
little crazy out there.
let's just get to the blow jobs.
blow whats?
i don't know.
look,we called you back here because we want
you to share our love of christ with you.
and see if you'll wear
purity rings from now on.
purity rings?
we all wear purity rings.
it means we are going to be pure
and not have sexl in we're married.
and it means we stay away from bad stuff,and
avoid people who swear on watch naughty tv shows.
that's just how we roll.
- yeah.
- yeah!
so what do you say girls?
you want to be kid hipsters like
us and wear purity rings,too?
okay.
and be sure to give a ring to
all the kids you care about.
'cuz it's the hip new way to roll.
wel,well,well. here he comes.
it's b.j.makay and his best friend bear.
so how'd it go last night?
- what's that?
- a purity ring.
purity ring?
yeah,it's a purity ring.
what does it mean?
it means i'm gonna be pure and
not have sex until i get married.
dude,you?we thought you really wanted
to have a b.j.before you got too old --
i did! i was really excited to get a
b.j.,but now i have to wear this purity ring!
all right,all right. kenny,calm down.
you're too young to be
getting b.j.s anyway.
it's good you and tammy are making a commitment
to each other that isn't based on sex.
yeah!
it isn't fair. i was so close to getting
a blow job and i'll never get one now.
fellas! hey,fellas!
i heard that kenny is still going
out with that slut tammy warner!
yeah,but it's okay,butters.
they have purity rings now.
what's that?
they're rings that says they're not gonna
have sex or do anything naughty anymore.
a ring that say you'll be
together but not have sex.
isn't that called a wedding ring?
* i've got a ring on my finger
to remind what i cannot do
* can't just do whatever i feel like
i've got to stay righteous and true
* i can't hang out with my
buddies or get into trouble
* 'cuz now we're both wearing
these rings for each other
* but who needs sex
and drugs and partying
* when we can cook a meal then
sit around and watch net flix,baby
* i've got a ring on my finger
to remind me that  i must behave
* no need to chase after girls
it's a promise i can never break
* we made a commitment and it is forever
* so we can spend every
waking minute together
* and if we get bored
it won't be a problem
* 'cuz we can just hang out with
other couples who wear these rings,baby
yeah,we found out that
once you wear purity rings,
it's best to hang out
with other couples that do.
got more in common,isn't
that right,sarah?
you know what carol and i
really enjoy is "grey's anatomy."
we love "grey's
anatomy," don't we,carol?
we adore "grey's
anatomy." don't we,nancy?
adore it.
kenny and tammy,do you
watch "grey's anatomy"?
we look forward to it all week long!
- sure is!
- most fun we've had in weeks!
* i've got a ring on my finger
to remind me what i cannot do *
* baby baby,baby,baby,baby *
and cut! great video shoot,guys.
this is bull pucky!
yeah! we've had it,gosh darnit!
oh,oh,look like we've got a problem.
our decision is final!
we have decided as a band not
to wear purity rings anymore.
yeah! you tell 'em,joe.
boys,i know you're tired, but the purity
rings are important to the company's image.
we don't care about the company!
and you're gonna say
that to the boss' face?
we aren't afraid of him.
well,i hope you're right, because
the boss is on his way here now.
oh,jesus. he's here. boss is here.
let's be strong,guys.
hello,sir! how was your trip?
what's this i'm hearing about
not wearing the purity rings?
uh,we'll just leave you alone.
so i guess we have some issues?
we need to talk about something.
oh,boy.
i just love flying all the way to
colorado to hear about your problems.
look,we just want our concerts to be
about our music and not about purity rings.
oh,gosh,fellas,let me explain
this to you one more time.
you have to wear the purity rings because
that's how we can sell sex to little girls.
se,if we make the posters with
little girls reaching for your junk,
then you have to wear purity rings
or else disney company looks bad.
but we don't want to be selling
sex to little girls anymore.
the rings stay on.
well,well maybe we'll
just refuse to go onstage.
you don't talk to me like that.
you little piece of
get the up. get the up.
now do we have a problem?
- no,sir.
- no,mr. mouse.
no,mr. mouse.
oh,that's good,'cuz i thought we
had a problem for a minute there.
all right. now get out there
and make me my goddamned money.
yup! he's in here!
dude,what the hell are you doing,kenny?
this is the day we were supposed
to throw cow turds at cars together.
we've had just about enough, dude!
you've been blowing us off
for two weeks now. what's up?
need to buy more dvds.
"grey's anatomy"?
kenny,what kind of douche
bag garbage are you watching?
c'mon,kenny. this isn't
you. we want you back,dude.
kenny? kenny? kenny?
you wanna look at "playboys"?
wanna get high sniffing paint? kenny?
you want your "grey's
anatomy" back,kenny?
oh,"grey's anatomy," cool!
oh,wow! this was a great season!
you guys,i think this is serious!
there's something really wrong with him.
it's that ring.
somehow putting on that ring has
turned kenny into a boring turd.
oh,my god,look at this! mother!
what?
jonas brothers talk music,
faith in god and purity rings.
these disney douche bags are
the ones causing all this!
yeah,this all happened the day
after he went to their concert.
all right,c'mon,guys.
we're not sitting back and
watching our friend die!
hold tight,buddy. we're
gonna find a cure for you.
cool.
live from 5 news studio in
colorado,it's good morning,denver!
we are joined this morning by the disney
super group,the jonas brothers. hello,boys!
hello.
now tell us what you're
doing in denver,guys.
uh,we're gonna be doing a live
concert from red rocks tonight
that will be live broadcast
on the disney channel.
in 3d,don't forget to mention in 3d.
and it's gonna be in 3d.
now,guys,a lot has been
made about your purity rings.
can you tell us about those?
well,um,we wear these to
symbolize how pure we are
and how we don't approve of
things that are naughty or filthy.
yeah,that's good. get a
close-up on their purity rings.
close up on the purity rings.
that's wonderful,boys.
it's good that little girls can see a
concert and not have it be about sex.
we understand that at the concert tonight
you'll be dousing girls in the audience
with white foam; is that correct?
yup.
well,can we give our audience
a peek? what do you think,girls?
you want the jonas brothers to
douse you with their white foam?
oh,boy! this is tv gold!
excuse us. excuse us.
hey,what do you think you're doing?
that's great stuff,boys.
you like taking the jonas brothers'
hot foam in your faces,girls?
hey,those jonas brothers are assholes!
yeah,their purity rings turned
our friend into a douche!
what the hell do you think you're
doing spreading this crap to kids?
who the hell are these guys?
are they from dreamworks?
goddamn eisner trying to
hurt this company again?
this whole thing is a frickinyou tsham!
i see what you're doing now!
you're trying to sell sex to young
girls and then confuse them by --
cartmahey
you aren't ruining my
plans this time,dreamworks!
dude,who the hell did that?
fifteen minutes! that's
fifteen minutes,people!
get another mic on that drum kit.
they almost g giined to ve> wthing!
how did something like this happen?
he up. he up,you little prick!
who do you work for?dreamwospuch
answer me!
we don't work for anybody.
oh,boy,i sure believe that!
you just s? ied to rirls n disney company's
big night for your own amusement,husc
what the hell did you do to us?
shut up!
and now,disney channel presents the
jonas brothers 3d concert spectacular!
live from red rocpre ae
guhitheater in colorado!
truly a night of magic,as we're set for
the biggest concert event of the year!
in about 10 minutes,the jonas
brothers are going to t> he the stage
in what disney is calling "the most pure
an innocent rock event of the millennia."
do we put the 3d gnfsses on now,da,da?
not yet,kailee.
everyone around the couns? y is tuning
in to see disney's latest kid pop stars.
yeah,jonas brothers at red rocpre.
we understand the jonas
brothers are getting ready.
what's going on bacpretage
must be exci -ng!
you better start talking.
you better start talking right now.
we told you. we aren't
working for another studio!
and there isn't a pnfn to
sabotage your big night!
we came on our own 'cuz our
friend's purity ring is killing h-- .
yohisre lying,i'll cut you up!
you see? we were right
about the purity rings!
a nice christian symbol can't
be used for profit gains!
we've all angered god!
you think god is in control here?
i'm in control!
i ue been in control since the
fifties in case you haven't noticed!
you ts pee faggots are going onstage.
and you three faggots
aren't going to st! a me!
nobody is rirls ning this. went.
i have worked too long and too
hard to have anybody this up!
where would you be
without me, jonas brothers?
your musi it!
it's because you make
little girls giney's tectkle.
and when little girlsyou
tgine. "s tickle,i make money.
and that's because
little girls are stupid.
and the purity rings make it
okay to do what. wer i want.
ven the christians are too stupid to figure
out that i'm selling sefricto their daughters!
i've made billions off of
christian ignorance for decades now!
and do you know why?
because christians are retarded!
they beli. we in a talking dead wouuy!
hello,folks.
now,noany' t> he it easy.
here's the jonas brothers!
c'mon,guys.
no,st! a! bring them back here!
it's over,mr. mouse. to
ve> wone's tuning out.
no! no,goddammit! no!
shut up! tarhut up!
that's it,girls.
no more disney tv for a while.
tom,the disney jonas brothers
3d television special has failed.
costing the disney coe guany millions.
and once agaihris mickey is
pissed off and throwing a fit.
vengeance is mine.
you are all ants and
i am your destroyier.
the disney "purity ring" venture will
most likely now prove a marketing bust
as mickey returns to
valhalla to slumber and feemak
aw,kehris look what we've become.
we're way too young to be this boring.
lsysl. i pnl put in "grey's anatomy."
no,i don't want to watch
"grey's anatomy," ken.
let's t> he off these rings,ken.
take off the rings? we can
take os i the rings?reallgu
let's take 'em os i
and just be kids again!
there'll be plenty of t-- e to wear rings and be
boring and ak and we're boring and lame a we wat d
yeah! tarcrew these things!
oh,i feel better already.
me,tobet
what ssl you and me go to tgi fridays?
and so,as we cos ]it this
young child to the earter a
let us all be reminded that
syphilis is still a deadly disease.
and it can be caught.
wen if using protection.
this young boy learned the hard way ...
i told him. woman's mouth is the most
wouerm-ridden pnfce on earter a i said.
statistically the most unsafe pnfce
for a man to put his edenis,i said.
well,now we know.
and knowing is half the bat] e.