-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Proudly Presents
I'm goin' down to south park gonna have myself a time
friendly faces everywhere
humble folks without  temptation
goin' down to south park gonna leave my woes behind
ample parking day or night
people spouting howdy   neighbor
heading on up to south park gonna see if I can't unwind
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Sync: YTET-天外飞砖
Come on down to south park and meet some friends of mine
south parks13e11
Alright,everyone.
Welcome to the dolphin encounter here at the denver aquarium!
My name is chad and I'll be your guide and trainer as you meet  these intelligent,
and t truly  magical creatures.
And here they come.This is trigger and dolly.
And there's bubbles.
Wow,cool!
Pretty neat birthday,huh  stan?
Yeah,this is gonna be  awesome!
If they come near you,you  can touch their backs.
Just no grabbing,please.
What whimsical creatures,aren't they?
All the dolphins you will be  encountering today are atlantic  bottlenose dolphins.
Now who'd like to get a kiss  from one?
- I would like to
- Oh,me,me,me.
I wanna kiss it!
Uh,alright.Let's just get you to put your  hands,
palms down on the water.
What the hell is that?
Oh no!It's the japanese!
*****You dolphin!
These are our favorite  animals here at the atlanta zoo.
It's dolly and seamore.
They are beluga whales.
These whales live mostly in the  arctic region.
Alright,jessica.
Now put your arms out like this.
Great job,jessica!
****You wha-ruuuuu!
Hey pal.
Sorry your birthday got a little ruined by the japanese.
Dad,why did they do that?
Well stan,the japanese just
don't really like dolphins very much.
Certainly not as much as us normal people do.
But hey,at least you still got  your t-shirt!
And you'll always have your  neat picture!
my new friend!
Dan dierdorf here welcoming you to this great football matchup
between the kansas city chiefs and the miami dolphins.
We're all set for kick-off and
Uh dan,it looks like some japanese people are now rushing  onto the field.
This is not the kind of thing you want happening during  kickoff.
****You dolphin!
Several whales and dolphins  were again slaughtered by the  japanese today.
This time at the six flags  discovery kingdom near san  francisco.
Aquariums had been experimenting with methods to keep the  japanese out,
but so far nothing seems to stop them.
When asked if all of japan  supported the slaughtering of  whales and dolphins,
the current prime minister of japan,yukio  hatoyama had this to say.
You way-ruuuu!
And  You dolphin!
Can't read my,can't read  my
no,he can't read my poker face
she's got to love nobody
can't read my,can't ready my
no,he can't read my poker face
she's got to love nobody
p-p-p-poker face
- You guys,you guys!
- p-p-p-poker face
Look,I really think it's time for us to do something.
This is all getting way out of  hand.
What do you mean? This song is sweet.
No,not the song.I'm talking about the japanese  killing whales and dolphins.
Dude,they've been doing that for a long time.
So?Dude,don't you guys care?
We have to do something!
What are we going to do,stan?
It's not like we can change the  way an entire country thinks.
I don't like it,but it's just  the way they are.
It seems like everyone has an attitude of
'that's just the way they are' and 'that's just the  way it is.
'Nobody likes it but everyone's  too busy to do anything about  it.
- I'm not too busy stan.
- You're not?
- No.I just don't care at all.
- Yeah,me neither.
Kenny?You don't care about whales and  dolphins being slaughtered?!
Stan,me and kenny don't give two shits about stupid ass  Whales.
You know,when all the whales and dolphins in the world are  gone
people are going to wish that at some point they had  taken the time to care
just a  little god dammit!
I wanna roll with him a hard pair we will be
I don't give a crap bout  whales so go and hug a tree
Hey,stan!
I heard you're looking for  people who care about the  japanese slaughtering whales!
Yeah!Butters,you wanna help?!
No,no,no,no.I got stuff to do.
But I wanted to tell you,there's these fellers on tv.
They go out in the ocean and try to stop the japanese wherever  they are!
Really?People who are doing something?!
I watch their show all the  time.
And they take volunteers!
Then that's where I belong.
The world is a vampire
Yeah,we are bad ass.
Any means necessary.
We're not protesters.
We're pirates.
WHALE WARS
That's definitely a japanese  boat!
Looks like they're whaling now!
****You whale!
Oh my god,they're gonna kill those humpbacks!
We gotta do something!
Pull up next to them!
The fight is on!
Sweet!
- Are we ready to do this?
- Yeah!
Yeah!Hell yeah!Let's do it!
Are we bad asses?!
Yeah!
Are we bad asses?
Alright.So.
what do we do?
Wait.I know!
How about we go on their ship  and then beat ourselves up!
And then we can tell the media  they did it!
Great idea,captain!
I'll start right now!
Oh my god.Luke's been hurt trying to save  whales!
Wait,wait,wait!I've got a better idea!
How about I pretend to be shot!
Then we can tell the media the  japanese shot me
and it'll start a international crisis!
Wul,wait.We don't wanna just lie about  stuff.
Why not?
Because then we're just  douche bags,dude.C'mon,they're right here.
Let's get hardcore!
You know what?He's right!
It's time to bring out the big  guns.
You guys ready?Ready?
And.throw the stinky butter  at them!
you stink now.
- Wait that's it?
- Yeah,we make'em stink!
Ha-ha,your boat is stinky!
Here,throw one!
Those guys always covered in  dolphin and whale guts!
They don't care if they stink!
C'mon lets break their boat!
Wul,no,that'd be illegal.
Yeah.
I thought you guys were  pirates in a war!
I'm a pirate in a war!
Pirates don't worry about the law.
You guys said you were bad ass!
We are!People think our methods are  extreme,
but we'll keep making  their boat stink as long as they are killing whales and dolphins!
The japanese are scared of  how hardcore we are!
Paul!
- Paul?
- What do we do?
- We don't have a captain!
- Oh,my god!Oh,my god!
Maybe he's okay.
UTILITY
Oh my god!
What did you do?
What you Acted like  you were doing.
WHALE WARS GETS BETTER
Things Actually Happen Now!
I want to hold them like they do in texas play
a little gamble and it's fun  when you're with me********
russian roulette is not the  same without a gun
baby,when it's not love,it  isn't fun
New Captain Not a fat liar like the old one
I'll get him hot,
show him  what I've got
WHALE WARS NEW CAST Member
I'll get him hot
show him what I got
Wait for it.
wait for it.
Now!
she get me like nobody
LITTLE BOY SINKS ANOTHER JAPANESE BOAT!
Inpo no gaijin!
Kuso 0 taberu na!
And now larry king,live!
My guest tonight is the  little boy who took over the  whale wars reality show
and turned it into a big hit.
Please welcome,stan marsh and  his crew.
Hey jordon!I'm on larry king,mate!
So stan,what motivated you,
what inspired you to get out  there and  make a hit tv show?
No,I -I don't really care  about the tv show.
I'm just trying to stop the  japanese from killing dolphins  and whales.
Once you became captain the  methods used
to stop the  japanese definitely became more  aggressive.
Was that the key to helping  boost your ratings?
No,I don't care about the  show.
We're pirates!
I just want people to know  that you can stop the japanese
if you have some real   Balls.
I've got balls!
Well,there are many people  who see what you're doing as a  positive thing,
and of course  many that see problems with it.
Joining us now is one of those  people,
and you say stan's  methods are unethical.
Larry,you can't just go out  and take matters into your own  hands like this.
If you want a hit tv show you  have to go through producers,directors,
people that are in  the unions.
But sid,you saw the show  before stan took it over.
You have to admit that it was  nothing
but incompetent vegan   Doing absolutely nothing
and trying to turn it into  drama.
Yes,but it doesn't justify
changing the entire show  structure that their old captain had pitched to the network.
Could we just talk about the  actual whaling problem for a  second?
But their old captain,paul  watson,was an unorganized,
incompetent media whore who  thought lying to everyone was  okay
as long as it served his  cause.
Yes,of course everyone knows that paul watson was a smug,
- narcololeptic liar with no  credibility but
-  Screw this.
I gotta get back to work.
On this episode of real  actual whale wars.
captain marsh searches for the  japanese fleet,
knowing they  could be absolutely anywhere.
Would you mind stepping back  a little?
Captain!Captain,some new volunteers  showed up to help us in our  crusade.
No,dude,we really can't  take any more volunteers.
But they say you know them.
Alright,dude.This is pretty sweet.
- Oh,no.No,no!
- What,dude?
Oh what,so now that I have a hit tv show you guys care about  dolphins and whales?
We always have.
Yeah,totally!
I asked you guys to help me  and you said no.
That's not what we said.
You said 'stan,me and kenny  don't give two -about stupid  ass whales'.
We were talking about wales  the country.
Look,if you admit that you  are only doing this because you  want to be on tv,
then I'll  consider it.
Admit you just want to be on  tv.
I just want to be on tv.
Kenny,
I deserve to be on tv.
Captain!
Captain the japanese have  been spotted near buoy 24!
Takes us out of port!All hands to stations.
Alright.Let's go save those whales,you  guys!
Captain marsh races his boat  to the last known location of  the japanese whalers.
If he doesn't get there in time,hundreds of dolphins or whales  could die.
As soon as we get there we  gotta be ready to deploy the  tracking devices!
We can't let those whales get  hurt!
What the hell is that?
We just got rammed.
The japanese want to play  that way,huh?
It's not the japanese.
What?
On deck,the crew is  surprised at what they saw.
The other boat is from deadliest catch.
A crab fishing reality show.
You think you're so cool,don't you?
You think you're a big boat  reality show on the block?
Take it away men's livelihoods.
what?We're trying to save whales.
***************
You're show is gay,maN.
Your show is  Gay.
Screw this.Turn to port.
But everywhere his reality  show boat turns,
the crab  fishing reality show blockses  its path.
Dude,You.
You.
It's been three hours and the crab fishing reality show isn't  budging.
Captain marsh's boat is dead in  the water.
Can't go after the japanese,can't help the whales or  dolphins.
Once again on whale wars,nothing is happening.
It's pretty typical time  because we know that
every  minute we're sitting here  stopped,another whale is dying.
Really tough.It's really hard.
It's like we've dedicated all  our times and our lives to  saving these creatures.
*******
Oh,he's taking it especially hard.
He loved dolphins so much,********
he *********** would do anything.
Anything, anything
Crab fishing reality show is doing fine.
But for the whale wars crew,it appears the show is over.
Until a sound is heard.
What was that?
Captain,look!
The whales are taking out the crab fishermen reality show.
It's like they know.
They do know.
They know everything I've been  trying to do for them.
Our********* friends of the sea have  saved the day.
Because they know that only we  can save them from the japanese.
Bonsai!
Jesus christ!
We got to get somebody to  shoot them with.
Look out!
I I can't believe it.
Dude,you know what?
Japanese people really do not  like whales.
Well,I'm in japanese prison  lord.
Japanese prison got me down.
Said I'm in japanese prison  lawwwd,
don't belong here.My eyes are round.
Will you stop that?
Oh,I'm sorry.Am I making things uncomfortable for you,stan?
It's your fault me and kenny are in the mess!
Things are bad enough without you being a smart ass!
There's whales out there being  slaughtered right now
and I  can't do anything about it!So just keep quiet.
You don't have a tv show  anymore,captain,
so you can  suck my japanese imprisoned  balls.
I'm in a japanese prison lawd,
japanese balls got me
Kite kure!Akihito sama irashaimasu!
So you are the ones who has  been a sinking our boats!
You speak english.
You have caused us many  problems!
Set us back many months!
Sir,we actually don't give  two -about you killing whales.Can we go?
Yeah,can we go?
Why have you done this?
Why do you insist on making  trouble for the japanese?
Why do you do what you do?
You know that 98% of the world  is against whaling?
Why can't you just stop?
You think you have the right  to tell us what is ok?
I have something to show you.
This is hiroshima.
Over 50 years ago,this entire  city was destroyed by nuclear  bomb.
We built this museum so that we  never forget what happened.
What?Dude.
At 8:15 am,the people of  hiroshima were just minding  their own business,
when out of  nowhere,a flash devastated them all.
Women,children,who died in the flash simply evaporated.
Those left alive,suffered the  worst pain of all.
Burns,radiation poisoning.
For generations the radiation  affected the victims.
Japanese babies born without  limbs.
Without eyes!
Sorry.
Little gassy.'Scuse me.
140,000 japanese were kill by atom bomb.
We have never recovered from the memory of that day.
It is impossible for a nation to ever forgive an act so horrible.
This picture shows the plane  that dropped the bomb.
It was called the enola gay.
And it was flown by the monsters who dropped the bomb that day.
Dolphin!
And whale!
where did you get  that picture.
The americans were nice  enough to give it to us the day  after the bombing.
We were so thankful for the  picture,
that the next day we  ended our war with america.
We will never forgive.
Never rest until they are all  wiped out.
****You.
****You dolphin and whale!
So that's what this has all  been about.
Dude,it actually wasn't a  dolphin and a whale who bombed  hiroshima,
it was the
Dude,they won't rest until  whoever is responsible is  completely wiped out.
Right.
Look,I -I think I can make everything ok here.
Can I just use a phone?
- Hello.
- Stan?
Dude,are you sitting at your computer?
I need you to do something for  me.
Mr.Prime minister,japanese  officials.
there's something you need to  know.
The photo you were given of the  enola gay was doctored.
Because the real bombers feared  retaliation so badly that
they  simply pointed the finger at  somebody else.
My government has authorized me  to give you the original photo,unaltered,
so you can finally  know the truth.
Dolphins and whales were just  framed by the real bombers.
A chicken and a cow.
Chicken and a cow?
Chicken and cow used poor  dolphin and whale as scapegoat?
This is outrage!
****You,cow!
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Proudly Presents
****You chicken!
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=-Sync: YTET-天外飞砖
Great job,son.
Now the japanese are normal,like us.
south parks13e11