[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Subtitles
Original Script: Subtitles
website: www.zimuzu.tv
Sina Weibo: @zimuzu
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134
Style: LOGO,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.56,0:02:16.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第六季  第八集』
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.56,0:02:16.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs21}本藍光版外掛字幕由  {\c&H9B30FF&}風吹來的那片云{\c&HFFFFFF&}  用WEB版調軸
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.77,0:02:21.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\fs16\fn方正大黑_GBK\move(-150,211,56,211,400,600)\clip(54.24,192,230.88,228.48)}本字幕首發于{\c&HEBAE00&}字幕組{\c&HFFFFFF&}網站\N{\c&H00C0FF&}www.ZiMuZu.tv {\c&HFFFFFF&}歡迎交流
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.77,0:02:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\alpha&B0\c&H000000&\t(0,200,\fscx2000\fscy600\t(200,400,\fscx2500\fscy300\t(29800,30200,\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\alpha&AA\fscy400\fscx400)))\move(158,211.2,46.5,211.2,29800,30200)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.77,0:02:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,200,\fscx206\fscy266\t(200,400,\fscx103\fscy133\t(29600,29800,\fscx206,fscy266\t(29800,30000,\fscx0\fscy0))))\c&HEBAE00&\bord0\shad0\frz180\t(0,500,\clip(-1,0,386,289))\pos(27.7,188.26)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.77,0:02:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,200,\fscx206\fscy266\t(200,400,\fscx103\fscy133\t(29600,29800,\fscx206,fscy266\t(29800,30000,\fscx0\fscy0))))\c&HEBAE00&\bord0\shad0\fad(0,330)\pos(51.4,231.16)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.77,0:02:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\p1\bord0\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,200,\fscx206\fscy266\t(200,400,\fscx103\fscy133\t(29600,29800,\fscx206,fscy266\t(29800,30000,\fscx0\fscy0))))\c&H573E00&\pos(39.5,211)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10m -13 -14 l 13 -14 l 13 12 l -13 12 l -13 -14 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.77,0:02:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,281,227))}翻譯  冰藍 送小孩 艾瑞卡 自然卷 小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.77,0:02:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,291,227))}翻譯  33來了 CS小明漫畫家 Reginamoon
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.77,0:02:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\frx-630\t(0,500,\frx0\t(4500,5000,\clip(40,213,40,248)))\pos(57.12,210.56)}校對 送小孩 冰藍
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.77,0:02:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,0)\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\move(57.12,210.56,400,210.56,4500,5000)\clip(54.24,193.92,284.24,228.48)}時間軸  加森 雪貴人 濤濤
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.77,0:02:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(300,300)\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs17\bord0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&HEDB425&\4c&H9EF6FF&\shad0\bord0\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))\pos(57.12,210.56)}后期 送小哥 拉圖  總監 送小孩喝胡辣湯
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.49,0:03:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都后退\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everyone, get back!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.74,0:03:23.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快回到你們家里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get into your houses, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.81,0:03:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.52,0:03:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得后退\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You need to get back.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.06,0:03:47.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我們得后退\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need to get back!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.40,0:04:32.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.33,0:04:37.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后退\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Back!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.38,0:04:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后退\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get back!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.22,0:04:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪安娜  你沒事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Deanna, you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.70,0:04:49.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, god. Oh, my god.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.49,0:05:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.19,0:06:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克  能收到嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick, you copy?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.89,0:06:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Anybody?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.69,0:06:25.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Help?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.48,0:06:33.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這里  尤金\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In here, Eugene!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.32,0:06:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.52,0:06:51.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  你沒事  走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good, you're safe. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.94,0:06:55.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.23,0:06:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好槍法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.63,0:06:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那邊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.95,0:07:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走  朱迪思在我家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, I have Judith!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.82,0:07:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行尸往東邊的墻去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The walkers are flooding into the east wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.15,0:07:58.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就說明西邊的墻會最先清空\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That means that the west wall will be the first to clear up.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.70,0:08:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們從那里進去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's-- that's how we get in.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.68,0:08:06.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔倒了并不意味著...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just because the tower's down doesn't mean that...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.08,0:08:10.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著  里面的人還活著\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Listen, people are still alive in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.50,0:08:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is how it happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.21,0:08:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總是會這樣  格倫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And it always happens, Glenn.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.07,0:08:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們還在  我們的朋友在里面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're still here. Our friends are in there,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.60,0:08:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關心你的那些人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}people who care about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.17,0:08:28.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懷孕的妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My pregnant wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.13,0:08:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想跑開  心懷恐懼  忘了這一切嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You just want to run away, be afraid, forget about this?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.37,0:08:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just go.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.97,0:08:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你就是這樣失去人們的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But that's how you lose people.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.63,0:08:46.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至是在他們死后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even after they're gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.64,0:09:00.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-把她放在沙發上  -樓上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Put her on the couch. - Upstairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.16,0:09:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,左手邊第一個房間\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}First room on the left.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.04,0:09:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:04.27,0:09:06.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在哪  -右邊這個\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Where? - This one on the right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.47,0:09:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-哪個房間  -進去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Which room? - Go in there!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.98,0:09:13.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆  你得關掉音樂  合上百葉窗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sam, I need you to turn off the music and shut the blinds.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.33,0:09:14.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為那些怪物嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because of the monsters?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.42,0:09:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你待在這里  保持安靜  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You stay up here and you stay quiet.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.62,0:09:28.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會沒事的  好嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's gonna be okay, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.30,0:09:31.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-媽  -親愛的  努力裝一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Mom-- - Honey, just-- just try. Just pretend--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.01,0:09:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,裝作你不害怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, just pretend that you're somebody who's not scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.37,0:09:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-努力裝一下吧  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Just try. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.29,0:09:36.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我愛你  我愛你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay. I love you. I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.52,0:10:09.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let me take a look at that.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.71,0:10:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我沒事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.42,0:10:16.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你誰都不信任  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't trust anybody, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.37,0:10:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那要分人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Some more than others.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.57,0:10:24.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你是我最不信任的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But you're dead last.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.32,0:10:28.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少我們彼此坦誠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, at least we're being honest.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.45,0:10:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不信任你  但我從沒想過你在撒謊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't trust you, but I never thought you were lying.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.85,0:10:46.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面怎樣了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How is it out there?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.94,0:10:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滿大街都是行尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're filling the streets.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.42,0:10:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可能腦震蕩了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, that's probably a concussion.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.61,0:11:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快坐下歇會  不然要摔倒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You should sit down before you fall down.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.33,0:11:03.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我沒事  -卡蘿爾...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I am okay. - Carol...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.99,0:11:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管我們要解決什么事  都可以等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whatever we have to settle, it can wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.28,0:11:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It has to.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.26,0:11:32.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得他不會回來了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't think he's coming back.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.69,0:11:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得他會回來嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you think he's coming back?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.98,0:11:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以聊天的  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can talk, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.23,0:11:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒必要害怕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't have to be afraid.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.08,0:11:52.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說話啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.77,0:11:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面有受傷的人  我那里還有病人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's injured people out there. I have patients.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.49,0:11:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不應該在這里的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I shouldn't be here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.18,0:12:00.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們都不應該在這里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}None of you should.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.02,0:12:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What about you?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.72,0:12:05.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What about me?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.67,0:12:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你干了那些事情之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After the things you've done,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.47,0:12:11.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你屬于這里嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you belong here?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.14,0:12:15.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.69,0:12:20.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以為我干了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you think I've done?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.29,0:12:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你殺了人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've killed people.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.13,0:12:24.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們解放了他們\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We freed them,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.14,0:12:26.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and then...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.12,0:12:28.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不過是準備利用一下剩下的東西而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we were just going to use what was left.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.48,0:12:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你來之前并不知道是什么事  對不對\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You came here without knowing what this was, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.47,0:12:36.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道摩根把我關在了這里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That Morgan had me here?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.20,0:12:39.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他說過他不會放你走的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He said he wouldn't let you go
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.31,0:12:41.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非他確定了你不會再殺人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}until he was sure you wouldn't kill again.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.47,0:12:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是感染了而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's just an infection.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.81,0:12:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前闖進了一輛車里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was breaking into a car
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.69,0:12:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后被生銹的保險桿割傷了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and cut myself on a rusty bumper.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.28,0:12:59.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,僅此而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.39,0:13:04.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什么公平不公平的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not unfair or just.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.09,0:13:07.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今沒什么是不公平的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing's unfair anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.35,0:13:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感染可能不會害死我  也可能會\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It might not kill me, but it might.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.02,0:13:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謀事在人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've done my part.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.48,0:13:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,成事在天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The world will take care of the rest.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.90,0:13:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,永恒不變\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It won't change.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.29,0:13:29.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我看看傷口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Show me the wound.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.83,0:14:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你生來不是這樣的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You weren't born this way.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.16,0:14:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你變了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You changed.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.45,0:14:10.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能改變的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can change.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.01,0:14:30.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怎樣了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.46,0:14:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是針對米瓊恩  但她在干的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No offense to Michonne, but whatever she's doing
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.61,0:14:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我弄得疼死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}hurts like a son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.94,0:14:38.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我剛剛把腿部處理好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just finished with the leg.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.81,0:14:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起來那是最嚴重的...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And that seems to be the worst of--
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.11,0:15:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.39,0:15:11.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.16,0:15:20.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經開始發燒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fever's setting in.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.10,0:15:23.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的時間不長了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She doesn't have long.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.28,0:15:29.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她清楚接下來會發生什么  對吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She knows how it happens, right? All of it?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.52,0:15:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  她清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, she knows.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.93,0:15:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她居然還有心思講笑話\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's cracking jokes.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.15,0:15:42.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.11,0:15:44.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有你她逃不掉的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She wouldn't have run.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.71,0:15:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儲備的食物足夠我們撐一段時間\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have food to last us a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.19,0:15:59.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它們遲早會聚起來  匯集到某處\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're bound to cluster up by then, move off to one area.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.86,0:16:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到那時我會想辦法去武器庫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When they do, I'll try and get to the armory...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.40,0:16:05.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把它們引開\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Draw them away.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.97,0:16:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-用槍聲嗎  -照明彈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- With guns? - Flares.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.74,0:16:12.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會把大門打開  發射照明彈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll open the gate, fire them off...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.47,0:16:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看能不能把它們引到...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See if I can get them somewhere...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.17,0:16:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正引出這里就好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Somewhere that's not here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.94,0:16:23.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你給瑞克的那張設計圖...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The plans that you gave Rick...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.01,0:16:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我仔細看過了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been looking them over.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.47,0:16:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.63,0:16:31.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那計劃行得通\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They could work.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.72,0:16:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼下你還這么想嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even now?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.33,0:16:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,深信不疑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even now.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.19,0:16:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空白處的拉丁文  是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The latin in the margins, what was that?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.81,0:16:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是雷吉在情況很糟時常說的一句話\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was something Reg used to say when things went really, really badly.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.96,0:16:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很幸運  米瓊恩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm lucky, Michonne.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.80,0:16:59.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟家人一起  為了美好的未來而奮斗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Working with my family towards a better future is--
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.44,0:17:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我的畢生所愿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's all I ever want
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.17,0:17:05.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我也得償所愿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what I got.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.23,0:17:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了自己想做的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got to do what I wanted...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.41,0:17:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到最后一刻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}right up to the end.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.66,0:17:22.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.93,0:17:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要這個地方運作下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want this place to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.21,0:17:31.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  但是那對你有什么意義\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, but what does that mean for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.59,0:17:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己想要什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you want for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.32,0:17:37.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.27,0:17:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You better.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.23,0:17:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羅恩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ron?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.53,0:18:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You all right, man?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.81,0:18:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊妮德死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Enid's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.47,0:18:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're all dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.92,0:18:18.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著  我爸會想到辦法的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, my dad's gonna figure something out.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.32,0:18:21.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他總是能想到  -胡扯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- He always does. - That's bullshit.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.00,0:18:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸只會害死更多人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your dad's just gonna get more people killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.49,0:18:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為他只會那樣做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'Cause that's what he does.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.95,0:18:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他就是那樣的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's who he is.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.01,0:18:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸是個殺人兇手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your dad's a killer.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.32,0:18:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So was yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.65,0:18:50.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我們得想辦法  -我死了  卡爾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- We need to work this out. - I'm dead, Carl.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.52,0:18:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我媽死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My mom is dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.77,0:18:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我弟死了  -他們沒死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- My brother is. - No, they're not.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.85,0:19:00.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會活下來的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're gonna make it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.04,0:19:07.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸  你們也死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your dad-- you're dead, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.36,0:19:13.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're all dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.33,0:19:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡爾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Carl!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.11,0:19:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卡爾  -羅恩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Carl!  - Ron!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.71,0:19:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-讓我進去  卡爾  -羅恩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Let me in! Carl! - Ron!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.17,0:19:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡爾  開門\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Carl, open the door!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.23,0:19:41.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羅恩  馬上開門\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ron, open the door right now!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.94,0:19:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,退后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Back up.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.45,0:19:53.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幫把手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Help!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.03,0:20:00.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  羅恩  過來\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please, Ron! Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.12,0:20:04.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.47,0:20:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來了  讓開\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here, move.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.04,0:20:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-小心  -讓開\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Watch out! - Move!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.10,0:20:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個不夠  而且我們得保持安靜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need more, and we need to be quiet.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.55,0:20:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去找找還有什么能用的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll see what I can find.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.95,0:20:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我也去  -幫把手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Me, too. - Help.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.64,0:20:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我來  -里面發生了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I got it. - Hey, hey, what happened in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.13,0:20:35.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們在找工具  結果打翻了一個架子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We were looking for tools and knocked over a shelf.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.78,0:20:38.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們聽到了叫聲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We heard yelling.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.60,0:20:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  羅恩看到它們沖破了門\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, Ron saw them break through the gates.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.14,0:20:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們必須逃走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We had to move.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.24,0:20:43.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是這樣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.37,0:20:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡爾  我媽臥室有床頭柜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Carl, there's nightstands in my mom's room.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.10,0:20:46.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以用它們抵住沙發\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can brace the couch with them.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.11,0:20:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么  -你們那時聽起來像是在打架\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What? - Hey, it sounded like you were fighting.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.43,0:20:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  但我們是在跟行尸打架\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, but we were fighting them.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.23,0:20:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡爾  沒事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Carl? It's okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.34,0:20:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.96,0:21:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-聽著  我...  -槍給我  槍柄對著我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Listen, I, uh-- - Hand me the gun, grip first.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.68,0:21:11.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卡爾  對不起  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Carl, I'm sorry. - Yeah, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.22,0:21:13.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把槍給我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now give me the gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.30,0:21:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著  伙計\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, man...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.97,0:21:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.36,0:21:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爸殺了你爸  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My dad killed your dad, but,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.02,0:21:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些事你得明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you need to know something.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.40,0:21:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸是個混賬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your dad was an asshole.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.86,0:21:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它們把雕像推倒了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They knocked the sculpture over.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.40,0:21:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噪音引來了更多行尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All that noise, it's drawing more.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.31,0:21:52.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去照顧她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll get her.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.36,0:22:28.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我還活著\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, it's still me!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.91,0:22:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm so-- I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.96,0:22:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.36,0:22:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想看她最后一眼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I-- I wanted to see her one last time.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.93,0:22:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以為我能走過來\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought I could make it.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.28,0:22:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我的腿不聽計劃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My legs had other plans.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.07,0:22:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,過來\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.07,0:22:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢點  慢點\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Easy, easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.95,0:23:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就喜歡亂計劃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You and plans.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.60,0:23:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在是你的計劃了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're yours now.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.04,0:23:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從現在起...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}From now on...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.07,0:23:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須有人陪著你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Someone needs to be with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.36,0:23:16.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Y-yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.80,0:23:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能是她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It can't be her.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.12,0:23:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.47,0:23:29.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把她放到別的地方去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll find someplace else to put her.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.75,0:23:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.68,0:23:34.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I, uh--
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.16,0:23:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我寫了點東西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I wrote something...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.08,0:23:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給斯賓塞和瑪姬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For Spencer, for Maggie.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.35,0:23:48.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一定會送到他們手上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll make sure they get them.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.63,0:23:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能照顧好他嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Will you look out for him?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.05,0:23:56.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我會的  -你會像照顧你的人一樣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I will. - Will you look out for him
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.86,0:24:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,照顧好他嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}like you look out for your people?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.22,0:24:05.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你猜怎么著\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Guess what.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.18,0:24:09.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們都是你的人  瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're all your people, Rick.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.87,0:24:11.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They are.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.87,0:24:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情還沒有發展成那樣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We haven't had a chance to make it that.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.89,0:24:16.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但已經是那樣了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But that's how it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.70,0:24:22.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沖過去幫你不是因為我喜歡你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't run over to help you out there because I like you...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.69,0:24:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是因為我認為你是一個好人  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or because I think you're a good man,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.38,0:24:27.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個好父親...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a good father...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.77,0:24:31.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是因為你能長出一嘴大胡子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or that you can grow one hell of a beard.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.85,0:24:37.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跑過去幫你是因為你是我們的一員\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I ran over to help because you are one of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.20,0:24:41.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這才是正確的答案\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's the right answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.89,0:24:46.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.40,0:25:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}世界史
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.11,0:25:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分人都跑進自己屋里了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Most people got inside their houses. There's that.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.27,0:25:15.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得到此為止了嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You think this is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.18,0:25:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.08,0:25:21.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得這地方完蛋了嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you think this place is over?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.81,0:25:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.59,0:25:29.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得我們所有人都應該努力爭取\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think we gotta earn it, all of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.51,0:25:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是等著  得知大家是否安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whether it's waiting, knowing if everyone's safe,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.36,0:25:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應對此事或者對抗它們\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}dealing with that, or fighting them.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.96,0:25:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,住在這種地方總得付出相應的代價吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A place like this has gotta have a price, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.56,0:25:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們付出的還不夠多嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We haven't paid it already?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.59,0:25:49.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顯然不夠\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Apparently not.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.22,0:26:04.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺亞伯拉罕已經死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It feels like Abraham's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.19,0:26:09.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺就是這樣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what it feels like.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.58,0:26:10.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他沒死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's not dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.67,0:26:13.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How do you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.82,0:26:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我沒看到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'cause I didn't see it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.57,0:26:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你感覺怎么樣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Doesn't matter what it feels like.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.78,0:26:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他還沒死  這地方還沒有完蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's not dead, and this place isn't over.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.92,0:26:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們在這里呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.65,0:26:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我們要做什么  美女\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, what are we gonna do, gorgeous?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.94,0:26:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們進屋子  看看另一邊的情況\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Gonna get in there, see what's happening on the other side.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.92,0:26:43.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以用槍把鎖崩了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can shoot out this lock.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.99,0:26:48.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不應該浪費子彈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We shouldn't waste the bullet.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.58,0:26:52.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要用子彈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You won't need to.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.03,0:27:01.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開鎖是我的技能之一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lock-picking is within my skill set.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.64,0:27:25.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還好嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.88,0:27:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,閉目養神而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just resting my eyes.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.00,0:28:02.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡蘿爾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Carol?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.22,0:28:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它們太多了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's just too many of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.67,0:28:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人上樓  快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everybody get upstairs now!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.03,0:28:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后退\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Back off!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.40,0:28:40.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后退\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Back off!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.00,0:28:45.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快點  快點\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on! Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.83,0:28:49.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用沙發\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The couch!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.17,0:28:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把樓道封住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's block the stairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.38,0:29:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我搞定這個  你去搞定后面那個\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got this one, you get the one behind it.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.95,0:29:10.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少需要兩只\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're gonna need at least two.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.58,0:29:21.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,離他遠一點\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get the hell away from him.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.05,0:29:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他被綁上了  他沒有...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's tied up, he's not--
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.08,0:29:24.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說離他遠一點\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I said get away from him.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.61,0:29:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這事本可以等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This could've waited.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.15,0:29:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該等等的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It should have.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.14,0:29:40.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在等不了了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now it can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.43,0:29:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你待在這\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You stay here.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.64,0:29:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到它們擠進來就叫我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You see anyone squeezing through, you get me.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.78,0:29:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們需要床單  足夠所有人用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're gonna need bed sheets, enough for everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.77,0:29:57.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要床單干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bed sheets for what?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.50,0:29:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們一起去武器庫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We all go to the armory.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.71,0:30:02.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-怎么去  -我們要把它們開膛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- How? - We're gonna gut these things.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.96,0:30:04.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后披著內臟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Cover ourselves with the insides.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.58,0:30:07.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這能掩蓋氣味  讓它們覺得我們是行尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It'll mask our smell, make them think we're like them.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.26,0:30:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前也干過\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've done it before.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.40,0:30:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們保持冷靜  別引起它們的注意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We stay calm, we don't draw attention,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.40,0:30:15.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就可以穿過尸群\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can move right through them.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.82,0:30:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它們在房子里  發出聲音\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're in the house, they're making noise.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.11,0:30:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會引來更多行尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}More are coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.98,0:30:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留在這會死的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Anyone who stays here is gonna die.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.54,0:30:41.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪安娜怎么辦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What about Deanna?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.76,0:30:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不需要用刀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't need the knife.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.26,0:31:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以談談\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.57,0:31:02.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  沒什么好談的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, this is over.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.87,0:31:04.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們能比他們好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can be better than them.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.56,0:31:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們本來就比他們好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We are better than them.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.09,0:31:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺人就未必了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not if we kill.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.14,0:31:11.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們逼我們殺人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They made us kill.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.73,0:31:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們必須得阻止  我必須得阻止\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We had to stop it. I had to stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.02,0:31:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要活著  就有各種可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}With life, there's possibility,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.82,0:31:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使我們永遠不放他出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even if we never let him out.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.49,0:31:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我會出去的  -即使我們永遠不放他出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I'd get out. - Even if we never let him out,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.83,0:31:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也有可能反省他的所為\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}he could know what he's done.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.48,0:31:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他有可能...  -我不想殺你  摩根\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- He could know... - I don't want to have to kill you, Morgan.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.88,0:31:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不會的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You won't.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.69,0:31:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.96,0:31:34.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做不到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.26,0:31:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會讓你殺了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I won't let you.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.15,0:32:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's happening out there?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.35,0:32:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它們在涌進來\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're getting in.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.64,0:32:08.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們余下的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The rest of us...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.99,0:32:12.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們得走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we're gonna have to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.19,0:32:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你要是想的話  我可以...  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- If you want me to, I'll-- - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.53,0:32:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒準備好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.07,0:32:25.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.24,0:32:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后會的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I will be.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.81,0:32:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.91,0:32:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當我準備好時\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And when I am...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.82,0:32:45.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會自己動手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll do it myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.72,0:32:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,命是我自己的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.66,0:32:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己開頭  自己結尾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Start to finish.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.46,0:33:01.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,[拉丁語]\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dolor hic tibi proderit olim.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.89,0:33:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What does it mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.33,0:33:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"總有一天  你所承受過的痛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Someday this pain
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.69,0:33:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會有助于你"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}will be useful to you."
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.94,0:33:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.33,0:33:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們需要你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They need you.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.99,0:33:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.56,0:33:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For what?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.17,0:33:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝你還有信念\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For believing.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.34,0:33:50.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我依舊有信念\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I still believe.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.07,0:33:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我全搞砸了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I cocked it all up...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.48,0:33:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我想明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...but I figured it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.78,0:34:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.12,0:34:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在該你想明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now you figure it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:11.96,0:34:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.16,0:34:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.89,0:34:18.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺出去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give'em hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.75,0:34:29.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們得走了  你先走我隨后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need to move. You, then me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.80,0:34:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.59,0:34:45.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mom?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.87,0:34:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得聽我說  好嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You need to listen to me, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.21,0:34:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不再安全了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We aren't safe here anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.55,0:34:59.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有這么做我們在外面才會安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, we need to do this so that we can be safe out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.83,0:35:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們得裝得像怪物一樣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need to look like the monsters.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.32,0:35:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要  求你了  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, please, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.51,0:35:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親愛的  我們得走了  好嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, honey, we have to go, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.99,0:35:06.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們必須這么做  山姆\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have to, Sam.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.10,0:35:10.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親愛的  假裝你很勇敢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Honey, just-- just pretend you're brave.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.16,0:35:14.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好嗎  就裝一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay? Just make it all pretend.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.23,0:35:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這都不是真的  你是個不害怕的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, none of this is real and you're somebody who isn't afraid.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.87,0:35:21.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.77,0:35:24.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.68,0:35:29.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了殺他我會殺了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I will kill you to kill him
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.90,0:35:32.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我不想再讓任何人死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because I don't want anyone else to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.24,0:35:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你應該殺了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You should kill me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.71,0:35:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過你們都會死的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But you're all going to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.15,0:35:44.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們不屬于這里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't belong here.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.89,0:35:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我你很肯定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You tell me you're sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.57,0:35:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我你知道會發生什么  是什么結局\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You tell me you know what'll happen, how it will go.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.79,0:35:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,請讓開\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please step aside.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.17,0:36:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只說一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not asking you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.97,0:36:32.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.62,0:36:44.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們必須走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.63,0:36:50.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們準備好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.99,0:36:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羅恩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ron?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.86,0:36:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.87,0:37:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我去帶上朱迪思  -瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I'll get Judith. - Rick.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.20,0:37:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在外面不會放棄\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not gonna give up out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:05.07,0:37:07.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會回頭  不管發生什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I will not turn back, no matter what happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.24,0:37:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.29,0:37:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.90,0:37:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你別這樣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:27.83,0:37:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別哪樣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't what?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.34,0:37:32.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別殺他們\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't kill them.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.07,0:37:36.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說他們已經死了  你說我已經死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You said they were already dead you said I was.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.27,0:37:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒必要殺我們\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't need to kill us.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.73,0:37:40.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我們自己死吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just let us die.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.91,0:37:43.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我們自己死吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just let us die.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.95,0:37:52.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說的都是屁話\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You are so full of shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.73,0:37:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就喜歡你們身上這點\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're what I like about people.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.45,0:38:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔拉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tara.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.17,0:38:03.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, god.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.87,0:38:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-別亂動  -別這樣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Just be still. - Don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.74,0:38:09.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放下槍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lower the guns.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.48,0:38:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放下槍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lower the guns.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.65,0:38:14.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.72,0:38:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丟過來\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Slide them over.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.62,0:38:18.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要槍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want them.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.81,0:38:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不需要她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't need her.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.95,0:38:34.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.48,0:38:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不需要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:38.85,0:38:39.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后退\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Back.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:40.95,0:38:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后退\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Back.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.42,0:38:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在外面活不下去的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're not gonna make it out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.69,0:38:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走著瞧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll see.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.58,0:42:01.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mom?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:04.39,0:42:05.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mom?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:07.89,0:42:09.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:43:01.84,0:43:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-達里爾  -我看見了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Daryl? - Yeah, I see.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:04.64,0:43:06.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What in the holy shit?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:17.36,0:43:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們為什么不出來\N{\fn微軟雅黑\fs14}Why don’t you come on out?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:18.83,0:43:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到路上來\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Join us in the road.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:21.59,0:43:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你們想反抗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, if you want to resist,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:23.54,0:43:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耍花招\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}try something. I mean,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:25.48,0:43:26.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你們的自由  我猜\N{\fn微軟雅黑\fs14}it’s a choice, I guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:27.34,0:43:29.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我們會消滅你們\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But we will end your asses.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:30.09,0:43:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把你們從菊花到鼻子撕成兩半\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Split you right in two, straight through to the sinuses.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:34.57,0:43:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以下來吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:55.35,0:43:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's great,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:57.17,0:43:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一開始就很順利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's going well right out of the gate.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:00.16,0:44:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在  第二步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, step 2.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:01.63,0:44:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出你們的武器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hand over your weapons.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:03.23,0:44:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,憑什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why should we?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:05.20,0:44:06.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為武器不是你們的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, they are not yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:07.38,0:44:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:09.64,0:44:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是這樣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See...
Dialogue: 0,0:44:12.09,0:44:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們的武器  卡車  卡車里的汽油\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your weapons, your truck, the fuel in your truck,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:15.79,0:44:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,貯物箱里的薄荷糖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if you got mints in your glove compartment,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:18.38,0:44:20.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,座位下的色情片\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if you got porn underneath the seat,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.27,0:44:22.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,座位里的零錢  甚至是座位本身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}change in the seats, hell, the seats themselves,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:22.38,0:44:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,腳墊  地圖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the floor mats, your maps,
Dialogue: 0,0:44:24.99,0:44:28.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放在中控臺里"應急"的紙巾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}little stash for emergency napkins you got there in the console.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:29.43,0:44:33.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那些東西都不再是你們的了  -那是誰的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- None of those things are yours anymore. - Whose are they?
Dialogue: 0,0:44:35.47,0:44:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們的財產...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your property...
Dialogue: 0,0:44:37.56,0:44:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在歸尼根所有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}now belongs to Negan.
