* i'm going down
to south park *
* gonna have
myself a time *
* friendly faces
everywhere *
* humble folks
without temptation *
* going down
to south park *
* gonna leave my
woes behind *
* ample parking
day or night *
* people spouting
"howdy neighbor" *
* headin' on up
to south park *
* gonna see
if i can't unwind *
* tim-Tmah tim-Mah,
tim-Mah tim-Mah timmy tim-Mah *
* so come on down
to south park *
* and meet some
friends of mine *
Be careful
with my baby!
What have we got?
Not sure- Looks like
a possible code 56!
Kenny...
shut up, kenny!
You're going to
be okay, baby...
Get me 50 ccs
of ketamine stat!
And get something
for the kid too!
Is he going to
be okay?
Let the doctor
do his work, ma'am.
Doctor!
Did you find out
what's wrong with him?
I'm afraid he's...
Running out
of time.
Why, what's
wrong with him?
It's his time,
it's running out.
Well, what
does he need?
He needs to have
more time.
What can we do?
Well, i suppose we could
try a time transplant...
I'll have to call in
a specialist.
It's going to be
okay, baby.
We're going to
get you more time.
Kenny!
Goddamn you kenny!
Hello there, children!
Chef, cartman is
in the hospital.
They think
he might die.
Yeah, and we don't know
whether or not we should care.
Well, what's
wrong with him?
Well, nobody
seems to know.
But we think it's because
he drank kenny's soul
Four weeks ago.
Kenny's ashes
were in an urn
And cartman drank it thinking
it was chocolate milk mix.
Children!
Why didn't you tell me
about this sooner?
Like we said, we didn't know
whether or not we should care.
Well you should!
Cartman is your friend
whether you like him or not!
Now come on, we gotta
get to that hospital!
He's looking
a little better today.
Yes, but his time
is still getting weaker.
It will give out soon
unless we do something.
Hey guys!
How's it going?
Cartman?
No, that's kenny.
What the hell are
you assholes doing here?
That's cartman.
Oh my god, eric
How long have you been
channeling kenny?
Oh, about a month.
Let's not validate
his delusions.
Kenny?
Kenny do you know
what you need to get free?
He's gone again.
Ms. Cartman, we need to
get eric to a medium
Who can speak with people
who have crossed over.
What!
That's preposterous!
What this child needs
is a time transplant!
This hospital isn't
gonna do him any good!
We need to take him
to see john edward.
Hey, i've
seen that guy!
He has a tv show where
he brings people on
And talks to
their dead relatives!
That's right.
We have to go see him
in new york!
I warn you, ms. Cartman,
Your son's time could
give out at any minute.
He needs to be kept here where
his time can be monitored!
Oh what should i do!
I'm playing roulette
with my child's life!
Ooh, wait, "hairspray" is
showing in new york isn't it?
Let's go there!
Good! You children
need to come to.
Eric needs all the support
he can get right now.
We're going
to new york?
Welcome aboard
flight 673 to new york.
We are happy to show you a
feature film during the flight.
In a moment, we will
be showing a preview.
Oh cool, we get
to watch a movie?
Awesome!
Rob schneider
was an animal!
Then he was a woman!
And now
rob schneider is...
A stapler!
And he's about to
find out
That being a stapler...
Is harder than it looks!
Rob schneider is
"the stapler" rated pg-13!
Weak.Weak.
Heh-Heh!
That was kenny
laughing, not me!
This must be
the place.
Okay, audience members, hi.
Welcome to the
taping of the show.
It's all general
seating in there,
And just remember, mr. Edward
might not hear from
The particular dead person
you want to talk to.
So just keep
an open mind.
Don't worry, eric, i'm sure
he'll be able to help you!
Ladies and gentlemen,
john edward.
Thank you... thank you...
Alright,
let's get started.
It's coming from over here...
Does the name mike
mean anything to anybody?
I'm getting mike-
Definitely an m...
Maybe matt.
Mike- Matt- Mary.
Mary was
my mother!
Okay, okay,
and she died?
Yes, yes she did!
Okay and she's telling me
something about the money?
"The money is safe"
is that making sense?
Hmmm, not really.
It must be from somewhere else
in the audience then.
The money-
Uh, over here, please.
We have
a dead friend.
Quiet down, boys, it doesn't
work that way...
Uh... uh, okay i'm getting
someone now who's name is
J... t... l... m... k...
Kenny!
Kenny says hi.
Woaaaaa!
Okay, now i'm getting
that kenny died?
We told you that.
And it wasn't
a good death.
It was,
it was a sad death.
It was like, a death
that made people sad
Does that make sense?
Yyyyeah.
Oooh!
Look, mr. Edward,
can you just ask kenny
How we can
get him out please?
Doesn't work that way-
Now kenny is telling me
that you were his best friends
And he's in
a safe place.
No, no, he's trapped
in cartman's body.
Oh, there's
somebody with him.
Who is kyle?
I'm kyle!
Oh right... and did
an older woman pass.
She's asking for kyle,
maybe a grandma.
Yeah, my grandma-
She's here?
She says there's something
she asked you to do
And you're not doing it.
She wants you to
look for four white doves.
Oh my god!
Now she's sending me
a "p" word
Maybe it's a
"b" or a "h"...
My harry
died last year!
Oh it's coming
from over here!
I'm getting all kinds
of voices today, wooo!
Hey, wait
a minute, dude!
Okay, now harry,
he's telling me-
Ooh well, he's saying that
you two used to do things?
And that those
things involved, stuff?
The things
did involve stuff!
Wow-Aoao-Oao!
Aw man!
I can't believe i got
fooled by that asshole!
He seemed
better on tv?
Yeah, they must edit
the shows down on television
To only show him getting
mostly right answers!
Grandma is watching me...
always watching me...
Dude, you don't believe that guy
talked to your grandma, do you?
Aagahgh!
Agahgahgagh!
Eric?
It must be
his time!
I think it's
running out!
We've got
no choice.
The only people i know
who might be able to help eric
Are my parents.
We'll have to take the
next flight to scotland!
Okay, children, this is your
flight back to colorado.
Your parents are meeting you
at the airport in denver.
We don't get
to go to scotland?
It's too far, and your
parents want you back home.
Oh well, good luck getting
kenny out of you, fatso.
Thanks, asshole.
Come on, we gotta
catch our plane!
You children get right on
that plane now!
This is a final boarding
announcement
For flight 342 to denver.
That's us, come on.
Four white birds!
Huh?
There's four
white birds!
This is what
grandma wants!
She wants me
to attend jewleeard!
Dude, you were going to see
four white birds eventually!
So is it coincidence that
grandma did talk to me
About me going to
jewleeard someday?
Yes, now come on,
our plane's gonna leave.
I'm not going back.
What?!
I have to join jewleeard
and make grandma proud!
Tell my parents
i'll call them.
Kyle!
No, kyle!
Aw crap!
Hey, uh, i need to
talk to mr. Edward, please.
He doesn't do
private readings.
I'm not here
for a reading
I just need to ask him
something real quick.
Alright,
come on in.
Just wait right here,
i'll go fetch him.
Jesus christ...
Here he is!
Ladies and gentlemen,
john edward.
Thank you, thank you.
Hey, i need to ask you
a big favor.
You did a reading
of my best friend
And uh, well you kinda
messed him up.
Ohhh...
"The john edward show
is not liable for
Opinions and materials given for
entertainment purposes only."
Look, my friend kyle won't
fly back home to colorado.
All i need you to do is
just talk to him and tell him
Y'know, that the whole talking
to dead people isn't for real.
Maybe it is
for real.
Right,
but it's not.
It's a trick you do
and i need you
To just let my friend
kyle know that
So he can go on
with his life.
Look, people have the right
to be skeptical.
I really hear
voices in my head.
Yes, we all hear
voices in our heads.
It's called intuition.
Get over yourself and tell my
friend it's just for fun.
Look, what i do
doesn't hurt anybody.
I give people closure and
help them cope with life.
No, you give them
false hope
And a belief in something
that isn't real.
But i'm a psychic.
No dude,
you're a douche.
I'm not a douche!
What if i really believe
dead people talk to me?
Then you're
a stupid douche.
I think i've had enough
of your bullying me!
Get out of my house
or i'll run upstairs
Lock myself in my panic room
and call the police.
I'm nine years old!
I'm not talking to your friend
and i'm not a douche!
Get outta my house
or i'm calling the police!
You are so a douche!
I'm nominating you for biggest
douche in the universe award,
Ya douche!
Son of a bitch!
Kenny!
Shut up, kenny!
You shut up, fat ass!
Hang in there, sweetie,
we'll be there soon.
Welcome aboard scotland air.
Our trip to edinburgh should
take about twelve hours.
Twelve hours?
Jesus christ!
In the meantime, we'd like to
show you a complimentary film.
Oh good.
Rob schneider is a
wall street executive.
With everything
going for him!
Only problem is
He's about to become...
A carrot!
I'm a carrot!
It's twenty four
carrot comedy!
Rob schneider is...
"A carrot"
rated pg-13.
Oh for the
love of christ.
I wanna watch,
fat boy!
No, kenny,
it's not funny!
Kyle- Kyle!
Don't try
and stop me, stan,
This is what
my grandma wants!
Look, i went and saw
that john edward guy.
He's just a big douche.
He's not a douche!
He talked
to my grandma!
Kyle, you can't
run your life based on
What some douchie
psychic said.
They all just use a technique
called "cold reading".
They've used it for
hundreds of years
To make people
believe them.
Hey, woa now,
john edward is for real!
No, he's not.
Yeah, my sister
told me
He knew our mother's name
and when she died!
John edward?
Oh yeah, i heard he walked up
to a guy on the street
And said his dead father
wanted to say happy birthday
And it was his birthday!
Yeah, kid, how do
you explain that?
Alright, look
i'll show you.
I just need a volunteer,
how about you?
Ohhh, me!
Okay, i'm going to
pretend that a dead person
Is talking to me
about you, okay?
Okay...
Okay, watch, kyle.
It's an older man-
Someone very close to you.
My father?
Does this month, november,
hold a special significance?
My birthday
is in november!
Right, because he's saying
"tell her happy birthday".
Oh my god!
See kyle, i just started with
something really vague.
I chose "older man"
because i'm betting
That based on this woman's age
her father is most likely dead.
But if her
father wasn't dead
I could still say it was
some other older man.
But how'd you know her
birthday was in november?
I didn't, i asked her if
november meant anything.
Her father could have
died in november
Or thanksgiving could've
been really special for them
But i go with the birthday
and validate now as if i knew
By saying, "he wishes you
a happy birthday".
What else does he say?
Okay, i'll just use
an old standard...
He's saying, "the money-
Stop worrying about the money".
Oh my god...
My sister and i have been
fighting over his inheritance!
That's amazing!
No, it isn't.
When a father dies
inheritance is usually an issue.
And money is something
everyone worries about.
That sounds a little
too coincidental.
Yes, there's only
one explanation.
This kid can communicate
with the dead!
Wow!Wow!
Woaaa!
Do me next, i want to
talk to my mother!
Can you try to reach
my grandfather?
You have to tell me
If my sister is
in a good place!
Me next!
I'll pay you!
Kid, how would you
like your own
"Talking to the dead" show?
Hi, pop!
Junior! Aw son, it's
good to see you, na!
These are my friends,
the cartmans.
Well come in
out of the cold, na!
There's heavy fog on
the moors tonight.
Look what the
cat dragged in, nelle!
Oh my baby,
come home!
Hi, momma!
Lord, i thought you
wasn't coming til 9:00!
Mom, this is
my friend ms. Cartman.
Please,
call me liane!
So nice to
have you here, liane.
And is this the children
you told us about?
Yeah, pop,
this is eric.
Let's see hya...
Mm-Hmm...
Yup, there is definitely more
than one children in there!
Oh dear.
Nelle, you best
have at it, na.
Oh lord, and i just put the
roast in the oven, too.
Ain't gonna have no time
now to baste it...
Don't nobody blame me.
Woman can't baste the roast and do
everything else at the same time.
I ain't saying the roast is
going to be terrible,
Maybe just a little dry
But i suppose we can make
some extra gravy
To take the dryness
out later.
Alright, children,
stand up on this chair, na.
Right na?
Yes, right na.
Watch it, lady!
Just stay still, eric,
mom knows what she's doing!
At a very young age
One young boy learned
he had a special gift
This is
"the other side"
Okay...
listen to me.
Listen very carefully.
This-Is-A-Trick
that i am doing, okay?
Watch- All i'm gonna do
is say a name
That i'm gonna
pick at random, okay?
"They want me to acknowledge
pete or peter... "
Yes!
Yes my peter!
Ooohh!
No, stop clapping!
All i did was
pick a random name
And wait for somebody in the
audience to give a response.
Now that i see that there
is a lone woman, crying
My instinct tells me
peter was her husband.
So i say,
"peter was your husband?"
Yes! Yes,
my husband, peter!
Ohhh!Wow!
Ooh!
Stop it!
I didn't do anything!
You knew
peter was dead!
I didn't start
by saying "peter is dead"
I started by saying,
"They want me to
acknowledge peter".
That could have meant
peter was in the audience
Or that peter was somebody's
friend or that peter had died.
I couldn't
be wrong, see?!
Now, i can look at this woman
and see that she's fairly young
So odds are, her husband was
fairly young when he died.
So i can say something like,
"I'm getting that peter's
death was very untimely."
Yes, it was!
Ohhh!Wow!
Ooh!
Amazing!
Ask peter if he knows
my little billy!
Okay...
let's back up.
Not literally!
In the name of
all that is holy
We demand this spirit
be set free!
Agh... agh...
There we go!
We're gettin'
something, na!
Come out, spirit soul!
Come on out, na!
It's safe!
Ughhhhhh!
Here it comes!
The spirit is
coming out, na!
Ooh, that's
the potatoes.
Well, hold on the potatoes
two seconds woman!
The soul's
coming out, na!
Yaghagh!
Aaghaghag!
It's almost out!
Alright, son, now
bring me the victim child!
The victim child?
Yeah, you know!
The child that we sacrifice,
So we could put kenny's soul
into its body!
Oh lord they didn't
bring a victim child.
Where were we going to find
a child to sacrifice?
We weren't going to ask you
where you got it from.
Blabblefalg!
Aw, damage!
The spirit's out and
it don't have nowhere to go!
Ooh thomas, don't let it
get on the curtains.
Rob schneider derp da derp-
Derp dee derp
de derpy derp!
Until one day
Derp da derp
da derp derp!
Derp dee derp-
Da teetley tum!
Rob schneider is
Da derp dee derp da teetley
derpee derpee dumb
Rated pg-13!
Here, look, kyle.
I found tons of testimonials
on the internet
Stating that john edward
has the entire studio wired
To hear what people are
talking about before the show
And he pays actors to be
plants in the audience!
You're just jealous he's a
better psychic than you.
Fine, i give up!
You wanna stay in new york,
then go ahead!
So, you think you can talk to
dead people better than me?
No, i don't think
either one of us can.
They told me your show is
getting better ratings than mine!
That you're saying
i'm a fraud on your show!
You better not
ever call me a liar
Or a fake or a douche again or
else i'll sue you for slander!
I am saying this
to you, john edward.
You are a liar,
you are a fake
And you are the
biggest douche ever.
Everything i tell people is
positive and gives them hope!
How does that
make me a douche?
Because the big questions
in life are tough.
"Why are we here?" "Where are
from?" "Where are we going?"
But if people believe in
asshole douchie liars like you
We're never going to find the
real answers to those questions.
You aren't just lying,
You're slowing down
the progress of all mankind.
You douche.
I'm not a douche!
And i challenge you
to a psychic showdown!
I'll prove to the world that
i'm psychic and you're not!
Fine, douche!
I'm not
a douche!
Well come on,
the soul is in here,
It's panicking, na!
It's going
to the light!
Unfortunately it's
the living room light!
I'll open a window, you
try to chase it out, thomas.
Go on, na, soul, na!
Here spirit,
come out the window
And i'll give you
tree-Fiddy!
Now don't go offering the soul
no tree-Fiddy, woman!
I just trying
to persuade it.
Well, i know but
you could at least
Start at a buck o' five
or something!
Oh christmas,
there it go again!
It's headin'
for the kitchen!
Oh thomas,
the pot roast!
Don't let it
get in the roast!
Oh well...
I guess the child's
a pot roast now.
What do we do
with it now?
I'll wrap it up
with plastic wrap
So you can take it
home with you.
Should last a few months
in the freezer...
Hey, i feel
a lot better.
Eric, you're okay!
Oh baby,
your time is back!
This child...
is clean.
Ladies and gentlemen
it's "psychic showdown".
Here are john edward
and stan marsh.
Thank you!
Alright, asshole, i know you're
here to try and throw me off
So go ahead
give me your best shot!
No, i don't want to
talk to you,
I want to talk
to the audience.
What- Why?
You see, i learned
something today.
At first i thought
you were all just stupid
Listening to this
douche's advice.
But now i understand
that you're all here
Because you're scared.
You're scared of death and he
offers you understanding.
You all want to believe in it
so much, i know you do.
You find comfort in the thought
that your loved ones
Are floating around trying
to talk to you.
But think about it...
Is that really
what you want?
To just be floating around
after you die
Having to talk
to this asshole?
We need to recognize this stuff
for what it is- Magic tricks.
Because whatever is really
going on in life and in death
Is much more amazing
than this douche.
You're right, stan.
My grandma isn't
floating around
Judging me and
watching what i do.
She's dead.
Dead and gone forever!
Yeah!
But i do have a special power
i know i do!
There's nothing special
about you, dude.
Get over yourself.
Goddammit,
i'm special!
What the-
Agh!
Greetings from
the janax galaxy.
We seek the great
john edward!
Why that's...
that's me!
Sir, it is an honor
to meet you.
Well, thank you
very much!
No, it can't be.
I am quagmar and this is the
intergalactic bdiu committee.
Mr. Edward, it is my honor
to inform you
That you have been nominated for
biggest douche in the universe!
What?
You are the first nominee
from the milky way galaxy!
Congratulations!
Oh dude!
If you'll step into
our blavlefreed
We'll give you a first-Class
ride to the awards show!
No, wait,
i'm not a douche!
I make people feel
good about themselves!
I give people resolution!
Now do you people
believe me?
I don't know...
How'd edward know
my father died in march?
Goddammit that was
a long flight!
I thought'd we never get out of
stinky-Ass smelly scotland!
Oh it's so good
to have you
Acting like yourself
again, sweetie!
Well come on, we better get
kenny back to his parents.
Wait a minute-
Who's got
the pot roast?
I thought
you got it!
It's still at
baggage claim!
Aw dammit!
Come on, we
gotta find him!
Kenny!
Rob schneider is a somewhat
popular comedic actor
Who seemed
to have it all...
Until one day
he came across a pot roast!
And his life
changed forever!
Now, he's sharing his body
with an eight-Year-Old boy!
And he's about to find out
That being eight...
Ain't so great.
Rob schneider is
kenny!
Rated pg-13.
Live from space station zaed
in the valxen galaxy
It's the biggest douche
in the universe awards!
This year's nominees are:
Graglar
the destructor
Andromeda galaxy
planet j-Eleven.
Dormanta unit five,
jalax galaxy- Planet heelm.
Durrrrrrr!
John edward, milky way galaxy,
planet earth.
I'm not a douche!
And finally,
ursala, the giant douche
From the horsehead nebula -
Station j-12.
And the winner for biggest
douche in the universe is...
It's john edward, milky
way galaxy, planet earth!
Aw, now come on now!
* here he is
* the biggest douche
of the universe *
* in all of the galaxies
* there's no bigger douche
than you *
* you've reached the top
the pinnacle of douchedom *
* good going, douche
* your dreams
have come true *
Derp da derp
da derp derp!
Derp dee derp
da teetley tum!
www.tvsubtitles.net