* i'm going down
to south park *
* gonna have
myself a time *
* friendly faces
everywhere *
* humble folks
without temptation *
* going down
to south park *
* gonna leave my
woes behind *
* ample parking
day or night *
* people spouting
"howdy neighbor" *
* headin' on up
to south park *
* gonna see
if i can't unwind *
* tim-Tmah tim-Mah,
tim-Mah tim-Mah timmy tim-Mah *
* so come on down
to south park *
* and meet some
friends of mine *
Alright, i'm done.
You're done?
Yes, i've tallied up all the
times you've been naughty
And deducted the times
you've been nice.
Yeah, so,
how's it look?
It doesn't look good, eric,
it doesn't look good.
But i'll still be getting
presents this year, right?
Actually it looks like
this year you're gonna
Owe santa 306 presents.
What?!
4,312 instances
of being naughty against
Three deductions
of being nice.
It's bad.
Three?
You didn't deduct
all my nice invoices.
Look, what about
this one?
Yes, well, i didn't think
"Hitting clyde in the balls
with slingshot"
Really counted as nice.
It was nice for token, he
laughed for like 20 minutes.
You can't deduct things
like that, eric,
Santa will know and
he'll come after you.
God dammit, i have to get
that haibo robot doll,
You son of a bitch!
Hey, i'm just your
naughty or nice accountant,
Don't blame me
for the numbers!
Haven't you seen
the haibo doll?
It's like a pet,
a robot pet.
You have to feed it and pet it
or else it dies,
And it's the coolest
thing ever!
Santa has to
bring me one!
Well, look, aren't there
any other nice things
You've done recently
we can write off here?
Oh! I brushed
my teeth last night.
Brushing your teeth isn't
naughty or nice, eric.
It just falls more into
the category of
"Brushing your teeth".
Well, there's still time
before christmas.
Can't i still
make up for it?
If you cured cancer
and aids next week,
You would still owe
two presents.
Jesus christ!
I'm afraid you're gonna
have to find a way to do
The nicest, greatest thing
anyone has ever done.
Ever.
Good evening, everyone.
In a moment we'll be lighting
the south park christmas tree
To kick off
the holidays!
Hooray!
Christmas tree!
Hi, guys!
A very merry christmas
to you!
God bless us,
every one!
What are you doing,
cartman?
I'm just letting you guys know
how special you are to me.
But now before
we light the tree
I think we should all
reflect for a moment
On those who are
less fortunate than us.
Right now in iraq
there are children who fear us
And what we might do
to their country.
The threat of war
touches us all-
But over in iraq,
there is no christmas.
They have nothing.
I hate when the mayor
uses christmas
For her own political
agenda-
Light the damn tree!
Yeah!
Christmas tree!
Oh my god-
That's it.
What's it?
Don't you see?
This time of year,
we should be bringing christmas
To the less fortunates!
Follow me!
You guys,
come on, right now!
Alright, here to light
the christmas tree
Is a very special
young man
Who shows us all the true
meaning of christmas-
Jimmy!
Wow, what a
terrific audience.
Thank you for giving me
this great honor, mayor.
Before i l-L-Light
the tree
I was wondering if i could
sing my favorite
C- Christmas song
real quick?
Aww!Aww!
Well, we'd love a christmas
song, wouldn't we, folks?
Christmas songs!
Alright, here it goes.
* on the first day
of c-C... *
* christmas my t-T...
true-True love *
* g-G-Gave
g- G-Gave *
* gave to...
m- M-M... *
* me
* a par...
a par... *
Oh, no.
And here's some old toys
that i don't need anymore!
And here, here are some
christmas cookies!
And some holly
and mistletoe!
Oh, this will be
the happiest christmas
The middle east
has ever seen!
Guys, get those lights down
from the door.
We'll give them to
the needy iraqis too!
Cartman, why are you
doing this?
They don't have
christmas there, guys,
We have to
give it to them.
That's a retarded idea
that won't work-
Why are you
really doing this?
Hoooowdy ho!
Mr. Hankey!
Oh, i hate that stupid
christmas poo.
Hello, mr. Hankey!
A merry christmas
to you!
Gee whiz, things sure look
christmassy out here!
What are you boys doing?
Cartman is trying to
bring christmas to iraq.
The people of iraq deserve
a good christmas
Just like
everyone else.
Well, gosh, eric,
Looks like you really have
the christmas spirit!
I know someone who can help-
Santa claus!
Really?
Sure, we should take this stuff
to him right away!
But how are we gonna
get to the north pole?
Oh, that's no problem!
We just need a little
christmas magic!
All aboard
the poo-Choo express!
Wow!
Ooh, that smells.
Yeah.
Next stop
the north pole!
Get the rest of the
stuff, you guys!
Uh, i don't really
wanna get on that.
Me neither.
You guys, we have to
bring christmas
To those less
fortunates!
Now come on!
Let's go,
poo-Choo train!
Poo-Chooo!
* the poo-Choo train's
laying down its tracks *
* with a-
Poo-Choo!
* all the way
and back *
* poo-Choo train
is my favorite thing *
* spreading christmas joy
as we ride and sing *
Dude, what the hell has
gotten into cartman?
I don't know.
* christmas time
wouldn't be the same *
* without hugs and kisses
and a poo-Choo train *
* and a partridge
in a p-P... *
* pear t-T-Tree
* on the third day
of c-Chri... chri... *
Here we are, kids,
the north pole!
Finally!
God,
it took forever!
Wow, is that
where santa lives?
That's it-
Santa's fortress
of solitude!
Mr. Hankey!
We need to see santa
right away
On urgent
christmas business.
Sure thing!
Hey, aren't you guys the
underpants gnomes?
10 months
out of the year.
But this time of year
we help santa!
Here he is!
Ho ho ho!
Merry christmas!
Wow!Wow!Wow!
Howdy ho, santa!
Mr. Hankey,
how are you?
All ready
for christmas?
I was just starting
to look over
The new naughty and nice list
the gnomes prepared for me.
Oh, heh...
Are the tabulations
all closed off then?
Oh, no, they keep it open until
midnight of christmas eve.
Some kids actually
try to cram in
A lot of niceness
right at the end.
Ho, that's so
lame of them.
Santa, my friends are
trying to do something
Very special
this christmas.
Tell him, eric.
Well santa,
it's just that-
I was thinking about
all the people in iraq
Who are afraid that
we might bomb them.
And i just thought-
Well, maybe it wouldn't hurt
To send them a little bit of our
christmas spirit as well.
You know,
you're right.
Santa hasn't been to that part
of the world in a long time.
Perhaps santa could bring peace
to this whole situation!
That's what
i thought.
Gnomes, load up the sleigh
with toys!
Santa's going to make
a special run!
Alright!
And you boys can all watch me
from our flight control room.
Hooray!
* and a p-P-Partridge
in a p-Pear tree *
* on the f-Fourth day
of ch-Ch- *
* christmas my t-True
love ga-Gave to m-M-Meee *
This is santa's
flight control center.
From here, we can monitor
santa from satellite
As he travels the globe
delivering presents!
Wow, cool!
It looks like santa's
already made it to baghdad!
Ho ho ho!
Merry christmas everyone!
A merry christmas to all!
Derka derka derka!
Hala derka
berka derka!
Merry christmas!
I'm hit!
Sleigh is hit!
Instrument failure
at 0600 feet!
The sleigh's going down!
Sleigh is going down.
Sleigh is
going down!
Hang on, santa!
Sleigh one is going down.
It is going down.
Alert ground troops
to stand by.
We got a red sleigh down,
we got a red sleigh down.
Red sleigh one,
this is north pole.
Mr. Kringle?
Jesus christ,
they killed him!
No- Santa claus
can't be dead.
He can't.
Why would iraqis
do that? Why?
It certainly doesn't seem
very christmassy of them.
North pole,
this is santa.
Santa,
are you alright?
What is your
status?
Sleigh is down.
Reindeer... all dead.
Both santa's legs
are broken.
Santa's...
very sad.
Santa will have to-
Oh no-
They're coming for me.
Stay back,
you bastards!
Stay back!
Oh, no.
Well, what are you gnomes
sitting there for?
You have to go
rescue him!
What the hell are we
supposed to do?
We're like
nine inches tall!
Now i'm never gonna get
my haibo robot doll!
Is that what
this is all about?!
You came up with this whole idea
so you can get a stupid toy?!
It's not stupid, it's a
toy that you can starve!
If you don't feed it,
it dies!
It's so cool!
Well, good going,
asshole!
Thanks to you, there's not
gonna be any christmas,
And there's no one left
to help us!
Oh, christ.
Jesus!Jesus!Jesus!
Hey, that's right-
Jesus can save anybody!
Follow me!
You can take santa's
backup sleigh!
* on the f-F-Fifth day
of c-C-Christmas *
* my true love
gave to m-Me *
* five g-G-Golden
r- R-Rii... rings *
* ba dump dump
d- D-Dump *
* four call-
Ing birds... *
We fed jesus christ's data
into the auto pilot-
The sleigh should be able
to take you right to him!
I hope so, or else santa
clause is as good as dead.
Here it is,
red sleigh two.
Come on, gang, it's up
to us to save christmas!
Tell santa's workers
to keep making toys-
We'll have santa back
in no time!
Uh, how do we
start this thing?
You just have to call out
the reindeer's names!
Oh yeah!
On dasher, on prancer,
on comet-
No, no-
They're all dead!
You have to call out
the new ones!
On steven, on fluffy,
on horris and chantel!
On skippy and rainbow
and patches and montel!
Good luck
finding jesus!
Wow, look, you guys, we're
riding in santa's sleigh!
We should be able to find
jesus in no time!
* i'm riding in
santa's sleigh *
* so high above the trees
at christmas time *
* with candy cane wishes
and smiles- *
What are you doing?
I'm having a precious
christmas time moment, kyle,
If you don't mind.
Singing a christmas song
Isn't gonna get you
nice deductions, cartman!
Don't forget
it's because of you
That santa's sleigh
got shot down!
It isn't my fault that iraqis
are filled with hate!
All i'm saying is it's gonna
take a lot of singing
To make up for that!
* it's christmas magic time
on santa's sleigh *
* so high in the sky
* candy cane
children smiles... *
* six geese
of laying *
* f-Five
* golden
r- R-Rings *
* ba-Dump
dump d-D-Dump *
* four calling
b- Birds... *
Where are you
taking me?
Klak bakala kala!
You are all being
very naughty.
Why you come to iraq,
my main man?
To bring happiness and joy
to the children.
And this is-
This is what you think
brings happy?
This is material.
This is commercialism.
Your country
is sick... sick.
No, your country has just
lost all its christmas spirit.
What's going on here?
America wants to bomb
my house, my main man.
They want to kill
my wife and children.
We need to know-
What is their plan?
I don't know, i live in
the north pole!
What are you doing?
They say that the chinese
were the first
To experiment with electro-Shock
to the testicles.
Oh no...
not santa's balls!
What else is
america planning?!
I'm gonna
kill you!
You're not in a position to
kill anyone, my main man.
I just want you to
tell me america's plan!
Then we're in
for a long night
Because i don't know
In nome del mio, padre,
sia guarito.
Benedicali, jesus,
benedicali.
Jesus, mio bambino
non puo sentirsi.
Il vostro bambino
sara giusto.
Bene, benedicali!
Ahhhh!
Ahhh!
La morte rossa!
Hooowdy ho!
Jesus!
Stan, kyle, mr. Hankey
and eric cartman-
What are you doing here,
my children?
Jesus, santa's sleigh was
shot down over iraq!
Santa?
Is he alright?
We don't know.
They lost all contact
with him.
We have to get him
out of there.
Do you know a way?
Yes.
Yes, i think i do.
We need a little
christmas miracle.
Lock and load.
We're going in!
* on the s-S-Seventh day
of christmas *
* my tr-Tr-True love... *
You're a sick capitalist
dog, my main man.
This is baghdad?
God, what a
- Hole.
I mean- Oh wow, these poor
unfortunate people!
Red sleigh two,
two come in.
We're here!
You're coming up on the
source of the signal.
You're right on
top of him!
He must be in that
building below us.
Land it on the roof,
mr. Hankey.
Howdy ho, jesus.
Kak bala?!
Wait here,
i can handle this.
Keem kala?
Keeem kak bala!
Yea, look upon me
and know me.
Halak bala!
Kleem bala!
My children, you should
know something-
I'm packing.
Let's go!
This is such a magical
christmas adventure, you guys.
* on the e-E-Eleventh day
of c-Christmas *
* my t-True love
gave to m-M-Me *
* eleven p-P-Pipers
p- P-Piping... *
Drink it!
Drink the oil!
This is all you western
capitalists want!
Jesus christ!
Aah!
Thank, thank god
for you, jesus.
Here-
Can you walk?
Santa's legs
are broken.
They are healed.
Santa.
I just couldn't do it.
I just couldn't
let him live.
He shocked
santa's balls!
More soldiers
are coming!
Let's move- Move!
* eight maids
of m-Milking... *
Get up the stairs!
The sleigh is on the roof!
Jesus!
Behind you!
Ahhagahg!
Jesus?
Don't, don't worry, jesus,
it's nothing.
Just a scratch.
You're a...
bad liar.
Hey- But we sure gave 'em
one hell of a fight, huh?
We sure did, jesus.
Dude, this is pretty
up right here.
Santa-
I'm here, jesus.
Don't, don't ever-
Let them take away-
Our christmas spirit.
Oh my god-
Iraqis killed jesus.
You bastards.
Come on, kids!
Get to the sleigh!
Start the sleigh!
On steven, on fluffy,
on horris and chantel!
Uhh...
On skippy and rainbow
and patches and montel!
* look at me, i'm riding high
in santa's sleigh *
* it's a christmas
special time for me- *
Oh shut up, cartman!
Your sweet christmas act
isn't fooling anybody!
It's not an act,
kyle!
All i wanted was for these
people to understand
What christmas means.
You're right, kid.
What are you
doing, santa?
I came to bring
christmas to iraq,
And by god
i'm gonna do it!
Ho ho ho!
Merry christmas!
R.P.G. 4:00!
Boy, things are sure starting
to look christmassy now!
Merry christmas!
Ho ho ho!
Merry christmas to all!
And to all a good night!
Ho ho ho ho ho
* and a p-Partridge
in a p-Pear treeeee *
That's it?
That's it!
The song's over!
We can light the tree!
Oh, finally!
Go on, jimmy!
There's only five more seconds
until christmas.
Awwwww!
Christmas is
ruined again!
Ho ho ho!
Stan!
Kyle!
Mom! Dad!
We rode in santa's sleigh!
We brought christmas
to iraq!
Everyone!
Everyone, can i please
have your attention?
Christmas is a very special
time of year,
But this year it almost
didn't happen.
There's a man named jesus who
gave his life to save me.
And so, i declare that
every year on christmas day
We should remember jesus
for what he did
And thank him for it.
From now on, christmas will be
a day for remembering
A brave man
named jesus.
Now if you'll all
excuse me,
I've got a lot of work
to do.
I'll help you, santa!
Oh, and boys,
you might want to check
Under the christmas tree!
Ho ho ho!
Merry christmas!
Wow, look, you guys!
Santa got us all haibo dolls!
Aw, god dammit!
Cartman, i thought all
you wanted was a haibo doll!
Yeah, but not if
you guys have one too!
Now it's worthless
and gay!
God dammit, i'll never
try to be nice again!
Well, all in all
i have to say
This was a pretty
special christmas.
Hey guys,
what's going on?
Oh, hey, kenny.
Dude, where
have you been?
I've just been
hanging out.
Well, come on, we gotta
tell you what happened!
I'm sure glad
it's over with!
Yeah, but i feel like things
are finally back to normal.
Yeah!
* the poo-Choo train's
laying down its tracks *
* with a-
Poo-Choo!
* all the way
and back *
* poo-Choo train
is my favorite thing *
* spreading christmas joy
as we ride and sing *
www.tvsubtitles.net