* i'm going down
to south park *
* gonna have
myself a time *
* friendly faces
everywhere *
* humble folks
without temptation *
* going down
to south park *
* gonna leave my
woes behind *
* ample parking
day or night *
* people spouting
"howdy neighbor" *
* headin' on up
to south park *
* gonna see
if i can't unwind *
* tim-Tmah tim-Mah,
tim-Mah tim-Mah timmy tim-Mah *
* so come on down
to south park *
* and meet some
friends of mine *
Oh, hello there, kids!
Welcome to
lolly's candy shop!
We're the kids whose
names you called
On your commercial
last night.
We're here to do
the shopping spree.
Oh, that's great.
You bet your fat
clown ass it is!
Okay, i'll just need
your ticket stub.
Ticket stub?
You know, when you
entered the contest
You got the other half
of this ticket.
Oh,
who has the ticket stub?
It was such a
long time ago!
We don't really need
the ticket stub, do we?
Don't need
the ticket stub?
Are you high?
How else do i know
you're the winners?
Our names were called on
the commercial last night.
Sorry, boys, no ticket stub,
no candy shopping spree.
If you find it,
you can come back,
But you only have one week
to claim the prize.
That's called
a "ticking clock".
Works great
in the movies.
God damn it!
We've gotta
find that ticket!
Which one of us
took it?!
It was so long ago
i can't remember.
We've got to focus!
We've got to focus
and remember.
Alright,
there you go!
Hold on to that
ticket stub.
You'll need it to
claim your prize!
Sign up for the 5-Minute
shopping spree!
You hold onto this, cartman,
i might lose it.
No, i'll lose it
for sure.
You keep track
of it, kyle.
Okay.
No, i don't want that
much responsibility.
Here, you hold
onto it, kenny.
Okay.
Kenny!
Gaaah!
Yes?
Where's kenny?
Uh, boys...
Kenny died last december,
don't you remember?
We know he's dead!
We mean, where
is his body?
His body?
But why?
Because he has the
god damn ticket for-
Look, we just really
miss our friend and, uh,
We need to see his remains
for closure.
Yeah, closure.
What the f-K
is closure?
Oh, alright, boys,
come on in.
We haven't seen you boys
for so long.
We thought you'd
forgotten all about him.
Here he is, boys,
our dear little kenny.
You turned him
into a teapot?
No, that's an urn, boys.
Kenny's inside it.
Your friends are here
to see you, kenny.
They miss you an awful lot,
like we all do.
Thanks for
coming by, boys,
It means a lot to us.
Oh, now, honey.
Did you get it?
Hold on, i'm checking
for robot guards.
There's not gonna be any
robot guards, retard!
Just get kenny!
Alright!
We made it!
Kenny better have the ticket
stub with him in there!
Let him out,
cartman.
Kenny?
Kenny!
Is he in there?
I can't see.
What the hell is this?
Chocolate milk mix?!
I knew kenny couldn't
fit in that teapot.
It was a trick!
God dammit, this isn't even
good chocolate milk mix!
Kenny's parents must be
laughing pretty hard about now-
We were dumb enough to believe
kenny's body could be in a teapot.
Why would they play
such a cruel joke on us?
Because they're
poor, kyle!
Poor people don't have
anything better to do
Than piss other
people off.
Don't you watch
"springer"?!
We just have to face it,
we're not gonna get kenny back
And we're not gonna
have our shopping spree.
It's over!
God dammit, there
has to be a way!
Hmm...
Hmm, not bad.
Hurry up, kenny, you're
gonna be late for school!
Wagh!
I don't think that chocolate
milk mix agreed with my stomach.
Cartman, come on!
What, what?!
Jesus, you buttholes,
it's 6:00 in the morning!
Kyle figured out a way to get
our winning ticket stub
Back from kenny!
How?
A ladder to heaven.
We build it, climb up and
get our winning ticket back
From that asshole kenny.
Hey, if you boys are
building a clubhouse
You should start with
the floor.
We're not building
a clubhouse,
We're building
a ladder to heaven.
A ladder to heaven?
Why, son?
Because we wanna
see kenny again.
Oh...
oh, that's so sweet...
That's the saddest
thing i've ever heard.
Hey, randy,
can i borrow your-
What the hell
are they doing?
The boys want to see their
dead friend kenny again, jimbo,
So they're... building
a ladder to heaven.
Aw...
Kyle, i think you've bothered
the marshes enough.
No, it's alright, sheila,
the boys were just...
Building a ladder to heaven to
see their old friend kenny.
A ladder to-
Oh... oh gosh...
Oh, that's
so touching.
Tom, i'm standing in
south park, colorado,
Where last december,
8- Year-Old kenny mccormick
Died of a terminal illness.
But now, that little boy's
three closest friends
Miss their friend so much
That they are building
a ladder to heaven in order-
A ladder to heaven in order
to try to see him again.
It's so sad and yet
so beautiful, tom.
Here's what some people
had to say.
Well, our son
just said to us
That he really needed to see
his little friend kenny again
And... and that he thought
it would work if he...
Built a ladder to heaven!
They just believe
in their little hearts
That it will work-
We can't tell them it won't,
we just can't!
It shows how beautiful the
innocence of a child really is.
A ladder to heaven?
That's stupid.
These boys symbolize how
we all feel about loss.
Who are we to tell them
it's impossible?
Tom, people from all over the-
I'm sorry-
People from all over the country
are coming to see the ladder,
Feeling a connection to its
symbolism and beauty.
Even country singer
alan jackson has shown up
With a song he has written
about the ladder.
Alan jackson is of course the
man who wrote the song
"Where were you when
the world stopped turning"
About the tragedies on
september 11th.
And now he's here once again to
capitalize on people's emotions.
Let's listen in.
* where were you when they
built the ladder to heaven? *
* did it make you feel
like cryin' *
* or did you think
it was kinda gay? *
What a beautiful song.
* well i for one believe in
the ladder to heaven *
* yeah yeah yeah
* nine-Eleven
* i said 9-11
9-11, 9-11 *
* nine, nine...
* eleven *
Thank you!
I have a new c.D. Out
with all my 9-11 songs
For sale right here!
Oh good, cartman's back
from the junkyard.
I found this car seat
in mr. Garrison's car.
Mr. Garrison threw away
his car?
No.
Eh!
Whuu...
Hurry up, kenny, you're
gonna be late for school!
Kenny, do you by chance
know what happened
To my playboys?
Kenny, answer me!
Cartman?
Cartman!
Wha, what?
Dude, what the hell's
wrong with you?!
I don't know, it's like
my brain just keeps...
Jacking off.
Maybe you've got
brain cancer.
You think?
Don't get cancer on
the ladder, cartman,
You're gonna fall off
and break it!
The nation is rallying behind
three sweet boys in colorado
Who are building
a ladder to heaven
To be with
their dead friend.
It's making americans start to
believe in heaven- Again.
Well, when i see how this ladder
has brought people together,
How it has
changed america,
I mean, how can i
not believe?
Do you actually believe
in the ladder to heaven?
If heaven is
an 8-Year-Old boy
And the ladder
is my penis...
And the pearly gates
are the-
Fffssshhhhh...
Uh, meanwhile
the american economy-
Wait, wait a minute-
We are getting reports now
That japan is building
their own ladder to heaven
To compete with the u.S.'S.
Let's go live to
snn correspondent
Nobu hirasama...
This is nobunaga hiroichi
reporting rive from a tokyo,
Where japan has started building
its own ladder to heaben.
Already the japanese ladder
extend far into space,
And is growing by
1,000 miles every day.
As the endeavor continues
it is becoming clear
That japan will reach heaven
before the united states.
Pltftfff!
Uh, excuse me...
excuse me!
Uh, we ran out of stuff.
We ran out of stuff to
build the ladder with.
Oh no!
Oh, jesus, no.
* where were you *
* when they ran out of
stuff to build *
* the ladder to heaven? *
We can keep going but we need to
start tearing down houses for wood.
No!
Uh, look, i think maybe
this has gone far enough.
Yeah, it's time we told
the boys the truth,
That they aren't really
going to get to heaven.
Wait!
Look!
We've come to help you
beat those japs, boys!
There won't be anyone
stopping this great ladder
From being built today!
Alpha team, get that
support structure up!
Surveillance team, get us
photos and recon!
Yes, sir!
* where were you *
* when they saved
that ladder to heaven? *
Man, i can't believe
how much people want us
To get our
winning ticket back.
Candy shopping sprees have
that effect on people, kyle.
Do you see anything?
No.
Hello?
Kenny?
God?
Grandma?
Aw, don't tell me we haven't
even reached the cloud city yet!
No cloud city,
not even the giant.
Heaven must still be
a long way off.
Alright, look, i didn't
wanna have to say this,
But i think maybe we're
not seeing heaven
Because one of us doesn't
believe in it enough.
Huh?
Heaven could be like pixie
fairies of bubble-Yum forest-
You only see them if you
really believe in them.
What?
You know- Maybe we're
not seeing heaven
Because one of us
is a j-O-O.
What does me being a jew
have to do with anything?!
Because jews don't
believe in heaven!
Yes we do!
Just not a
christian heaven!
Right, your idea of heaven
Is getting $5 off your
matzo ball soup
At barney's beanery by lying
about a hair in it.
Aaagh!
Ah!
Hey, kenny.
We can watch it
at my house!
* in the ghetto
in the ghetto *
* he's a boy wearing orange
who's losing his pride *
* 'cause kenny and
his family all reside *
* in the ghetto
in the ghetto *
Shut up, cartman, you
blood-Belching vagina!
What did you say?!
I said, shut up,
you blood-Belching vagina!
What did you say?!
I said shut up, cartman,
you blood-Belching vagina!
Did i just call myself
a blood-Belching vagina?
Dude, what the hell
is wrong with you?!
I don't know, i just-
Keep feeling like i'm kenny,
Seeing memories
through his eyes.
You're too fat
to be kenny.
You're a...
stupid jew.
Let's just
keep building.
We only have 5 more days
until the shopping spree.
Alright, how's the
ladder going, general?
Are we beating
the japanese?
Not quite.
But we have a new problem,
mr. President.
Our recon team on the ladder
just found new evidence
Of threats from
saddam hussein.
Saddam hussein, but...
we killed him.
We secretly took him out
months ago.
Yes, sir,
and now we believe
That he is building weapons
of mass destruction.
In heaven.
Dear christ, that son of
a bitch just doesn't stop.
These surveillance photos
were taken atop the ladder
Of what appears
to be heaven.
Here we see what we believe
to be a missile silo.
And here we see what looks like
a laboratory of some sort
For making
chemical weapons.
That kind of looks
like a seagull.
Yes, it could be a laboratory
disguised as a seagull.
That tricky bastard.
Sir, you must
understand our fears.
We must take out
those facilities.
We must- Bomb heaven.
Snn question of the day:
Now that americans believe in
heaven, should we bomb it?
The polls right now show
that 51% of americans
Think saddam has to
be dealt with,
While 49% are wimpy,
tree-Hugging pussies.
War's not my voice!
This country's just run by rednecks
and bumpkins with their guns!
We have to take saddam out
to protect ourselves!
I for one believe that if saddam
hussein were an 8-Year-Old boy
And my penis were
the united states,
Then there would-
Hard nipples!
God damn it.
Ffffssshhh...
Tom, it's been five days
since three sweet boys
Set out to build
a ladder to heaven
And captured
the nation's heart.
They've made a nation believe
heaven might be up there-
And it could prove to be
a threat to our country.
President bush will seek u.N.
Approval for military action.
Boys, it's really neat
That you want to see your old
pal kenny so much, but-
But, it's time for you
to get back to school
And on with your lives.
No, we have to
see kenny!
You have to understand that
kenny's body isn't up in the clouds.
He was cremated.
Cremated?
What's that?
When you die, your body is
put into a broiling oven
And cooked until
you're nothing but ashes.
What?!
For god's sake, why?!
Kyle, its just what
some people do!
Are you gonna burn me?!
Kyle, that's not the
issue right now.
Jesus christ!
A person's ashes are
put into an urn,
And that's where
kenny's body is.
You see, boys,
kenny is in here.
What the-
Wait a minute!
This is kitty litter!
Alright, alright, i drank
the chocolate milk mix
And replaced it
with kitty litter.
You what?!
Dude, don't you know
what this means?
You drank kenny!
Shut up.
You did, dude!
You drank his
whole body!
Shut up!
Oh my god, this is awful!
And disgusting!
Bad, eric, bad!
That explains it-
Why i'm having kenny's
memories all the time!
His soul is inside me!
Well, so much for
our winning ticket.
Cartman probably drank that
with the rest of kenny.
Yeah, good job, fat-Ass!
I can't live like this.
I- I have to
find a place
Where they remove living souls
from your body!
Looks like i've come
to the right place.
Can i help you?
Yes, hello, i have a
living thing inside of me
That i need
sucked out, please.
You'll have to make
an appointment.
The charge is $230.
$230?! I just want you
to vacuum him out of me
And not put him up
in a condominium!
It's gonna be
okay, babe.
Listen, lady, you gotta
get this crap out of me!
I don't want him
in me anymore!
Just suck him up
and throw him out!
Oh steven, i can't go
through with this.
I have to keep it!
Dammit!
Thanks a lot, kid!
Eh!
Kenny, kenny!
Kenny, lolly's candyland is
giving away a shopping spree!
We're all gonna pitch in
on an entry!
Alright, there you go.
Hold on to that
ticket stub.
Hold onto this, cartman,
i might lose it.
No, i'll lose it
for sure.
You keep track
of it, kyle.
Okay.
No, i don't want that
much responsibility.
Here, you hold
onto it, kenny.
Okay.
You better not lose
that ticket, kenny,
Else i will kick you
in the nuts!
The nuts, the nuts...
The ticket!
Kenny didn't have it on him
when he died,
He put it away
somewhere!
Don't you see?
I can still have my
candy shopping spree!
Oh my god,
you guys!
You guys!
Ladies and gentlemen
of the u.N.
We have evidence that
saddam hussein is up there
Building weapons
of mass destruction.
We have tried to communicate
with saddam, through a psychic,
To ask him to let us see
his warehouses in heaven,
But he has not
responded.
Of course he has not responded
because he's dead!
Right, dead
and in heaven.
This is
preposterous!
Even if there
was a heaven,
What makes you think
saddam hussein's soul
Would be sent there?
Our intelligence
tells us
That when saddam was
originally killed
His soul actually
went to hell.
But while in hell he began
a homosexual relationship
With satan,
the prince of darkness.
Satan, however, decided he didn't
wanna be with hussein anymore
And broke up with him
around august.
When saddam became jealous and tried
to kill satan's new lover, chris,
Satan had saddam sent to heaven
to live with the mormons
As punishment.
Questions?
Yes?
Are you high or just
incredibly stupid?
I assure you-
I am not high.
You guys, you guys!
I saw the ticket!
What do you mean,
fat-Ass?
I had another vision,
you buttholes!
Kenny didn't keep
the ticket with him.
He put it away
somewhere.
Where?!
I don't know!
I got conked in the head down
at the abortion clinic
And i clearly saw kenny
putting the ticket
In a little a red box.
I just have to wait for
another vision to come.
I could clearly see through
kenny's- Ugh!
You see anything?
Yes, kyle...
I see a dead jew!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Maybe kyle's right-
We gotta spark
the vision somehow.
Not by giving me
brain damage!
Do you want a candy
shopping spree or not?
Alright, go ahead.
Ah!
No.
Randy, gerald, we were
wrong about heaven.
The japanese just reached it
with their ladder.
What?
See for yourself.
This is nobunaga hiroichi
reporting rive from heaben.
The great nation of japan
reached heaben today
About 8:00
pacific standard time.
Ohhh!
Therefore, heaben
is now declared
An official
part of japan.
Because we got here first.
And now for the
weather in heaben
Let's go to
natsuko sen.
Partly cloudy.
That's the news
from heaben.
Oh god, and we told our boys
they'd never reach heaven.
Kids!
Good, as soon as the boys
finish their ladder
We'll be ready to
take saddam out.
Do you really think this is
a good idea, randy?
If saddam is building weapons,
we have to stop him.
With our weapons.
Excuse me, everyone!
We're not working on
the ladder anymore.
Thank you, we're done.
Ohh...
Not working on
the ladder?
But the japanese
won't let us use theirs.
Kenny didn't have
the ticket stub,
It was in his room!
So we got all our candy
and you can all go home!
Wait, are you saying
That you boys only wanted
to build a ladder to heaven
So you could
get some candy?
I've never heard the words
"only" and "candy"
In the same
sentence before.
But what about
your lost friend?
What about your
fragile innocence
In believing we could
all get to heaven?
Yeah, well, people
make us kids believe
That heaven is this white place
with fluffy clouds and angels.
Yeah, but now we think maybe
heaven isn't a place you can get to.
Maybe heaven is
just an idea.
A frame of mind,
or something gay like that.
Maybe heaven...
is this moment right now.
So, you're saying we should
bomb this moment right now?
Right, johnson!
Sir!
No, no!
We shouldn't bomb anybody.
These boys are right.
The only heaven we can hope for
is one here on earth, now.
We should stop waiting
to get into heaven
And start trying
to create it.
Aww...
Oh, that's
so beautiful.
And i was dumb enough
to believe
Saddam could actually be
up there building bombs.
* where were you *
* when they decided heaven
was a more intangible idea *
* and couldn't, couldn't
really get there *
You little bastards
ruined my latest song!
Well, i'm sure glad
this is all over with.
Let's go count our candy.
Yeah, but what
about kenny?
His soul is still
in cartman's body.
No, no, i just drank
his memories.
I'm not sharing my body
with that poor piece of crap.
Stop calling me poor,
you fat dick!
Oh, jesus christ.
Whoa, kenny,
you in there?
Stop it!
Where am i, you guys?
Oh god!
Dude,
come back here!
Stop him, kenny!
Keep those nitrogen capsules
over there by the warheads.
Right, chop chop!
Come on!
Saddam, i've been
hearing rumors
That you're
secretly building
Weapons of mass
destruction up here.
Weapons of
mass destruction!
No, this is a chocolate chip
factory, see?
It looks like
a chemical weapons plant.
Look, god,
If i was gonna secretly build
a chemical weapons plant
I wouldn't make it look like a
chemical weapons plant, would i?
I'd make it look like
A chocolate chip factory
or something.
Alright, just checking.
Stupid asshole.
www.tvsubtitles.net