* i'm going down
to south park *
* gonna have
myself a time *
* friendly faces
everywhere *
* humble folks
without temptation *
* going down
to south park *
* gonna leave my
woes behind *
* ample parking
day or night *
* people spouting
"howdy neighbor" *
* headin' on up
to south park *
* gonna see
if i can't unwind *
* tim-Tmah tim-Mah,
tim-Mah tim-Mah timmy tim-Mah *
* so come on down
to south park *
* and meet some
friends of mine *
Okay, children, step off
the bus and form a group
Next to the
nice redneck.
I mean, rancher.
Hello, boys and girls,
my name is rancher bob.
Let's all say hello
to rancher bob.
Hi, rancher bob.
I'm pleased to show you all
the wonderful world of beef.
Follow me.
City kids get to go to
museums for field trips.
We get cow farms.
Now, out here you can
see our cattle.
This is where the magic begins
as the cows eat, sleep
And prepare for
certain death.
They look
so delicious.
And here we have
the slaughterhouse.
This is where we turn the cows
into steaks and burgers!
Ewww!
Aw, dude!
Anybody want
a free sample?
Me me me me!
And in here, boys and girls,
we have our veal ranch.
You see, with veal,
The whole key is keeping
the cows chained
So they can't walk around
or get any exercise.
That way, their muscle
tissue stays soft,
And makes for
tender veal.
Wait a minute,
veal is...
Little baby cows?
Yepper!
Then why the hell do
they call it "veal"?
Well, if we called it
"little baby cow"
People might not
eat it.
Yeah!
I wouldn't have!
Me neither.
Oh man,
look at that one!
He looks delicious!
What?
Mmm, succulent
and juicy...
Can we have a free
sample of these too?
Well, no, but all these
veals are going to
The slaughterhouse
tomorrow morning.
They'll be steaks
by the afternoon,
And then you can buy them
at your grocery store.
All right!
Tomorrow morning?
Dude, we gotta
help them.
Yeah.
Psst-
Cartman.
No, uncle jessie, no!
Cartman, wake up!
What?
What the hell are
you guys doing?
Come on,
we gotta go!
Where we going?
We're gonna go save the
little baby cows, fat-Ass.
What, why?
They're gonna get
slaughtered, butthole!
So?
So we can't let 'em die,
douche bag.
You're our friend,
now come help us.
Well, let's see,
in the last 3.2 seconds
You've called me fat-Ass,
butthole, and douche bag.
I really don't feel much
like your guys' friend.
We're sorry,
you are our friend.
We need you to help us because
friends stick together.
Wait, i thought you said we
needed him because he has
Impossible
breaking and entering playset"?
Dammit, butters,
will you shut up?
Oh ho!
So you need me and my
impossible
Breaking and
entering playset.
Yes, we do.
We're those little
baby cows' only hope.
Will you help us?
Yes, yes, i will.
If kyle will kiss
my black ass.
What?
Just give it a little kiss
and i'll help.
Screw you, cartman!
Okay, but if you
want my help
You have to give it
just a little kiss.
Kiss it.
Go on, dude,
it's the only way.
No!
Kiss it.
Come on, kiss it!
Just do it really fast
and we can go.
Have butters kiss it!
No, it has to
be kyle.
Ohhh!
Oh man, that was
so awesome!
Sick, i felt it
on my face!
Okay, very funny, cartman,
now come on.
Hey, i'm not
going with you.
Yaaa!
I don't know
about this, fellas,
It says right on the
impossible
Breaking and entering
playset:
"Not for actual
breaking and entering.
Breaking and entering
is a crime."
Yeah, well, killing little
helpless baby cows
Should be a crime too.
How does this thing
work, cartman?
Jesus, don't you guys
have any toys?
First you put on
the black ski mask.
Then use the torch to
cut a hole in the roof.
Okay, that's far enough,
i'm going to go delta.
You have to talk louder,
I forgot the
double-A batteries
For the super talk
playaction headset.
I said that's
far enough!
Don't be scared,
little baby cow,
We're here to
set you loose.
There you go,
you're free!
Run away!
Go, they're gonna
murder you!
Stan, could you
hurry it up?
I'm freezing
my ass off.
You need to freeze
some of your ass off.
Oh, at least i have
an ass, jew!
What?
Come on, you stupid
baby cows!
You have to get
out of here!
What's the matter?
They aren't leaving!
See? Maybe they want to become
sweet, juicy veal steaks.
Hey, they've never been
allowed to walk before.
They just don't know how!
Oh yeah, they're
too weak to move.
We've got to get them
out of here.
We'll just keep them
at butters' house
Until they can get
their strength back.
No, no, no, no, no!
I can't bring calves
into my house,
I'll get grounded.
Okay, fine, butters,
I guess you're not
a team player.
We'll bring them
to my house.
Dude, how are we gonna move
23 calves to your house?
I don't know.
I've got it!
We could kill butters,
And then float the calves
on a river of blood.
Don't be stupid,
cartman!
Butters doesn't have
that much blood in him.
Yeah, i do, too!
We're just gonna have to
carry them one by one.
Come on you, guys!
Ehh!
Check it out, you guys,
i'm calf curling.
Man, these calves
smell like crap.
I don't see how you're
gonna hide them
From your mom
much longer.
We won't have to.
Butters said he had
something at his house
That makes baby cows
strong again.
He's bringing it over.
Butters had that
at his house?
Hey, fellas!
Butters,
did you bring it?
I sure did!
We'll have those poor baby
cows in shape in no time!
All right!
"Suzanne sommers
calf exerciser."
What?
"Makes your calves stronger
in just two days."
Oh, goddammit!
That's your plan?
You think
it's a gimmick?
Suzanne promises right on
the box that it works.
Hello, mrs. Marsh!
Officer barbrady,
what can i do for you?
Well, we've got
a little problem.
Jed here caught your
boy and his friends
Trespassing on his ranch.
They stole some
of his property.
Stole?
Are you sure?
I followed
a calf curling trail
Right to your
house, ma'am.
Ooh, stan's
in trouble!
Let me kick
his ass, mom!
Now, now,
my son is not a thief.
I'm sure this is just some
kind of misunderstanding.
Stanly, did you see-
Oh, crap!
Stanly, what are you doing
with those calves?
That asshole was
gonna kill them
And feed them
to people!
Stanly, they
belong to him.
They don't belong
to anybody!
Please, mom, we don't want
these cows to die!
Let me hit him, mom!
Stanly, this isn't up
for discussion.
The rancher is going to
take his cows back
And you don't
have a choice.
Stanly!
Stanly, you open
this door right now
Or you're gonna
get it!
No!
Stan, you're behaving
like a kid.
You're the ones who
made me eat veal
Without telling me
what it was!
You're the ones who
knew we were making
Little baby
animals suffer!
Open this door, now!
Kiss my ass!
Oh, jeez, he said "ass"
to his parents.
You're getting in
pretty deep, dude.
I apologize for this,
mr. Rancher person.
Well, why don't you
just tell them
That the cows
will be safe?
And when they come out
i can take them back.
I can't lie
to my son, okay?
If i betrayed him
like that,
I'd pay for it
the rest of my life.
Well, that's just
too bad!
Look, that's $800's
worth of veal up there
And i have to
ship out friday!
What are you going to do,
officer barbrady?
Me? How'd i get
into this mess?
So what happens now?
I'm gonna lock myself
in here with these cows
Until we have a guarantee of
their safety, in writing.
We're with you, dude.
Yeah!
Don't be so sure.
Because i'm gonna
tell you-
This is gonna get ugly,
real ugly.
When all is said and done
you could all be looking at
Being grounded for three,
perhaps even four weeks.
So if any of you guys want out,
just say the word now.
I want out.
Shut up, cartman.
We're with you, stan.
Yeah, we can't let those
little baby cows down.
They've got no one else
to turn to.
Then it's settled.
One for all and
all for one, except cartman!
Yeah!Yeah!
Yeah!
Wait, what?
And so that's
the situation.
Our boys have locked
themselves in stan's room
Until we can promise them
the calves will live free,
In writing.
Well, this is
ridiculous.
I don't know how you
raise your kids,
But my son does not play
negotiator with me!
Well, excuse me, sheila,
but it wasn't that simple.
Ha! Give me
15 seconds with kyle,
And i'll have
that door open.
Kyle, this is
your mother!
You will open this door
right now!
No i won't.
Yes, i see what
you mean, sheila,
That was very
impressive.
Kyle, if you don't do
what you're told,
I'm going to
be very angry!
Well, you made me
eat veal
And didn't tell me
what it was!
So go ahead and be angry,
you baby-Cow-Killing bitch!
Very persuasive.
Ahhh!
Open this door!
Ho, ho-
Let me try.
Butters?
Butters, this is
your father.
Oh, sweet jesus!
What do i do?
Be strong, butters, you knew
it would come to this.
Butters, answer me!
But dad's angry
at me.
Don't panic, i'll
tell you what to say.
Butters, right now!
Dad, uh, why don't you
suck my fat one.
What?!
Oh, sweet jesus.
What's gotten
into them?
All right, stanly, this
has gone on long enough.
Your little game
is over!
This isn't a game, mom.
We're not coming out until we
know the calves will be safe.
Well, that's fine, you boys
can just stay in there
And starve to death.
Us parents are going to
go to pizza shack
And eat pepperoni pizzas
and ice cream.
Oh, god dammit,
you guys.
Cartman, stay away
from that door!
You'll have to come out
sooner or later, boys,
The longer you wait, the more
trouble you'll be in.
Aagh!
Round one is over,
we made it.
We didn't make it, your
mom is right, douche bag,
What are we gonna do, stay
in here until we starve?
Our parents would never let us
starve, they're bluffing.
This is a battle
of wills.
If we hold out long enough
they'll give in.
But we will have to
sleep, dude.
Three of us can sleep
while one keeps watch.
We'll shift every
couple of hours.
Hey, this is gonna be just
like vietnam, huh, fellas?
Whoopie!
We'll stay in this room
with these baby cows
For as long
as it takes!
Well, we tried
everything.
We can't get through the door
without tearing apart the house.
Dear god, it's been
over 13 hours.
Ooh, but my poor
little poopsie
Must be getting
so hungry.
Maybe we should get them
a little food.
Miss cartman,
this is a battle of will.
We need our boys to know that
we're not gonna cave in, at all.
Oh, all right.
Let's all just go to bed and
let them play their little game
For as long as they can.
Good night,
fellas!
Good night.
Good night, patches.
Good night, halloway.
Good night, neptune.
Good night, davis.
Good night, bud.
Good night, red.
Good night, paulette.
Good night, chastity.
Butters, i'm going to kill you
over and over again.
Can't go on...
need food...
I didn't realize hunger
made you feel so bad.
There's only one
alternative, you guys,
We're gonna have to
eat a calf.
No, cartman,
we're not eating a calf.
All right! Then we're gonna
have to eat butters.
He might be
right, dude.
Aw, heck.
Wait, what is that?
Dude! Food!
Miss cartman,
what are you doing?
Ooh, i just can't stand
to see my baby suffer.
Oh dear god, you've
ruined everything!
All right!
See, now we can
hold out for weeks!
Look, you guys,
beef jerky!
Yeah!
And fried chicken!
Wha-?
Mmm!
Dude, what are
you guys doing?
We're eating, dude.
You're eating meat!
What the hell do you guys think
we're doing all this for?
Hey, i'm doing it to
save little baby cows.
I'm not gonna stop eating
meat all together.
Me neither.
Yeah, if you don't
eat meat at all
You become a pussy.
That's fine, you guys
can live off of flesh,
But i'm never eating
meat again.
Go ahead,
that's more for us.
You want some
beef jerky, buddy?
Yes, who's your buddy?
Who's hungry?
Who's a hungry man?
Dude,
that's messed up.
You guys,
check this out!
Tom, i'm standing in front
of the house
Where three insane
boy-Terrorists
Have barricaded themselves
inside a room
With 23 live
infant cattle.
Hey, look,
some other kids
Are doing the
same thing we are!
Several attempts to
break into the room
Have proven
unsuccessful, tom,
And the crisis
is intensifying.
Here's what some people
had to say.
We were just sleeping
When suddenly we heard
all the commotion.
I mean, to think this
could happen right here
In our own community.
We gave those kids
everything,
And they've turned into
little john walkers.
The police chief of
south park says
That there will be no
negotiations with terrorists.
Oh, no, this is big-Time
trouble now, fellas.
No, this is exactly
what we wanted.
It is?
Yes, don't you see?
This validates everything
that we're doing.
If we're making the news
Then this is obviously
important to people.
Tom, it looks like
i have an update.
Yes, it looks like
the boy-Terrorist story
Is not interesting news
to anyone.
Uh, nothing else
was going on, tom,
So this was the only story we
had to make seem important,
But people are just
simply tuning out.
So, hbc will now be
switching programming
Once again to "puppies
from around the world!"
I don't believe it.
The chinese puppy is
my favorite so far!
Butters?
Butters, you have
your arm around me!
Oh sorry, i thought
you were mr. Pickles.
* we must help the helpless *
* we must save
the unsaved... *
What the hell is that?
* for if we
fight together *
* we can make sure
the road is paved *
* for a brighter
tomorrow... *
Hippies!
What are they
doing here?
We're with you, boys!
Your message is real
and your fight is just!
Yeah!
Hooray!
Dude, those gaywads
are on our side?
Eww,
they're all dirty.
What did i
tell you, stan?
We saved some baby cows
from being eaten
And now we're no good dirty
goddamn hippies!
Tom, the calf terrorist
standoff continues
As now members
of the f.B.I. Arrive
To put an end
to the conflict.
Oh, jesus christ.
Who's in charge here?
I am- But i
don't want to be.
Where's the negotiator?
Right here- Glen dumont,
negotiator squad.
All right, see
what you can do.
Dude, are you okay?
Oh, i just feel
so run down.
I don't know what's
wrong with me,
I've got these sores.
What is that?
Dude, maybe we should
end this.
No!
Get me a hard line to
the phone in that house.
The terrorists
already said
There's no way
they're coming out.
Don't worry,
i'm a negotiator,
It's my job to talk to
freaks like this
And bring about
a peaceful resolution
Using clever psychology.
Hello?
Hello, my name is mike,
i'm a negotiator.
Is it okay
if i talk to you?
Uh, hold on.
It's some negotiator named
mike, what do i do?
Don't give him anything!
What do i say?
Ah, gimme that.
Talk to me, mike.
I'm here to make sure we can
all end this peacefully.
You want that, right?
Sure, sure.
How about we make a trade,
Just to show that we can
trust each other.
What'd you have
in mind?
Well, how about you send out
one of the calves?
Oh, mike, you're breaking
my balls here, mike.
Just one,
that's all we want.
All right,
how about this?
You guys have all the leverage
and we have nothing.
So how about we
give you one calf-
Cartman, no!
Dude!
We'll give you one calf
if you'll give us
Some guns and ammunition
of our own.
What?
I can't do that!
Oh, i'm sorry, i thought
we were talking here,
But i guess you're not
talking to me, good-Bye.
No, no, wait!
I'm sorry, i'm sorry.
You're right, what reason
do you have to trust me?
I'm just a guy from lakewood
trying to make ends meet.
Just a blue collar guy
like your dad.
Don't have a dad, mike,
that's not gonna work.
Oh, all right, some guns,
i'll see what i can do.
Okay, up a little...
Left a little...
almost there.
What is that?
We're giving the boys
some guns
In return for a calf.
What?
You're giving
my baby guns?
Hey, this is a negotiation
process, okay?
Did you people go to
negotiators' school?
No, you didn't!
Get 'im on
the line for me.
Hello?
Okay, you see that?
I keep my end of the bargain.
All right,
we'll keep ours.
We'll send out one calf.
Well, how about you
send out two calves?
Oh, jesus!
Y'know, there's just no
talking to you, is there, mike?
We had a deal.
Do you think i'm stupid?
Don't treat me like
i'm stupid here!
I'm sorry!
Dammit, i'm losing them!
Okay, i'm sorry,
just send out one calf.
Oh, no, no, no-
Now you're gonna have to
get us something else.
What'd you have in mind?
A little to the left.
Okay, that's good.
A little to the right.
You're giving them
a missile?!
Stand down, ma'am,
stand down!
This is a delicate process,
i've almost earned their trust.
Stan's getting
worse, you guys.
Mike, babe.
How we doing?
We got a real sick
kid here, mike,
Did you get the other
things for us?
I did manage
to get the f.D.A.
To officially change
the word "veal"
To "tortured baby cow".
Good, good.
But i couldn't get you
north and south dakota.
Oh, mike, breaking
my balls, mike.
Now, please, can we
get you to come out?
All right, everything
has worked out.
The boys have promised
to come out
And bring the cows out
with them.
All right!
Woo-Hoo!
I'm sorry i doubted your
abilities, mr. Negotiator.
They're
coming out now?
Yes, all we need
to do in return
Is get a cattle-Transporting
semi truck
That will take the boys
and the cattle
To denver
international airport
Where we will have a
fully-Gassed airplane
Waiting to take them
all to mexico.
What?
And they want the guy that
plays "mr. Worf" on "star trek"
To drive the truck...
in full makeup.
Jesus christ!
All right,
that does it!
You are, in fact,
the worst negotiator
I have ever seen
in action!
All right, all right,
i'll give you that.
But in return i want
three staples.
Get out of here!
We'll get them the semi,
And we'll get them the
worf guy from star trek.
If they see that,
then they'll come out
And then,
we can take them.
But isn't that
dishonest?
Maybe so, but if we don't
do something soon
There could be 50,
even 60 people
Who have to go without
veal for dinner.
Are you prepared
to let that happen?
All right,
where is mr. Dorn?
I was woken up
at three in morning,
Told i had to put on makeup
and come to this town.
What the hell
is going on?
I'm sorry, mr. Dorn,
it's f.B.I. Business.
We've got terrorists making
demands and we need your help.
This is highly unusual.
All right, boys,
we have your truck.
And we have an airplane on the
tarmac at denver international.
And worf?
My name is
michael dorn,
I play a character
called worf.
Stan, it worked!
It... did?
They got us a truck and an
airplane and mr. Worf!
The calves are gonna be okay!
Pick me up, i...
i want to see.
Step back, tell those men
to step back!
Do it!
All right!
Ah, shut up,
ya friggin' hippies!
All right, mr. Worf,
Start the engine
and put her in gear.
Oh, and you must refer
to me as "captain".
Where am i supposed
to drive to?
No, see, you must say,
"Captain, where am i
supposed to drive to?"
Captain, where am i
supposed to drive to?
You're going to back the truck
up to the door of the house
So we can safely
load in the calves.
This whole thing
is ridiculous.
"Captain, this whole
thing is ridiculous."
Captain, this whole
thing is ridiculous.
Okay, all set!
Tom, it looks as though
the terrorists
Are now loading the baby cows
into the back of a semi!
This is still very
uninteresting news, tom.
Okay, cartman!
Step on it,
mr. Worf!
All right!
We're going!
Mexico, here we come!
Wait a minute,
they're following us!
Full speed, mr. Worf!
We cannot keep going fast
on these icy roads!
"Captain, we cannot keep going
fast on these icy roads."
Captain, we cannot keep going
fast on these icy roads.
Alright, mr. Worf,
then reduce speed to 45
But maintain distance from
those police cruisers.
Stan, we're
almost there.
You've got to hold on.
All right, they're in front
of the cattle ranch.
Hit it!
Oh, it's a double-Cross!
All right, boys,
the game is over.
Get out of the truck
with your hands up.
Oh, no, no!
What are you waiting for?
Go kill them, worf!
I'm not killing
anybody!
Some goddamn
klingon you are.
We're sorry, cows.
We tried...
we tried.
All right, boys,
Just stay right there
until your parents arrive.
Can i go now?
Here you go,
mr. Rancher,
I got your cattle
back for you!
Oh... well, it
doesn't matter now.
What do you mean?
You see, in the six days
since the word "veal"
Was officially changed to
"little tortured baby cow",
The market has gone dry.
Seems when people see
"little tortured baby cow"
On their menus, they don't
feel like ordering.
Really?
Yup, damn things
ain't worth spit now.
I'll let 'em live outside
with the other cows
And live a normal life.
You hear that, stan?
It worked!
We've shut down
the veal industry!
Stan, stan?
He's very lucky you got
him here when you did.
He was in a very advanced
state of "vaginitis".
Vaginitis?
It occurs when a person
stops eating meat.
Those sores on his skin were
actually small vaginas.
If we hadn't
stopped it in time,
Stand would have
eventually just become
One great big,
giant pussy.
Whoa, dude.
We've got an i.V.
Of pure beef blood
Pumping into stan's veins,
and the sores are fading.
Thank god we
stopped it in time.
Well, i guess we learned
something today.
It's wrong to eat veal because the
animals are so horribly mistreated,
But if you don't eat meat at all
you break out in vaginas.
Hear, hear.
All right, boys,
it's time to go home.
You've got some serious
grounding time to start.
I'll say!
Aw, we're still
grounded?
But, but we learned things
and took up a cause.
Yes, kyle, but you still
defied your parents.
And you need to learn
that terrorism
Is never the answer.
That's right, let's get these
terrorists to their rooms.
But first- Maybe we can
grab some burgers.
All right!
www.tvsubtitles.net