* i'm going down
to south park *
* gonna have
myself a time *
* friendly faces
everywhere *
* humble folks
without temptation *
* going down
to south park *
* gonna leave my
woes behind *
* ample parking
day or night *
* people spouting
"howdy neighbor" *
* headin' on up
to south park *
* gonna see
if i can't unwind *
* tim-Tmah tim-Mah,
tim-Mah tim-Mah timmy tim-Mah *
* so come on down
to south park *
* and meet some
friends of mine *
Parents, it's that
time of year again
When the bishops and priests
from around the country
Are organizing the
young men's catholic retreat.
This year, we're taking the boys
on a weekend boat trip,
To discuss jesus' role as the
navigator of our lives.
That sounds
pretty fun!
A catholic boat trip?
* the catholic boat... *
* is gonna be
heading on out today *
* the catholic boat...
* time to throw
all of your cares away *
* get some hot
christian action *
* that'll take you- *
Aghhhh!
Aghhh!
Excuse me...
Look, i just don't think
it's the best idea
To let our boys go
on a cruise with the priest!
We can't
let them go, can we?
There's no way
my son's going.
What are they
talking about?
I don't know.
Maybe they want
to kill us!
With everything that's
been in the news,
I think it's best we keep our
kids far away from the priest.
Now come on,
everybody
Just because a few priests in
the country have been corrupt
It doesn't that all priests
are child molesters.
Well sure, that's
easy for you to say,
Your son's dead.
But those of us
with alive children
Need to be sure that father
maxi is on the up and up.
I've heard about other towns
bringing in counselors
That know how to
find things out from kids
Without really telling them
what's going on.
It couldn't hurt.
Shhh-Shhh,
here he comes!
Uh... goodbye,
everyone.
'Night!'Night!
'Night, father.
Alright then, it's settled.
Tomorrow we'll find
an outside counselor and...
Find out the truth.
Hi, boys, my name
is mrs. Garache
And i need to ask you
a few questions
About your priest, okay?
Okay.Okay.
Alright.
Okay... would you say that
father maxi is nice or mean?
Nice.Cool.
He's fine.
Okay, what words would you use
describe your church's priest?
Compassionate.
Okay... and did father maxi,
at any time,
Ever try to put
something in your butt?
In-In our butt?
You don't need to be ashamed
or embarrassed, just-
Did he ever try to
put anything in your butt?
Like money, what?
You mean like
a goldfish?
No, no... did he ever
try to put anything
That belonged to him
in your butt?
No.No.
No...
This is ridiculous.
Having to sit out
here waiting to find out
If our priest
molested our kids!
Yeah, what has catholicism
come to, anyway?
You know, i think we've
just had it with the church.
All the horrible things
they've done to kids.
I think i'm going to
become an atheist!
That's a good idea!
I'm going to be
an atheist too!
Let's all be atheists!
Yeah!Yeah!
Yeah!
If there was a god,
Why would he let our kids be
molested in the first place?
Yeah, let's
kill god, yeah!
Well, let's
just be atheists.
Same thing.
Alright!
Yeah!Woo-Hoo!
What would the priest...
Possibly want to
put in our butts?
Maybe- No...
Hey, dudes.
Hey.
Hey.Agh!
What are you
guys doing?
We had to go meet
with this counselor lady,
And she asked us if the priest
ever put anything in our butts.
In your butts?
Yeah, isn't that
the damnedest thing?
Why would he put
anything in your butts?
We don't know, that's what
we're trying to figure out.
Hmm...
hmm...
Hello there, children!
Chef!
What would a priest
want to stick up my butt?
Goodbye!
Ugh, nobody's
going to tell us!
This is going to
drive me insane!
Calm down, tweek, there has to
be a rational explanation.
Oh, dude, i think i might have it. What?
It makes perfect sense...
okay, run with me on this:
If you eat food, you crap out
your butt, right?
Yeah...
Alright, now keep with me here,
it gets a little complicated...
If you eat food and
crap out your butt,
Then maybe if you
stuck food in your butt
You could crap
out your mouth.
Hmm?
Cartman, that's the dumbest
thing you've ever said!
This week.
That's not dumb
think about it!
Food goes in the mouth,
comes out the butt
Food goes in the butt,
comes out the mouth.
That's not dumb,
that's genius.
It wouldn't work!
Have you ever tried it?
I don't need to,
it wouldn't work!
I'll bet you 20 bucks
it'll work!
You're on,
fat boy!
Okay, let's go, jew!
Down with god!
Stan, you're
an atheist now!
You too, tweek!
Down with god!
I'm a what?
Fathers, i want to
thank you all for coming.
No, thank you
for finally organizing
An all-Priest meeting,
father maxi.
I think
we all agree
Something has
to be done quickly.
Uh-Huh.
That's right!
I don't know how
it has been for all of you,
But attendance at my church
in fort rollins is down 63%.
I'm down almost
70 in greenleaf.
Yes, i'm afraid if things
keep going the way they are,
We could lose
our entire religion!
Yes, we've got to stop these
boys from going to the public!
They've got to know
to keep their mouths shut.
Yup!Uh-Huh!
Right!
Right, and so-
Wait a minute, what?
Yes, but we've got to
find out why these children
Are suddenly finding
it necessary to report
That they're
being molested.
Stop the problem
at its source.
Yes, but how?
Whoa, whoa-
Hold on a second.
The problem is that
children are being molested,
Not that they're
reporting it.
How do you mean?
Well, i mean, obviously
what we need to put a stop to
Is all the
sexual misconduct
That is allowed to
take place in our churches.
Not just tell the children
not to tell anybody about it.
I mean, right?
Did any of the children
you've molested come forward?
No!
That's good.
No, i mean,
i never molested
Any of the children
in my church!
It's okay, father maxi,
we're all priests here,
The doors are closed.
For the love of god!
Are you all saying
that you have engaged in
Inappropriate relations
with your altar boys?
We are here to
bring the light of god,
Not harm the innocent!
Ha, ha!Ha, ha!
Ha, ha!
I'm serious!
Father...
having sex with boys
Is part of the catholic
priest's way of life.
Yeah.Yeah.
Yeah.
Dear god, this problem
is much more severe
Than i could have
possibly imagined.
I have to go to
the vatican and get help!
Hghnn... hghh...
Well, cartman?
Hold on!
God, let a man crap!
Hgh... hgh...
What's going on?
Cartman shoved
food up his ass
And now he's trying
to crap out his mouth.
Oh.
Ugnh... hgnnnh...
Well go on, smart-Ass, and do it!
I'm doing it
a'ready!
God, give me
a minute!
You've had
five, dude!
I can't do it with
you guys watching.
Turn around.
No, because you'll
just crap out your butt
And then say it
came out your mouth!
Do you really think i'd be
that deceitful, you guys?
Oh goddammit, you guys,
i'm so seriously...
Ugh... hgngg!
Hwaaaaagh...
Get the f-K
out of here!
Yesss!
Yes, i did it!
I crapped out
my mouth!
* i crapped
out my mouth *
You owe me
20 bucks, dickface!
There you go...
uh... gratsie.
Wow...
i'm actually here!
Vatican city!
Your holiness, this is
father maxi from america,
He has brought this all
to our attention.
Your holiness.
Rhohhh...
Ado ramus te christe.
In dominus reo.
Cardinals, bishops
and priests.
An american priest
by the name of maxi
Has brought to our attention
the most troubling of news.
All over his country,
there are reports
Of children being molested
by men of the church.
If things
continue this way
We'll never be able to have
sex with young boys again!
Yeah!Uh-Huh!
That's right!
That's right-
Wait, what?!
In france as well, we are
finding it harder and harder
To make love to our boys.
In morocco they have
arrested five of my priests.
It's only a matter of time
before they get the rest of us!
Father maxi, what do
you suggest we do
To not get caught?
"Not get caught"?!
No!
I think what we should do
is not have sex with boys!
Rumble, rumble.
It is not written anywhere
In the holy document
of vatican law
That sex with boys
is wrong.
Maybe we need to change the
holy document of vatican law.
Rumble!Rumble!
Aaagh!
Speaking on behalf of
the british catholics,
It is obvious
the priest doesn't realize
That the holy document of
vatican law cannot be changed!
Yeah!True!
That's right!
Yes, and speaking on behalf of
the gelgamek catholics,
I believe we should move on to
other solutions to this problem.
Rumble!Rumble!
Yeah!
Gelgameks?!
Kyle, could you
help me out?
I need some advice...
What?
It's just that...
I can't decide what to buy
with your twenty dollars!
I was thinking of getting this
megaman racer for 19.95
Or i could get two broncos
trading packs for 10 apiece.
And then i thought-
Oh boy, now that
we're atheists
We don't have to pray
for our food!
That's right,
everyone just dig in!
So kids, anything fun happen
with your whole sunday off?
Cartman shoved
his lunch up his ass
And crapped
out his mouth.
Stanly!
What, he did!
No, it doesn't
work that way, son.
Yeah, it does.
No, it doesn't.
Yeah... it does.
Hgh... hgh...
Hughh...
Hwaaaaaa...
Honey!
Honey, come quick!
Look, people...
i'm just trying to say
That if we don't change the
holy document of vatican law
Then we might lose
everyone to atheism!
What exactly do you
suggest we change, father maxi?
Well for one...
no sex with boys.
Rumble!Rumble!
Agh!
The holy document
of vatican law states that
A priest, bishop or cardinal
cannot get married.
So where are we
to get our sex?
Well then perhaps we could
change the holy vatican law
To say that it's okay for a
priest or bishop or cardinal
To have sex...
With women.
Hawhhh!Rumble!
Women!
The gelgamek vagina
is three feet wide
And filled with
razor-Sharp teeth!
Do you really expect us
to have sex with them?!
Maybe we need to forget about
the gelgameks for a second
And focus on-
Forget about
the gelgameks!
I'm just saying that
what works on planet gelgamek
Isn't necessarily going to
work for the rest of us.
You see, that's the problem
we're having here.
But the holy document of
vatican law cannot be changed!
Why not?
Because we don't know
where it is.
You see, father, the holy
document of vatican law
Has hidden away deep in the
catacombs of st. Peters below us.
Hidden away so that it
can never be changed.
But if we locate it, we could
make changes to it?
Ha!
Good luck, father!
The document
is guarded by
Water lizards, rattlesnakes
and sand traps.
The fools who tried before to
recover it, met their death!
Well we have to try,
our religion is dying!
You guys, you guys, look!
Agh!
I went down to the bank,
and i got kyle's 20 dollar bill
Turned into 20
single dollar bills!
So?
So?!
So now i can do this...
Yesssss... yyyyesss...
kyle's money...
Mmmmm, kyle's money...
Go f-K yourself,
cartman!
Oh... feels so good
on my skin... mmmm...
Get up, fat boy, i'm
gonna kick your ass!
Geez, kyle, don't be
a sore loser.
It's over, okay?
I won, let it go.
So you crapped
out your mouth!
Good for you!
It's still stupid
and immature!
Dude, look!
Our top story tonight:
The age-Old question
has been answered.
"If i put food up my ass
will i crap out my mouth?"
All over the country people are
discovering that yes,
In fact, you will!
The surgeon general
had this to say:
...and the immediate research
shows that the act
Is not only amusing,
but in fact much healthier
For our bodies
than the old way of eating.
You see, food entering
through the anus
Has the benefit of being broken
down on its way to the stomach
Rather than afterward.
Therefore, i believe that
intero-Rectogestion
Would actually put a stop to
high cholesterol
And most kinds
of stomach cancers.
And i base that
on absolutely nothing.
The surgeon general's response
Has made americans change their
eating habits almost instantly.
"That's stupid
and immature, cartman."
It is stupid and immature!
So you got people to crap out
their mouths, what do you want?
A freaking medal?
The mayor of south park has
announced that
For first discovering this
healthy way of eating,
Young citizen eric cartman will
be given a freaking medal!
Aaaghhg!
Back now with more on
"martha stewart living".
In the past few days we've all
heard of the benefits
Of intero-Rectogestion,
and so making foods
That can easily be inserted
into the ass is essential.
Everyone knows that some foods
are simple to shove up the ass;
Puddings, soups, raisins-
This is a nice
raisin pudding right here-
But we can also still
eat our favorite foods.
What we're going to do today,
Is prepare a thanksgiving turkey
for intero-Recto.
The key to shoving
a turkey up your ass,
Is first wrapping
it in string,
Keeping the pointy wings
neatly at the side.
Mrs. Stewart,
we have some questions.
Not right now, i just want to
focus on my turkey right now.
Now we're going to
baste the turkey
With lubricating gel
rather than with juice,
This will help smooth the
insertion later on.
We still bake at 400 degrees for
twenty minutes a pound...
And when it's done we'll get
something like this.
So now we're
ready to go.
Looks delicious,
let's try it out!
Ugnnn...
Uuggghhhn...
Yeah, get it up there,
yeah, uggnnnhhh, yeah!
Agh... whew!
And that is how
you eat a turkey.
We'll be right back with more.
Prego!
Hello, my name is father maxi
from the united states.
What do you seek, father?
I'm trying to find the
holy document of vatican law
So that we can
make revisions to it.
The gospel lies somewhere
beyond this door.
But many trials
await thee inside.
Only he whose heart
truly belongs to the lord
Shall make it through.
I have to try,
our religion is in trouble
And that scroll
may be our only hope.
Then prepare yourself.
The time of trials begins...
ado ramus te christe!
I wish you luck, father.
Use all the strength, agility
and faith that you have.
Very well...
here we go.
Hmm, there's
a ladder up here...
Oh my god, a rattlesnake!
A way back up!
I made it!
Praise be to god,
he hath shown me the way.
This must be it...
The holy document
of vatican law.
Well sharon and i are having
a great time being atheists.
I for one can't believe
i used to live my life
By what a very old and very
fictional book used to say!
It's true, what do
a bunch of stories
About people in robes
slaughtering goats
Have to do with
today's world?
Atheism has definitely
made our lives better.
I made some quesadillas
if anybody wants some!
Ooh!Ooh!
Ooh!
And if anybody
needs to potty,
There's a potty basket
right here.
Oh thanks, sharon.
For martha and i
we're worried
We might have a hard time
raising our son atheist.
I mean- Oh, thank you.
I mean it could end up
being very difficult
Raising an atheist child
in such a christian society.
I feel like everywhere
my poor son goes
He's going to be
persecuted for his beliefs.
That's true.
If i'm going to
raise my son to be atheist,
I don't want him saying
"under god" every day at school.
That could really
damage him!
"Under god" should be
taken out of the- Excuse me-
Hhhhwaaaa...
"Under god" should be taken out
of the pledge of allegiance.
Yup!Yup!
I agree.
And it should be taken
off of money as well.
The religious right
in this country
Is trying to force our children
to believe what they-
Hwaaaaaagh...
And we can't let the religious
right corrupt our kids!
Yeah!Yeah!
That's right.
Cardinals, bishops
and priests!
Father maxi has returned!
And he has the holy document
of vatican law!
How did he make it
past the water lizards?
Yes, i have returned with the
holy document of vatican law,
So can we please
change it now
To say it's not okay
to have sex with boys?
Wait, wait!
The pope wants
to say something!
The pope says we shall
ask the highest source!
Ahhhh!Ahh!
Oh my!
The holy one!
Behold the great
queen spider!
Hail, queen spider.Hail, queen spider.
Queen spider?
Oh, great queen spider,
we seek your guidance.
What do you ask of me?
Great queen spider,
We wish to change
one of the vatican rules.
The vatican rules
cannot be changed.
So sayeth the spider.
Go on, priest maxi,
see if you can convince her.
All right,
that does it!
I have had enough!
You people have completely lost
touch with the outside world!
You sit in this big room with your
gelgameks and your queen spider
And none of it applies to what
being a catholic is all about!
But the holy document
of vatican law states that-
To hell with the holy document
of vatican law!
You guys, you guys!
I took kyle's 20 dollars
down to the bank again,
And i got it changed
into quarters!
So?
So now i can dump them
into this pool
And swim in them
all day long!
Yayyyy, kyle's money.
Cartman, there's something
i need to tell you.
Ooh, what's that, kyle?
You were totally,
100% right.
Huh... huh...... what?
You won the bet.
You were
totally accurate
About being able
to crap out your mouth,
And i've just
been frustrated
Because i didn't
think of it first.
I want you to
enjoy that money because
You really impressed me
with your insight,
And i'm proud to
have you as a friend.
You son-Of-A-Bitch, kyle!
I hate you!
Down with god!
Yeah!Atheists rule!
Great news, stan,
the vatican is burning down!
Score one
for us atheists!
Come on, tweek, we're
gonna go watch on tv!
Gone...
it's all gone.
Well, thanks a lot,
father maxi
You've killed
our religion.
No, i didn't!
All that's dead are
your stupid laws and rules.
You've forgotten what
being a catholic is all about:
This book...
You see, these are
just stories.
Stories that are meant to help
guide people in the right direction.
Love your neighbor,
be a good person.
That's it.
And when you start
turning the stories
Into literal translations
of hierarchies and power,
Well... well you
end up with this!
People are
losing faith because
They don't see how what you've turned
the religion into applies to them.
They've lost touch with any idea
of any kind of religion,
And when they have no mythology
to try and live their lives by
They just start spewing a bunch
of crap out of their mouths!
What was that
last bit?
Look, i'm proud
to be a catholic.
But i am a catholic
in the real world,
In today's world.
It's time for you all
to do that too.
It is time... for change.
He's right, sharon.
We don't have to believe
every word of the bible
They're just stories
to help us live by.
We shouldn't toss away
the lessons of the bible
Just because some assholes
in italy screwed it up.
Oh, randy, i don't want to
put food up my butt anymore.
Gang... i think maybe
we owe god an apology.
Does this mean we have to
go to church on sundays again?
No... it means
we get to, son.
It means we get to.
Hwaaaaa...
www.tvsubtitles.net