* i'm going down
to south park *
* gonna have
myself a time *
* friendly faces
everywhere *
* humble folks
without temptation *
* going down
to south park *
* gonna leave
my woes behind *
* ample parking
day or night *
* people spouting
"howdy neighbor" *
* headin' on up
to south park *
* gonna see
if i can't unwind *
* tim-Tmah tim-Mah,
tim-Mah tim-Mah timmy tim-Mah *
* so come on down
to south park *
* and meet some
friends of mine *
...and in other news,
Another school shooting
has taken place,
This time in idaho.
As these kinds
of shootings increase
One thing becomes clear:
Your children are not
safe at school!
Oh god!
Change it, change it!
...this was the second time
a terrorist threat
Has been made on a theme park
Leaving everyone to realize that
children are not safe outside!
Oh god, change it!
...and it seems there is
a new danger to look out for.
Children who are
taken by strangers!
The bottom line: children are
not safe in their own homes!
Aagahghgh!
Tweek!
Come to the kitchen, sweetie,
we need to see you real quick.
Oh god...
they're gonna get me.
Sit down and
have some coffee, son.
Tweek, there are starting to be
a lot of reports on the news
About children being abducted
and we thought we should talk.
I saw!
You know never to talk to
strangers, right, tweek?
You can't trust anybody.
Oh god!
Now, we don't
want to alarm you, son,
But we've installed new locks on
your bedroom windows and door.
It's important
for you to know
Never to unlock
them night for anyone
Except your mother and i.
Oh jesus!
It's just
a precaution, sweetie.
Probably nothing
will ever happen.
No! No!
They're gonna get me.
Agh, oh god...
just a dream.
Oh my god!
Aghgh!
Tweek, this is
officer daniels!
Now try and stay calm,
But we believe an
abductor is in your room!
Inside my room?
Oh god!
Give it up, buddy
we've got you surrounded!
Okay, tweek, i want you
to very calmly but quickly
Walk to your door,
and come out to us!
Oh my god!
Oh, oh jesus
see me through this.
Aaghgh!
Bang, you're dead, tweek.
What?
You failed
the test, son.
Didn't i tell you not
to open the door for anybody
Except your mother and i?
Oh god!
Oh jesus!
What if that had been
a child abductor
Pretending to be
a police officer, tweek?
He could have sprayed
your brains all over the floor
Then taken your body
off to the woods.
Uhhho!
Aghaha!
You've got to be
on your toes, tweek.
All right, now go to bed
and get some rest.
Night, pumpkin!
I hope this movie
doesn't suck ass.
It will.
One please.
Wait, that's not the usual
ticket-Taker guy!
So?
So i don't
know him!
Dude, relax.
You relax!
What if he wants
to kill me?
God, what the hell do
his parents do to him?
Excuse me, is this
the right road to breckenridge?
Aaghgh!
Please, i just need to know
if this is south park?
Get away from me!
Agh!
Could you help me
across the street?
I don't know you!
Oh hey, kid!
Oh thank god
you happened by!
My chair ran out of juice
right on these train tracks!
If you hadn't have
shown up-
Well, anyway, could you
give me a push?
Nuh-Uh!
No, you don't understand,
I'm paralyzed
from the neck down!
I push the chair with this
device in front of my mouth
But it's not working,
so, you see.
I'm not a supposed
to talk to you!
Please!
This isn't funny, kid,
you have to help me!
But it could be a trick!
Blech!
That's a pretty good trick.
Aaaaahhhh!
Relax, tweek.
I am not here
to hurt you.
I am the ghost
of human kindness.
The ghost
of human kindness?
You have never seen
the likes of me before!
What do you want?
You have lost faith
in humanity, lad.
Something i cannot
bear to see happen.
How can i help it?
It seems like everywhere i turn,
somebody is out to get me!
That is the world
that the news reports!
It is the world that adults
preoccupy themselves with!
But it is not the world
as it is!
It isn't?
Look here, tweek.
This woman is on her way
to the retirement home.
She doesn't get paid,
She volunteers her time
to talk with lonely,
Elderly people who want
nothing more than a friend.
But do you hear
about her on the news?
No!
Now gaze upon
this humble house, tweek.
Inside, there are two people
who have adopted needy children.
They were strangers
to those kids once,
Now they are loving parents.
Now look here, boy.
A car has broken down
with a flat tire
And two complete strangers
have stopped to help.
Will their kindness be reported
on the news tomorrow?
I think not!
Are you starting
to understand, boy?
I think so.
You mean that
even though all the news
Is about murderers
and abductors,
Those kind of people
only make up
A very small part
of the world.
That's right, lad.
So do you think you can learn
to trust people now?
I'll try.
Good.
Then why don't you get
into the back of my van,
And i'll drive you home.
Your van?
All right, johnston,
give it up!
Damn! Damn! Damn! Damn!
Oh, i was so close.
What the hell
is going on?
Tweek, tweek,
are you okay?
Did he hurt you, son? No!
Then we aren't
too late.
His name is
frederick johnston.
He's been abducting
children by dressing up
Like the ghost of human kindness
for over a year now.
And i would have gotten
away with it again
If it weren't for you
meddling policemen!
What's going on?
A stranger was caught
trying to abduct the tweek boy!
An abductor,
in our own town?
Oh my god, what are we
going to do?
Rabble, rabble, rabble, rabble!
People, people, calm down.
Well what are
we going to do, mayor?
We have to stop
these abductors
From being able to get
into our town!
Rabble! Rabble! Rabble!
Yes, but standing out here
yelling "rabble, rabble, rabble"
Isn't going
to help anything!
But we don't know
what else to do, mayor!
Rabble, rabble, rabble!
People, what do you
think we need to do?
Uhh...
Well, we need to find a way
to close our town off
From unwanted strangers!
Yes, we need a barrier
to protect our kids!
That's it,
a wall.
We could to build a huge city
wall all around south park
So that we have complete
control over who comes in.
That's not a bad idea,
a city wall.
But who can we get
to build it?
And so, we want you
to design and build
A great wall all
around the city.
I don't build walls!
I just own and
operate city wok!
We just think that
you're the best person
To put up a wall,
We're sure you've got it
in your blood.
Ohhh i get it!
Just because i chinese you
fink i can build a wall!
That is bullsh-T!
I'm not
a stereotype, okay?
Just because i'm chinese
doesn't mean i go around
Building walls!
I'm just a normal person
like all of you,
I eat rice and
drive really slow
Just like the rest of you,
i'm not a stereotype!
Please,
mr. Twang lu kim.
Your ancestors put up a great
wall that kept mongolians out
For thousands of years.
We know you can
do it for us.
Hey, hey!
Hey!
What the hell you doing?
Tsao nugu kwaaa!
Mongolians!
What the hell
is mongolian doing here?
You, mongolian!
Don't you
break down my wall!
Get outta here!
Mongolian!
Naini tantsu kwaaaa!
Goddamit, how come every time
us chinese put up a wall
Stupid mongolians have
to come and knock it down?
Stan, our abduction
problems are over!
We got the new child tracker!
Child tracker?
It's a little
electrical device
That can tell us where
you are anywhere on earth.
If anybody takes you,
we'll be able to locate
Your exact location
within two meters.
There, i think
that's got it.
Dude, no way.
I'm not wearing
a child tracker.
You can barely even tell
you have one on.
I'm not going
to school like this!
What will all
the other guys say?
I wouldn't
worry about that.
So weak.
So weak, dude.
Man.
Why did you have to go
and be abducted, tweek?
Now all our parents
are freaking out.
I didn't mean to!
Okay.
Finally.
Oh, no!
It's those goddamn
mongolians again!
Stop!
Stop right there,
mongolians!
God damn it stop!
Stop breaking down my city wall,
you stupid mongolians!
All right,
you sons of bitches,
What the hell?
Aw, sh-T!
Oh goddamn mongolians!
I gonna get you,
mongolians!
Stop breaking
my city wall!
Aw, goddammit!
Bi urgalsan!
That's the last time you gonna
break down my city wall!
You hear me,
mongolian?!
God damn mongolians.
All right, cows!
We're gonna go out there and
we're gonna give 'em hell!
But wait, where's
the other team?
There is no other team.
Huh?
Well, we put a wall around
the city to get outsiders out.
You don't think we want a bunch
of strangers coming in
To play ball, do you?
But there's no other team,
that won't be any fun.
Don't worry, it'll still
be fun for us.
Go cows! Go cows!
Play ball!
Steeeeee-Rike!
South park cows
do it again!
Congratulations
on your victory, boys!
Dude, we weren't
playing anybody!
Yeah, and
you kicked ass!
Isn't this awesome having
a great wall around our city?
Nobody in town
except for our good friends!
Hey, sshh!
Quiet everybody!
And this newest study
reveals more
About child abductions than
we apparently knew before, tom.
Turn it up.
That's right, chris,
This newest
study shows that
The majority of
child abductions
Are not committed by strangers,
But by somebody the child
knows in their own town!
The report further states
that it is because
The child trusts
the individual
That problems occur
in the first place.
Well, i guess the enemy
is in our own backyard
So to speak.
Sure does, tom.
All right, thanks, chris.
Is the weather
going to turn-
Well, if you'll
all excuse us.
I think
we'll be going now.
Yeah, come along, kyle.
Stanly, time for us
to get back to the house.
I'm not done
with my pizza.
Now, stanly!
There we go,
all finished.
My mongolian
missile defense system!
Those mongolians try to break
down my city wall again,
They gonna get a big
heat-Seeking missile surprise!
Oh!
Herro mongolian!
Yeah.
You come to break down
my city wall?
Oh, you gonna frow
dat baseball at my wall?
Oh no, not a baseball!
I'm pretty scared.
But you know what?
I might have
something here
That's a little bigger
than a baseball!
Say harro
to my rittle friend!
Oh cwap.
Ughhhh...
God damn mongolians!
You break down my city wall
for the last time!
Dude, this is worse
than child tracker.
It's okay, boys, just
act as if we weren't here.
Right, do what
you normally would do.
You're such
a fat ass, cartman.
At least i'm not
a stupid jew.
What-What, whaaat?
M'kay, kids, so now
who can tell me
What year the first
moon landing took place?
Uh, how about you, clyde?
No helping!
M'kay, i'm not really sure
having all the parents here
Is a good idea!
Well, maybe things would be
better if we could trust people
Like the stoch's!
Us? Your family has always
been the shifty-Eyed ones!
Uh, this is just
too much to take.
Mom, dad, could you
please leave me alone?
We just want
to make sure
Nobody hurts you,
junior, m'kay.
M'kay.
Ha ha ha!
My master plan!
When those mongolians
come next time
I pour this sweet-And-Sour pork
on their heads.
Ha ha!
Sweet-And-Sour pork
so hot and sticky,
Mongolians will
stick right to the wall
And scream, "awoooooo!"
I can't wait.
Oh, i get it,
a trojan mongolian horse!
Mongolians hiding inside
thinking that
I'll bring it
in the city wall
Then mongolians pop out and
destroy wall from inside out
Without getting sweet-And-Sour
pork on their heads!
Okay,
i'll pray along.
Oh rook!
My very own
mongolian trojan horse.
Gee, what a surprise,
I guess mongolians aren't such
crappy, smelly people after all.
Yeah.
Yeah, what
a great present!
I just gonna push it
inside the gate
And show it
to all my friends.
Ahaah!
Oh it's sweet-And-Sour pork!
I gonna get you mongolians
If it's the last thing i do!
...and so all the residents
of manhattan
Are prepared to evacuate
If ms. Clinton's ass
gets any bigger.
And in other news,
New findings on the increase
in child abductions.
Oh jesus,
turn it up, honey.
The study shows that the most
likely abductors of children
Are the parents themselves!
The study reveals that nine out
of every ten abduction cases
Are committed by
the child's mother or father.
The bottom line being
That your children aren't safe,
even from you!
Where are you going?
I'm just going
to go upstairs
And see if tweek
is still in his bed.
Oh?
I think
i'll go with you.
It's okay, i can do it.
I just want
to make sure that-
That i don't abduct him?
How do i know you haven't
done it already?
Me? I would never
abduct our son!
That's not what
the new study says!
But what are
we supposed to do?
How can we protect
tweek from ourselves?
Here you go, stanly.
This should hold you over
for three years.
But why do
i have to leave?
The news says that at your age
you aren't safe with us, son.
You have to get out of here
before we abduct you.
Goodbye, son,
remember to eat right.
Look out for
your brother, kyle.
You're the man, now.
Oh boys, don't ever forget
that we love you!
Be careful out there!
Where are
we supposed to go?
We can't tell you because
we can't know where you are!
Oh this is
terrible!
Go on, kids!
Go! Go and
don't look back!
Good-Bye, kids,
we'll never forget you.
Dude, sometimes i think
our parents are really stupid.
Oh, hey dog,
over here,
Over here, dog.
Got some sweet-And-Sour
for you.
Good dog!
That's it,
keep licking, dog!
Ha ha haaaa!
I'm free mongolians!
And now i'm gonna
make you pay!
Finally,
some good news tonight.
It's been several days
since any child abductions
Have taken place,
The main reason, parents don't
know where their children are.
What's the matter?
Oh, it's just-
I was wondering if stan's okay.
Oh, i'm sure he's made it
somewhere safe by now.
Do you really think we did
the right thing, randy?
Sending all the young kids
in town off
To live on their own?
Sweetheart,
you saw the news.
I know.
Don't you worry.
I'm sure that
stan and all the other kids
Are somewhere safe, off
in a whole new city by now
Making a new life
for themselves.
Ta terniig dakhiad
kheleed ogooch.
Bi oilgoj bain
bi naim nastal.
Tand ikh bayarlaa!
Ta yamar ajil
khiideg ve!
Kheden tsag bolj bain!
Sain banaaaaaaa!
All right, mongolians!
Your only way through
this wall is through me.
This is my last stand!
I'm gonna do
my war dance now!
Does my dance scare you,
mongolians?
Yeah, you think you
wanna piece of this?
This is the ancient chinese
dance of- Oh, herro, kids.
Be careful, there's
mongolians up there.
Oh cwap.
What's going on?
I heard an explosion!
God damn mongolians
attack city wall again!
Mongolians?
What the hell
are they doing here?
Rabble! Rabble, rabble!
Wait a minute.
Those mongolians are
our children.
Ike?
Kyle?
My son has
become a mongolian!?
No! Nooooo!
Oh god,
what have we done?
We sent our children away
and now they don't
Even remember
who they are.
Kids, don't you
remember us?
Wait...
I learned some
mongolian in college.
Uh, let's see.
Kids!
Uhh, bi khuutel.
Bi sanakh khuutel.
Ta tasalbaraa uzuulenuu.
Oh my god, our parents
are so stupid, dude.
Biii khuutel.
We are your parents,
You use to live here
with us.
Yeah, it was like
four days ago!
They're starting
to remember!
Staaaaan.
Your name is staaan.
Uh-Huh, stan marsh.
That's it!
Remember, son,
Remeeeeember!
We're sorry, tweek!
Are you okay, clyde?
Oh son, can you
ever forgive us!
I'm over here, dad.
Oh.
We're sorry, kids,
We just let all those
sensationalist news reports
Go to our heads!
Oh my god, do you see
what this means?
The ghost of human kindness
was right all along!
You mean how he said
we should trust each other
Or how he abducted
children?
The... uh, no, the part about
being more trusting.
We should follow what
he said, not what he did.
Yeah!
No, no, you know
who was right along?
The mongolians.
They knew that you can't
just wall yourself off
From the outside world.
Putting walls up
never helps anything
Tearing them down
brings us together.
Oh, you better be not say
what i think you gonna say.
Mr. Lu kim,
tear down this wall!
Oh god, i hate
this whole city!
Randy, can we just
take our son home now?
Yes, kids.
With us, now come.
Home.
Hooommeee.
Jesus christ, dude,
They've done some stupid crap
but jesus christ!
www.tvsubtitles.net