* i'm going down
to south park *
* gonna have
myself a time *
* friendly faces
everywhere *
* humble folks
without temptation *
* going down
to south park *
* gonna leave my
woes behind *
* ample parking
day or night *
* people spouting
"howdy neighbor" *
* headin' on up
to south park *
* gonna see
if i can't unwind *
* tim-Tmah tim-Mah,
tim-Mah tim-Mah timmy tim-Mah *
* so come on down
to south park *
* and meet some
friends of mine *
Okay, now put on
the nose, tweek.
I can't!
You do it!
Just stick it on!
But what if i put it
in the wrong place?
Just put it
between its eyes!
Agh! But what if while
i'm putting on the nose,
The snow man comes to life
and tries to kill me?
Tweek, when has
that ever happened
Except for
that one time?
Yeah!
Hey fellas!
Oh, hey butters.
How are things going
with your new best friend?
Well, tweek's okay,
But he's certainly
no kenny!
Agh!
Yeah, but he's still
better than you, butters.
Well, that's good.
Good luck being their
new friend, tweek.
Hopefully you'll do
better than me.
See ya, fellas.
Oh man, that is
way too much pressure!
You guys!
You're not gonna
believe it!
Uh, oh.
Everything's gonna
be okay, you guys!
Life isn't so crappy
after all!
It's not?
No, i was looking
in this magazine,
And i found an ad for
little ocean creatures
That you can buy
and raise in your room!
No way.
Look!
Sea people.
You keep them in
a big tank of water,
And they build castles
and play basketball and stuff.
Nuh-Uh.
Yeah!
And they ride around
on turtles
And they play
games with fish!
No way.
Okay, kyle, you're being a
negative nancy, stop it.
Unless you want everyone to call
you negative nancy from now on.
Now, what we need is
to all chip in $4.00
And we can
have them here tomorrow.
Only $16.00?
They can't be cool
if they're only $16.00.
If nancy doesn't
want to chip in,
Then it will be
$5.35 per person.
Alright,
i'll chip in.
Agh, me too!
Oh, alright.
Butters, don't forget
dinner is in two hours!
Okay, mom.
I'm just gonna be
up here doin' my homework.
Yes, by day he's mild-Mannered,
sweet and innocent butters!
But nobody knows that he is
actually his dark underside!
Professor chaos!
Ha-Ha, time to wreak havoc
on the world that shunned me!
Ha ha... ha ha...
Professor chaos!
Ah, my faithful companion
in world destruction,
General disarray!
I have done
as you asked
And brought the
first load of scrap wood!
Excellent,
general disarray!
Now we can begin my most
horrible, evil plan yet
To wreak havoc
on humanity!
What dastardly deed
are we doing now?
Simple, my dear general...
We are going to
block out the sun!
Whoa!
I have
plotted for weeks
And figured that if we
build a huge wooden shade
80 feet high
and 50 feet wide
Precisely on this hill,
South park will forever be
cast in a great shadow!
Oh, awesome!
Soon all people will
have to live like moles!
They will live only
to remember with sorrow
How great the sun
used to be!
Ha ha ahaaaaa!
Cool, it'll be just like
on 'the simpsons'!
Huh?
They did that
on 'the simpsons'.
I think it was the
mr. Burns character,
He tried to block
springfield from the sun.
He did?
Aw heck, i thought
i was being original.
So how do
we build it?
Aw, i don't
wanna do it now.
Not if they already
did it on 'the simpsons'.
Now i gotta think
of something else...
Goddammit, how come every time
i think of something clever
'The simpsons'
already did it?
Sea people...
Coming in the mail
tomorrow...
Yes... yes...
* look at me,
i'm living free *
* free and clean
amongst the sea people *
* we look for pirates,
and search for gold *
* life is an adventure
with the sea people *
* they don't ever complain
* they don't
call me fat *
* they don't make me
do homework *
* or nothing like that
* this is the way
life was meant to be *
* laughing and singing
* the sea people
and me *
* sea people
and meeeeee *
Wow, only 3 more hours,
sea people-
Only 3 more hours
and you can take me away
From this crappy goddamn planet
full of hippies.
Okay, i've added the water
purifier tablet
To the "sea people
kingdom tank".
Now, it says "step 2...
"Add the sea people eggs
to the water
You will see sea life
spring instantly."
Okay, let's just run through
this one more time.
When the sea people arrive,
I will welcome them south park
as ambassador of earth.
Tweek, you give them
the key to the city,
And we'll all engage them
in simple, conversation.
We've got to make the sea people
feel comfortable, ready?
Ready,
let's see 'em.
Hold the sign up, kyle!
Higher, kyle!
Okay...
Here we go...
Are they playing
basketball?
What the
f- Is this?
Hey, these are
brine shrimp.
I used to feed them
to my fish.
I got ripped off!
I told you, cartman-
Oh shut up, kyle!
Shut your
goddamn jew mouth!
You people are why there's
war in the middle east!
And you, tweek, why don't you learn
to button your shirt right for once!
You're as bad as stan
with his stupid girlfriend
Always spending time
with her!
God, i hate you guys!
They were supposed to take me
away to their underwater kingdom!
on adventures of the deep!
They package brine shrimp
and sell them to kids?
That's not right, man!
What are we gonna
do with them?
Who cares,
throw them away!
Let's pour them in the teacher's
coffee tomorrow morning!
Yeah, that'd be funny!
Huh-Huh, okay!
Alright,
listen to me.
We must take a strict
vow of silence.
Jesus christ,
we killed her!
Shhh, tweek
shut the hell up!
General disarray, are
your parents home? No.
I've done it,
general disarray!
I've completed my most
horrible deed to date!
What?
You know the big statue
in the town square
Of pioneer john
wesley powell?
I snuck over there
with a hacksaw
And i cut off his head!
Ha ha!
Oh... uh-
They're probably
just realizing it now!
Quick, we must
turn on the news!
...but hillary clinton's ass
just keeps getting bigger.
Also in the news tonight
A vandal has apparently
cut off and stolen
The head of the powell statue
in the south park town square!
Look!
I made the news!
I've wreaked havoc!
The head was taken
in the early morning hours,
And the police
have no leads!
I finally made
the world sorry!
I brought
sadness and chaos!
This act reminded
all of us of the time
That bart simpson took the head
of the springfield statue
In one of their
classic episodes.
Here's what some people
had to say.
Well, i think whoever
took the head
Was really just doing
an homage to the simpsons
And i think it's great!
Yes, it really made me reflect
on that episode and laugh!
The simpsons is
such a great show
And we need reminders like this
to keep us watching!
Aw... aw,
son-Of-A-Bitch.
The police say that instead of
looking for the missing head,
They'd rather
leave it off,
And be reminded of
the simpsons every day.
Why didn't you tell me the
simpsons already did that?
You seemed so proud
I didn't wanna
bum you out.
Stupid simpsons...
Hello there, phillip!
I brought
you something!
Ooh, what is it?
See? We're just watching
cartoons like always.
Nothing's changed.
Jesus christ,
she's dead!
Stop it, tweek!
We're pretending like
nothing happened.
Phillip, i think
i may have accidentally
Killed celine dion!
Killing is never
an accident you dickface!
Oh jesus,
change the channel!
...and in other news
still no cause of death found
For elementary school teacher
diane choksondik.
However, doctors say
that during the autopsy,
They did find semen
in her stomach!
They found
the sea men!
It's only a matter of time
before they find the women too!
The autopsy is ongoing,
And cause of death
has yet to be determined.
Oh god!
We're dead!
Oh jesus,
that's it, man!
I want nothing more
to do with you guys!
Tweek, where
are you going?
They're gonna
find you out!
And when they do i don't wanna
be within 50 feet of you!
You're gonna fry, man!
Hey, tweek, you're in this
just as much as we are!
What? I told you not to put
the sea people in her coffee!
I wasn't even there
when you did it!
Yeah, but you're our new friend
and that makes you co-Pee-Able.
In fact, it makes you
the most responsible.
Tweek, you might have to
take the fall on this one.
Argghhh!
Well, hello there,
children!
Chef, we did
something kind of bad.
We don't know
who else to talk to!
Oh, i'm sure your
little cracker problems
Ain't all that bad.
Come on in.
Now just sit down
and take a deep breath
And tell ol' chef
what's goin' on.
We need you to promise
not to tell anybody.
Now children, every problem
can be worked out.
What was it?
We killed our teacher,
And they found our
sea men in her stomach.
Oh children,
that's a problem
We all have to face
one time or another.
Here, let me sing you a little
song that might cheer you up.
* sometimes you
kill your teacher *
* and they find your
semen in her stomach *
* and the-
Wait, what?
So what
should we do?
Wow, i guess this
really is a big deal.
We've only got
one option, you guys.
We're gonna have to
go to the hospital
Where they're
doing the autopsy,
And get our sea men
back ourselves!
Aghagh!
I pulled out my hair!
Okay, how 'bout this, dougie?
I am going to pose
as a real estate agent,
And con everyone in town
into buying a monorail,
And then skip town
with all their money!
No?
Simpsons did it-
They did it in episode 204.
Okay, then i'm going to
start a website
To spread vicious rumors
about everyone in town!
And then-
Simpsons did it.
I'll bury a skeleton
wearing angel wings
So that the townspeople will
think a fallen angel has-
Simpsons did it.
This is it.
Alright, everyone scatter
and look for the sea men.
Tweek, stay by the door
and keep a look out.
If you see anybody coming
say the code word:
'Hammer time'.
Hammer time?
Can't the code word
just be 'look out'?
I won't remember
'hammer time'!
Just remember the song
'can't touch this'
And you'll remember
the code word!
Yeah stupid!
Oh god!
There's nothing here.
Dude, it's probably
still in her stomach.
Is it her?
Yeah, it's
ms. Choksondik, alright.
What do we do now?
Just reach in there and get
the sea men out of her stomach.
Oh god, you guys
are such pussies.
Agh!
You guys!
Ham... hamma... i can't
remember the code word!
Can you see
the sea people?
No, just a bunch of goo.
You guys!
Uh...
* dun dun-Dun-Dun,
dun-Dun dun-Dun *
* can't touch this
* dun dun-Dun-Dun,
dun-Dun dun-Dun *
* can't touch this
Mrs. Choksondik
stinks inside.
Yeah.
* dun dun-Dun-Dun, dun-Dun
dun-Dun can't touch this *
Stop- Hammer time!
Agh!
Quick, hide!
Well, at least we
got shannon sharpe back.
Alright, let's just leave the
semen sample next to the corpse.
I want to run a
hair & fiber test next.
Hey, do you
smell children?
No...
Got it, let's go!
Blgh!Agh!
Ugh!
Bring the world cup
to south park
So that a huge soccer riot
can destroy-
Simpsons did it!
Take all the beer cans
in south park
And have them shaken up in a
huge mixer at the paint store
So that they-
Episode 9f17 entitled
'so it's come to this'.
Fine!
Then maybe i'll just forget
about destroying the town,
And just run away
and join the circus!
Simpsons did it.
Aaagh!
There, we just put
the sea people back
In the tank with the others,
and nobody will ever know.
The blood is washed
neatly from our hands.
Alright, children, i got you
four tickets to thailand
And 300 dollars cash.
It's gonna be
tough livin' for a while,
You might have to do
some things for money
You never thought of
doing before.
It's alright, chef.
We got our sea people
out of the teacher's stomach,
And we put them back
in their aquarium.
Wait... what?
"Sea people"?
The sea people that we
put in the teacher's coffee!
Uh, maybe you better
start from the beginning.
...and then we put them
back in the tank.
Oh, children,
you misunderstood!
Sea people is
different from se-Men!
It is?
Yes, that stuff that was
in that vial
Didn't come from you,
It came from
someone else!
And i thought
you children
Took turns raping and then
murdered the teacher.
Ha ha ha.
Well if they found somebody
else's se-Men in her stomach
Maybe they'll find
our sea people too!
Relax, children!
Drinking some brine shrimp
can't kill you!
Your teacher must have died
from something else!
Oh really?
Agh!
I'm so relieved!
Aaaghh!
Alright, you children
have had a long night.
Why don't we all get some rest,
and on monday,
I'll sing you a song
explaining the difference
Between semen
and sea people.
Come on, children,
i'll walk you all home.
Okay, g'night cartman.
'Night, guys.
I'm so glad
we're not murderers.
Ah, it's so great that
everything is back to normal.
You guys, come quick,
you won't believe it!
Oh no, what now?
Those sea men from the teacher's
stomach somehow combined with
The remaining sea people
we had left in the tank and...
Well look!
Whoa!
How?
How did that happen?
I've been up for hours
doing some calculations,
And i've come up with my final
theory of composite dynamics:
Sea people plus sea men
equals... sea ciety.
Whoa... they've already
accomplished so much!
They're like bacteria!
Small organisms live
much faster lives
And do things at
a much faster rate.
That's right, tweek.
If my theory is correct,
all we need is to
Get more of the
two reacting agents
And we can really
see them thrive!
Tweek!
Agh!
You go and send away for more
sea people from the magazine ad.
Get at least 5 gallons
of them here, stat!
Stan and kyle, you go find
a bigger fish tank
To put them all in!
What are you gonna do?
Me? I'm going to
go out on the town
And find ten gallons
of sea men.
I have done it,
general disarray.
I've watched all 132
episodes of 'the simpsons'.
Twice.
And i have finally
come up with something
That they have never done.
Behold, this device
that i made,
Will take the cherries out of
chocolate covered cherries
And replace
the inside instead,
With 2-Month-Old
mayonnaise!
People will think
they are going to
Get a bite of a
sweet, delicious cherry,
But instead they get a mouthful
of yucky, sticky mayonnaise!
Ha ha haaaa haaaa!
You've never seen this
on the simpsons, right?
No, i think the simpsons
would be more clever than that.
Good!
Then let us take
my machine outside
And make society finally
pay for shunning us!
Tonight on 'the simpsons'!
It's a laugh-A-Rama
when bart builds a machine
That takes the cherries out of
chocolate covered cherries
And replaces it
instead with mayonnaise.
No... no, it can't be!
Uh-Oh,
simpsons did it!
Simpsons did it!
No... no!
Aaagh!
Don't have a cow, man.
Oh sweet jesus!
Can i help you?
Yes, my mommy told me
that this is where
I could find
some sea men.
Your... mom told you?
Do you have
them or not?
We sell semen, yes, but
not normally to children.
What's your name?
Francis bellman.
Francis, let's talk.
I don't wanna bunch of
bullcrap from you,
And you don't want a bunch of
bullcrap from me, right?
Where does that
get us- Nowhere.
The truth is i am completely
certified to handle sea men,
And though i may
appear young,
I'm one of the leading sea men
authorities of the midwest.
Up and comer, you know
what i'm saying.
Have my own business soon and
i'll need people to help me run it,
I'm talking
about you, francis,
And i'm talking about
a six figure income,
How's that sound?
Everything we supply
is by the quarter ounce.
One donor, certified
and on record.
I see, very interesting.
What are you doing?
Let's take a look here...
Seems like quality stuff
you got here, francis.
Yeah, good texture,
nice consistency.
The sea men must be alive
and healthy in there.
I'll take five.
Five?
Vials?
No, gallons.
We don't have
that much here.
Dammit, give me
all you got then!
Aaahghh!
No!
Simpsons did it!
Aaaahhh!
Hey, let me on,
let me on!
Sit down
and shut up!
Aaaagh!
Butters, have you
seen mr. Hat?
Hello there, children!
Aaaaaaghg!
Nooooooo!
What the hell's
wrong with him?
Look the sea people
have evolved to an
Egyptian-Like culture!
Soon they'll discover
frozen foods- Agh!
That should be
enough water, kyle.
You got the new
sea people packets, tweek?
Well, drop 'em in!
And i've got
the sea men...
Wow, that's a lot of sea men
you got there, cartman.
Yeah, i bought all
that i could at this bank,
And then i got the rest from
this guy ralph in an alley.
That's cool.
Yeah, and the
sweet thing is,
The stupid asshole didn't even
charge me money for it!
He just made me close my eyes
and suck it out of a hose.
Ha...
There we go...
Okay, now let's put
the sea-Ciety in its new home!
Nothing to do now
but wait...
Close your eyes and
suck it out of a hose?
Uh-Huh, suck it out
of a hose, yup.
Huh.
Oh my god...
Their tiny underwater
civilization
Has advanced
hundreds of years!
Look, there's a library
and a temple and a...
Oh... they think i'm god...
Yyyyyyes, i am god
of the sea people!
You hear that?
I am god of
the sea people!
I am master of
the great sunken empire!
Mom!
I'm god of
the sea people!
That's nice, poopie.
...and in other
south park news,
Elementary school teacher
ms. Choksondick's autopsy
Has shown that
the semen in her stomach
Belonged to
school counselor, mr. Mackey.
However, the semen apparently
did not contribute to the death,
And so mr. Mackey's identity
is to remain anonymous.
Hey, butters!
Hey, what are
you doing, man?
Cartman said he has something
really cool to show everybody!
You gotta come.
Cartman?
Ha ha!
Behold!
You see my tiny minions
groveling at my likeness!
I am eric cartman, god.
Hey, we paid for
the sea people too,
How come they're not
making statues of us?
Be you not jealous, jew.
I am creator
of all things, yea.
That is very
impressive, eric,
What do you intend to do
with your underwater society?
I am going to send
a message to my people
And tell them to
develop a great machine
That will shrink me
down to their size
So i can live
amongst them forever!
A ha!
A- Ha-Ahahahaaa!
What the hell is
wrong with you, butters?
They did that
on the simpsons!
Ha!
'Treehouse of horror' episode
4f-02- 'The genesis tub'!
Lisa loses a tooth and the
bacteria on it starts to grow
And makes
a little society
And they build a statue of her
thinking she's god!
Ha!
Ha-Ha-Ha!
So?
Yeah, so?
Dude, the simpsons has done
everything already, who cares?
They've been on for
like thirteen years.
Of course they've
done everything.
Every idea has
been done butters,
Even before the simpsons.
Yeah, in fact,
that episode was
A rip-Off of
a twilight zone episode.
Really?
So i shouldn't care
if i come up with an idea
And the simpsons
already did it...
It... doesn't matter!
Everything is
back to normal!
I think...
i think i can go back
To trying to
destroy the world again!
Good for you!
Yeah, that's
great, butters,
Now get the hell
out of my room.
I feel like
a spring chicken!
I'm ready to
wreak havoc once again!
Hey, look, everybody!
The other side of the aquarium
is building another statue!
Hey, it's tweek!
Me?
Oh man!
I don't want
to be a god!
That is way
to much pressure!
That is bullcrap!
You better stop
worshiping him, sea people!
What's going on now?
The sea people
from cartman's side
Are suicide-Bombing the
buildings on tweek's side!
Agh!
Yeah, go!
Now what's happening?
The sea people
on tweek's side
Just suicide-Bombed
the cartman statue!
Oh goddammit!
Oh no!
Oh, the humanity!
Well, it was a nice project
while it lasted, boys.
Yeah, but i guess
this proves that
War is the natural
order of life.
Why can't societies
just live in peace?
www.tvsubtitles.net