* i'm going down
to south park *
* gonna have
myself a time *
* friendly faces
everywhere *
* humble folks
without temptation *
* going down
to south park *
* gonna leave my
woes behind *
* ample parking
day or night *
* people spouting
"howdy neighbor" *
* headin' on up
to south park *
* gonna see
if i can't unwind *
* tim-Tmah tim-Mah,
tim-Mah tim-Mah timmy tim-Mah *
* so come on down
to south park *
* and meet some
friends of mine *
Oh cool, a preview!
Coming this summer,
It's the classic film
that changed america.
"E.T. The extra-Terrestrial"!
The new, redone version
for 2002!
All the e.T. Effects have been
digitally upgraded.
All the guns have been digitally
changed to walkie-Talkies.
And the word "terrorist" has
been changed to "hippie".
Aw, dude, why would
they do that?
Yeah, hippies and terrorists
are the same thing.
No, dude, spielberg changed
terrorist to hippie
To make e.T. More p.C.
That's gay.
Coming this summer,
It's the motion picture
that changed america.
"Saving private ryan",
the re-Re-Release,
Where the word "nazi"
has been changed to
"Persons with political
differences".
And all the guns have been
replaced by walkie-Talkies.
Why the hell do these directors
keep updating their movies?!
And now for your
feature presentation!
The classic re-Re-Re-Release
Of "star wars: the empire
strikes back!
Woo hoo!
Aaaaaghhh!
God dammit,
that pisses me off!
Yeah, we want
our money back!
Sorry, suckers!
You asshole!
Why don't they leave
those movies alone!
We liked them the way
they were!
Don't you see
what this means?
All our favorite movies are
going to be changed and updated
Until we can't even
recognize them anymore!
Tweek is right.
It isn't fair for those
asshole directors
To keep changing their movies
and making them different!
Movies are art and art
shouldn't be modified!
Yeah, what if
they had modified
The roman colosseum
every year?
It would just be another
big "douchie" stadium now!
We have to
do something!
Let's form a club!
Yeah, we could
form a club
That takes food stamps
from poor people
And then sells them back to
the government for a profit!
No, fat-Ass!
I mean a club to protect
films from their directors
So they can't be
messed with!
Yeah, we'll be the "save films
from their own directors' club".
Yeah!
No!
No, no!
I don't wanna form a club!
That's too much pressure!
Look, i'm supposed to
take it easy.
Just watch the clouds,
sit in the grass.
If we form a club there'll be
responsibilities,
Commitments!
Tweek, now god dammit,
We picked you to
replace kenny
Because we thought you were
a team player!
I'm not!
I'm not
a team player!
Now either you stop with
these "faggotronics"
Or we'll find someone
to replace you!
Aaagh!
Oh, jesus!
Dude, that sign sucks,
nobody's gonna show up!
What's wrong with it?
Look at it, dude,
You're not offering
any fabulous prizes.
You have to offer
fabulous prizes
If you want people to show up
for your stupid crap.
Here...
Free hat?
Yeah, if you offer free hats,
maybe people will show up.
But we don't
have hats!
We can make them
out of paper.
It's not hard, just stupid
little paper hats.
People just need free stuff.
Don't you guys
know anything?
You see?
First we were just forming a
club, now we have to make hats!
Where does it end?!
Alright, let's go get
the gymnasium ready.
Tweek, you go make
50 hats.
50 hats?
Oh jesus!
I'll never make it!
Tweek!
Calm down, son.
Remember what
dr. Norris told you-
Find your center.
My center?
My center.
Calm... puppies.
Tweek!
Tweeeeeekk!
How many hats
have you made?
Oh god!
We only have until 10 a.M.
Tomorrow, get the lead out!
Aagh, oh god!
You guys,
we have a big problem!
I was up all night
making hats-
I only slept for an hour-
And then i dreamt about
making hats!
But i only made 15!
Calm down, tweek.
15 might be enough.
Yeah, let's see if anyone's
even shown up yet.
Dude, there's like a thousand
people in there!
A thousand?
Oh jesus, man!
I don't have nearly
a thousand hats!
They're gonna kick
your ass, tweek!
Tweek, it's okay!
Look, maybe these people
all turned out
Because they believe
in saving films!
Maybe they don't even care
about the free hat!
Free hat!
Free hat!...
Oh god!
I told you guys-
Never underestimate
the power of a free hat.
I gotta move away,
you guys!
Relax, tweek, we're just gonna
have to go in there
And explain what happened.
There are more important things
right now than free hats.
Okay, uh, we wanna thank you
all for coming.
We're really happy to see such
enthusiasm for our cause.
Uh, one thing
before i continue:
Unfortunately, we don't have enough
of the free hats for everyone.
Uh, excuse me?
Yes, we apologize,
but our friend tweek here,
Didn't make
enough of them.
Oh jesus, don't
tell them it was me!
We don't care about that.
You don't?
You mean you just came because
you believe in our cause?
Yeah, free hat!
What?!
Hat mccullough!
He was sent to
prison in '82
And we believe he should
be released!
Yeah!
Free hat!
Free hat!...
Okay, apparently, there's been
a bit of a misunderstanding.
This is a rally to save films
from their directors.
To do what?
We believe that films are pieces
of art that must be preserved
From the perverse hands
of their aging filmmakers.
Oh... sorry.
Come on, everyone, guess
we're in the wrong place.
Free hat!
Wait, wait, wait!
Don't you see what's happening
out there?
The films that you all grew up
with, that touched your lives
And are a part of your soul, are
now being updated and changed.
Join us and we can be a group
that makes a difference!
Can we also work towards
freeing hat?
Uh, sure, and we'll also
try to free hat.
Free hat!
Free hat!...
212, 213, 214 members!
You guys, you guys!
Oh god!
I've got terrible news!
What?
Ted koppel wants us
to appear on "nightline"
To talk about our cause!
Really?
That's great!
No, it isn't, man!
That is way
too much pressure!
If we go on nightline, the whole
country can hear about
What's happening to
our classic films!
Just remember that
i do all the talking.
You? Why?
Because i'm the
official spokesman.
I got dibs on it.
When did we do
dibs for it?
Just now.
One two three- Dibs!
Knee.
Alright, fine, you're
the spokesman, cartman.
But you better not
screw it up!
What could
possibly go wrong?
A new movement is
sweeping the country,
Led by four determined boys
from south park, colorado.
The organization was created
to protect hollywood's
Classic films from the hands
of their directors,
And also to free
hat mccullough.
So boys, i'll ask you the question
that's on everyone's minds.
Why does your organization want
to free hat mccullough,
The convicted, confessed serial
murderer of 23 babies?
I believe that can
best be answered
By our official
spokesman, tweek.
Agh!
Well, hat mccullough admitted
he killed those toddlers,
Why do you want him free?
Oh, jesus, man!
Just answer me
this, tweek-
What do you see as positive
about toddler murder?
Uh, uh, it's...
it's easy?
Yes, it is easy.
Alright, then on to
your other cause.
"Saving films from
their directors".
What got you boys
interested in this?
Especially given your
pro-Toddler murder status.
We believe that films have to be
taken away from people like
Steven spielberg and george
lucas because they're insane.
I'm glad you said that, boys,
because joining us now
Are steven spielberg
and george lucas!
Oh christ, agh!
Hello, ted.
Hi, ted.
Gentlemen, these toddler murder
fans think that you're insane
And shouldn't be allowed to
alter your films. Your response?
Well, first of all,
both george and i
Are very firmly against
the murdering of toddlers.
Hear, hear.
Dude, that's steven spielberg
and george lucas.
Get me out of here!
Please somebody get me
out of here!
And as for
altering our films,
All we're doing reaching a
new audience with our movies.
As the makers of dreams, we like
to speak for the children.
Uh, we thought we were
speaking for the children.
Yeah, we're children.
Look, if the beatles went back
and updated "the white album"
Every few years,
what would we have now?
Yeah, these guys are only
motivated by money, ted.
How so?
Think about it-
Jew.
Coincidence?
I'm not a jew!
You little brats- I mean,
you darling children
Don't know what
you're talking about.
Changing e.T. Was the
best thing i ever did.
Dude, don't you see
that it's not?
It'd be like changing
"raiders of the lost ark"!
Wait a minute,
what did you say?
That's brilliant!
Yes, change raiders
of the lost ark,
Why didn't we
think of it before?
No! No!
Members, this is our
darkest hour.
We have just learned that
george lucas and steven spielberg
Now intend to update and change
"raiders of the lost ark".
There is only one way we can
stop this important,
Historical piece of art
from being harmed.
Mr. Secretary?
Thank you.
Our intelligence tells us that
the original negative
To raiders of the lost ark
Is currently somewhere
in george lucas' house.
We need to find
and usurp that negative.
And if we can get a hold
of the negative,
They can't change
the movie?
That's our
understanding.
Sounds like
a good idea to me!
I don't want them to change
raiders of the lost ark!
Yeah!
We should get that negative
as soon as we get hat free!
Yeah!
Free hat!
No, no, we need to do
this first.
But we have to free hat.
It's just that, you know,
he killed 23 babies.
Yeah, but it was
in self-Defense!
Yeah!
He killed 23 babies
in self-Defense?
Hat was attacked maliciously
and unprovoked
By a gang of babies
in westown park.
When that many babies
get together
They can be like piranha.
Three eyewitnesses
testified that
If hat hadn't killed those
babies, they'd a killed him!
Yeah!
Free hat! Free hat!
Alright, but right now
we gotta focus on
Getting those original
prints of raiders.
He's right,
we better split up.
Some of you go with the boys
to get those film prints,
The rest come with me
To go talk to the governor
about freeing hat!
Yeah!
Free hat!
Free hat!...
Well, looks like we're gonna
have to do this ourselves.
No, that's it!
I'm out!
I can't deal with the stress
you guys create!
We're just gonna
fly to california
And break into george
lucas' house-
What's stressful
about that?
Aagh!
Okay, tweek, let me
tell you something.
You've been our new friend now
for two weeks, okay?
And i've gotta be honest with
you, it isn't going well.
People aren't that into you,
tweek, they find you annoying.
Now i'd say you've got
one last shot here,
And i don't want you
to blow it, okay?
Does that help take
the stress off?
Okay, go.
I'm not breaking into
george lucas' house.
I'm not breaking
into george lucas' house.
I'm in a green field.
Shut up, tweek, this is not
the time for "faggocity"!
This looks like
the right room.
I'm in a field,
surrounded by deer.
Over here!
That's it!
Alright,
get it, tweek!
Nu-Uh!
Get it,
you piece of crap
Before i grab your nutsack
and twist it!
What are you doing?!
Oh god!
Oh jesus!
You're the boys from
that stupid club!
Gimme that!
Do with us
what you will, mr. Lucas,
But please don't change
raiders of the lost ark.
We're gonna
make it better.
The movie is gonna be changed
and that is that!
Alright, you asked for it.
I'm afraid you
leave us no choice!
It's time for plan b.!
Aw, really?
Oh god,
not plan b.!
You have a heart
made of ice, mr. Lucas,
So we're going to
melt your icy heart
With a cool island song.
Gentlemen?
What?!
Hit it, tweek!
* in the tropical isles
with the coconut trees- *
Wait, wait!
I thought we were gonna
cool his hot heart
With a cool island song.
No, he has a icy heart.
But you can't melt ice with
a cool song, r-Tard!
So we have to warm
his icy heart
With a hot
island song?
It's a cool island song!
Then we're gonna end up
freezing his hellish heart
With a cool island song.
Aw, do we wanna
do that?
Alright, that does it!
Yes, thank you,
officer.
The police are
on their way, boys.
Soon you'll be in jail
getting rammed!
Aagh!
Those rams can do to us what
they will, mr. Lucas,
But we'll never stop
trying to protect films!
It's not too late
to do what's right.
Give us the print.
There's still some good
in you, mr. Lucas,
We know there is!
It is... too late
for me, boys.
You yourself
led the campaign
Against the colorization
of films.
You understand why films
shouldn't be changed!
That's different.
These are my movies,
i made them,
And i have the right to do
whatever i want with them.
You're wrong,
mr. Lucas.
They're not your movies,
they're ours.
All of ours.
We paid to go see them,
And they're just as much a part
of our lives
As they are of yours.
When an artist creates,
Whatever they create
belongs to society.
Have i...
become so old
That i've forgotten what
being an artist is about?
Give the print to us so that we
can protect it from spielberg
And anyone else
who wants to alter it.
Perhaps...
you are right.
Stop!
What are you
doing, george?
Steven, i-
Give me that print,
george.
We need to make
the alterations.
Steven, these boys
had a point.
I don't remember what
it was, but it was good.
You haven't let these
doe-Eyed children
Affect your judgment,
have you, george?
Don't forget-
You belong to me.
Don't listen to him!
You still have a chance to
preserve your film!
I'm...
i'm sorry, boys.
Ha ha ha-Haaaa!
Now, take the children
prisoner!
What?!
You troublemakers shall be
my guests of honor
At the premiere of the new
raiders of the lost ark!
Your gay little club
is over!
You,
steven spielberg!
Come on, you guys!
Oh my god, they're
gonna kill us!
Don't even
think about it, kid!
I'm not afraid to use
this walkie-Talkie.
The one with the cocaine
problem escaped, mein director!
Leave him!
Let him run back
to his mommy.
We must get the film ready
for the premiere.
Lucas! Come!
It's the digitally
re-Enhanced re-Release
Of the very first, pilot episode
of "south park"!
Yes, the classic, rough,
hand-Made first episode
Is getting a makeover
for 2002!
The simple, funny aliens are now
super bad-Ass and cool!
The flying saucer?
No longer cheap construction
paper- But a 4.0 megapixel
Non-Drop digital masterpiece
of technology!
Yes, everything's new.
New is better!
When we first made
south park,
We didn't want to use
construction paper,
We just had to
because it was cheap.
Now with new technology we can
finally re-Master south park
To make it look sharp,
clean and focused.
And expensive.
Yes, all the charm of
the simple little cartoon
Will melt before your eyes
As it is replaced by newer and
more standardized animation!
For instance, the scene
at the bus stop.
We always meant to have imperial
walkers and giant dewback lizards
In the background, but
simply couldn't afford it.
Get this special enhanced
version quick!
Because another enhanced version
will likely be coming out for 2003!
Members!
Uh, oh jesus-
You have to do something!
Our club's president, treasurer,
and secretary
Have all been taken hostage
by steven spielberg!
Agh!
Prisoner?
You mean like hat?
Yes, just like hat!
But the governor
won't pardon hat,
So how can we get him
out of prison?
Yeah!
No, listen to me!
We're not talking about
hat right now, okay?
Get it?!
Look, we went to
george lucas' house
And tried to melt his icy heart
with a warm island song,
But then spielberg showed up
And took three of
our members prisoner!
They're going to premiere the
new raiders of the lost ark
And we have to rescue them,
do you understand?!
Hey, he's got
a point there.
Yeah, maybe we could melt
the governor's icy heart
With a cool
island song!
Yeah!
Let's go!
No!
No?
No, he's right.
We have to freeze his hot heart
with a cool island song!
Or is it freshen his hot temper
with a cool island song?
Let's cool his hot temper
with a fresh island song!
That's it!
Oh god, i'm gonna have to
do this myself!
Oh god!
Well, the print is finished
and the day has come!
Tonight, steven spielberg
and george lucas
Will be at the premiere of
the new, special edition
Of raiders of the lost ark.
Lots of celebrity guests
and other rich people
Will be on hand to witness
all the updated effects
And modernized technology!
Ho-Oh!
The kid?
The tweeked-Out kid?
I'm gonna blow up
the print, spielberg!
Your persistence
surprises even me.
Surely you don't think you can
escape from this premiere?
That depends on how reasonable
we're all willing to be.
All i want
are my friends.
Wow...
Except for cartman,
you can keep him.
Ah!
And if we refuse?
Then your premiere
has no movie!
He's definitely
lost it.
Yup.
Okay, okay,
stand back.
Stand back, back!
Okay, kid, you win,
blow it up.
Zuroch!
Blow it back to god.
All your life has been the
pursuit of seeing a great film.
This new version of raiders
has digital effects
Beyond your wildest dreams.
You want to see it screened
just as much as i.
Come on, tweek,
blow it up!
Son, we are simply passing
through history.
This- Is improved history.
Do as you will.
* in the tropical isles
with the coconut trees *
* the air is fresh and
the people are free *
* but here in the mountains
there's no freedom like that *
* there's a man in prison
and his name is hat *
Haffaaa mali fi!
Thanks for coming,
everyone!
This is the birth
of the new version
Of raiders
of the lost ark!
We shall screen it here
and then destroy
All the old prints
in celebration!
Hooray!
Begin the film!
Ohh, aaahh!
You guys!
Close your eyes,
don't look at it!
What?
Don't watch the movie,
you guys!
It'll be terrible,
close your eyes!
Oohhh...
aahh...
It's beautiful!
Wait a minute.
This version
is awful!
Yeah, they ruined it!
Oh my god,
it's terrible!
Aaaagh!
You...
you guys okay?
Yeah, i think so.
Man, that new version
must've sucked balls.
Today is a day
of celebration!
And we owe it all to these
four brave, young boys!
Yeah!
Alright!
And thanks to the bravery of
this young man in particular-
Hat mccullough is finally
free from prison!
What?
Hat! Hat! Hat!...
Thank you, everyone-
Kill the innocent!
Uh, i'm so thankful for all your
support- Rape the virgin!
And uh, i just wonder if i could
get a baby real quick?
Sure, give that
man a baby!
Come on, you guys,
let's get outta here.
Oh my god!
Do you think we did
a good thing, stan?
I mean, no one even
seemed to notice.
Yeah, well, sometimes
the things we do
Don't matter right now.
Sometimes they matter
later.
We have to care more about later
sometimes, you know?
I think that's what separates us
from the steven spielbergs
And george lucases
of the world.
That and youth-
Those guys are old.
But what about the
original prints
Of raiders
of the lost ark?!
What if somebody else takes
them and tries to change them?
Don't worry, tweek,
it's somewhere safe,
Somewhere where nobody
will ever find it.
www.tvsubtitles.net