* I'M GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK *
* GONNA HAVE
MYSELF A TIME *
* FRIENDLY FACES
EVERYWHERE *
* HUMBLE FOLKS
WITHOUT TEMPTATION *
* GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK *
* GONNA LEAVE MY
WOES BEHIND *
* AMPLE PARKING
DAY OR NIGHT *
* PEOPLE SPOUTING
"HOWDY NEIGHBOR" *
* HEADIN' ON UP
TO SOUTH PARK *
* GONNA SEE
IF I CAN'T UNWIND *
* TIM-TMAH TIM-MAH,
TIM-MAH TIM-MAH TIMMY TIM-MAH *
* SO COME ON DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK *
* AND MEET SOME
FRIENDS OF MINE *
OKAY, HERE HE COMES.
WHO WANTS TO TELL HIM ?
I'LL DO IT.
HEY, FELLAS !
I'M GLAD YOU CALLED ME !
THERE'S A PIE EATING CONTEST
DOWN AT THE FIREHOUSE,
AND I THOUGHT
WE SHOULD ALL GO !
BUTTERS, COULD YOU
TAKE A SEAT, PLEASE ?
WELL, SURE.
BUTTERS, WE HAVE TO HAVE A VERY
DIFFICULT CONVERSATION.
WHAT IS IT ?
WELL, IN THE MONTHS SINCE
OUR FRIEND KENNY DIED
YOU'VE REALLY STEPPED UP
AS A FRIEND
AND "FILLED THE GAP",
SO TO SPEAK.
OH, IT'S MY PLEASURE !
I LOVE BEING YOU GUYS'
NEW FRIEND.
YES, WELL, BUTTERS,
IT'S JUST NOT WORKING OUT.
NOT WORKING OUT ?
I'M AFRAID WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
LET YOU GO-- AS OUR FRIEND.
YOU'RE JUST TOO...
LAME.
LAME, YES.
BUT I CAN GET BETTER.
BUTTERS, YOU JUST DON'T REALLY
FIT IN WITH US HERE.
WE THINK IT'S BEST
FOR ALL OF US
IF YOU LOOK FOR FRIENDSHIP
OPPORTUNITIES ELSEWHERE.
BUT WE CERTAINLY WANT TO THANK
YOU FOR ALL YOUR HARD WORK
AND ATTEMPTS AT
BEING OUR FRIEND.
LAME AS THEY WERE.
BUT I THOUGHT WE WERE REALLY
GETTING ALONG GREAT.
I THOUGHT WE WERE REALLY
HAVING FUN TOGETHER.
YES, WELL, WE WEREN'T.
PLEASE, FELLAS,
DON'T FIRE ME.
WE'RE SORRY, BUTTERS,
OUR MIND IS MADE UP.
BUT WE CERTAINLY WANT TO
THANK YOU FOR COMING BY.
YOU KNOW YOUR WAY OUT, RIGHT ?
PHEW !
WHEW !
HE TOOK THAT
PRETTY WELL I THINK.
WHO CARES ?
SO LET'S GET STARTED
ON WHO'S GONNA BE
THE NEW PERSON TO
TAKE KENNY'S PLACE.
THE WORLD ISN'T FAIR.
I DO EVERYTHING
PEOPLE ASK ME TO.
I STAND IN THE
LUNCH LINES FOR THEM...
I BUY TAMPONS AT
THE STORE FOR THEM...
I GO ON MAURY POVICH WITH
BALLS ON MY CHIN FOR THEM.
AND YET,
NOBODY ACCEPTS ME.
I AM AN OUTCAST--
A SHADOW OF A MAN WHO CAN FIND
NO COMPANIONSHIP,
NO LOVE FROM OTHERS.
FINE !
IF I'M TO BE
AN OUTCAST, SO BE IT.
I'M THROUGH DOING WHAT
OTHERS TELL ME TO DO,
AND I AM SICK OF THIS WORLD
AND THE STINKY PEOPLE IN IT.
FROM NOW ON,
I WILL DEDICATE MY LIFE
TO BRINGING CHAOS TO THE WORLD
THAT HAS DEJECTED ME !
I WILL BECOME THE
GREATEST SUPER-VILLAIN
THE WORLD HAS EVER SEEN !
WHERE I GO,
DESTRUCTION WILL FOLLOW !
PREPARE, OH LITTLE TOWN.
PREPARE FOR THE
GREATEST SUPER-VILLAIN
YOU HAVE
EVER SEEN...
PROFESSOR CHAOS !
( mom knocks )
BUTTERS, TIME FOR BED.
OKAY, MOM.
YES, SLEEP FOR NOW.
TOMORROW,
THE CHAOS BEGINS.
HA HA...
HA HA HA...
HA HA HA
HA HA HA !
AH HA HA HA !
ALRIGHT, WE WANT TO THANK
EVERYBODY FOR COMING,
THIS IS A GREAT TURNOUT.
UH, AS YOU KNOW, OUR FRIEND
KENNY DIED A FEW MONTHS AGO
AND WE ARE LOOKING TO FILL
THE VOID WITH A NEW FRIEND.
YOU'VE ALL BEEN SELECTED
AS POSSIBLE CANDIDATES,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY THERE IS
ONLY ROOM FOR ONE OF YOU.
AND SO, STAN AND KYLE AND I WILL
BE SPENDING THE NEXT FEW DAYS
GOING OUT WITH EACH ONE OF YOU,
AND NARROWING OUR CHOICES DOWN,
UNTIL WE THINK WE'VE FOUND
THE PERFECT FRIEND.
ARE THERE ANY QUESTIONS ?
WHAT IF WE DON'T
WANT TO BE YOUR FRIEND ?
CLYDE... OKAY ?
NOW, THE FIRST THING WE HAVE
TO DO IS CUT THE LIST DOWN
FROM 20 CHOICES TO 10.
AND SO TODAY WE WILL
ALL BE GOING
TO THE AMUSEMENT PARK TOGETHER
TO SEE WHO WE WANT TO CUT.
PLEASE KEEP IN MIND THIS
WILL ALL BE VIDEOTAPED,
SO PUT ON YOUR BEST FRIEND FACES
AND MAY THE BEST FRIEND WIN !
OH, AND WE WILL BE NEEDING
A $10 PER PERSON ENTRANCE FEE.
ORDER 23 IS UP,
AND ORDER 24 IS UP.
( ding-ding )
UH, WAITRESS, I ACTUALLY
ORDERED THE CHICKEN SOUP.
THIS IS MINESTRONE.
YEAH, I HAD THE
MINESTRONE OVER HERE.
AH HA HA !
HA HA HA HAAA !
HA HA HA
HA HAAA !
I AM PROFESSOR CHAOS !
AND NOW THIS PUNY WORLD
WILL BOW DOWN TO ME !
HA AH HA HAAA !
( Stan )
SO TODAY, WE WENT TO
THE AMUSEMENT PARK
WITH ALL OUR
POSSIBLE FRIENDS.
IT WAS A REALLY FUN TIME,
WE RODE ALL THE RIDES,
AND EVERYONE
GOT ALONG GREAT.
I THINK THE PERSON
THAT STOOD OUT MOST
AT THE AMUSEMENT PARK
WAS JIMMY.
WELL, THE REASON I THINK I WOULD
MAKE THE PERFECT FOURTH FRIEND
IS THAT I LOVE
TELLING JOKES.
YOU KNOW, WHO DOESN'T
LIKE TO LAUGH ?
TWEEK-- NOW THERE'S
AN INTERESTING CHOICE.
TWEEK HAS A LOT OF QUALITIES
THAT I LOOK FOR IN A FRIEND.
WHAT IF THEY DON'T
PICK ME ?
WHAT IF THEY
GET US ALL, MAN ?
I MEAN, CHRIST, IF THEY CAN
GET TO THE PENTAGON
THEY CAN GET
TO US ALL, MAN !
AAAGH !
I THINK I DESERVE TO TAKE
KENNY'S PLACE THE MOST,
BECAUSE I'VE BEEN HANGING AROUND
THESE GUYS FOR LIKE, FIVE YEARS
AND I NEVER GET
TO SAY OR DO ANYTHING.
YEAH, I'VE ALWAYS
SEEN THAT KID IN CLASS,
BUT HE NEVER DOES ANYTHING,
HE'S MORE LIKE A PROP.
TOWELIE IS A TOUGH CHOICE,
BECAUSE EVEN THOUGH I CAN SEE
HOW ALWAYS HAVING A TOWEL AROUND
COULD COME IN HANDY,
HE'S JUST ALWAYS SO HIGH.
YEAH, I REALLY HOPE
I WIN BECAUSE--
WAIT, WHAT IS THIS AGAIN ?
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT'S GOING ON.
WE DECIDED TO GET SOME
ONE-ON-ONE TIME WITH JIMMY
AND RIDE THE LOG RIDE.
AND THE GREAT THING WAS THAT
BECAUSE JIMMY'S CRIPPLED
WE GOT TO GO TO
THE FRONT OF THE LINE.
THAT WAS DEFINITELY BIG POINTS
FOR JIMMY, Y'KNOW.
BUT THEN, WE GET TO
THE RIDE ITSELF AND...
HEY, I'M GONNA NEED SOME HELP
GETTING IN THE LOG, FELLAS.
OH, SHUT HER DOWN,
SOMEONE NEEDS ASSISTANCE.
OH, REALLY ?
THAT'S GONNA
COST SOME POINTS.
BUT RIGHT NOW I'D SAY IF WE'RE
GONNA HAVE A RETARD FOR A FRIEND
I'D HAVE TO PICK TIMMY,
BECAUSE TIMMY DOESN'T
TELL LAME JOKES.
( Jimmy )
BOY, ISN'T THIS
GREAT, FELLAS ?
ARE WE GREAT PALS
OR WHAT ?
( Kyle )
ONE THING'S FOR SURE,
PICKING OUR NEW FRIEND
ISN'T GONNA BE EASY.
KNEEL !
KNEEL BEFORE
PROFESSOR CHAOS !
HA HA, HA HA HA !
AHH HA HA HAA !
HA HA HAAA !
HEE HA HA HA HAA !
OH, THE LOOK ON THEIR FACES
WHEN THEY GOT THE WRONG SOUP !
I LOVE BRINGING CHAOS !
HA !
HA HA HAA !
AND THAT IS ONLY
THE BEGINNING.
HA HA HA,
HA HA HA HAA !!
ALRIGHT, EVERYONE,
IT WAS A TOUGH DECISION
BUT BASED ON OUR TIME WITH YOU
ALL AT THE AMUSEMENT PARK,
WE HAVE WHITTLED OUR
CHOICES DOWN TO 10.
IF YOU RECEIVE A ROSE,
PLEASE STAY.
IF YOU DON'T, PLEASE
GET THE FUDGE OUT.
KYLE, WILL YOU ANNOUNCE THE
PEOPLE WE WANT TO STAY ?
TOKEN...
CLYDE...
CRAIG...
TIMMY...
TIMMY !
OH, MAN, THIS IS
TOO MUCH PRESSURE !
PIP...
JIMMY...
JASON...
TOWELIE...
LOUIGI.
JUST ONE ROSE LEFT, KYLE,
WHO DOES IT GO TO ?
TWEEK.
AAH !
ALRIGHT, THE REST OF YOU,
THANKS FOR COMING,
GET THE FUDGE OUT.
( groans )
I DIDN'T MAKE THE CUT ?
OH GOD, I DIDN'T
MAKE THE CUT ?
I DIDN'T EVEN GET A CHANCE
TO HAVE THEM GET TO KNOW ME.
ALRIGHT, CONGRATULATIONS TO
THOSE OF YOU SELECTED TO STAY.
IN THE END, ONE OF YOU
WILL BE THE NEW KENNY.
GOOD LUCK.
GOOD MORNING, BUTTERS.
IT CERTAINLY IS, MOTHER !
DID YOU HEAR ABOUT
WHAT'S BEEN GOING ON ?
SOME HORRIBLE NEW
SUPER-VILLAIN
MADE SOMEBODY GET THE WRONG
SOUP ORDER AT BENNIGAN'S.
NO, I DIDN'T
HEAR ABOUT THAT.
YOU, YOU DIDN'T ?
DAD, COULD I SEE THE
NEWSPAPER REAL QUICK ?
WELL, SURE, BUTTERS, I WAS JUST
ABOUT TO GET SOME BREAKFAST.
NOTHING...
NOTHING !
IT'S THE LIBERAL MEDIA,
THEY'RE KEEPING THE STORIES
OF MY DEEDS COVERED UP
SO AS NOT TO
CAUSE A PANIC.
WELL THEN, I GUESS IT'S TIME
TO STEP IT UP A NOTCH !
( * South Park segue music * )
OKAY, NEXT.
( * South Park segue music  )
THIS LOOKS
PRETTY GOOD.
YEAH, IT'S NOT BAD.
NEXT.
( * South Park segue music  )
TIMMY !
NEXT.
( school bell rings )
OKAY, SO NOW WE'RE GONNA
SEE HOW YOU ALL WORK
AS A FRIEND
DURING CLASS TIME.
YOUR PERFORMANCES WILL
BE JUDGED PRIMARILY
ON HOW YOU HELP US CHEAT
AND GIVE US ANSWERS.
SO GOOD LUCK,
EVERYBODY !
( Ms. Choksondik )
SIT DOWN, BOYS.
ALRIGHTY, THEN.
ALRIGHT, CHILDREN,
BEFORE WE GET STARTED,
HAS ANYBODY SEEN THE ERASER
FOR THE CHALKBOARD ?
HEH HEH HEH, HEE !
IT PROBABLY GOT KNOCKED
ON THE FLOOR SOMEWHERE.
CAN YOU ALL PLEASE JUST LOOK
AROUND YOUR DESKS FOR IT ?
( Butters )
YES... LOOK AROUND FOR
YOUR PRECIOUS ERASER.
YOU WON'T FIND IT.
THAT ERASER
IS IN MY BACKYARD,
BURIED THREE FEET BELOW
THE SURFACE OF THE EARTH.
AND DO YOU EVEN
SUSPECT ME ?  NO.
NOW WE SHALL SEE HOW YOU ALL
LIKE YOUR DEAR CHALKBOARD
WITHOUT AN ERASER !
INFORMATION THAT JUST KEEPS
PILING UP AND PILING UP,
UNTIL YOUR MINUSCULE BRAINS
CAN TAKE IT NO LONGER !
NO ?
OH WELL, NEVER MIND, I'VE GOT
A BACKUP ONE IN THE DESK.
OKAY, TODAY, CHILDREN,
WE'RE GONNA LEARN ABOUT
MULTIPLYING TIMES FIVE.
SO !  YOU ALL THINK
THAT YOU CAN OUTSMART
PROFESSOR CHAOS, DO YOU ?
NOW, WHENEVER WE MULTIPLY
A NUMBER TIMES FIVE
THE RESULT IS GOING TO END
IN A ZERO OR FIVE.
MS. CHOKSONDIK ?
WHAT IS IT, BUTTERS ?
UH, I NEED TO GO TO THE
BATHROOM, REALLY BAD.
ALRIGHT, BUTTERS, TAKE THE
BATHROOM PASS AND GO.
OKAY, SO FOR INSTANCE,
CHILDREN--
ALRIGHT I'M GOING TO
THE BATHROOM NOW.
IF ANYBODY NEEDS ME,
THAT'S WHERE I'LL BE.
JUST GO, BUTTERS.
OKAY, SO FOR INSTANCE, FIVE
TIMES ONE IS... WHAT, ERIC ?
UH, WHAT'S THE
QUESTION AGAIN ?
FIVE TIMES ONE.
FIVE TIMES ONE
IS OF COURSE...
FIVE.
FIVE.FIVE.
FIVE !
HA HA HA HAAA !
THE TIME FOR FUN AND GAMES
IS OVER, FEEBLE-MINDED FOOLS !
WHO ARE YOU ?
I AM PROFESSOR CHAOS !
BRINGER OF DESTRUCTION
AND MAKER OF DOOM !
THOSE WHO DO NOT KNOW ME YET
SHALL KNOW ME VERY SOON,
FOR THE HOUR OF CHAOS
IS AT HAND !
HA HA HA HAAA !
HEY, THAT KID
TOOK MY LAST ERASER !
COME BACK HERE, KID !
OH, I'M BACK FROM
THE BATHROOM.
I REALLY LET ONE GO
IN THERE.
BUTTERS DID YOU SEE ANOTHER
LITTLE KID RUN OUT OF HERE ?
WHY YES, I DID !
BUT HE PUSHED ME DOWN
AND I SCRAPED MY ELBOW.
GO ON, LOOK AT IT.
IT'S SCRAPED, LOOK !
YES, GO ON AND SEE
THE RED MARK ON MY ELBOW,
THE RED MARK I MADE MYSELF
TO THROW YOU OFF
PROFESSOR CHAOS' TRAIL !
IT LOOKS FINE, BUTTERS.
OKAY, HOLD ON AND
STAY HERE, CHILDREN.
( bell rings )
YOU'RE SUCH A
FATASS, CARTMAN !
OH YEAH ?  WELL,
YOU'RE A STUPID JEW !
SHUT UP, FATASS !
OH, UH...
YOU GUYS ARE DUMB.
OKAY, CRAIG,
INTERESTING CHOICE.
POWERFUL STUFF THERE, CRAIG,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT IS ALMOST COMPLETE--
THE CREATION OF MY MINIONS
WHO WILL ASSIST ME
IN BRINGING TERROR
TO THE WORLD.
THERE WE GO.
YES, MY MINIONS OF CHAOS.
( squeaking )
SHH.
NOT NOW, MY LOVELIES,
YOUR TIME TO BRING DESTRUCTION
WILL COME VERY SOON.
AAH !
BUTTERS, A NOTE FOR YOU
WAS LEFT ON THE FRONT DOOR.
A NOTE ?
HERE YOU GO.
AND WASH YOUR HANDS AFTER
YOU TOUCH THOSE HAMSTERS,
YOU'LL GET AIDS.
OKAY, MOM.
SO, SOMEONE HAS DISCOVERED
MY HORRIBLE SECRET.
THIS COULD BE A TRAP
SET BY THE F.B.I.
OH, I'LL BE AT THE DOCKS,
PRECIOUS F.B.I.,
BUT IT IS I WHO WILL HAVE
THE TRAP SET FOR YOU !
COME, MY MINIONS,
WE HAVEN'T MUCH TIME.
ALRIGHT EVERYONE,
THE TIME HAS COME FOR US
TO NARROW THE LIST DOWN
FROM 10 TO SIX.
BUT FIRST, LET US JUST SAY THAT
THE PEOPLE WHO WE DIDN'T PICK
WERE ONLY NOT PICKED BECAUSE
THEY TOTALLY SUCK BALLS-- KYLE ?
THEY'RE NOT
GOING TO PICK ME.
I JUST KNOW THEY'RE NOT.
OH JESUS !
I CAN'T TAKE IT !
TOKEN.
ALRIGHT !
TIMMY.
TIMMY !
TWEEK...
PIP.
REALLY ?
I DON'T BELIEVE IT !
TOWELIE.
WHAT ?
JUST ONE MORE
ROSE, KYLE.
JIMMY.
OH BOY !
OH THANK GOD !
ALRIGHT, THOSE WITH
ROSES WILL MOVE ON
TO THE SWIMSUIT AND
TALENT COMPETITION.
THE REST OF YOU--
GET THE FUDGE OUT !
THIS WHOLE THING IS STUPID !
YOU DON'T PICK PEOPLE
YOU WANNA BE WITH
BY MAKING IT INTO A GAME !
EWW, SOMEBODY'S
A SORE LOSER !
CLYDE, I BELIEVE I SAID
GET THE FUDGE OUT,
WHICH MEANS KISS MY FUDGEN'
ASS, GO FUDGE YOURSELF,
WOULD YA GET THE
FUDGE OUT, CLYDE ?
HEY, BUTTERS.
OH, HEY, DOUGIE--
I MEAN--
MY NAME IS PROFESSOR CHAOS !
I SAW YOU CHANGE
IN THE SCHOOL BATHROOM.
YOU STOLE THAT ERASER
IN YOUR CLASS.
VERY WELL !
YOU CALLED OUT
PROFESSOR CHAOS,
AND YOU ALSO CALLED OUT
YOUR OWN DEMISE !
GO NOW, MY MINIONS !
GO AND TAKE THIS
FOOLISH MORTAL DOWN !
AW, MINIONS,
NOT THAT WAY.
COME BACK, MINIONS.
I'M NOT TRYING TO CALL YOU
OUT-- PROFESSOR CHAOS.
I WANT TO JOIN YOU.
JOIN ME ?
YEAH, I WANT TO JOIN YOU IN
YOUR CONQUEST OF DESTRUCTION.
BUT WHY ?
I'M AN OUTCAST TOO--
A FRAIL CHILD
CAST ASIDE BY SOCIETY.
I WANT TO FOLLOW YOU AND--
WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING.
VERY WELL, YOU SHALL BE
MY ACCOMPLICE IN EVIL.
TOGETHER, WE SHALL BRING
THE WORLD TO ITS KNEES
AND MAKE ALL THOSE WHO BANISHED
US FROM SOCIETY RUN WRECKED.
DO I GET A NEAT-O COSTUME MADE
OUT OF ALUMINUM FOIL TOO ?
WELL, SURE YOU DO.
I AM PROFESSOR AND
YOU SHALL BE MY GENERAL.
FROM NOW ON YOU ARE
GENERAL... DISARRAY.
GENERAL DISARRAY.
NOW LET US GO LOOK
FOR MY MINIONS !
BECAUSE THEY RAN AWAY...
THE SWIMSUIT COMPETITION
REALLY GAVE US A FRESH LOOK
AT SOME OF THE CANDIDATES.
WELL, I DON'T THINK
I DID TOO WELL
IN THE BATHING SUIT
COMPETITION.
BUT I CAN'T WAIT FOR THE
TALENT SHOW COMPETITION.
THAT'LL REALLY BE MY CHANCE
TO... SHINE.
WOW, WHAT A
TERRIFIC AUDIENCE.
SO ANYWAY,
A GUY WALKS INTO A B...
A GUY WALKS
INTO A B...
A GUY WALKS,
A GUYS WALK INTO A B-B...
( struggling to play intro
to "Stairway to Heaven" )
OKAY, WAIT.
NO, NO, WAIT.
NEXT, PLEASE.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO ?
ANYTHING THAT'LL
IMPRESS US, TOKEN.
IF YOU WERE OUR FRIEND,
HOW WOULD YOU KEEP US
ENTERTAINED ?
UH... OH, I KNOW !
VERY NICE.
I LIKE IT.
TOKEN WAS THE DEFINITE WINNER
OF THE TALENT SHOW.
BUT THEN WE DECIDED TO TAKE
EVERYONE TO A BASEBALL GAME,
TO SEE HOW WE
GOT ALONG THERE.
( announcer )
THERE GOES A HIT TO LEFT FIELD !
AND FOLEY'S GOING TO SCORE !
WOO-HOO !
YEAH !
ISN'T THIS GREAT ?
DRINKS !
GET YOUR DRINKS HERE !
YES, COULD I HAVE
SOME TEA, PLEASE ?
YOU DON'T DRINK TEA
AT A BASEBALL GAME,
YOU FRENCH
PIECE OF CRAP !
OH, VERY WELL--
JUST SOME
CRUMPETS THEN.
ALRIGHT,
THAT DOES IT !
PIP, GET THE
FUDGE OUT !
NEXT !
OKAY, LET'S TRY THIS.
HEY, WHAT'S WRONG
WITH THE JUMBOTRON ?
People of earth !
Your meaningless lives
are about to end !
I am Professor Chaos
and this is my partner in evil,
General Disarray.
In the past few days I have
rained terror down
upon the society
that shunned me,
and now it is time for
my final labor of loathing.
I am going to--
flood the world !
FLOOD THE WORLD !
MY GOD !
I DON'T WANNA DIE.
I DON'T WANNA DIE !
Oh yes, every living creature
and every sacred building
will soon be under leagues and
leagues of cold and dark water !
And there is nothing
you can do to stop it !
General Disarray, begin
the flooding of Earth !
You brought this
upon yourselves !
You made the outcasts
of the world.
Now watch, watch as your
precious planet drowns !
Watch !
DEAR CHRIST,
WHO WILL SAVE US ?
WE HAVE VERY LITTLE
TIME TO LIVE.
HOW SHALL WE SPEND OUR
LAST HOURS ON EARTH ?
OUR REIGN OF TERROR
IS COMPLETE !
THE TURMOIL HAS NOW
COME FULL CIRCLE !
HEY, IS THAT HOSE ON FULL,
GENERAL DISARRAY ?
IT'S ON ALL THE WAY.
OH, ALRIGHT THEN.
NOTHING TO DO NOW BUT
WATCH THE WORLD DIE !
HA, HA HA HAAA !
HA HA HAA !
BOY, THIS SURE IS
TAKING A LONG TIME.
OKAY, SO HOW DO
WE ALL FEEL
ABOUT TOWELIE
AS OUR NEW FRIEND ?
I THINK
TOWELIE'S AWESOME.
TOWELIE'S COOL, BUT HE GETS
STONED ALL THE TIME.
YOU CAN'T REALLY
RELY ON HIM FOR ANYTHING.
UGH, THIS IS GIVING ME
A HEADACHE.
NOW COME ON, YOU GUYS,
WE CAN'T TAKE THIS
DECISION LIGHTLY.
WHOEVER WE PICK
IS GOING TO BE THE PERSON
WE DO EVERYTHING WITH
FROM NOW ON.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WELL, HOW ABOUT TIMMY ?
HE'S QUIET AND HE TAKES
DIRECTION WELL.
REALLY, THE PERFECT FRIEND.
YEAH, BUT TIMMY CAN BE
REALLY SELF-CENTERED.
HOW ABOUT TOKEN ?
TOKEN'S A SMARTASS.
SO,
YOU'RE A SMARTASS.
YEAH, BUT DO WE REALLY
NEED ANOTHER ONE ?
GOOD POINT.
HEY, FELLAS, I WAS JUST
IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD,
AND THOUGHT I'D STOP BY
THIS GIFT BASKET.
OH, THANKS, JIMMY.
THERE'S SOME CHOCOLATES
AND LICORICE
AND SOME GAMES
AND PUZZLES INSIDE.
THAT'S GREAT.
COOL.
YEAH, WELL, I GUESS I'LL BE
SEEING YOU FRIENDS LATER.
ALRIGHT, JIMMY,
SEE YA.
SUCK UP.
NOT LONG NOW,
GENERAL DISARRAY,
AND OUR HORRIBLE PLAN
WILL BE COMPLETE.
HEY, DO YOU THINK MAYBE
WE SHOULD BUILD A BOAT ?
YOU KNOW, LIKE,
A LITTLE RAFT OR SOMETHING
SO THAT WHEN
THE WORLD FLOODS,
YOU AND ME AND
THE MINIONS CAN LIVE ?
OH YEAH, I HADN'T
THOUGHT OF THAT.
THAT'S A PRETTY GOOD IDEA.
I'LL GO GET A HAMMER.
HEY, WHO IS THAT ?
IS THIS IT ?
YEAH, 213,
THAT'S THE ONE.
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOIN' ?
AH !  YOU MAY HAVE
WON THIS TIME,
BUT I WILL BE BACK !
WHAT DO WE DO NOW ?
WELL, I HAD ANOTHER IDEA
OF HOW TO KILL THE WORLD.
I THOUGHT IT WAS ALMOST TOO
HORRIBLE TO EVEN SPEAK OF,
BUT NOW THEY'VE LEFT ME
WITH NO OTHER CHOICE !
WELL, THIS IS IT.
WE'VE MADE OUR FINAL DECISION,
AND ONE OF YOU,
IS WHO WE WILL SPENDING
OUR CHILDHOOD WITH,
AS OUR NEW FRIEND.
OH PLEASE...
OH GOD, PLEASE.
FOUR FRIENDS,
JUST ONE ROSE.
THE MOMENT OF TRUTH
IS HERE.
KYLE, WHO DOES
THE ROSE GO TO ?
THIS IS IT,
GENERAL DISARRAY--
MY FINAL SOLUTION.
WHAT EVIL PLOT DO YOU HAVE
THIS TIME, PROFESSOR CHAOS ?
SIMPLE, MY DEAR GENERAL.
WE ARE GOING TO TEAR DOWN THE
EARTH'S PRECIOUS ATMOSPHERE !
OH YES, MY LATEST PLAN
WILL MELT THE POLAR ICE CAPS
AND BURN ALL THE WORLD
WITH THE SUN'S HARMFUL RAYS.
SAY GOOD-BYE TO YOUR PRECIOUS
OZONE AND HELLO TO CHAOS !
( pssssssssssss )
OKAY, HAND ME ANOTHER ONE,
GENERAL DISARRAY.
AH HA HA,
HA HA HAA.
HA HA HA !
HAA HA HA HA HAA !
AH HA HA,
HA HA HA.
HA HA, HA HAA !
( announcer )
WILL PROFESSOR CHAOS'
LATEST PLOT SUCCEED
AND BE THE FINAL
UNDOING OF EARTH ?
AND WHICH BOY HAS BEEN CHOSEN TO
BE THE REPLACEMENT FOR KENNY ?
AND WHICH ONE OF THESE SIX
SOUTH PARK RESIDENTS WAS KILLED
AND WILL NEVER BE SEEN AGAIN ?
THE ANSWER TO THESE QUESTIONS
WILL BE ANSWERED... RIGHT NOW.
NO.
TWEEK.
MS. CHOKSONDIK.
www.tvsubtitles.net