1
00:00:01,610 --> 00:00:02,530
我們就在那里
So there we were,

2
00:00:02,970 --> 00:00:05,290
在沙漠里艱難行軍
scraping our sacks in the sandbox.

3
00:00:06,000 --> 00:00:07,970
沙丘之上的活靶子
Open targets in the dunes.

4
00:00:08,070 --> 00:00:10,710
我們都在流汗咒罵
All of us sweating and swearing.

5
00:00:10,730 --> 00:00:13,930
總比坐在方圓三十公里內荒無人煙的地方
Sure as hell beat sitting on our asses 30 clicks to nowhere

6
00:00:13,930 --> 00:00:15,980
等待有駝峰的朋友
waiting for our humpbacked friend

7
00:00:16,180 --> 00:00:18,110
拉出車鑰匙要好
to defecate the keys to our transport.

8
00:00:18,110 --> 00:00:19,530
駱駝不吃鑰匙
Camels don't eat keys.

9
00:00:19,530 --> 00:00:21,050
吃的  它吃了
They do, it did.

10
00:00:21,490 --> 00:00:22,780
而且拉出來了
And it shit it out.

11
00:00:24,250 --> 00:00:25,510
不騙你
I shit you not.

12
00:00:27,190 --> 00:00:28,540
你是個傻瓜
You're an idiot.

13
00:00:28,750 --> 00:00:30,000
我從來沒否認過
I've never denied it.

14
00:00:36,350 --> 00:00:37,770
美好新世界
Brave new world.

15
00:00:40,370 --> 00:00:43,010
我還是一直在想瑪姬懷孕的事
I still can't stop thinking about Maggie having a pup.

16
00:00:44,040 --> 00:00:44,930
在這種情況下
In this.

17
00:00:44,980 --> 00:00:46,220
怎么了
What about it?

18
00:00:47,180 --> 00:00:48,680
現在這種情況
You know, the way things go.

19
00:00:49,950 --> 00:00:51,090
什么壞事都有可能發生
The way they can.

20
00:00:53,770 --> 00:00:54,710
是啊
Yeah.

21
00:00:55,820 --> 00:00:57,030
也許這就是原因
Maybe that's why.

22
00:00:58,810 --> 00:01:00,390
因為現在這種情況
Because the way things go.

23
00:01:10,630 --> 00:01:12,340
你已經說我是傻瓜了
You already called me an idiot.

24
00:01:13,260 --> 00:01:14,430
我開玩笑的
Never had to.

25
00:01:16,620 --> 00:01:17,480
好吧
Yeah.

26
00:01:22,250 --> 00:01:23,400
明天見
I'll see you tomorrow.

27
00:01:24,410 --> 00:01:25,190
不
Nope.

28
00:01:26,490 --> 00:01:28,670
我
I'm, uh,

29
00:01:28,670 --> 00:01:30,360
要重新排班了
starting a new shift.

30
00:01:31,280 --> 00:01:33,040
巴格里那邊的崗哨
The watch post on baggarly.

31
00:01:35,450 --> 00:01:36,330
是嗎
That so?

32
00:01:37,620 --> 00:01:39,290
我和尤金談過了
Yeah, I already talked to Eugene.

33
00:01:39,310 --> 00:01:40,870
他想幫更多的忙
He wants to help out more.

34
00:01:41,150 --> 00:01:43,190
他說他會代替我跟你巡邏
Said he'd take over my patrol with you.

35
00:01:46,700 --> 00:01:47,770
太好了
How about that?

36
00:01:48,530 --> 00:01:50,170
-是啊  -是啊
- Yeah. - Yeah.

37
00:01:50,170 --> 00:01:51,140
太好了
How about that?

38
00:01:57,260 --> 00:01:58,130
回頭見吧
See you around?

39
00:01:58,940 --> 00:01:59,720
好
Yeah.

40
00:02:03,470 --> 00:02:04,330
好
Yeah.

41
00:02:05,900 --> 00:02:07,200
回頭見  亞伯拉罕
See you around, Abraham.

42
00:02:25,790 --> 00:02:27,550
亞伯拉罕
Hey, Abraham.

43
00:02:29,970 --> 00:02:31,020
你還好嗎
You're still here?

44
00:02:37,600 --> 00:02:39,730
你知道尤金要開始巡邏了嗎
You know Eugene's gonna start patrolling?

45
00:02:42,880 --> 00:02:45,530
他讓我教他怎么拆自動手槍
He asked me to teach him how to fieldstrip automatics.

46
00:02:46,690 --> 00:02:48,240
他要教我化學
He's gonna teach me chemistry.

47
00:02:51,480 --> 00:02:53,720
化學[反應]沒法教
You can't teach chemistry.

48
00:02:53,830 --> 00:02:55,510
-真的嗎  -是的
- Really? - Mm-mm.

49
00:03:03,910 --> 00:03:06,210
我的天啊
Sweet flaming mercy.

50
00:03:08,390 --> 00:03:12,380
那真是太棒了
That was just... beyond.

51
00:03:12,380 --> 00:03:14,050
是嗎
Mm-hmm. Oh, yeah?

52
00:03:31,780 --> 00:03:32,600
接住了
Catch.

53
00:03:37,400 --> 00:03:38,700
是油罐車上的
It's from the fuel truck.

54
00:03:39,620 --> 00:03:40,910
我打碎了一個剎車燈
Had to crack a brake light.

55
00:03:43,560 --> 00:03:44,620
這是你做的嗎
You made this?

56
00:03:45,240 --> 00:03:47,080
我覺得你的脖子看起來有些孤獨
Thought your neck looked a little lonely.

57
00:03:47,500 --> 00:03:49,280
羅西塔·埃斯皮諾薩
Rosita Espinosa,

58
00:03:51,200 --> 00:03:53,730
你真是太完美了  知道嗎
you are damn near perfection, you know that?

59
00:04:00,440 --> 00:04:01,330
戴上給我看看
Show me.

60
00:04:07,860 --> 00:04:08,830
去浴室
In the shower.

61
00:04:10,340 --> 00:04:11,380
馬上去
In a minute.

62
00:04:25,590 --> 00:04:55,590
m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10m -13 -14 l 13 -14 l 13 12 l -13 12 l -13 -14

63
00:04:25,590 --> 00:04:55,590
m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10

64
00:04:25,590 --> 00:04:55,590
m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10

65
00:04:25,590 --> 00:05:05,590
■

66
00:04:25,590 --> 00:04:30,590
本字幕首發于字幕組網站
www.ZiMuZu.tv 歡迎交流

67
00:04:30,590 --> 00:04:35,590
翻譯  冰藍 Reginamoon CS小明漫畫家

68
00:04:34,370 --> 00:04:35,170
瑪姬
Maggie.

69
00:04:35,590 --> 00:04:40,590
翻譯  艾瑞卡 小酸奶 送小孩 自然卷

70
00:04:39,370 --> 00:04:42,090
我們搭好棚架  就能垂直種植了
We get the trellises in, we can start going vertically.

71
00:04:40,590 --> 00:04:45,590
校對  冰藍 送小孩

72
00:04:42,730 --> 00:04:45,020
每平方英尺的西紅柿產量能翻番
Double our yield of tomatoes per square foot.

73
00:04:45,590 --> 00:04:50,590
時間軸  加森 雪貴人 濤濤

74
00:04:46,700 --> 00:04:48,960
定量配給撐不了太久
We can only keep stretching our rations so far.

75
00:04:50,590 --> 00:04:55,590
后期 吉吉 拉圖  總監 送小孩

76
00:04:54,180 --> 00:04:56,050
還是沒看見一顆小芽
Still haven't seen a single bud.

77
00:04:58,690 --> 00:04:59,470
親愛的
Babe.

78
00:05:00,920 --> 00:05:01,900
會長出來的
It'll grow.

79
00:05:03,480 --> 00:05:04,780
我們會沒事的
We're gonna be okay.

80
00:05:31,800 --> 00:05:33,560
你在我們家里做什么
What the hell are you doing in our house?

81
00:05:36,140 --> 00:05:38,570
我坐在臺階上
I'm, uh, sitting on the steps

82
00:05:38,900 --> 00:05:40,450
看著這幅畫
looking at this painting,

83
00:05:41,110 --> 00:05:43,260
等著你爸媽穿好衣服
Waiting for your mom and dad to get dressed.

84
00:05:45,980 --> 00:05:47,130
我是耶穌
I'm Jesus.

85
00:05:50,130 --> 00:05:52,920
卡爾
Carl, hey, um...

86
00:05:56,780 --> 00:05:58,000
沒事
It's-- it's okay.

87
00:05:59,540 --> 00:06:01,210
你說了我們該談談
You said we should talk.

88
00:06:02,640 --> 00:06:04,080
那就談吧
So let's talk.

89
00:06:05,650 --> 00:06:07,070
你怎么逃出來的
So, how'd you get out?

90
00:06:08,380 --> 00:06:10,360
一個守衛看不住兩個出口
One guard can't cover two exits

91
00:06:10,850 --> 00:06:12,380
或者三樓的窗戶
or third floor windows.

92
00:06:12,650 --> 00:06:14,780
解開繩結  撬開鎖
Knots untie and locks get picked.

93
00:06:14,780 --> 00:06:16,950
-熵來源于秩序  對吧  -對
- Entropy comes from order, right? - Right.

94
00:06:19,090 --> 00:06:20,730
我查看了你們的武器庫
I checked out your arsenal.

95
00:06:21,550 --> 00:06:23,890
很久沒有見過這么多武器了
I haven't seen anything like that in a long time.

96
00:06:24,040 --> 00:06:27,250
你們裝備精良  但是食物不足
You're well-equipped, but your provisions are low.

97
00:06:27,790 --> 00:06:29,750
不夠你們這么多人吃
Very low for the amount of people you have.

98
00:06:30,220 --> 00:06:32,370
-54個嗎  -更多
- 54? - More than that.

99
00:06:35,560 --> 00:06:37,070
餅干很好吃
Well, I appreciate the cookie.

100
00:06:37,090 --> 00:06:38,430
廚師手藝不錯
My compliments to the chef.

101
00:06:38,440 --> 00:06:39,420
她不在
Yeah, she ain't here.

102
00:06:41,320 --> 00:06:43,370
我們開局不順
Look, we got off to a bad start.

103
00:06:44,310 --> 00:06:48,020
但我們是站在同一邊的  生存的那一邊
But we're on the same side-- the living side.

104
00:06:49,610 --> 00:06:52,020
你和瑞克完全可以丟下我
You and Rick had every reason to leave me out there,

105
00:06:52,780 --> 00:06:53,730
但你們沒有
but you didn't.

106
00:06:55,070 --> 00:06:57,290
我來自的地方和這里很像
I'm from a place that's a lot like this one.

107
00:06:58,210 --> 00:07:01,240
我的工作之一就是尋找其他可以做交易的營地
Part of my job is searching out other settlements to trade with.

108
00:07:01,410 --> 00:07:03,250
我開走了你們的車  
I took your truck because

109
00:07:03,320 --> 00:07:05,130
是因為我的社區需要東西
my community needs things,

110
00:07:05,480 --> 00:07:07,250
而你倆看起來都不像好人
and both of you looked like trouble.

111
00:07:08,390 --> 00:07:09,400
我錯了
I was wrong.

112
00:07:10,500 --> 00:07:11,630
你們是好人
You're good people.

113
00:07:12,090 --> 00:07:13,530
這里是個好地方
And this is a good place.

114
00:07:14,570 --> 00:07:17,120
我覺得我們兩邊可以互相幫助
I think our communities may be in a position to help each other.

115
00:07:17,450 --> 00:07:18,600
你們有食物嗎
Do you have food?

116
00:07:18,680 --> 00:07:20,310
我們飼養牲畜
We've started to raise livestock.

117
00:07:20,330 --> 00:07:22,200
尋找補給  種地
We scavenge, we grow.

118
00:07:22,740 --> 00:07:24,740
從西紅柿到高粱應有盡有
Everything from tomatoes to sorghum.

119
00:07:24,740 --> 00:07:26,660
告訴我們為什么要相信你
Tell us why we should believe you.

120
00:07:26,940 --> 00:07:27,870
我可以帶你們去看
I'll show you.

121
00:07:27,960 --> 00:07:30,440
如果我們開車  一天內就能回我家
If we take a car, I can take you back home in a day,

122
00:07:30,730 --> 00:07:32,180
你們可以自己看看
and you can all see for yourselves

123
00:07:32,180 --> 00:07:33,900
我們是什么人  可以提供什么
who we are and what we have to offer.

124
00:07:34,400 --> 00:07:37,530
等等  你在尋找更多營地
Wait, you're looking for more settlements.

125
00:07:37,970 --> 00:07:40,240
意思是你們已經和別的團體交易了嗎
You mean you're already trading with other groups?

126
00:07:44,330 --> 00:07:46,450
你們的世界即將變得更廣闊
Your world's about to get a whole lot bigger.

127
00:08:19,970 --> 00:08:24,180
本藍光版外掛字幕由  風吹來的那片云  用WEB版調軸

128
00:08:19,970 --> 00:08:24,180
行尸走肉
『第六季  第十一集』

129
00:08:32,580 --> 00:08:35,300
給  自制的燕麥蛋糕
Homemade oat cake.

130
00:08:35,700 --> 00:08:38,060
復合碳水化合物  含有歐米伽3脂肪酸
Complex carbohydrates, omega-3s.

131
00:08:38,130 --> 00:08:40,100
不  我不要
Nah, I'm good.

132
00:08:40,530 --> 00:08:43,640
我們路上要停車  到時候我再找吃的
We're gonna make a pit stop. I'll pick up something then.

133
00:08:44,550 --> 00:08:45,840
你想染上狂犬病嗎
Like rabies?

134
00:08:49,060 --> 00:08:50,870
這是因為我想給你弄到汽水嗎
Is this 'cause I tried to get you that stuff?

135
00:08:51,570 --> 00:08:52,340
是的
Yeah.

136
00:08:53,910 --> 00:08:55,870
還有你讓我想到了我以前認識的某人
And you remind me of someone I used to know.

137
00:08:59,730 --> 00:09:00,520
好吧
Well...

138
00:09:01,220 --> 00:09:02,830
希望要比看起來好吃
I hope it tastes better than it looks.

139
00:09:03,480 --> 00:09:04,710
因為看起來跟屎一樣
'Cause it looks like shit.

140
00:09:05,300 --> 00:09:06,990
屎也比路上的死動物要好
Shit's still better than roadkill.

141
00:09:07,940 --> 00:09:09,830
好吧  也許  吃了吧
Okay, maybe-- just eat it.

142
00:09:17,400 --> 00:09:18,230
你確定嗎
You sure?

143
00:09:19,050 --> 00:09:19,850
不
No.

144
00:09:20,720 --> 00:09:22,470
但如果他說的是真話
But if he's telling the truth,

145
00:09:22,470 --> 00:09:24,260
這可能是新生活的開始
this could be the start of everything.

146
00:09:30,180 --> 00:09:32,410
我打算跟你說我和米瓊恩的事
Look, I was gonna tell you about me and Michonne,

147
00:09:32,410 --> 00:09:34,750
但這事剛發生
but it just happened.

148
00:09:34,750 --> 00:09:36,780
這事剛發生
It just happened.

149
00:09:37,400 --> 00:09:38,360
就在昨晚
Last night.

150
00:09:44,310 --> 00:09:46,050
這次不一樣
This is-- this is different.

151
00:09:47,850 --> 00:09:48,660
沒事
It's cool.

152
00:09:51,040 --> 00:09:51,780
好吧
All right.

153
00:09:52,190 --> 00:09:53,820
拿上你的東西
Well, get your stuff.

154
00:09:55,190 --> 00:09:57,530
我們離開時加百利能照顧朱迪思
Gabriel can take care of Judith while we're gone.

155
00:09:57,530 --> 00:09:58,720
我不去
No, I'm not coming.

156
00:10:00,730 --> 00:10:03,710
得有人留在家里  保護這里
Someone's gotta stay back, keep this place safe.

157
00:10:04,740 --> 00:10:06,230
反正一個毀了容的小孩八成也不能
A kid with a messed-up face probably wouldn't make

158
00:10:06,230 --> 00:10:07,890
給人留下多好的第一印象
the best first impression anyway.

159
00:10:22,440 --> 00:10:24,100
我們上路吧
Let's chew up some asphalt!

160
00:11:00,030 --> 00:11:01,230
我能問你個問題嗎
Can I ask you a question?

161
00:11:02,360 --> 00:11:03,160
當然
Sure.

162
00:11:09,580 --> 00:11:13,460
當你倒松餅粉時
When you were, uh, pouring the bisquick,

163
00:11:14,690 --> 00:11:16,270
你是想做松餅嗎[懷孕]
were you trying to make pancakes?

164
00:11:20,040 --> 00:11:21,540
是的吧
Yes?

165
00:11:23,370 --> 00:11:25,030
我懂了
Oh, okay, um...

166
00:11:27,380 --> 00:11:30,600
我們之前談論過
It's something that we talked about, yeah.

167
00:11:30,820 --> 00:11:32,080
-是啊  -為什么問
- Yeah. - Why?

168
00:11:32,570 --> 00:11:33,620
沒什么  我只是...
No, I just...

169
00:11:35,980 --> 00:11:42,320
在這種朝不保夕的情況下
Well, given the precarious state of affairs on any given Sunday,

170
00:11:43,800 --> 00:11:46,970
我他媽真的是被你們這些有膽量
I am damn near floored that you or anyone else

171
00:11:46,970 --> 00:11:49,340
做出這種決定的人嚇到了
would have the cojones to make a call like that.

172
00:11:49,480 --> 00:11:50,490
我...
I mean, well...

173
00:11:52,120 --> 00:11:55,430
我們試圖營造一些東西  我和她
we're trying to build something, me and her.

174
00:11:56,520 --> 00:11:57,550
我們所有人
All of us.

175
00:12:01,660 --> 00:12:02,790
聲明一下
For the record,

176
00:12:03,360 --> 00:12:05,750
我一旦看到要下雨  就會穿膠鞋
I see rain coming, I'm wearing galoshes.

177
00:12:09,230 --> 00:12:10,350
我穿兩雙
I double up.

178
00:12:32,630 --> 00:12:34,720
瑞克  怎么了
Yo, Rick. What's going on?

179
00:12:34,720 --> 00:12:36,500
前面出車禍了
We got a crash ahead.

180
00:12:36,960 --> 00:12:38,630
看著像是剛剛發生的
Looks like it just happened.

181
00:12:43,150 --> 00:12:44,340
是我們的人
It's one of ours.

182
00:13:05,430 --> 00:13:08,880
假如這是個陷阱  你不會有好下場的
If this is a trick, it won't end well for you.

183
00:13:08,930 --> 00:13:10,260
我的人遇到麻煩了
My people are in trouble.

184
00:13:10,480 --> 00:13:13,930
他們不...  我們之中沒有多少戰士
They don't-- we don't have a lot of fighters.

185
00:13:15,050 --> 00:13:17,550
我知道這看起來有詐  但我會乖乖的
I know how it looks, but I'll play it out.

186
00:13:17,550 --> 00:13:18,480
能借我一把槍嗎
Can I borrow a gun?

187
00:13:18,480 --> 00:13:19,270
不行
No.

188
00:13:20,330 --> 00:13:21,560
這里有痕跡
We got tracks right here.

189
00:13:26,090 --> 00:13:27,120
他們一定是在里面
They gotta be in there.

190
00:13:30,100 --> 00:13:31,480
我們是進去還是怎樣
We moving in or what?

191
00:13:31,970 --> 00:13:34,300
我們怎么知道這會不會是陷阱
How do we know this ain't firecrackers in a trash can?

192
00:13:34,300 --> 00:13:35,400
你們不知道
You don't.

193
00:13:35,780 --> 00:13:37,280
我們會把你的人救出來
We'll get your people.

194
00:13:38,510 --> 00:13:40,580
你和我們中的一個留在這里
You're staying here with one of us.

195
00:13:42,800 --> 00:13:43,950
這是條件
That's the deal.

196
00:13:44,250 --> 00:13:45,690
-你留下好嗎  -好的
- Will you stay? - Yeah.

197
00:13:46,110 --> 00:13:48,130
你們去吧  千萬小心
Y'all go. Just be careful.

198
00:13:48,130 --> 00:13:49,090
好的
Yeah.

199
00:13:49,560 --> 00:13:51,160
我們會很小心的
We're gonna be careful.

200
00:13:52,160 --> 00:13:53,330
快點吧
Just hurry.

201
00:13:55,470 --> 00:13:57,830
我一吹口哨  你就殺了他
You hear me whistle, shoot him.

202
00:13:57,830 --> 00:13:58,700
我會的
I will.

203
00:14:45,300 --> 00:14:47,590
出來吧  我們不會傷害你們
Come on out. We're not gonna hurt you.

204
00:14:47,740 --> 00:14:49,040
我們是耶穌的朋友
We're friends of Jesus.

205
00:14:49,270 --> 00:14:50,300
我們是來救你們出去的
We're here to get you out.

206
00:14:50,300 --> 00:14:51,330
還有人嗎
There more of you?

207
00:14:51,330 --> 00:14:52,770
還有兩個  他們跑到前面去了
Two more. They ran ahead.

208
00:15:13,460 --> 00:15:14,170
來吧
Come on.

209
00:15:14,780 --> 00:15:16,250
我們是耶穌的朋友  走吧
We're with Jesus. Let's go.

210
00:15:16,710 --> 00:15:19,280
我不能和你們走  我在找我的朋友
I can't go with you. I'm looking for my friend.

211
00:15:19,280 --> 00:15:22,200
他就在附近  還在車禍中受了傷
He's close, and he's hurt from the crash.

212
00:15:27,320 --> 00:15:28,880
不
No!

213
00:15:42,670 --> 00:15:43,990
快  伙計  我們撤
Come on, man, let's go.

214
00:15:44,210 --> 00:15:44,970
走吧
Come on!

215
00:15:46,100 --> 00:15:47,590
-扶住了嗎  -走
- You got him? - Go.

216
00:15:47,650 --> 00:15:49,470
走吧  走吧
Come on. Come on.

217
00:16:02,880 --> 00:16:04,370
順便說句  我叫哈蘭
Name's Harlan, by the way.

218
00:16:05,340 --> 00:16:06,270
瑪姬
Maggie.

219
00:16:09,250 --> 00:16:10,840
那是我丈夫  格倫
That's my husband, Glenn.

220
00:16:12,120 --> 00:16:13,340
我們正要把藥品帶回去
We're bringing back medication,

221
00:16:13,340 --> 00:16:16,750
所以你救下的人可能不止我們  格倫
so you may have saved more people than just us back there, Glenn.

222
00:16:18,820 --> 00:16:19,950
你是醫生嗎
You're a doctor?

223
00:16:20,610 --> 00:16:21,750
是的  沒錯
Yeah, that's right.

224
00:16:22,630 --> 00:16:24,700
你那里有孕期維生素嗎
You have any prenatal vitamins in there?

225
00:16:29,430 --> 00:16:30,260
給你用的
For you?

226
00:16:32,780 --> 00:16:36,400
我之前是婦產科醫生
Well, uh, I was an obstetrician before,

227
00:16:36,720 --> 00:16:38,630
而且我絕對欠你們人情
and I most definitely owe you.

228
00:16:39,030 --> 00:16:42,570
所以  我會說你們倆中了頭彩
So, I'd say you two just hit the jackpot.

229
00:16:55,430 --> 00:16:56,580
你還好嗎  弗萊迪
You okay, Freddie?

230
00:17:01,760 --> 00:17:03,360
剛才
For a second back there,

231
00:17:04,640 --> 00:17:07,580
當我以為他就要...
just when I thought he was gonna...

232
00:17:09,850 --> 00:17:11,310
我看到了我妻子
I saw my wife.

233
00:17:11,670 --> 00:17:13,530
災變之前她就去世了
She died before all this.

234
00:17:14,540 --> 00:17:16,320
正當我以為我死定了的時候
Just when I thought it was over,

235
00:17:17,480 --> 00:17:18,660
我看到了她
there she was.

236
00:17:20,910 --> 00:17:22,240
一清二楚
Clear as day.

237
00:17:44,710 --> 00:17:45,770
該死
Damn it.

238
00:17:48,540 --> 00:17:50,770
肯定是剛下過暴風雨
A storm must've passed through.

239
00:17:51,240 --> 00:17:52,520
我們被困住了
We're stuck.

240
00:17:53,290 --> 00:17:54,510
別擔心
No worries.

241
00:17:55,370 --> 00:17:56,270
已經到了
We're here.

242
00:18:10,150 --> 00:18:11,210
就在那
That's us.

243
00:18:12,660 --> 00:18:13,890
那就是山頂寨
That's the Hilltop.

244
00:18:52,300 --> 00:18:53,430
站住
Stop right there.

245
00:18:55,020 --> 00:18:55,910
你想逼我們停嗎
You gonna make us?

246
00:18:55,910 --> 00:18:57,530
耶穌  這是怎么回事
Jesus, what the hell is this?

247
00:18:57,540 --> 00:18:58,940
把門打開  卡奧
Open the gates, Cal.

248
00:18:59,730 --> 00:19:00,800
弗萊迪受傷了
Freddie's hurt.

249
00:19:01,610 --> 00:19:03,080
聽著  我為他們道歉
Look, sorry about these guys.

250
00:19:03,080 --> 00:19:05,860
他們一整天站在那里無所事事  有點焦躁
They get antsy standing up there all day doing nothing.

251
00:19:05,860 --> 00:19:08,460
他們必須交出武器  然后我們才會開門
They give up the weapons. Then we'll open the gates.

252
00:19:08,460 --> 00:19:09,570
你干嘛不下來自己拿
Why don't you come down here and get 'em?

253
00:19:09,570 --> 00:19:12,690
先生們  我們為這些人擔保  好嗎
Gentlemen, look, we vouch for these people, all right?

254
00:19:12,690 --> 00:19:14,260
是他們救了我們
They saved us out there.

255
00:19:14,400 --> 00:19:16,230
別舉著矛了
Lower the spears.

256
00:19:16,230 --> 00:19:17,850
聽著  我可不想冒險
Look, I'm not taking any chances.

257
00:19:17,850 --> 00:19:20,560
-還是讓那位格雷戈里出來吧  -不
- Tell your guy Gregory to come out here.- No.

258
00:19:21,200 --> 00:19:22,770
你沒看到剛發生了什么嗎
Don't you see what just happened?

259
00:19:24,060 --> 00:19:25,950
我同意你們保留武器
I'm letting you keep your guns.

260
00:19:26,950 --> 00:19:29,030
聽著  幾個月前我們就沒有彈藥了
Look, we ran out of ammo months ago.

261
00:19:31,220 --> 00:19:32,570
我挺喜歡你們的
I like you people.

262
00:19:34,190 --> 00:19:35,340
我相信你們
I trust you.

263
00:19:37,600 --> 00:19:38,850
也請相信我們
Trust us.

264
00:19:52,800 --> 00:19:54,200
開門  卡奧
Open the gates, Cal.

265
00:20:31,970 --> 00:20:33,000
再次感謝
Thanks again.

266
00:20:33,910 --> 00:20:34,930
隨時可以來找我
Come see me whenever.

267
00:20:34,940 --> 00:20:37,310
我就在醫療拖車里  好嗎
I'm just over here in the medical trailer, okay?

268
00:20:37,830 --> 00:20:38,560
好
Ok.

269
00:20:54,090 --> 00:20:57,200
這曾是附近一家電力公司的材料場
There was a materials yard for a power company nearby.

270
00:20:57,750 --> 00:20:59,390
所以我們才能建起高墻
That's how we put up the walls.

271
00:21:01,010 --> 00:21:03,270
很多人都是從應急營地來的
A lot of people came from a FEMA camp.

272
00:21:03,270 --> 00:21:04,630
他們帶來了拖車
Trailers came with them.

273
00:21:05,800 --> 00:21:07,940
人們是怎么找到這里的
How did people find out about this place?

274
00:21:09,170 --> 00:21:11,440
那地方叫巴林頓公館
That's called Barrington House.

275
00:21:11,980 --> 00:21:15,150
三十年代  這家的主人把它捐給了州里
The family that owned it gave it to the state in the '30s.

276
00:21:15,290 --> 00:21:19,020
州里又把它改造成了生活史博物館
The state turned it into a Living History Museum.

277
00:21:19,120 --> 00:21:20,020
五十英里內的所有小學
Every elementary school for

278
00:21:20,020 --> 00:21:23,060
都讓學生來這里參觀過
50 miles used to come here for field trips.

279
00:21:23,580 --> 00:21:24,820
現代社會建立之前
The place was running a long time

280
00:21:24,820 --> 00:21:27,110
它就已經運轉了很長時間
before the modern world built up around it.

281
00:21:28,240 --> 00:21:29,960
我想人們之所以會來  是因為
I think people came here because

282
00:21:29,970 --> 00:21:32,700
他們想著現代社會毀滅之后它仍會繼續
they figured it'd keep running after the modern world broke down.

283
00:21:34,340 --> 00:21:37,670
我們可以從那些窗戶看到數英里之外的各個方向
Those windows up there let us see for miles in every direction.

284
00:21:38,020 --> 00:21:39,520
能保證安全
It's perfect for security.

285
00:21:40,640 --> 00:21:42,810
來吧  我帶你們看看里面
Come on. I'll show you inside.

286
00:22:06,790 --> 00:22:09,630
我的老天爺啊
Good gracious, Ignatius.

287
00:22:09,630 --> 00:22:12,470
多數房間已經被改造成起居室了
Most of the rooms have been converted to living spaces.

288
00:22:13,300 --> 00:22:15,250
就連曾經不是臥房的也改了
Even the ones that weren't bedrooms.

289
00:22:15,550 --> 00:22:17,830
人們住在這里和拖車里
People live here and the trailers?

290
00:22:18,160 --> 00:22:19,520
我們還計劃多建些房屋
We plan to build.

291
00:22:20,840 --> 00:22:22,490
有孩子在這里出生
There's babies being born.

292
00:22:24,350 --> 00:22:25,660
耶穌
Jesus.

293
00:22:26,100 --> 00:22:27,530
你回來了
You're back.

294
00:22:29,740 --> 00:22:31,340
還帶了客人
With guests.

295
00:22:31,340 --> 00:22:33,770
各位  這位是格雷戈里
Everyone, this is Gregory.

296
00:22:34,290 --> 00:22:36,320
他讓這里正常運轉
He keeps the trains running on time around here.

297
00:22:36,330 --> 00:22:37,880
我是頭兒
I'm the boss.

298
00:22:39,640 --> 00:22:41,010
我叫瑞克  我們有個社區...
Well, I'm Rick. We have a community...

299
00:22:41,010 --> 00:22:43,070
你們為何不去清理一下
Why don't y'all go get cleaned up?

300
00:22:48,040 --> 00:22:49,200
不用了
We're fine.

301
00:22:49,640 --> 00:22:52,340
耶穌會帶你們去洗澡的地方
Jesus will show you where you can get washed up.

302
00:22:52,340 --> 00:22:54,200
搞干凈了再下來
Then come back down here when you're ready.

303
00:22:55,700 --> 00:22:58,060
這地方不容易保潔
It's hard to keep this place clean.

304
00:22:59,370 --> 00:23:01,470
好的  可以
Yeah. Sure.

305
00:23:05,200 --> 00:23:06,230
跟我來
Follow me.

306
00:23:13,330 --> 00:23:16,140
你先洗  你跟他談
You clean up first. You talk to him.

307
00:23:16,250 --> 00:23:17,090
為什么
Why?

308
00:23:17,870 --> 00:23:19,130
不該我來
I shouldn't.

309
00:23:19,620 --> 00:23:21,820
你也要開始和人談判了
And you gotta start doing these things.

310
00:23:47,610 --> 00:23:50,940
你覺得瑞克和米瓊恩搞在一起多長時間了
How long do you think Rick and Michonne been ugging bumplies?

311
00:23:51,930 --> 00:23:53,000
不知道
I don't know.

312
00:23:55,500 --> 00:23:57,030
你想過嗎
You ever think about it?

313
00:23:59,310 --> 00:24:00,440
安定下來
Settling down?

314
00:24:02,800 --> 00:24:04,450
你覺得有可能安定嗎
You think shit's settled?

315
00:24:24,080 --> 00:24:25,060
格雷戈里
Gregory.

316
00:24:25,260 --> 00:24:27,350
-娜塔莉是嗎  -是瑪姬
- Natalie, right? - Maggie.

317
00:24:27,590 --> 00:24:28,870
沒啥區別
That's pretty close.

318
00:24:29,290 --> 00:24:30,340
還是有的
Not really.

319
00:24:31,060 --> 00:24:34,100
有一說一  我喜歡
She calls them like she sees them. I like that.

320
00:24:34,920 --> 00:24:36,290
請進  我們談談
Come in, let's chat.

321
00:24:43,510 --> 00:24:44,460
好了
Yeah.

322
00:24:44,530 --> 00:24:47,860
我以前來過這里一次
I-- I came to this place once before,

323
00:24:47,860 --> 00:24:49,790
那時還是個博物館
when it was a museum,

324
00:24:49,790 --> 00:24:53,080
因為商會的事
this, um, Chamber of Commerce thing.

325
00:24:55,860 --> 00:24:57,600
我喜歡這幅畫
Love that painting.

326
00:24:58,280 --> 00:25:01,110
我從沒想過會是我的
I never figured it'd be mine,

327
00:25:01,900 --> 00:25:03,180
但現在就在眼前
here it is.

328
00:25:04,010 --> 00:25:06,680
就像它一直在等著我一樣
It's like it was waiting for me the whole time.

329
00:25:17,990 --> 00:25:21,150
耶穌告訴我  你們救了卡森醫生
Jesus told me your group saved Dr. Carson.

330
00:25:21,150 --> 00:25:23,690
顯然現如今醫生是稀缺資源了
Obviously, a doctor's a rare commodity today,

331
00:25:23,690 --> 00:25:25,460
所以感謝你們帶他回來
so I want to thank you for bringing ours back.

332
00:25:25,460 --> 00:25:26,980
是我丈夫救了他
My husband saved him.

333
00:25:27,540 --> 00:25:29,250
也同樣感謝他
I'll be sure to thank him, too.

334
00:25:29,970 --> 00:25:32,960
你擁有的這地方
This place, what you have here,

335
00:25:33,330 --> 00:25:35,270
-一開始就這樣嗎  -沒錯
- has been here since the start? -That's right.

336
00:25:35,350 --> 00:25:39,840
那你們是怎么活下來的
And how-- how is it-- how have you survived here?

337
00:25:39,840 --> 00:25:42,470
就像這樣  只能說我擅長此道
You're looking at how. I'm good at this.

338
00:25:43,100 --> 00:25:45,390
而且我不拘泥于細節
And I don't get hung up on the details.

339
00:25:46,100 --> 00:25:48,870
你們住的地方和山頂寨一樣好嗎
Where you live, is it as nice as the Hilltop Colony?

340
00:25:48,870 --> 00:25:49,890
不一樣
It's just different.

341
00:25:49,890 --> 00:25:51,340
你怎么保證食物供給
How do you feed everyone?

342
00:25:51,350 --> 00:25:54,710
耶穌說你們有菜園  但沒有莊稼
Jesus said you had land for gardens, but no crops.

343
00:25:54,710 --> 00:25:56,230
我們才開始種植
We just started planting.

344
00:25:56,230 --> 00:25:58,560
-種什么  -黃瓜  西紅柿
- Planting what? - Cucumbers, tomatoes.

345
00:25:58,560 --> 00:26:02,580
莊稼指的是大豆  玉米  麻類  高粱
Oh, crops-- soy, corn, hemp, sorghum.

346
00:26:02,580 --> 00:26:04,960
-我們種蔬果  -但你們有槍
- Garden stuff. - But you have guns,

347
00:26:04,960 --> 00:26:07,640
我猜你們有不少武器庫存
so I assume you have a decent weapons cache.

348
00:26:07,640 --> 00:26:08,850
確實不少
It's decent.

349
00:26:09,190 --> 00:26:12,050
那你們的醫務室  醫療用品充足嗎
And your infirmary, is it stocked?

350
00:26:12,050 --> 00:26:13,690
你們的充足嗎
Is yours?

351
00:26:14,530 --> 00:26:16,770
我們是來談交易的
We came here hoping to talk trade.

352
00:26:17,200 --> 00:26:18,860
你有足夠的資源嗎
Do you have enough here for that?

353
00:26:20,510 --> 00:26:21,830
你能看到我有什么
You see what I have here.

354
00:26:21,830 --> 00:26:23,290
你能看到我建立了什么
You see what I've built.

355
00:26:25,160 --> 00:26:30,140
耶穌說你們的食物狀況不容樂觀
Jesus said that your food situation was challenged right now.

356
00:26:31,890 --> 00:26:34,700
如果人們吃不飽  一切就會崩潰
You don't keep people fed, it comes apart.

357
00:26:36,090 --> 00:26:38,350
別繞彎子了好嗎
Let's speak the common tongue here, huh?

358
00:26:39,330 --> 00:26:40,890
你們屁都沒有
You don't have shit.

359
00:26:41,120 --> 00:26:43,840
我很樂意幫忙  我是個好人
Now, I'm happy to help. I'm a nice guy.

360
00:26:44,370 --> 00:26:46,730
但我們不能白給
But we can't just give things away for free.

361
00:26:48,670 --> 00:26:49,720
不如這樣
How's this?

362
00:26:50,560 --> 00:26:51,940
既然你們沒什么物資
Since you can't offer much,

363
00:26:51,940 --> 00:26:54,260
我就讓你們的人在這里用勞動交換
I'll let your people work here for their share.

364
00:26:54,700 --> 00:26:56,960
這個社區很歡迎你這樣的人
You'd be a welcome addition to the community,

365
00:26:57,030 --> 00:26:59,350
一位聰明美麗的女士
a smart and beautiful woman.

366
00:26:59,660 --> 00:27:02,070
話說回來
Getting back to that common tongue,

367
00:27:03,020 --> 00:27:05,320
我告訴你  我會讓你覺得物超所值的
I can tell ya, I can make it worth your while.

368
00:27:05,320 --> 00:27:07,510
-給我打住  -聽著  親愛的
- Let me stop you right there. - Listen, honey.

369
00:27:07,510 --> 00:27:10,620
不要叫我親愛的來騷擾我
Stop coming on to me with calling me honey.

370
00:27:11,420 --> 00:27:13,410
你們一點彈藥都沒有
You don't have any ammunition.

371
00:27:13,470 --> 00:27:14,370
誰說的
Who said that?

372
00:27:14,370 --> 00:27:15,900
你們藥物不足
You're low on medication.

373
00:27:16,780 --> 00:27:19,350
我們雙方都有需要的東西
You need things. We need things.

374
00:27:19,350 --> 00:27:22,130
所以你們要給我們一瓶阿司匹林和一盒子彈嗎
What, are you gonna give us a bottle of aspirin and a box of bullets?

375
00:27:22,130 --> 00:27:24,240
我們兩個社區能互相幫助
Our communities can help each other.

376
00:27:26,400 --> 00:27:28,660
謝謝  娜塔莉  談得很愉快
Thank you, Natalie. Been a good talk.

377
00:27:33,710 --> 00:27:35,340
我們能互相幫助
We can help each other.

378
00:27:35,580 --> 00:27:37,310
我們現在過得挺好
We're doing fine.

379
00:27:37,850 --> 00:27:39,130
你們呢
Are you?

380
00:27:50,120 --> 00:27:52,760
我們想要交易  格雷戈里想要交易
We want to generate trade. Gregory does.

381
00:27:52,800 --> 00:27:54,860
但是子彈不是我們迫切所需的
But ammo isn't something we urgently need.

382
00:27:54,860 --> 00:27:56,960
-為什么  -墻還能撐著
- Well, how's that? - The walls hold.

383
00:27:56,960 --> 00:27:58,580
我們剛帶回來了更多藥物
We just brought in more medicine.

384
00:27:58,930 --> 00:28:00,560
格雷戈里想要最好的交易
Gregory wants the best deal possible.

385
00:28:00,560 --> 00:28:03,240
我們也有想要的東西
Yeah, well, we want things, too.

386
00:28:03,240 --> 00:28:04,590
我們需要食物
We need food.

387
00:28:05,030 --> 00:28:07,380
我們大老遠來  必須拿到
We came all this way, we're gonna get it.

388
00:28:09,630 --> 00:28:11,310
我會跟他談
I will talk to him

389
00:28:11,930 --> 00:28:14,030
我們能解決的
and we will work this out.

390
00:28:16,110 --> 00:28:17,920
情況變了
Circumstances change.

391
00:28:17,920 --> 00:28:21,510
我們現在過得不錯  你們以后也會的
We're doing well now, and you will next.

392
00:28:22,270 --> 00:28:24,630
我會讓他理解這點
I will make him understand that.

393
00:28:25,480 --> 00:28:27,200
能再給我幾天時間嗎
Can you give me a few days?

394
00:28:31,470 --> 00:28:32,820
可以
We can.

395
00:28:38,650 --> 00:28:39,870
好的
Yeah.

396
00:28:48,580 --> 00:28:49,850
出什么事了
What's wrong?

397
00:28:49,960 --> 00:28:51,270
他們回來了
They're back.

398
00:29:04,460 --> 00:29:06,890
內森  其他人呢
Nathan, what happened to everybody else?

399
00:29:06,890 --> 00:29:09,480
蒂姆和瑪莎呢
Where's Tim and Marsha?

400
00:29:09,480 --> 00:29:10,840
他們死了
They're dead.

401
00:29:13,320 --> 00:29:15,320
-尼根干的嗎  -是的
- Negan? - Yeah.

402
00:29:16,310 --> 00:29:19,350
-我們有約在先的  -他說那不夠
- We had a deal. - He said it wasn't enough.

403
00:29:20,070 --> 00:29:21,710
貢品少了嗎
Was the drop light?

404
00:29:21,990 --> 00:29:23,270
沒有
No.

405
00:29:23,460 --> 00:29:24,940
克雷格還在他們手上
They still have Craig.

406
00:29:24,940 --> 00:29:28,450
他們說會留他一命  把他還給我們
They said they'd keep him alive, return him to us,

407
00:29:29,580 --> 00:29:31,290
只要我給你帶個信
if I deliver a message to you.

408
00:29:31,780 --> 00:29:33,280
說吧
So, tell me.

409
00:29:34,700 --> 00:29:36,010
對不起
I'm sorry.

410
00:29:39,890 --> 00:29:42,600
放開我  我必須這么做
Get off of me! I had to!

411
00:30:03,170 --> 00:30:04,570
也許這就是原因
Maybe that's why.

412
00:30:04,920 --> 00:30:06,780
因為現在這種情況
Because the way things go.

413
00:30:12,690 --> 00:30:13,610
住手
Hey!

414
00:30:13,680 --> 00:30:16,010
退后  誰攔著我
Stay back! Anybody who tries to stop me

415
00:30:16,010 --> 00:30:17,480
就是想害死我兄弟
is killing my brother!

416
00:30:21,810 --> 00:30:23,000
放下
Drop it.

417
00:30:49,490 --> 00:30:50,800
怎么了
What?

418
00:30:51,430 --> 00:30:54,580
內森  你殺了他
Nathan! You killed him.

419
00:30:54,580 --> 00:30:56,990
他想殺格雷戈里  然后殺我
He tried to kill Gregory, then me.

420
00:31:00,690 --> 00:31:01,690
別
Don't.

421
00:31:02,380 --> 00:31:03,710
放下武器
Drop it now!

422
00:31:04,610 --> 00:31:05,940
我覺得我不會
I don't think I will.

423
00:31:05,940 --> 00:31:08,590
大家聽著  都結束了
Everyone, this is over!

424
00:31:10,350 --> 00:31:11,660
結束了
It's over.

425
00:31:11,950 --> 00:31:15,580
內森是我們的朋友  但別忘了
Nathan was our friend, but let's not pretend

426
00:31:15,580 --> 00:31:18,580
他也是想襲擊我們的懦夫
he was anything more than a coward who attacked us.

427
00:31:18,740 --> 00:31:20,400
是他起的頭
He did this.

428
00:31:22,290 --> 00:31:23,920
而這些人制止了他
And these people stopped him.

429
00:31:31,550 --> 00:31:32,960
我該怎么做
What can I do?

430
00:31:33,660 --> 00:31:35,200
把槍拿開
Put the gun away.

431
00:31:36,390 --> 00:31:37,650
你做的夠多了
You've done enough.

432
00:31:42,070 --> 00:31:43,340
你得知道
You need to know

433
00:31:43,960 --> 00:31:46,100
事情沒你想象的那么簡單
that things aren't as simple as they might seem.

434
00:31:48,610 --> 00:31:50,140
給我點時間
Just give me some time.

435
00:32:04,020 --> 00:32:05,550
老兄
Hey, man.

436
00:32:06,140 --> 00:32:07,300
你還好吧
You good?

437
00:32:07,770 --> 00:32:08,860
是啊
Yeah.

438
00:32:10,030 --> 00:32:12,050
我好得很
I'm better than all right.

439
00:32:29,460 --> 00:32:31,710
卡森醫生幫格雷戈里包扎了傷口
Dr. Carson was able to patch Gregory up.

440
00:32:31,950 --> 00:32:34,190
他現在很痛苦  但還活著
He's in pain, but he'll live.

441
00:32:34,420 --> 00:32:35,900
現在怎么辦
So, what happens now?

442
00:32:37,360 --> 00:32:39,620
這種事很少在這里發生
Things like that don't usually happen here,

443
00:32:39,620 --> 00:32:42,620
但是已經解決了
but, uh, it's settled.

444
00:32:42,910 --> 00:32:44,710
我們聽到了尼根的名字
We heard the name Negan.

445
00:32:45,600 --> 00:32:48,840
之前達里爾和亞伯拉罕跟他的人起過沖突
A while back, Daryl and Abraham had a run-in with his men.

446
00:32:49,980 --> 00:32:51,160
他是誰
Who is he?

447
00:32:51,290 --> 00:32:54,630
尼根領導著一群他所謂的救世軍
Negan's the head of a group of people he calls the Saviors.

448
00:32:55,360 --> 00:32:59,010
墻造好以后  救世軍就出現了
As soon as the walls were built, the Saviors showed up.

449
00:32:59,910 --> 00:33:02,100
他們代表他們的老大見了格雷戈里
They met with Gregory on behalf of their boss.

450
00:33:02,890 --> 00:33:06,110
他們提出了很多要求  做出了更多威脅
They made a lot of demands, even more threats.

451
00:33:06,880 --> 00:33:10,100
他殺了我們其中一員  羅里
And he killed one of us-- Rory.

452
00:33:10,940 --> 00:33:12,940
他才16歲
He was 16 years old.

453
00:33:13,460 --> 00:33:16,240
他們當著我們的面  把他活活打死了
They beat him to death right in front of us.

454
00:33:17,750 --> 00:33:21,090
他說我們必須明白局勢
Said we needed to understand, right off the bat.

455
00:33:23,230 --> 00:33:25,560
格雷戈里不是很擅長處理沖突
Gregory's not exactly good at confrontation.

456
00:33:26,260 --> 00:33:27,940
他不是我心中的領導人選
He's not the leader I would've chosen,

457
00:33:27,940 --> 00:33:30,450
但是他幫我們創建了這個地方
but he helped make this place what it is,

458
00:33:30,790 --> 00:33:32,130
大家都很喜歡他
and the people like him.

459
00:33:32,360 --> 00:33:33,720
他接受了條件
He made the deal.

460
00:33:34,010 --> 00:33:35,290
全部的一半
Half of everything.

461
00:33:36,230 --> 00:33:38,770
我們的補給  我們的作物
Our supplies, our crops,

462
00:33:38,900 --> 00:33:42,340
我們的牲畜  一半都給救世軍
our livestock, it goes to the Saviors.

463
00:33:42,670 --> 00:33:44,350
你們能得到什么作為交換
And what do you get in return?

464
00:33:45,240 --> 00:33:46,900
他們不會攻擊這里
They don't attack this place.

465
00:33:47,170 --> 00:33:48,710
他們不會殺了我們
They don't kill us.

466
00:33:48,890 --> 00:33:50,430
為什么不能殺了他們
Why not just kill them?

467
00:33:50,700 --> 00:33:52,750
這兒大多數人都不知道怎么戰斗
Most of the people here don't even know how to fight,

468
00:33:53,150 --> 00:33:54,610
即使我們有彈藥
even if we had ammo.

469
00:33:54,610 --> 00:33:56,920
尼根手下有多少人
Well, how many people does Negan have?

470
00:33:56,920 --> 00:33:58,300
我們不知道
We don't know.

471
00:33:58,300 --> 00:33:59,930
我們最多見過二十個人
We've seen groups as big as 20.

472
00:34:00,010 --> 00:34:02,950
等等  他們就這么出現  殺了一個孩子
Now, hold up. So, they show up, they kill a kid,

473
00:34:02,950 --> 00:34:04,760
你們就乖乖奉上一半物資嗎
and you give them half of everything?

474
00:34:05,760 --> 00:34:07,550
這群混蛋只是在編故事
These dicks just got a good story.

475
00:34:07,550 --> 00:34:09,020
嚇小孩的  他沒什么了不起
The bogeyman, he ain't shit.

476
00:34:09,340 --> 00:34:10,700
你怎么能確定
Well, how do you know?

477
00:34:10,700 --> 00:34:13,580
一個月前  我們輕松干掉了他們的人
A month ago, we took his guys out PDQ.

478
00:34:14,090 --> 00:34:16,130
把他們打得七零八落
Left them in pieces and puddles.

479
00:34:16,700 --> 00:34:17,990
我們會幫你的
You know, we'll do it.

480
00:34:19,000 --> 00:34:20,450
如果我們救回你的人  
If we go get your man back,

481
00:34:20,530 --> 00:34:22,670
殺死尼根  干掉他的人
kill Negan, take out his boys,

482
00:34:22,670 --> 00:34:23,970
你能幫我們嗎
will you hook us up?

483
00:34:24,260 --> 00:34:26,720
我們要食物  藥品  和一頭奶牛
We want food, medicine, and one of them cows.

484
00:34:29,150 --> 00:34:32,480
我們從來不怕處理沖突
Confrontation's never been something we've had trouble with.

485
00:34:37,990 --> 00:34:39,560
我會告訴格雷戈里的
I'll take it to Gregory.

486
00:34:50,310 --> 00:34:52,990
他們有食物  我們沒有
They have food, we don't.

487
00:34:54,100 --> 00:34:55,940
我們什么都不夠
We don't have enough of anything.

488
00:34:56,950 --> 00:34:58,430
我們只有我們自己
Except us.

489
00:34:59,750 --> 00:35:01,420
和我們能做到的事
What we can do.

490
00:35:06,220 --> 00:35:08,480
這就是交易
This is the trade.

491
00:35:10,490 --> 00:35:12,360
我們也會付出代價的
It's gonna cost us something.

492
00:35:18,310 --> 00:35:21,350
格雷戈里起來了  他想談談
Gregory's up. He wants to talk.

493
00:35:23,750 --> 00:35:24,900
和瑪姬
To Maggie.

494
00:35:26,130 --> 00:35:27,830
他想和瑪姬談談
He wants to talk to Maggie.

495
00:35:29,420 --> 00:35:30,530
你可以的
You got this.

496
00:35:33,290 --> 00:35:35,350
迪安娜對你的看法沒有錯
Deanna was right about you.

497
00:35:39,330 --> 00:35:42,270
事先先向你道個歉  格雷戈里有時很混蛋
I'm sorry in advance. Gregory can be a real prick.

498
00:35:42,270 --> 00:35:43,340
我知道
I know.

499
00:35:46,490 --> 00:35:47,920
進來
Come in.

500
00:35:50,240 --> 00:35:51,830
抱歉房間里很暗
Sorry for the gloom.

501
00:35:53,840 --> 00:35:56,770
他們給我注射了抗生素
They have me on these antibiotics

502
00:35:56,770 --> 00:35:58,920
讓我對光線很敏感
that make me sensitive to the sunlight.

503
00:35:59,640 --> 00:36:01,300
實在是太痛苦了
This is agony.

504
00:36:01,800 --> 00:36:05,350
好像有人在用水泥攪拌機攪我的腸胃
It's like somebody's twisting my intestines with a cement mixer.

505
00:36:05,350 --> 00:36:06,890
本可能會更糟
It could've been worse.

506
00:36:07,320 --> 00:36:08,880
我們在這兒算你走運
You're lucky we were here.

507
00:36:10,000 --> 00:36:11,730
耶穌跟你說了我們的條件嗎
Jesus told you about our offer?

508
00:36:11,930 --> 00:36:13,000
是的
He did.

509
00:36:13,000 --> 00:36:15,130
你們憑什么認為能做到我們做不到的事
What makes you think you can do what we haven't done?

510
00:36:15,130 --> 00:36:16,950
我們對付過尼根這樣的人
We've handled people like Negan.

511
00:36:17,920 --> 00:36:20,350
-怎么對付  -他們已經死了
- How? - They're dead.

512
00:36:21,300 --> 00:36:22,730
我們能救回你們的人
We can get your man back.

513
00:36:25,420 --> 00:36:27,430
真不知道克雷格值不值得這樣大費周折
I don't know if Craig's worth the trouble.

514
00:36:28,070 --> 00:36:30,200
畢竟這是他兄弟做的
I mean, it's his brother who did this.

515
00:36:31,190 --> 00:36:33,590
他是為了救他所愛的人
He was fighting to save someone he loves.

516
00:36:35,190 --> 00:36:36,320
他很害怕
He was afraid.

517
00:36:36,620 --> 00:36:38,020
那令他軟弱
That makes him weak.

518
00:36:39,020 --> 00:36:41,600
說實話  我不知道我是否想讓他回到這里
Frankly, I don't know if I want him back in our gene pool.

519
00:36:41,900 --> 00:36:43,040
我爸爸曾告訴我
My dad used to tell me

520
00:36:43,040 --> 00:36:45,520
原諒比憤怒更需要勇氣
forgiveness takes more strength than anger.

521
00:36:46,140 --> 00:36:47,760
也許是吧
Yeah, I guess.

522
00:36:48,650 --> 00:36:50,270
他是個很好的廚師
He's a hell of a cook.

523
00:36:50,270 --> 00:36:53,470
他做的青西紅柿烤蛋非常好吃
He makes these amazing baked eggs with green tomatoes.

524
00:36:53,470 --> 00:36:57,020
你給我們物資  我們去救克雷格
You give us supplies, we'll save Craig

525
00:36:57,020 --> 00:37:00,060
滅掉尼根和救世軍
and take care of Negan and the Saviors, permanently.

526
00:37:01,390 --> 00:37:04,750
抱歉  我覺得這段對話很可笑
I'm sorry, I find this whole conversation pretty funny.

527
00:37:04,750 --> 00:37:07,320
我提出讓你們勞動換物資時
I mean, you balked when I proposed

528
00:37:07,320 --> 00:37:09,930
你猶豫了  但是現在
that your people work for our supplies, but now...

529
00:37:10,760 --> 00:37:12,890
結果不是完全一樣嗎
isn't that exactly what's happening here?

530
00:37:13,450 --> 00:37:16,020
我有籌碼  我利用了
See, I had leverage and I used it.

531
00:37:17,140 --> 00:37:18,980
瞧  這不是針對你
See? It wasn't personal.

532
00:37:19,390 --> 00:37:20,590
是的
Yes.

533
00:37:21,580 --> 00:37:24,290
我們需要食物  你們有食物
We need food. You have it.

534
00:37:24,490 --> 00:37:25,980
我們愿意用勞動交換
We're willing to work for it.

535
00:37:29,160 --> 00:37:31,940
那我會給你們的人準備物資
Then I'll get supplies for your people.

536
00:37:32,190 --> 00:37:33,380
很好
Good.

537
00:37:33,540 --> 00:37:36,510
我會跟耶穌談談  做好安排
I'll talk to Jesus and he'll make the arrangements.

538
00:37:37,310 --> 00:37:38,930
瞧  這挺有趣的
See, this was fun.

539
00:37:41,370 --> 00:37:42,710
令人激動
Exciting.

540
00:37:47,180 --> 00:37:48,740
一半
Half.

541
00:37:49,450 --> 00:37:50,400
什么
Excuse me?

542
00:37:50,400 --> 00:37:52,460
全部的一半
Half of what you have.

543
00:37:53,270 --> 00:37:54,970
我看到在外面發生了什么
I saw what happened out there.

544
00:37:55,160 --> 00:37:57,830
尼根想要這里進貢更多物資
Negan's expecting more supplies from this place.

545
00:37:58,780 --> 00:38:00,940
而且會越來越多
And more and more.

546
00:38:01,720 --> 00:38:03,110
如果繼續下去
And if it keeps going like that,

547
00:38:03,110 --> 00:38:05,560
你們很快會一無所有
pretty soon you won't have anything left.

548
00:38:07,150 --> 00:38:08,850
然后會發生什么
What happens then?

549
00:38:09,460 --> 00:38:12,740
沒有彈藥  沒有戰士
Without ammo, without fighters...

550
00:38:14,240 --> 00:38:15,630
你就死定了
you'd be a dead man.

551
00:38:18,830 --> 00:38:20,600
所以我要你們一半的物資
So half of everything you have

552
00:38:21,200 --> 00:38:22,440
現在就要
right now

553
00:38:23,710 --> 00:38:25,090
否則交易取消
or the deal's off.

554
00:38:26,970 --> 00:38:28,100
瞧
You see?

555
00:38:29,430 --> 00:38:31,060
我有籌碼
I have leverage.

556
00:38:36,340 --> 00:38:38,090
恭喜
Congratulations.

557
00:38:39,160 --> 00:38:41,200
交易達成
You have yourself a deal.

558
00:38:42,510 --> 00:38:45,430
你還要什么  要一個腎嗎
You want anything else? Kidney, maybe?

559
00:38:45,440 --> 00:38:47,100
不用了
Not that...

560
00:38:47,960 --> 00:38:49,750
但我的確想要一樣東西
but I do want something.

561
00:38:57,910 --> 00:39:00,200
連尼根第一次都沒拿走這么多
Even Negan didn't get this much up front.

562
00:39:03,450 --> 00:39:04,430
什么事
What?

563
00:39:04,990 --> 00:39:05,900
耶穌說你從一開始
Jesus said you've been

564
00:39:05,900 --> 00:39:08,400
就負責給尼根運送物資
taking supplies to Negan since the beginning.

565
00:39:10,250 --> 00:39:11,860
我們會救回克雷格
We're gonna get Craig back.

566
00:39:12,580 --> 00:39:13,610
救回克雷格的唯一方式是
The only way to get Craig back

567
00:39:13,680 --> 00:39:15,210
獻上格雷戈里的人頭
is to bring them Gregory's head.

568
00:39:17,160 --> 00:39:18,990
我們會救回克雷格
We're gonna get Craig back.

569
00:39:19,060 --> 00:39:20,190
怎么救
How?

570
00:39:20,980 --> 00:39:23,690
我們需要你提供尼根基地的情報
We need to know what you know about Negan's compound.

571
00:39:25,380 --> 00:39:26,680
我們需要你的幫助
We need your help.

572
00:39:28,420 --> 00:39:29,900
我們需要你一起走
We need you to come.

573
00:39:38,440 --> 00:39:39,550
好
Yeah.

574
00:39:40,570 --> 00:39:41,750
好的
Okay.

575
00:39:52,860 --> 00:39:54,460
還能坐下一個人嗎
You got room for one more, right?

576
00:39:55,670 --> 00:39:57,640
我們可是要去讓世界恢復正義
I mean, we're talking about righting the world here.

577
00:39:58,790 --> 00:40:00,630
再說了  我的刀還在你們那里
Plus, you still have my knives.

578
00:40:07,100 --> 00:40:08,480
你準備好了嗎
Hey, you up for this?

579
00:40:10,320 --> 00:40:11,760
肯定會戰斗的
It's gonna be a fight.

580
00:40:12,010 --> 00:40:13,280
我們會贏的
We'll win.

581
00:40:14,610 --> 00:40:15,850
我們必須贏
We have to.

582
00:40:18,710 --> 00:40:19,860
我們會贏的
We'll win.

