[Script Info]
; // The sub is created by AssToolkit
; // AssToolkit is an ASS Converter designed by David C.
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.20,0:00:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《行尸走肉》前情提要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Previously on AMC's The Walking Dead...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:04.07,0:00:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山顶寨的医生  他会让你好转的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The doctor at the hilltop. He's gonna make things better.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.08,0:00:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会到那里的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're gonna get there.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.55,0:00:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-选好路线了吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You got a route? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.01,0:00:11.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,北边还有两条路\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There are two more routes north from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.74,0:00:13.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们可能已经在路上等着我们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're probably waiting for us right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.85,0:00:16.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,调头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go back.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.32,0:00:17.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.66,0:00:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是尼根\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hi, I'm Negan.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.48,0:00:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不想杀你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't wanna kill you people.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.05,0:00:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你们替我工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want you to work for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.52,0:00:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你们杀了我的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But you killed my people.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.80,0:00:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因此  你们必须付出代价\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For that, you're gonna pay.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.03,0:00:29.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要打爆你们其中一个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna beat the holy hell outta one of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.18,0:00:43.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.28,0:00:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好笑吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Was the joke that bad?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.23,0:00:54.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要杀了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.43,0:01:05.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.09,0:01:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没听见  你得大声点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't quite catch that. You're gonna have to speak up.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.23,0:01:20.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在今天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not today...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.26,0:01:23.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在明天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...not tomorrow...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.56,0:01:29.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我要杀了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...but I'm gonna kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.73,0:01:41.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jesus.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.11,0:01:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西蒙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Simon...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.01,0:01:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有什么  一把刀吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}what did he have, a knife?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.25,0:01:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有一把短斧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Uh, he had a hatchet.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.22,0:01:58.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一把短斧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A hatchet?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.86,0:02:01.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有一把斧子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He had an ax.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.61,0:02:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西蒙是我的得力手下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Simon's my right-hand man.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.69,0:02:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有得力手下是很重要的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Having one of those is important.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.35,0:02:14.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没了他们  你会剩下什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, what do you have left without them?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.31,0:02:17.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,许多工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A whole lot of work.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.09,0:02:20.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有得力手下吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you have one?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.07,0:02:23.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是这里还活着的一个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe one of these fine people still breathing?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.15,0:02:29.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or did I...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.57,0:02:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.38,0:02:46.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.02,0:02:49.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他的斧子给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give me his ax.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.00,0:03:26.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我马上回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.96,0:03:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许瑞克会跟我一起回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe Rick will be with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.55,0:03:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And if not, well,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.29,0:03:33.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以将他们扒皮抽骨  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we can just turn these people inside out, won't we?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.58,0:03:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  剩下的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean... the ones that are left.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.69,0:04:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去兜兜风\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's go for a ride.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.17,0:05:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是垃圾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What a piece of shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.58,0:05:10.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"我要杀了你"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"I'm gonna kill you."
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.29,0:05:13.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开玩笑吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you kiddin' me?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.42,0:05:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看见刚发生的事了吗  我做的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you see what just happened, what I just did?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.98,0:05:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You just...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.89,0:05:24.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好的机会是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your best chance...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.05,0:05:27.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站起来  拿起那把斧子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is to stand up, grab that ax,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.98,0:05:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砍穿我的后脑勺\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and drive it through the back of my head.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.38,0:05:33.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See how you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.23,0:05:37.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续装硬汉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Keep actin' tough.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.07,0:05:39.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.55,0:05:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿起斧子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Grab the damn ax.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.49,0:05:51.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Drop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.79,0:06:11.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让我再起身\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't make me get up again.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.13,0:06:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, look at that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.54,0:06:21.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快破晓了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dawn is breakin'.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.77,0:06:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又是全新的一天  瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's a brand-new day, Rick.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.33,0:06:31.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要你想想可能发生的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want you to think about what could have happened...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.70,0:06:34.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想发生的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...think about what happened,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.83,0:06:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想还可能发生的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and think about what can still happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.82,0:07:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Boom!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.21,0:07:08.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那让你想到你认识的人了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That remind you of anybody you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.56,0:07:12.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.91,0:07:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You are mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.57,0:07:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里的人  他们是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The people back there -- they are mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.30,0:07:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.11,0:07:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.05,0:08:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Rick...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.67,0:08:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去捡我的斧子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}go get my ax.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.18,0:08:22.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们做朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's be friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.79,0:08:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去捡我的斧子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get my ax.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.38,0:11:33.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜你们一定都以为你们会一起变老\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bet you thought you were all gonna grow old together,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.95,0:11:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周日晚上围坐在桌边一起吃饭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}sittin' around the table at Sunday dinner
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.50,0:11:38.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从此幸福地生活在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and the happily ever after.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.41,0:11:40.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.21,0:11:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是那么回事  瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Doesn't work like that, Rick.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.43,0:11:45.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不再是了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.88,0:11:49.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想发生的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Think about what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.59,0:12:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是无法决定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I simply cannot decide.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.38,0:12:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got an idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.29,0:12:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Eenie...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.19,0:12:33.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}meenie...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.32,0:12:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}miney...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.84,0:12:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}mo...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.03,0:12:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,骑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}catch...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.06,0:12:44.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a tiger...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.26,0:12:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}by...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.98,0:12:49.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}his toe.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.57,0:12:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,点到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.83,0:12:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}he hollers...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.41,0:12:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪里就上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}let him go.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.75,0:13:01.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}My mother...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.25,0:13:03.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,破\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}told me...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.46,0:13:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,血\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to pick...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.37,0:13:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,流 \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}the very...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.96,0:13:14.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}best one...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.96,0:13:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.51,0:13:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,场\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}are...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.75,0:13:48.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.32,0:13:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人敢动或说话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Anybody moves, anybody says anything,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.34,0:13:55.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就把那孩子的另一只眼挖出来喂他父亲吃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}cut the boy's other eye out and feed it to his father,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.13,0:13:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们再开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and then we'll start.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.19,0:14:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以呼吸  你可以眨眼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can breathe. You can blink.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.73,0:14:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以哭泣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can cry.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.21,0:14:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼  你们每个人都会那样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hell, you're all gonna be doing that.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.30,0:14:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look at that!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.01,0:14:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真有种\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Taking it like a champ!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.02,0:14:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Suck...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.26,0:14:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}my...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.35,0:14:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}nuts.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.84,0:14:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们听见了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you hear that?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.48,0:14:44.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他让我滚蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He said, "suck my nuts."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.66,0:15:19.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, my goodness!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.71,0:15:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look at this!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.75,0:15:31.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大伙儿们  瞧瞧我肮脏的坏女孩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You guys, look at my dirty girl!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.34,0:15:39.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小甜心...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sweetheart...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.47,0:15:43.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lay your eyes on this.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.97,0:15:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, damn.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.35,0:15:53.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Were you --
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.69,0:15:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩是一对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Were you together?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.41,0:15:57.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真惨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That sucks.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.92,0:16:01.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如你俩真是一对  你就应该知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But if you were, you should know
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.42,0:16:04.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这一切都是有原因的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}there was a reason for all this.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.26,0:16:07.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,红毛  该死的  他过去是  现在是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Red -- and hell, he was, is,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.19,0:16:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,将来也永远会是红的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and will ever be red.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.23,0:16:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为你们团队里的一人  或六人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He just took one or six
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.34,0:16:12.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至是七人挡了一劫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or seven for the team!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.19,0:16:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  仔细  看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So take...a damn look.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.52,0:16:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔细看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take a damn look!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.11,0:16:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Daryl!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.14,0:16:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.10,0:16:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不成\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.40,0:16:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.76,0:16:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天爷\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, my!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.96,0:16:54.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.06,0:16:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不可取\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is a no-no.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.17,0:17:00.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这整件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The whole thing --
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.65,0:17:03.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不允许出现任何类似的行为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}not one bit of that shit flies here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.51,0:17:13.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想要我动手吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you want me to do it?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.51,0:17:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就地正法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.92,0:17:22.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.03,0:17:25.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你不能杀了他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, you don't kill them...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.80,0:17:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能这么轻易\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}not until you try a little.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.28,0:17:41.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,话说回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And anyway...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.08,0:17:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,规矩不是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that's not how it works.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.56,0:17:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经告诉过你们了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, I already told you people --
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.78,0:17:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次算了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}first one's free,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.92,0:17:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我说了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}then what'd I say?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.59,0:17:55.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说我会弄死你们的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I said I would shut that shit down!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.09,0:17:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有例外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No exceptions.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.84,0:18:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你们之前都是在和\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, I don't know what kind of lying assholes
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.85,0:18:04.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么样的骗子打交道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you've been dealing with...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.81,0:18:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我是个讲信用的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...but I'm a man of my word.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.77,0:18:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一印象很重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}First impressions are important.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.56,0:18:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你们了解我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need you to know me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.92,0:18:24.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.00,0:18:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重新再来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...back to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.48,0:18:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.14,0:18:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  你还有知觉吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Buddy, you still there?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.92,0:19:00.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.63,0:19:03.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像你想说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It seems like you're trying to speak,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.38,0:19:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你刚狠狠中了一棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but you just took a hell of a hit.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.67,0:19:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我砸你脑袋太用力了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just popped your skull so hard,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.78,0:19:10.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你眼球都爆出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}your eyeball just popped out,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.38,0:19:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是恶心死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and it is gross as shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.99,0:19:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬  我会找到你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maggie, I'll find you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.95,0:19:32.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, hell.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.63,0:19:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能看出来这对你们来说太残酷了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can see this is hard on you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.71,0:19:43.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I am sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.43,0:19:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真心的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I truly am.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.81,0:19:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我确实说过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I did say it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.66,0:19:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有例外\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No exceptions!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.08,0:20:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这帮孬种\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You bunch of pussies.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.75,0:20:25.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才刚开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm just getting started.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.88,0:20:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露西尔很饥渴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lucille is thirsty.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.38,0:20:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是根吸血棒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She is a vampire bat.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.13,0:21:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.21,0:21:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好笑吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Was the joke that bad?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.25,0:21:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们死了  瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}People died, Rick.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.37,0:21:22.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那确实发生了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.55,0:21:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不代表其他人也要去死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Doesn't mean the rest of them have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.48,0:21:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我的斧子给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get me my ax.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.16,0:21:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我的  斧子  给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get me...my...ax!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.48,0:21:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为你行  瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought you were the guy, Rick.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.51,0:21:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe you're not.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.48,0:21:49.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再给你一次机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll give it one more go.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.53,0:21:52.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在真心希望你再试一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, I really want you to try this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.15,0:21:55.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一次机会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Last chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.65,0:21:59.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把我的斧子给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bring me my ax!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.25,0:22:52.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间不等人  瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Clock is ticking, Rick!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.46,0:22:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想还可能发生的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Think about what can still happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.41,0:24:37.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真乖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Attaboy!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.14,0:25:26.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们到了  混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're here, prick.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.09,0:25:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一定不好受对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This must be hard for you, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.50,0:25:44.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直以来你都是最强者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, you have been King Shit for so long.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.17,0:25:52.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞬间失去两个自己人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Losin' two of your own like...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.67,0:25:58.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被那样殴杀  一个接着一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Gettin' 'em clipped like that, one nut, then the other,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.05,0:26:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还当着你儿子的面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and in front of your boy?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.32,0:26:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那真是糟透了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That is some screwed-up shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.55,0:26:12.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Goody.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.87,0:26:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以前是老大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were in charge.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.84,0:26:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hell...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.66,0:26:33.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可能...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...you were probably...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.09,0:26:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当上瘾了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}addicted to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.60,0:26:39.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And now, well, 
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.23,0:26:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啪啪两下  就结束了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}clip, clip -- that's over.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.11,0:26:46.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.63,0:26:52.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还是可以为我服务\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...you can still lead...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.81,0:26:56.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过上美好殷实的生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a nice, productive life producing for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.21,0:27:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你会用上的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think you're gonna need it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.64,0:27:15.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有预感\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just got a feelin'.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.89,0:27:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么拿去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.00,0:27:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here we are.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.31,0:27:48.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我问你  瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let me ask you something, Rick --
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.21,0:27:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那段小旅行的意义吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}do you even know what that little trip was about?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.38,0:28:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你说你就说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Speak when you're spoken to.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.70,0:28:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay. Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.67,0:28:13.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那旅行的意义\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That trip was about
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.98,0:28:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在于你看我的眼神\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}at you looked at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.52,0:28:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想改变你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I wanted to change that.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.95,0:28:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要你明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I wanted you to understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.41,0:28:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你还是用那同样该死的眼神看我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But you're still looking at me the same damn way...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.98,0:28:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像我在你的煎蛋里拉屎了一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...like I shit in your scrambled eggs,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.30,0:28:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是行不通的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and that's not gonna work.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.61,0:28:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.34,0:28:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要再给你一次机会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...do I give you another chance?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.47,0:28:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.57,0:28:48.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.26,0:28:50.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.92,0:28:54.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.69,0:28:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.07,0:29:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就开始吧  超级大奖赛\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And here it is -- the grand-prize game.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.27,0:29:06.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你接下来做出的选择  会决定这糟糕的一天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What you do next will decide whether your crap day
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.51,0:29:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会变成大家最后糟糕的一天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}becomes everyone's last crap day
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.92,0:29:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说只是普通糟糕的一天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or just another crap day.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.93,0:29:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用枪指着他们的头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get some guns to the back of their heads.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.26,0:29:31.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  那么...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good. Now...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.61,0:29:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和他们鼻子齐平  这样一开枪...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}level with their noses, so if you have to fire...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.59,0:29:40.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那画面会很惨烈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it'll be a real mess.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.31,0:29:52.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Kid...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.13,0:29:58.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.87,0:30:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子  快点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Kid...now.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.26,0:30:15.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是左撇子吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You a southpaw?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.13,0:30:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Am I a what?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:17.64,0:30:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你惯用左手吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You a lefty?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.13,0:30:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:22.32,0:30:23.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.54,0:30:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疼吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That hurt?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.50,0:30:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.92,0:30:35.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该疼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Should.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.71,0:30:37.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,应该觉得疼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's supposed to.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.64,0:30:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.45,0:30:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趴在地上  孩子  趴在爸爸边上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get down on the ground, kid, next to Daddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.93,0:30:45.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,展开双手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Spread them wings.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.52,0:30:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,西蒙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Simon...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.56,0:31:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有笔吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...you got a pen?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.17,0:31:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.47,0:31:19.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry, kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.69,0:31:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这会凉得像巫师的阴囊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is gonna be as cold as a warlock's ballsack,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.40,0:31:25.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像他在你身上挺着阴囊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}just like he was hanging his ballsack above you
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.80,0:31:29.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后拖过你的前臂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and dragging it right across the forearm.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.67,0:31:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.09,0:31:33.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你留一点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Gives you a little leverage.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.80,0:31:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please. Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.31,0:31:36.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.86,0:31:38.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你不要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.27,0:31:41.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Me?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.67,0:31:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么都不会干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I ain't doing shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.24,0:31:53.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克  我要你拿起斧头\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick, I want you to take your ax...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.02,0:31:56.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砍下你儿子的左臂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}cut your son's left arm off,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.45,0:31:57.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就顺着那条线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}right on that line.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.77,0:32:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, I know -- I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.94,0:32:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要花点时间接受这个信息\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna have to process that for a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.97,0:32:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是正常的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That makes sense.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.59,0:32:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我还是要你动手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Still, though, I'm gonna need you to do it,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.66,0:32:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然其他人就得死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or all these people are gonna die.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.61,0:32:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后卡尔也要死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then Carl dies,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.27,0:32:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里的那些人也要死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}then the people back home die...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.34,0:32:18.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后  你也得死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and then you, eventually.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.12,0:32:20.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会让你苟活个几年\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna keep you breathing for a few years,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.99,0:32:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你备受煎熬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}just so you can stew on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.09,0:32:24.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...你不用这么做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You -- you don't have to do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.75,0:32:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.99,0:32:27.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.67,0:32:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.26,0:32:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.54,0:32:34.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是不确定瑞克明不明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not sure that Rick does.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.27,0:32:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你干脆利落地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna need a clean cut
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.94,0:32:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺着那条线砍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}right there on that line.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.55,0:32:41.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这样要求很过分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, I know this is a screwed-up thing to ask,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.66,0:32:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你得砍成像意大利香肠片一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but it's gonna have to be like a salami slice --
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.85,0:32:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,切口齐整  干净  45度角\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}nothing messy, clean, 45 degrees --
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.49,0:32:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好让我们缝合伤口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}give us something to fold over.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.32,0:32:50.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有个好医生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We got a great doctor.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.69,0:32:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子不会有事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The kid'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:52.83,0:32:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Probably.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.22,0:32:57.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.04,0:33:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须现在就做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...this needs to happen now --
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.48,0:33:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}chop, chop --
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.32,0:33:07.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然我亲自砸烂这小子的脑袋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or I will crush the little fella's skull myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.75,0:33:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以换我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It can -- It can -- It can be me.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.57,0:33:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以换我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It can be me.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.58,0:33:15.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以砍我的手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Y-You can do it to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.60,0:33:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以跟你走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I c-- I can go with -- with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.70,0:33:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.28,0:33:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是唯一的办法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is the only way.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.36,0:33:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.88,0:33:26.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿起斧子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}pick up the ax.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.86,0:33:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不做决定也是个大决定\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not making a decision is a big decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.79,0:33:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真想看这些人都死吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You really want to see all these people die?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.52,0:33:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会看到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You will.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.04,0:33:44.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会看到每个肮脏的细节\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You will see every ugly thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.61,0:33:49.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.61,0:33:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要逼我倒数吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you gonna make me count?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.41,0:33:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, Rick.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:53.94,0:33:54.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你赢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You win.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.85,0:33:56.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我数\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I am counting.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.77,0:33:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-三  -求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- 3! - Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.93,0:34:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.83,0:34:02.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以换我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It can be me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.37,0:34:03.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.26,0:34:06.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}2!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.34,0:34:08.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please, don't do --
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.75,0:34:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时间要到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is it.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.58,0:34:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}1. ?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.66,0:34:27.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸  砍吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dad... just do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.12,0:34:29.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砍吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.31,0:34:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.33,0:34:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听我号令\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You answer to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.72,0:34:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你向我上贡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You provide for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.10,0:34:50.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你属于我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You belong to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:51.40,0:34:52.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.36,0:34:57.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你说你就说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Speak when you're spoken to!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.75,0:35:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听我号令\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You answer to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.54,0:35:01.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你向我上贡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You provide for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.91,0:35:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向你上贡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Provide for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.56,0:35:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你属于我  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You belong to me, right?!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.47,0:35:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.68,0:35:12.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.73,0:35:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.57,0:35:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我想看到的眼神\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...is the look I wanted to see.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:31.82,0:35:33.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们做到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We did it...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.06,0:35:36.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们所有人  齐心协力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}all of us, together...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.67,0:35:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至包括地上趴着的死人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}even the dead guys on the ground.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.11,0:35:42.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼  他们肯定要得精神奖\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hell, they get the spirit award, for sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.82,0:35:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是他妈高效的一天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Today was a productive damn day!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.01,0:35:54.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我希望  为了你们好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, I hope, for all your sake...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.77,0:35:58.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that you get it now...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.79,0:36:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们理解事情的运作方式\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...that you understand how things work.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.10,0:36:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切已改变\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Things have changed.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.91,0:36:13.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你们以前怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whatever you had going for you...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.12,0:36:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在都已结束\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...that is over now.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.72,0:36:21.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德怀特\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ah. Dwight...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.67,0:36:25.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉他上车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...load him up.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.72,0:36:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他有种\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's got guts --
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.61,0:36:49.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不像我认识的某个小婊子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}not a little bitch like someone I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.53,0:36:52.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I like him.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.70,0:36:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他现在是我的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's mine now.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.04,0:36:56.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果你还想打鬼主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But you still want to try something?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.81,0:36:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"不在今天  不在明天"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Not today, not tomorrow."
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.08,0:36:59.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"不在今天  不在明天"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Not today, not tomorrow"?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.24,0:37:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会砍下一部分...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I will cut pieces off of...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.95,0:37:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他叫什么来着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hell's his name?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.64,0:37:07.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Daryl.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.72,0:37:10.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听上去还挺配他的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That actually sounds right.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.77,0:37:12.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会切下达里尔的一部分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I will cut pieces off of Daryl
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.22,0:37:15.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后放到你的门口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and put them on your doorstep --
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.01,0:37:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者  更棒的是  我把他带到你面前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or, better yet, I will bring him to you
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.79,0:37:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让你来替我动手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and have you do it for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.13,0:37:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到全新的开始  你们这些可怜虫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Welcome to a brand-new beginning, you sorry shits!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.39,0:37:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你们一辆货车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna leave you a truck.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.87,0:37:39.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,留着吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Keep it.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.88,0:37:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用来装你们给我弄到的各种物资\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Use it to cart all the crap you're gonna find me.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:44.40,0:37:46.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会在一周后来收第一次的贡品\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll be back for our first offering in one week.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:46.98,0:37:48.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Until then...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.43,0:37:49.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}ta-ta.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.50,0:39:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬  玛姬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maggie. Maggie.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.10,0:39:47.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maggie...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.65,0:39:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得坐下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you need to sit down.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.01,0:39:52.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-玛姬  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Maggie. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.34,0:39:58.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要把你送去山顶寨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need to get you to the Hilltop.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.07,0:39:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得去做好准备\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You need to go get ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.91,0:40:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For what?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.04,0:40:05.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抗击他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}To fight them.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.24,0:40:15.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们手里有达里尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They have Daryl.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.51,0:40:17.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们有一支军队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They have an army.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.92,0:40:20.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会死的  全都会死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We would die -- all of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.70,0:40:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go home.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.40,0:40:29.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把大家都带回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take everybody with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.06,0:40:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以一个人去那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can get there by myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.94,0:40:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你站都站不稳了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can barely stand up.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.19,0:40:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:35.94,0:40:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你需要回亚历山大去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You need to go to Alexandria.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.71,0:40:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是为了我才出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were out -- out here for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:51.15,0:40:52.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在依然是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We still are.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.50,0:41:04.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在一个人可以走到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can make it now.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.67,0:41:05.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你们回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need you to go back.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.76,0:41:06.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能让你们在外面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't have you out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.94,0:41:09.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能再让你们在外面冒险了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't have you all out here anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.08,0:41:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你们回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need you to go back.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.58,0:41:19.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maggie...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:21.10,0:41:22.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不会让你一个人走的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we're not letting you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.47,0:41:24.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.04,0:41:26.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们必须让我走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:28.14,0:41:29.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是不可能的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not gonna happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:38.97,0:41:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带着她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm taking her.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.27,0:41:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会送她去那里的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna get her there.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:45.97,0:41:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会保护她的安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna keep her safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.69,0:41:55.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我由不得你拒绝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not giving you a choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.89,0:41:57.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要带着他一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm taking him with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.18,0:42:19.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要带上他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna take him.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:22.85,0:42:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what I'm gonna do.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:42.99,0:42:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须这么做  拜托了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need to do this. Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:46.05,0:42:47.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need to help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:50.92,0:42:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:53.01,0:42:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.41,0:42:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. No.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:58.48,0:43:00.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  让我们帮忙吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Pl-- Pl-- Please let us.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.72,0:43:07.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我们的家人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He-- He's our family, t--
Dialogue: 0,0:43:08.18,0:43:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也是我们的家人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's our family, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:23.50,0:43:25.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  数到三\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right. On three.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:25.59,0:43:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一  二\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}1, 2...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:42.23,0:43:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜你们一定都以为你们会一起变老\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Bet you thought you were all gonna grow old together,
Dialogue: 0,0:43:45.70,0:43:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,周日晚上围坐在桌边一起吃饭\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}sittin' around the table at Sunday dinner
Dialogue: 0,0:43:48.25,0:43:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从此幸福地生活在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and the happily ever after.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:51.03,0:43:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:52.93,0:43:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是那么回事  瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Doesn't work like that, Rick.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:56.16,0:43:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不再是了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.95,0:04:31.16,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第七季  第一集』
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.37,0:04:59.22,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx2300\fscy200\alpha&AA\pos(129.2,218.4)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.36,0:04:39.36,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻译:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}冰蓝  陈星晓实名捅死编剧  自然卷
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.33,0:04:44.33,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻译:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}童女小酸奶  首无送小孩  君君
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.29,0:04:49.29,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}校对:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}冰蓝  首无送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.26,0:04:54.26,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}时间轴:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}加森  涛涛
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.22,0:04:59.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}后期:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}童男送小哥  拉图    {\c&H008AFF&}总监： {\c&HFFFFFF&}首无送小孩

