[Script Info]
; // The sub is created by AssToolkit
; // AssToolkit is an ASS Converter designed by David C.
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.00,0:00:03.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《行尸走肉》前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.96,0:00:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.24,0:00:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.29,0:00:07.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-是的  -好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.53,0:00:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要做好准备  我们必须反抗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.64,0:00:12.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.93,0:00:15.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们给你找到枪  然后一起战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.91,0:00:18.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-说同意  -同意
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.54,0:00:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在外面  所以我要跟你去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.64,0:00:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.51,0:00:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,买一送一
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.85,0:00:26.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须给我搞些东西来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.43,0:00:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刀  枪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.01,0:00:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用这个就行  这是毒药
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.39,0:00:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\fs9\bord0\shad0\b1\c&HECB000&\pos(366.713,241.828)}官方合作
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.39,0:00:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\shad0\bord0\fs24\pos(342,231)}□|
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.39,0:00:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\shad0\bord0\fs7\pos(340,231)\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK}创意\N周边
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.39,0:00:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\shad0\bord0\pos(306,232)\fn方正综艺_GBK}我爱美剧
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.39,0:00:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\fscx1000\fscy170\shad0\bord0\alpha&66\c&H000000&\pos(331,232.5)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.39,0:00:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\fs16\fscx100\fscy85\shad0\bord0\c&HFFFFFF&\pos(306,232)\b1\fn方正行黑简体}淘
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.39,0:00:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\fs28\shad0\bord0\c&H3A72FF&\pos(306,233)}●
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.48,0:01:57.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第七季  第十五集』
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.87,0:02:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\fs16\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\b1\c&HECB000&\pos(99,242)}原创翻译  双语字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.37,0:02:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs17\pos(235.108,242)\K40}最新连载海外影视剧下载\N{\fs19\K30}请登陆 {\c&H26F4FF&\fn方正综艺_GBK\K30}www.YYeTs.com\N{\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs15\c&HFFFFFF&\K60}仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.10,0:02:11.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}翻译     冰蓝 Reginamoon CS小明漫画家
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.10,0:02:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}翻译     小酸奶 小僵僵 蘑菇 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.42,0:02:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.10,0:02:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}校对     冰蓝吃凉皮  小孩吃夹馍
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.45,0:02:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒醒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.97,0:02:23.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  醒醒
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.10,0:02:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(27,235)}时间轴     涛涛  仓鼠  知之
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.76,0:02:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  我们需要...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.02,0:02:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用  暂时没事
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.10,0:02:31.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}后期     吉吉喝冰峰  拉图吃泡馍
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.10,0:02:36.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}总监     送小孩饿了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.82,0:02:52.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也下午好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.86,0:02:56.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.07,0:02:57.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.03,0:03:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在见到你  我浑身舒服
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.97,0:03:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们回来了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.69,0:03:08.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.01,0:03:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你最近上夜班  今晚也是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.33,0:03:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不想吵醒你
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.70,0:03:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬有麻烦了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.19,0:03:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.38,0:03:22.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子出了问题
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.17,0:03:24.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克要带她去找山顶寨的医生
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.87,0:03:26.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还不知道  但我要跟他去
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.74,0:03:29.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.76,0:03:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我们才刚开始
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.28,0:03:36.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但我希望你...  -别
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.81,0:03:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.70,0:03:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别走
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.72,0:03:59.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到你余生的第一天  萨沙
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.52,0:04:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你今天要帮我确保一切回到正轨
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.59,0:04:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你聪明性感  尊严高尚
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.78,0:04:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,眼里容不得蠢货
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.72,0:04:24.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没人想看你死
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.85,0:04:26.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就不想
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.97,0:04:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你没必要死
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.48,0:04:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但总得有人死
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.49,0:04:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最多几个人
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.30,0:04:42.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你不用死  大部分人也不用死
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.60,0:04:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要解决一些问题
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.87,0:04:52.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽情吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.93,0:04:55.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是个大日子
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.00,0:05:04.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你需要我做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.10,0:05:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看着我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.36,0:05:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.49,0:05:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我想阻止这一切
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.72,0:05:39.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要尼根死
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.42,0:05:41.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你为什么不杀他
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.07,0:05:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一个人做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.69,0:05:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们都是尼根
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.39,0:05:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你谋杀的那个女孩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.21,0:05:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她有名字
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.84,0:05:59.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她叫丹妮斯  是一名医生
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.02,0:06:00.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她救助了很多人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.77,0:06:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我瞄的不是她
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.09,0:06:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动手  动手
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.19,0:06:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想这样结束
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.64,0:06:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,随便你
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.72,0:06:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉  真的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.07,0:06:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你很想
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.11,0:06:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可能只是来打探你是否在这里的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.67,0:06:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能信任他
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.67,0:06:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾是他的人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.14,0:06:44.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不再是了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.20,0:06:48.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我过去做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.72,0:06:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是为了某个人
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.76,0:06:54.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她最近跑掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.95,0:06:58.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我来了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.69,0:07:06.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你是为了她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.76,0:07:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.65,0:07:11.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有另一个选择
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.80,0:07:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.31,0:07:15.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-达里尔  你认识她  -尼根信任我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.34,0:07:20.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以合作  我们可以阻止他
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.35,0:07:31.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你认识之前的我  也认识现在的我
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.91,0:07:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我没有撒谎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.34,0:07:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没有
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.06,0:07:42.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动手啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.90,0:07:43.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动手
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.31,0:07:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们抓住了萨沙  如果她还活着的话
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.88,0:07:58.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么不早说
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.46,0:08:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可能是我们救回她的唯一机会
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.27,0:08:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我不信任他
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.56,0:08:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我信任达里尔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.57,0:08:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根马上就要来了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.66,0:08:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.69,0:08:18.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概会来三辆卡车
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.52,0:08:21.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他和二十名救世军
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.03,0:08:24.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以拖住他们
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.29,0:08:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄些树把路挡住
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.84,0:08:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为你们争取一点准备的时间
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.72,0:08:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如你们能把他们干掉  我们就起了个好头
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.43,0:08:42.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们杀了他们之后  我会发消息到救世堂
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.52,0:08:44.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救世堂
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.86,0:08:46.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根的住处
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.43,0:08:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是这么叫的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.50,0:08:53.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会发消息给他们  告诉他们一切顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.03,0:08:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们把卡车开回去
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.94,0:08:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以领着你们直捣黄龙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.48,0:09:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如计划得好  我们能把残党都干掉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.06,0:09:02.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再去看看你们的朋友是否还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.01,0:09:07.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们把工人拉拢到我们这边
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.91,0:09:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,增加人数
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.36,0:09:15.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后一个个哨站杀过去  结束这一切
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.98,0:09:28.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续说
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.94,0:09:41.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们刚挑起了大战
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.33,0:09:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如他在撒谎  我会慢慢折磨死他
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.80,0:09:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等这一切结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.77,0:09:52.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我才不管他是不是悔过了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.49,0:09:55.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会杀了那个混蛋的
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.66,0:09:58.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如他在撒谎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.78,0:10:01.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们早已完了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.20,0:10:29.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得走了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.08,0:10:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得走了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.70,0:10:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事实上  我觉得我们可以...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.15,0:10:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了一个梦
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.96,0:10:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.83,0:10:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你梦到我了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.95,0:10:46.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你死了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.21,0:10:51.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,计划就是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.93,0:10:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我需要你做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.24,0:10:58.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你出来的时候  别吱声
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.14,0:11:02.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们会投降  假如他们还没投降的话
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.83,0:11:06.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  露西尔会杀掉三个人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.31,0:11:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们带着全新的认知继续前行
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.81,0:11:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是在...你是在逗我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.62,0:11:26.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是真的眼泪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.97,0:11:31.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以配合  但没必要杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.09,0:11:32.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你错了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.58,0:11:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,惩罚...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.99,0:11:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没它什么都做不成
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.40,0:11:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们拥有的一切都是建立在惩罚之上的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.78,0:11:48.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为我会坐视你...
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.53,0:11:49.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当心点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.99,0:11:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做什么轮不到你管
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.01,0:12:04.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没必要死人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.82,0:12:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.49,0:12:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样如何
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.89,0:12:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.39,0:12:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只死一个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.13,0:12:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来打算选三个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.13,0:12:24.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但只杀一个
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.38,0:12:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,专门为了你
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.92,0:12:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.55,0:12:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只用死一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.08,0:12:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是把我玩弄于股掌之间
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.82,0:12:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.06,0:12:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这跟男女无关
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.46,0:12:56.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  就算你有根老二
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.56,0:13:00.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还是会有这种感觉的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.03,0:13:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,45分钟后出发
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.95,0:13:24.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没争取到海边旅馆  但我们有她们的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.94,0:13:27.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而尼根手里有萨沙
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.68,0:13:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔希望我们相信德怀特
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.94,0:13:32.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克希望我们留在这以防不测
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.34,0:13:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样还有另一手牌可打
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.29,0:13:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,另一个救世军以为受他们控制的安全之处
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.26,0:13:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他不知道格雷戈里已经离开了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.19,0:13:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他告诉了他们一些事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.72,0:13:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会让他们改变想法
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.94,0:13:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些都是会发生的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.28,0:13:50.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在考虑领导山顶寨反抗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.69,0:13:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.46,0:13:54.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果尼根发现他们在计划什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.02,0:13:55.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就需要帮助了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.05,0:13:57.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然那些拾荒者都站在他们那边
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.98,0:14:00.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须现在就决定
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.37,0:14:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个艰难的决定
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.11,0:14:07.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你笑什么
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.57,0:14:09.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我很高兴你是为我们做决定的人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.28,0:14:24.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么决定
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.64,0:14:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.81,0:14:29.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只知道你能做出决定
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.83,0:14:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来照顾她
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.44,0:14:35.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你拿着这个
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.55,0:15:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,端起枪
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.76,0:15:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事  他已经死了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.92,0:15:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.64,0:15:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前见过这个
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.39,0:15:15.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟以前一样
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.36,0:15:23.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伙计  你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.85,0:15:33.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你要一个人伏击他们吗  -对
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.43,0:15:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不可以一个人单干
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.85,0:15:37.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.70,0:15:43.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀过他们的人了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.66,0:15:46.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为如果你杀过  并且被他们发现了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.58,0:15:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们也许会认为是神之国干的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.86,0:15:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会失去有利条件
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.34,0:15:55.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是行尸的血
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.20,0:16:00.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能把路障移开吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.34,0:16:15.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你欲抹杀从前的自己吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.24,0:16:20.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有  但是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.62,0:16:26.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知所从
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.50,0:16:30.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让救世军们死吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.41,0:16:33.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-摩根  -是的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.96,0:16:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停止你的愚行
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.80,0:16:40.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加入我的军队
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.07,0:16:45.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救世军好似多头巨龙
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.69,0:16:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兵多将广
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.06,0:16:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须联合盟友与之一战
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.48,0:16:58.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是本杰明的盔甲
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.08,0:17:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你穿着是为了保护自己  还是为了纪念他
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.60,0:17:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩根
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.40,0:17:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\fs10\bord0\shad0\alpha&66\b1\c&HECB000&\move(348,30,348,40,900,1400)\clip(300,30,385,50)}最新海外影视剧下载
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.62,0:17:15.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没有走投无路
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.95,0:17:22.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加入我们的旅程  结为盟友
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.47,0:17:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我们一起战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.29,0:17:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会打败他们  不会再让别人
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.79,0:17:33.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被他们玩弄蹂躏
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.35,0:17:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们为了逝者
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.74,0:17:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了神之国
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.20,0:17:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了胜利的荣耀再次战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.77,0:19:19.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们为何而战
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.10,0:19:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是为了这个地方  而是为了彼此
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.55,0:19:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你们也是我们的一员了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.67,0:19:30.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只拿  不费心  这是我们的方式
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.12,0:19:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许该换种方式了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.02,0:19:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你男人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.46,0:19:42.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.98,0:19:44.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我过后要睡他
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.75,0:19:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你介意吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.57,0:19:53.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-该回去干活了  -是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.52,0:21:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得是他们干的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.88,0:21:07.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想过
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.67,0:21:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有后备计划
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.25,0:21:13.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恕我直言
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.78,0:21:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这突然的阻碍让我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.39,0:21:17.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有机会能好好考虑一下
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.02,0:21:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根据现在的严峻形势
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.47,0:21:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有潜在伤亡和资源消耗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.05,0:21:24.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能不能给我个机会
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.87,0:21:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去劝降他们  让他们冷静
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.82,0:22:02.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以前用过这种枪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.27,0:22:05.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.86,0:22:09.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,担心吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.42,0:22:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.97,0:22:14.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.52,0:22:19.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我去另一个塔  -为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.46,0:22:22.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分头行动视野更好
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.63,0:22:24.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.90,0:22:27.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.51,0:22:29.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.20,0:22:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会赢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.18,0:22:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.84,0:23:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道会发生什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.93,0:23:15.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这会如何结束
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.06,0:23:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道会发生什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.83,0:23:21.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这会如何结束
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.49,0:23:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要一起走出那扇门
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.76,0:23:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同甘共苦
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.06,0:23:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们就是这样  -我们这次可以不管
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.32,0:23:36.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正他们也需要我们留在这
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.42,0:23:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克说要准备好战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.85,0:23:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么死的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.77,0:23:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们当时在沙滩上
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.67,0:23:51.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是在灾变前
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.32,0:23:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你被水卷了进去
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.04,0:23:58.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没能出来
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.57,0:24:04.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试着去找你  但是你不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.22,0:24:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  我开始溺水
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.18,0:24:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我讨厌沙滩
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.64,0:24:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿着橡胶衣玩一天
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.99,0:24:19.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到车上的每一步
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.70,0:24:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛋都像在被喷砂
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.45,0:24:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还好今天不去海边
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.47,0:24:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是守卫和赶路
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.36,0:24:33.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗  来吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.41,0:24:36.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们去帮玛姬  -亚伯拉罕
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.28,0:24:38.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.74,0:24:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里需要我们
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.20,0:24:47.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这一次  我们不逞英雄
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.93,0:24:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-别人...  -应该是我们
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.89,0:24:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬应该靠自己
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.03,0:24:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃过敏药的事
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.91,0:25:03.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有没有改变主意
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.46,0:25:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-有  -很好
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.82,0:25:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你会适应这个地方的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.32,0:25:12.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.82,0:25:14.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不像你
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.95,0:25:16.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每个人都有自己的出路
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.60,0:25:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别因为我的选择批判我
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.42,0:25:21.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,顺便说  你也选的一样
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.25,0:25:25.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果今天有人死  都是自己选的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.59,0:25:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  确实如此
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.61,0:25:34.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在这里做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.61,0:25:39.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等这个
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.53,0:26:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗西塔
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.92,0:26:06.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就位
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.06,0:26:08.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你信号
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.11,0:26:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,墙没问题吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.93,0:26:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.88,0:26:26.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们已被包围
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.38,0:26:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有意外都在考虑内
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.29,0:26:32.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带着真相前来
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.54,0:26:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大考将至  而我给你们带来了小抄
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.07,0:26:53.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.96,0:26:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我前来劝降  因为我知道你们通情达理
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.13,0:27:00.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们没有选择余地
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.12,0:27:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,忠诚服从是唯一出路
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.15,0:27:08.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说白了  你们可生  亦或死
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.99,0:27:11.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我衷心希望是前者
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.46,0:27:12.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了所有人着想
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.90,0:27:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们已经完全暴露了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.20,0:27:21.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们投降吗  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.67,0:27:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.38,0:27:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是尼根
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.07,0:29:40.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.96,0:29:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会赢
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.32,0:29:54.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听过叫瑞克的小傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.51,0:29:57.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以为自己本事大却一无所知
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.53,0:30:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,害自己在乎的人被杀光的故事吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.30,0:30:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说的就是你
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.03,0:30:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们最好都把枪放下
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.49,0:30:11.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都别放下枪
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.39,0:30:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们说好的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.89,0:30:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔米尔去拿船上物资
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.73,0:30:18.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟踪了夺走物资的人
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.32,0:30:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做了笔更好的交易
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.29,0:30:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一而再  再而三地逼我  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.89,0:30:36.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚才想炸了我们是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.43,0:30:40.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想弄死我和我的人  我懂
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.15,0:30:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是尤金呢
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.26,0:30:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可是你的人
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.23,0:30:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他做了那事之后  洗心革面了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:52.12,0:30:53.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们这些人
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.57,0:30:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是禽兽
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.79,0:31:00.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝给了你们启示
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.59,0:31:03.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们却回了个中指  捅了他的菊花
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.07,0:31:10.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德怀特  西蒙  快去
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.92,0:31:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你们不喜欢尤金了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.66,0:31:54.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你们肯定喜欢萨沙
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.30,0:31:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也喜欢她
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.36,0:32:05.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了方便你们  我把她装在这里面了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.28,0:32:08.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,毫发无损
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.09,0:32:14.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带来了她  就不用杀了你们所有人了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.44,0:32:19.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不把你们都杀了  事情会变得很复杂
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.67,0:32:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道里面还有很多武器  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.70,0:32:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的要求很简单
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.51,0:32:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你们想方设法积攒来的所有枪
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.42,0:32:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  这个我也知道
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.96,0:32:40.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你们剩下的所有柠檬粉
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.33,0:32:44.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还要你选一个人
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.80,0:32:47.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,送给露西尔
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.77,0:32:52.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.62,0:32:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得要回我的达里尔
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.46,0:32:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到你了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.41,0:33:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有台球桌
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.17,0:33:04.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全部台球杆和巧粉
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.85,0:33:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在就要
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.85,0:33:09.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然萨沙就得死
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.19,0:33:11.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后你们所有人都得死
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.42,0:33:15.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大概吧
Dialogue: 0,0:33:17.85,0:33:19.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行了  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.69,0:33:22.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把她装在棺材里带来
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.72,0:33:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不意味着她就得死在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.68,0:33:33.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.71,0:33:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你逊毙了  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.49,0:33:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.04,0:33:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想杀她
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.82,0:33:44.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这正是你逼我要做的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.33,0:33:45.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我看看她
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.12,0:33:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  给我点时间
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.15,0:33:55.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也许得跟她说说现在什么情况了
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.69,0:33:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在棺材里可什么都听不到
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.54,0:34:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨沙
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.47,0:34:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你绝对不会相信这破事的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.71,0:34:16.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉很真实
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.90,0:34:21.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉很真实
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.55,0:34:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像是失去了这一切
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.17,0:34:31.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我们才刚刚开始
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.24,0:35:04.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-走吧  -等等
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.82,0:35:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你看穿我的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.06,0:35:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以这次让我来帮帮你吧
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.27,0:35:18.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来你要跟我说的是
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.42,0:35:20.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会去  这样我就可以留下
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.06,0:35:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我知道  你自己也不想说出
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.38,0:35:26.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"玛姬应该靠自己"这种话
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.13,0:35:29.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这句话会萦绕在你脑中
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.97,0:35:31.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久很久
Dialogue: 0,0:35:31.16,0:35:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会因为仅仅有这念头而做出补偿
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.67,0:35:35.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说得对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.46,0:35:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.61,0:35:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们为别人置生死于度外
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.85,0:35:51.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是为别人
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.17,0:35:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都知道  如果我们要死
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.16,0:35:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那最好死得有意义
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.15,0:36:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以或许我们觉得这一切都是有意义的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.76,0:36:04.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自始至终
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.35,0:36:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是在战场  还是在海边
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.10,0:36:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是别的什么地方
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.54,0:36:14.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.74,0:36:18.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她怀着未来
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.94,0:36:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.72,0:36:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就知道会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.38,0:36:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.61,0:36:42.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为别人冒生命危险
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.31,0:36:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为他们扫除障碍
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.21,0:36:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以前说过
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.88,0:36:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这才叫活着
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.62,0:36:59.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是个傻瓜
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.30,0:37:03.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从没说过我不是
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.62,0:37:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去那里要几个小时  对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.40,0:37:26.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.99,0:37:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,路上也许障碍重重
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.41,0:37:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鉴于他们在谋反  道路很可能被监视了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.46,0:37:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"他们在谋反"
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.16,0:37:36.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.01,0:37:40.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在市集拿的  存满了歌
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.37,0:37:42.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在途中恐怕无法交谈
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.84,0:37:45.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管我是个自私的懦夫
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.26,0:37:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有时也会为别人着想
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.50,0:37:50.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,请收下我的馈赠吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.84,0:37:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真心希望我能做好人
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.32,0:37:58.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你依然可以  尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.25,0:38:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会放弃
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.64,0:38:04.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会放弃你
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.59,0:38:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  你不用躺在那玩意儿里面过去
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.60,0:38:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想休息一下
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.12,0:38:16.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.71,0:38:17.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.70,0:38:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想睡觉
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.86,0:38:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我一小瓶水就行了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.07,0:38:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿拉特
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.03,0:38:29.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.28,0:38:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这有多难
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.25,0:38:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很感激
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.61,0:38:54.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死  你真了不得
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.53,0:39:11.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}正在播放\N《总有一天  我们都会自由》\N唐尼·海瑟威
Dialogue: 0,0:40:01.91,0:40:03.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨沙
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.00,0:40:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你绝对不会相信这破事的
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.66,0:40:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的妈呀
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.68,0:40:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走
Dialogue: 0,0:40:55.00,0:40:56.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.84,0:41:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  该死
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.71,0:41:20.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就后备计划吧
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.55,0:41:24.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跪下  快点
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.98,0:41:26.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以重新做笔交易
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.85,0:41:37.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了跪下
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.15,0:42:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又见面了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.96,0:43:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跪下  不然再吃一枪
Dialogue: 0,0:43:24.19,0:43:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:43:26.95,0:43:28.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就不能老实跟着我们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:43:28.67,0:43:32.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非要找这些捡破烂的脏人
Dialogue: 0,0:43:33.84,0:43:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无意冒犯
Dialogue: 0,0:43:35.44,0:43:37.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说好了是12个  对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:43:39.85,0:43:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,10个
Dialogue: 0,0:43:41.77,0:43:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人才是资源
Dialogue: 0,0:43:44.08,0:43:45.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,12个
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.97,0:43:54.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,10个
Dialogue: 0,0:44:02.44,0:44:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:44:05.37,0:44:07.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这会让你难过的
Dialogue: 0,0:44:09.08,0:44:10.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心碎
Dialogue: 0,0:44:10.84,0:44:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会希望你死了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:17.78,0:44:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢闹着玩
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.27,0:44:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的
Dialogue: 0,0:44:22.12,0:44:27.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也许你觉得对你朋友做出那种事的人不是我了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:27.55,0:44:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以为那不过是某种作秀
Dialogue: 0,0:44:30.20,0:44:32.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以为我不是拿着大棒的人
Dialogue: 0,0:44:32.21,0:44:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是个给你孩子做意面的人
Dialogue: 0,0:44:39.80,0:44:41.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠
Dialogue: 0,0:44:41.60,0:44:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许这怪我
Dialogue: 0,0:44:43.20,0:44:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许这全都怪我
Dialogue: 0,0:44:48.23,0:44:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须纠正错误
Dialogue: 0,0:44:52.15,0:44:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜又要重来一遍了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:56.36,0:44:58.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须告诉你  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:44:58.79,0:45:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如我有孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:45:01.18,0:45:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望他跟你孩子一样
Dialogue: 0,0:45:05.28,0:45:08.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以这就更难了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:08.97,0:45:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你赢不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:45:10.66,0:45:11.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡尔
Dialogue: 0,0:45:13.67,0:45:15.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:45:15.64,0:45:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何不用你的独眼
Dialogue: 0,0:45:17.49,0:45:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看那边  感受一下
Dialogue: 0,0:45:27.84,0:45:29.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会赢
Dialogue: 0,0:45:29.95,0:45:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会活
Dialogue: 0,0:45:33.09,0:45:34.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们
Dialogue: 0,0:45:37.30,0:45:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们
Dialogue: 0,0:46:07.66,0:46:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚失去了某个重要的人  就在刚刚
Dialogue: 0,0:46:13.76,0:46:15.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:46:16.18,0:46:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,时机刚好
Dialogue: 0,0:46:22.80,0:46:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:46:25.58,0:46:27.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你选的
Dialogue: 0,0:46:27.55,0:46:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真不知道我还能怎么警告你
Dialogue: 0,0:46:31.30,0:46:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且这不是警告了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:33.69,0:46:35.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是惩罚
Dialogue: 0,0:46:37.85,0:46:40.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我现在要杀了卡尔
Dialogue: 0,0:46:41.29,0:46:46.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会狠狠地  重重地挥一棒
Dialogue: 0,0:46:47.09,0:46:50.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试着一击毙命  因为我喜欢他
Dialogue: 0,0:46:52.73,0:46:54.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想让你把这个念头放进脑子里
Dialogue: 0,0:46:54.48,0:46:56.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,细细回味一下
Dialogue: 0,0:46:56.89,0:47:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会杀了卡尔  然后露西尔
Dialogue: 0,0:47:01.35,0:47:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她会砸烂你的双手
Dialogue: 0,0:47:07.21,0:47:09.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以就在我面前做
Dialogue: 0,0:47:10.10,0:47:12.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以砸烂我的双手
Dialogue: 0,0:47:13.64,0:47:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我已经告诉过你了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:15.83,0:47:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会杀了你
Dialogue: 0,0:47:19.35,0:47:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们所有人
Dialogue: 0,0:47:22.15,0:47:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许不在今天  也许不在明天
Dialogue: 0,0:47:26.67,0:47:30.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但没有什么能改变这点
Dialogue: 0,0:47:30.23,0:47:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有什么
Dialogue: 0,0:47:34.49,0:47:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们已经死了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:53.97,0:47:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠
Dialogue: 0,0:47:58.12,0:48:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:48:03.97,0:48:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:48:11.51,0:48:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说了我可以做
Dialogue: 0,0:48:24.00,0:48:26.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灭了救世军和他们的同伙
Dialogue: 0,0:48:28.44,0:48:32.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚历山大不会陷落  不在今天
Dialogue: 0,0:48:46.19,0:48:48.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,方形阵  第三队  上
Dialogue: 0,0:48:48.60,0:48:50.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上  我们掩护你们
Dialogue: 0,0:49:01.14,0:49:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他妈的一头老虎啊
Dialogue: 0,0:49:14.98,0:49:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那寡妇没死  活蹦乱跳的
Dialogue: 0,0:49:19.97,0:49:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你尝到了吗  西蒙  这就是吃屎的滋味
Dialogue: 0,0:50:39.31,0:50:40.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们撤退了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:40.76,0:50:42.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱德华多  伯蒂  去房屋之间
Dialogue: 0,0:50:42.33,0:50:43.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掩护大门
Dialogue: 0,0:50:44.96,0:50:45.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:50:49.23,0:50:51.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在收尾
Dialogue: 0,0:51:53.62,0:51:54.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上
Dialogue: 0,0:51:59.90,0:52:00.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉
Dialogue: 0,0:53:03.03,0:53:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米琼恩
Dialogue: 0,0:53:06.99,0:53:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米琼恩
Dialogue: 0,0:53:11.00,0:53:12.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:53:28.15,0:53:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们...
Dialogue: 0,0:53:33.96,0:53:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们...
Dialogue: 0,0:53:35.02,0:53:37.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:53:37.70,0:53:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:53:41.11,0:53:42.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们活下来了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:45.54,0:53:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:54:08.59,0:54:11.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准备已就绪
Dialogue: 0,0:54:11.85,0:54:13.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都是蓝色警戒
Dialogue: 0,0:54:14.74,0:54:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你下令  他们就出发
Dialogue: 0,0:54:18.30,0:54:19.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:54:31.72,0:54:35.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得她怎么会死在棺材里
Dialogue: 0,0:54:37.92,0:54:41.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最可能的原因是油布
Dialogue: 0,0:54:42.14,0:54:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,棺材被封得严严实实
Dialogue: 0,0:54:46.07,0:54:47.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没氧气了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:04.61,0:55:05.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧
Dialogue: 0,0:55:20.35,0:55:21.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么
Dialogue: 0,0:55:28.15,0:55:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要开战了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:30.11,0:55:31.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命
Dialogue: 0,0:55:43.52,0:55:45.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得萨沙是一个人做到的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:55:48.20,0:55:51.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道怎么做到的  但我知道她做到了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:57.17,0:55:59.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她给了我们机会  你给了我们机会
Dialogue: 0,0:56:00.18,0:56:02.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你选择过来是正确的
Dialogue: 0,0:56:04.90,0:56:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这选择很早以前就做了
Dialogue: 0,0:56:09.25,0:56:11.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们大家相识之前
Dialogue: 0,0:56:13.02,0:56:16.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我们还是在街上擦肩而过的陌生人时
Dialogue: 0,0:56:16.04,0:56:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在世界结束之前
Dialogue: 0,0:56:20.81,0:56:23.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我们对彼此意味着一切
Dialogue: 0,0:57:01.96,0:57:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你遇到了麻烦  你陷入了困境
Dialogue: 0,0:57:06.00,0:57:08.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格伦不认识你  但他救了你
Dialogue: 0,0:57:09.65,0:57:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他为你冒了生命危险
Dialogue: 0,0:57:15.49,0:57:17.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是一切的源头
Dialogue: 0,0:57:19.07,0:57:22.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从亚特兰大  到我爸爸的农场
Dialogue: 0,0:57:23.62,0:57:24.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到监狱
Dialogue: 0,0:57:26.29,0:57:27.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到这里
Dialogue: 0,0:57:36.52,0:57:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此时此刻
Dialogue: 0,0:57:42.20,0:57:43.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不再是陌生人
Dialogue: 0,0:57:45.95,0:57:47.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是家人
Dialogue: 0,0:58:08.69,0:58:13.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}当时不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:58:20.87,0:58:25.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为格伦那天选择救了你
Dialogue: 0,0:58:26.58,0:58:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久很久以前
Dialogue: 0,0:58:29.33,0:58:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而那个选择改变了一切
Dialogue: 0,0:58:41.07,0:58:42.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你们俩发起的
Dialogue: 0,0:58:43.46,0:58:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后不断壮大
Dialogue: 0,0:58:46.91,0:58:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今我们所有人
Dialogue: 0,0:58:52.29,0:58:54.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为彼此做出牺牲
Dialogue: 0,0:59:09.01,0:59:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,承受苦难
Dialogue: 0,0:59:12.25,0:59:16.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去哀悼  去给予
Dialogue: 0,0:59:17.33,0:59:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去爱  去生活
Dialogue: 0,0:59:23.65,0:59:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去为彼此而战
Dialogue: 0,0:59:30.90,0:59:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格伦做出了那个选择  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:59:35.38,0:59:37.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不过是在追随他的脚步
Dialogue: 0,0:59:43.50,0:59:46.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8\bord1\fs18\b1}纪念伯尼·怀特森(1948-2017)\N[注:惊悚漫画大师  沼泽怪物之父\N作品影响了多位《行尸》剧组成员\N与癌症抗争多年后辞世]
