1
00:00:03,630 --> 00:00:05,330
我看到你了
I can see you.

2
00:00:07,780 --> 00:00:08,780
出來
Come out.

3
00:00:09,360 --> 00:00:10,670
慢慢地
Slowly.

4
00:00:13,360 --> 00:00:15,310
我看還是免了吧
Yeah, I think I'm gonna pass on that.

5
00:01:02,710 --> 00:01:07,020
行尸走肉
『第六季  第十五集』

6
00:01:02,710 --> 00:01:07,020
本藍光版外掛字幕由  風吹來的那片云  用WEB版調軸

7
00:01:11,570 --> 00:01:16,080
我們在這里擁有很多
人  食物  藥品  圍墻
一切生存必需品

8
00:01:16,870 --> 00:01:21,880
m 330 133 l 343 133 l 343 125 l 330 125 m 330 122 l 343 122 l 343 115 l 330 115 m 330 112 l 343 112 l 343 104 l 330 104 m 322 136 l 322 133 l 327 133 l 327 101 l 346 101 l 346 133 l 350 133 l 350 136 m 316 121 b 316 121 316 121 316 121 b 316 121 320 121 323 121 b 323 121 323 123 323 123 b 318 124 315 124 311 125 l 311 122 b 311 122 317 114 317 114 b 317 114 317 114 317 114 b 316 113 310 115 310 115 l 310 112 b 310 112 317 99 317 99 l 320 100 b 317 105 316 107 314 112 b 313 112 314 112 313 112 b 320 112 322 105 322 105 l 325 107 b 325 107 316 121 316 121 m 310 131 b 313 131 318 130 324 129 l 324 131 b 319 132 315 133 310 134 m 296 126 b 296 125 293 124 293 123 l 288 123 l 288 126 m 281 123 b 280 123 277 126 277 126 l 285 126 l 285 123 m 276 116 l 298 116 l 298 113 l 276 113 m 276 111 l 298 111 l 298 109 l 276 109 m 291 99 l 294 99 l 294 101 l 306 101 l 305 104 l 294 104 l 294 106 l 291 106 l 291 104 l 282 104 l 282 106 l 279 106 l 279 104 l 268 104 l 268 101 l 279 101 l 279 98 l 282 98 l 282 101 l 291 101 m 268 120 l 278 120 b 280 119 280 119 278 120 b 280 119 280 119 280 119 l 272 119 l 272 106 l 301 106 l 301 118 l 287 118 b 285 118 284 119 283 120 l 305 120 l 305 123 l 297 123 b 299 123 297 123 307 128 b 306 128 307 128 305 131 b 301 128 300 128 300 128 l 300 130 b 300 134 297 135 297 135 l 291 135 b 291 135 291 135 291 132 b 291 132 291 133 291 133 b 292 132 292 132 297 132 b 297 130 297 130 297 131 l 297 129 l 288 129 l 288 138 l 285 138 l 285 129 l 277 129 l 277 136 l 274 136 l 274 127 b 274 127 274 127 268 131 b 268 131 268 131 266 129 b 266 129 272 125 276 123 l 268 123 m 244 98 l 244 98 b 244 98 246 103 247 104 l 244 104 l 263 104 l 263 112 l 259 112 l 259 108 l 229 108 l 229 113 l 225 113 l 225 104 l 244 104 b 244 104 241 99 244 104 b 244 104 241 99 241 99 m 242 119 l 251 115 l 231 115 l 231 112 l 256 112 l 256 116 l 246 121 l 246 122 l 264 122 l 264 125 l 246 125 l 246 129 b 246 134 246 137 243 138 l 235 138 b 235 138 234 134 234 134 b 236 134 236 134 242 134 b 242 134 242 130 242 130 l 242 125 l 224 125 l 224 122 l 242 122 m 210 58 l 192 58 l 192 54 l 210 54 m 225 55 l 239 56 l 261 28 l 245 28 l 225 53 b 224 49 221 45 216 46 l 178 46 l 178 66 l 193 66 l 193 77 l 189 77 l 191 68 l 178 68 l 174 87 l 188 87 l 190 81 l 193 87 l 209 87 l 209 66 l 225 66 m 192 19 l 210 19 l 210 21 l 192 21 m 192 9 l 210 9 l 210 12 l 192 12 m 228 34 l 210 34 l 209 31 l 226 31 l 226 27 l 238 27 l 261 0 l 244 0 l 226 22 l 225 22 l 225 6 b 225 3 224 0 217 0 l 177 0 l 176 30 l 193 30 l 193 34 l 174 34 l 174 43 l 227 43 m 246 57 l 226 79 l 224 69 l 212 69 l 215 85 l 223 84 l 222 87 l 238 87 l 261 57 m 336 77 l 336 59 l 329 58 l 329 14 l 315 14 l 315 49 l 291 87 l 306 87 l 324 58 l 324 87 l 346 87 l 350 77 m 310 10 l 334 10 l 335 56 l 345 56 l 345 6 b 345 4 343 0 339 0 l 298 0 l 298 56 l 310 56 m 295 36 l 286 36 l 295 21 l 295 10 l 288 10 l 284 0 l 267 0 l 272 10 l 261 10 l 261 20 l 279 20 l 260 51 l 270 51 l 270 86 l 283 87 l 283 42 l 285 39 l 287 64 l 297 64 m 155 87 l 129 35 l 104 87 l 84 87 l 128 0 l 146 0 l 132 30 l 146 30 l 174 87 m 66 87 l 39 35 l 14 87 l -5 87 l 38 0 l 56 0 l 42 30 l 56 30 l 84 87 m 203 138 l 199 138 l 190 111 l 194 111 l 201 133 b 201 134 201 134 201 133 l 209 111 l 213 111 m 188 135 l 188 137 b 183 137 188 137 183 137 b 183 137 179 138 179 134 l 179 115 l 176 115 l 176 111 l 179 111 l 179 104 l 183 103 l 183 111 l 187 111 l 187 115 l 183 115 l 183 135 b 183 135 183 135 188 135 m 166 132 l 171 132 l 171 137 l 166 137 m 154 111 l 158 111 l 158 137 l 155 137 l 155 133 b 153 136 151 138 145 137 b 143 138 139 137 136 132 l 136 111 l 140 111 l 140 127 b 140 131 139 134 146 135 b 151 135 153 132 154 128 m 110 134 l 132 134 l 132 137 l 104 137 l 104 135 l 126 105 l 107 105 l 107 102 l 131 102 l 131 105 m 96 111 l 100 111 l 100 137 l 97 137 l 97 133 b 94 135 93 138 88 138 b 85 138 81 136 79 130 l 79 111 l 83 111 l 83 130 b 84 133 86 135 89 135 b 94 135 97 130 96 123 m 69 107 l 57 137 l 54 137 l 42 107 l 42 137 l 38 137 l 38 102 l 43 102 l 56 132 l 67 102 l 73 102 l 73 137 l 69 137 m 27 111 l 31 111 l 31 137 l 27 137 m 27 102 l 31 102 l 31 106 l 27 106 m 0 135 l 23 135 l 23 137 l -5 137 l -5 135 l 17 105 l -3 105 l -3 102 l 22 102 l 22 104

9
00:01:16,870 --> 00:01:21,880
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

10
00:01:16,870 --> 00:01:21,880
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

11
00:01:16,870 --> 00:01:21,880
m 195 227 l 228 227 l 149 147 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 180 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 l 163 71 m 134 164 l 195 227 l 228 227 l 150 148 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 177 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147

12
00:01:17,870 --> 00:01:21,880
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.ZiMuZu.tv

13
00:01:17,870 --> 00:01:21,880
■

14
00:01:17,870 --> 00:01:21,880
原創翻譯  雙語字幕

15
00:01:21,870 --> 00:01:26,870
翻譯：冰藍 Reginamoon 自然卷

16
00:01:21,880 --> 00:01:56,870
■

17
00:01:21,880 --> 00:01:46,880
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

18
00:01:21,880 --> 00:01:46,880
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

19
00:01:21,880 --> 00:01:46,880
m 195 227 l 228 227 l 149 147 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 180 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 l 163 71 m 134 164 l 195 227 l 228 227 l 150 148 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 177 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147

20
00:01:26,870 --> 00:01:31,870
翻譯：艾瑞卡 小酸奶 送小孩

21
00:01:31,870 --> 00:01:36,870
校對：君君 送小孩

22
00:01:36,870 --> 00:01:41,870
時間軸：濤濤 加森

23
00:01:41,870 --> 00:01:46,870
后期：吉吉  拉圖   總監：送小孩

24
00:01:55,480 --> 00:01:56,650
卡蘿爾
Carol?

25
00:01:57,450 --> 00:01:58,510
你在嗎
You here?

26
00:02:02,690 --> 00:02:04,060
樓上
Upstairs.

27
00:02:09,130 --> 00:02:10,140
你好嗎
How are you?

28
00:02:10,360 --> 00:02:11,920
見到你真開心
Happy to see you.

29
00:02:15,230 --> 00:02:16,470
發生了什么
What happened?

30
00:02:16,570 --> 00:02:18,270
滑了一跤
Oh, I just slipped.

31
00:02:18,800 --> 00:02:20,760
在建新哨塔的時候
Building a new guard tower.

32
00:02:21,810 --> 00:02:23,140
我去了醫務室
I went to the infirmary.

33
00:02:24,080 --> 00:02:26,040
那里現在好安靜
It's so quiet over there now.

34
00:02:27,840 --> 00:02:30,450
從災變一開始我就認識丹妮斯了
I knew Denise since the beginning.

35
00:02:31,710 --> 00:02:34,990
皮特還在的時候  她不太出來
She wasn't around much before Pete, but...

36
00:02:36,030 --> 00:02:38,540
在那之前  她總是待在家里
before that, she just stayed inside.

37
00:02:39,410 --> 00:02:41,770
她總是在讀書
She was always-- was always reading something.

38
00:02:43,540 --> 00:02:46,430
她在必要的時候站了出來
And she really stepped up when she had to.

39
00:02:46,430 --> 00:02:48,180
她為我們站了出來
She was there for us.

40
00:03:00,840 --> 00:03:02,130
我不是有意提起這個
I didn't mean to bring it up.

41
00:03:02,580 --> 00:03:05,060
不  只是...
No, it's just--

42
00:03:06,330 --> 00:03:09,320
我一直擔心塔拉  擔心她得知這事
I just keep thinking about Tara, when she finds out.

43
00:03:11,580 --> 00:03:14,400
一切都會沒事的
Hey, everything's gonna be okay.

44
00:03:15,130 --> 00:03:16,310
是啊
Yeah.

45
00:07:10,960 --> 00:07:12,430
真好
This is good.

46
00:07:12,660 --> 00:07:14,750
是啊
Mm, it is.

47
00:07:18,000 --> 00:07:19,780
耶穌證明了自己
Jesus came through.

48
00:07:19,780 --> 00:07:21,070
他們都證明了自己
They all did.

49
00:07:22,210 --> 00:07:24,330
他們會繼續證明自己的
And they're all gonna keep coming through.

50
00:07:24,940 --> 00:07:26,230
瑪姬讓我和格倫
Maggie asked me and Glenn

51
00:07:26,230 --> 00:07:28,940
幫著安置更多的槍桶和哨崗
to help put up more bins and watch points.

52
00:07:33,620 --> 00:07:35,540
別走
S-stick around.

53
00:07:36,550 --> 00:07:39,630
朱迪斯還沒醒呢
Judith-- Judith isn't even up yet.

54
00:07:42,650 --> 00:07:44,580
等等  不不不
Wait, no. No, no, no, no.

55
00:07:44,580 --> 00:07:46,590
-是嗎  為什么不  -不
- Yeah? Why not? - No.

56
00:07:47,490 --> 00:07:49,700
瑪姬給我們排好班了
Maggie has us on a schedule

57
00:07:49,700 --> 00:07:53,220
我可不想惹一個懷孕的女士
and I'm not pissing off a pregnant lady.

58
00:07:55,040 --> 00:07:56,250
是啊
Yeah.

59
00:07:56,540 --> 00:07:59,210
-別惹那個懷孕的女士  -沒錯
- Not that pregnant lady. - Right.

60
00:08:00,010 --> 00:08:01,600
去吧
Go.

61
00:08:09,720 --> 00:08:11,640
她擔心我們遭到襲擊
She's worried about an attack.

62
00:08:14,160 --> 00:08:17,780
如果他們來找我們  我們就終結了
When they come for us, we'll end it,

63
00:08:17,780 --> 00:08:19,000
終結這一切
the whole thing.

64
00:08:19,560 --> 00:08:21,530
這次跟以前不一樣
This won't be like before.

65
00:08:23,000 --> 00:08:24,530
我們準備妥當
We're putting everything in place

66
00:08:24,540 --> 00:08:26,370
人們現在知道該做什么
and these people know what to do now.

67
00:08:29,210 --> 00:08:31,120
這個世界屬于我們
The world's ours,

68
00:08:31,740 --> 00:08:33,810
而且我們知道該如何拿下
and we know how to take it.

69
00:08:39,580 --> 00:08:41,030
我們需要的一切
Everything we need

70
00:08:42,090 --> 00:08:45,360
都在墻內
is right here inside these walls.

71
00:08:47,190 --> 00:08:49,460
我們不會再失去了
We're not losing any of it again.

72
00:08:50,410 --> 00:08:51,930
我不會
I'm not.

73
00:08:52,400 --> 00:08:53,690
不  你不會
No, you're not.

74
00:09:00,840 --> 00:09:02,220
我不會
I'm not.

75
00:09:11,820 --> 00:09:13,990
這些留著  但也應該藏幾把
We'll have these, but we should hide a few.

76
00:09:14,390 --> 00:09:16,500
那樣的話  我們找得到  外人找不到
That way, we can find them, but strangers can't.

77
00:09:17,160 --> 00:09:18,520
以防有人闖進來
In case anyone gets in.

78
00:09:20,520 --> 00:09:21,760
他們闖不進來的
They won't.

79
00:09:24,130 --> 00:09:25,570
糟了
Oh, no.

80
00:09:33,620 --> 00:09:34,850
你要去哪
Where are you going?

81
00:09:35,630 --> 00:09:36,650
外面
Out.

82
00:09:36,810 --> 00:09:38,780
扯淡  具體去哪
No, shit. You got specifics?

83
00:09:39,640 --> 00:09:41,100
他到底在干什么
What the hell is he doing?

84
00:09:41,100 --> 00:09:42,590
干他不該干的事
Something he shouldn't.

85
00:09:42,780 --> 00:09:44,080
我們得去制止他
We gotta stop him.

86
00:10:00,360 --> 00:10:01,980
給老子也騰個位置
Make room for my freckled ass.

87
00:10:01,980 --> 00:10:03,090
不行
No.

88
00:10:03,100 --> 00:10:05,190
替我站崗  你留下
Cover my watch. You stay.

89
00:10:05,190 --> 00:10:07,000
得有足夠人手留在這里
Hey, we should keep numbers here.

90
00:10:07,000 --> 00:10:08,560
我知道達里爾要去哪
I know where Daryl's going.

91
00:10:40,670 --> 00:10:42,280
她什么時候離開的
What time did she leave?

92
00:10:42,280 --> 00:10:43,020
你知道她帶了什么嗎
Do you know what she took?

93
00:10:43,020 --> 00:10:44,690
她是夜里離開的  我沒聽見她走
Sometime in the night. I never heard her go,

94
00:10:44,690 --> 00:10:46,170
但她做了一大堆吃的
but she made a bunch of food, you know.

95
00:10:46,170 --> 00:10:46,810
帶走了她的背包
She took her pack,

96
00:10:46,810 --> 00:10:48,650
-拿了我一件外套...  -她是步行離開的嗎
- one of my coats-- - Did she leave on foot?

97
00:10:48,650 --> 00:10:49,750
我...我不知道
I-- I don't know.

98
00:10:50,180 --> 00:10:53,360
瑞克  我十二點接的班  待到六點
Rick, I took over at 12:00, I was on till 6:00.

99
00:10:53,360 --> 00:10:54,900
我什么也沒看見
I never saw anything.

100
00:10:54,900 --> 00:10:57,050
在他們出去之后  前門一直沒動靜
Front's been quiet since the others left.

101
00:10:57,270 --> 00:10:58,780
什么  誰出去了
What? Who?

102
00:10:58,780 --> 00:11:01,370
達里爾  他出去找昨天那幫救世軍尋仇了
Daryl. He went ICBM after the Saviors from yesterday.

103
00:11:01,400 --> 00:11:03,210
格倫  米瓊恩  羅西塔
Glenn, Michonne, Rosita,

104
00:11:03,210 --> 00:11:05,030
他們都追出去阻止他了
they all went to shut that shit down.

105
00:11:06,330 --> 00:11:07,710
另一輛車哪去了
Where's the other car?

106
00:11:09,770 --> 00:11:11,820
我們昨天多擺了兩輛車
We added two more cars yesterday.

107
00:11:11,820 --> 00:11:12,890
現在有一輛不見了
One of them's missing,

108
00:11:12,890 --> 00:11:14,880
就是擺在那些房子中間的那輛
the one we put right between those houses.

109
00:11:14,880 --> 00:11:17,150
從上面基本看不清那些房子中間的情況
You can barely see between the houses from up top,

110
00:11:17,620 --> 00:11:18,920
特別是在晚上
especially at night.

111
00:11:18,920 --> 00:11:20,290
那張紙條  能給我看看嗎
The note, can I see it?

112
00:11:21,540 --> 00:11:24,090
你沒看見車頭燈車尾燈亮起來嗎
You never saw any headlights, taillights?

113
00:11:24,090 --> 00:11:26,040
她很聰明  知道如何掩藏蹤跡
She's smart enough to cover her tracks.

114
00:11:26,450 --> 00:11:28,370
她一定是趁著換班的時候溜走的
She must've left during the shift change.

115
00:11:29,630 --> 00:11:30,750
你要去哪
Where are you going?

116
00:11:31,080 --> 00:11:32,440
我去找她
I'm gonna go find her.

117
00:11:32,890 --> 00:11:34,180
等等
Wait.

118
00:11:37,190 --> 00:11:38,860
告訴卡爾我馬上回來
Tell Carl I'll be back soon.

119
00:11:38,860 --> 00:11:40,730
其他任何人都不準離開
No one else leaves.

120
00:11:40,740 --> 00:11:43,020
全員做好戰斗準備
Everyone else stays ready for a fight.

121
00:13:16,160 --> 00:13:17,260
舉起手來
Hands up.

122
00:13:20,060 --> 00:13:21,540
求求你們別傷害我
Please don't hurt me.

123
00:13:22,610 --> 00:13:25,270
為何大家總是把情況往最糟的方向想呢
Why does everyone always assume the worst?

124
00:13:26,450 --> 00:13:28,030
你從車里出來如何
How 'bout you come on out?

125
00:13:41,600 --> 00:13:43,300
我只有這輛車
I just have the car.

126
00:13:49,690 --> 00:13:53,060
以及一把對付行尸的小刀  沒別的了
And a knife for the dead ones, nothing else.

127
00:13:54,320 --> 00:13:57,310
不  你有情報
Naw, you got information.

128
00:13:57,840 --> 00:14:00,850
比如你是打哪里來的  要到哪里去
Like where you're from, where you're going.

129
00:14:03,580 --> 00:14:05,140
說嘛  這是個孤獨的世界
Come on, it's a lonely world.

130
00:14:05,140 --> 00:14:06,890
我們互相認識一下嘛
Let's get to know each other.

131
00:14:07,210 --> 00:14:08,480
我叫希羅
I'm Jiro.

132
00:14:09,240 --> 00:14:10,340
該你了
Your turn.

133
00:14:11,780 --> 00:14:13,580
我誰也不是  真的
I'm nobody, really.

134
00:14:15,790 --> 00:14:18,140
我叫南希  來自蒙特克萊爾
Nancy from Montclair.

135
00:14:21,610 --> 00:14:23,570
但我一直漂泊不定
But I've bounced around a lot since then.

136
00:14:23,570 --> 00:14:25,700
四處奔波
I-- I keep moving.

137
00:14:27,850 --> 00:14:31,030
我沒從哪里來  也沒打算到哪里去
I'm not really from anywhere. I'm not really going anywhere.

138
00:14:33,660 --> 00:14:35,110
至少我們在一件事上達成了共識
At least we agree on one thing,

139
00:14:35,110 --> 00:14:36,670
蒙特克萊爾來的南希
Nancy from Montclair--

140
00:14:37,750 --> 00:14:39,330
你哪里也去不成
you're not going anywhere.

141
00:14:41,110 --> 00:14:44,230
但你看起來確實像是從某個地方來的
But you do seem like you're from somewhere.

142
00:14:45,010 --> 00:14:46,810
在你離開蒙特克萊爾后  是吧
After Montclair, right?

143
00:14:48,200 --> 00:14:50,690
邁爾斯  那地方叫什么來著
Miles, what's that place called?

144
00:14:50,790 --> 00:14:52,250
那個帶柵門的社區
The gated one.

145
00:14:52,250 --> 00:14:54,760
離這12.75公里
12.75 clicks down?

146
00:14:54,770 --> 00:14:56,340
亞歷山大
Alexandria.

147
00:14:56,560 --> 00:14:59,550
對  亞歷山大
Yeah, Alexandria.

148
00:14:59,570 --> 00:15:02,160
那里的前門外停著一些車  插著木棍
You know, they got some cars out front, spikes through them,

149
00:15:02,160 --> 00:15:04,900
就像你開的這輛一樣
just like the one you're driving.

150
00:15:06,000 --> 00:15:07,620
你這樣的女人
A woman like you,

151
00:15:07,930 --> 00:15:12,510
手無寸鐵  毫無防衛  一無所知
no weapons, no protection, no clue,

152
00:15:13,720 --> 00:15:15,780
真不應該一個人出來
you really shouldn't be out here alone.

153
00:15:17,110 --> 00:15:19,540
我們正要去你們那
You know, we were just on our way to your place.

154
00:15:19,540 --> 00:15:21,360
我們可以送你一程
We can give you a ride back.

155
00:15:21,670 --> 00:15:25,000
也許有你陪著  他們會讓我們進去
Maybe they'll let us in if you're with us.

156
00:15:56,840 --> 00:15:58,110
不用這樣的
It doesn't have to be this way.

157
00:15:58,110 --> 00:16:00,260
你們可以掉頭回家
You could turn back and you could go home.

158
00:16:00,260 --> 00:16:02,540
沒人會受傷
Nobody has to get hurt.

159
00:16:03,560 --> 00:16:05,730
看來有人要受傷了
It's looking like someone's gotta get hurt.

160
00:16:07,680 --> 00:16:08,650
求你了
Please.

161
00:16:10,990 --> 00:16:11,490
求你了
Please.

162
00:16:11,490 --> 00:16:12,830
伙計  不如趁現在抓住她
Man, why don't you just grab her

163
00:16:12,830 --> 00:16:14,330
免得她待會兒暈過去了
before she passes out?

164
00:16:17,010 --> 00:16:18,630
不要  求你們了
Don't, please!

165
00:17:30,510 --> 00:17:31,830
我看到你了
I can see you.

166
00:17:32,120 --> 00:17:34,590
慢慢地出來
Come out slowly.

167
00:17:35,830 --> 00:17:37,560
我看還是免了吧
I think I'm gonna pass on that.

168
00:18:18,190 --> 00:18:19,140
你看起來很疲倦
You look tired.

169
00:18:19,140 --> 00:18:20,830
我們還有很多事要做
We still have a lot to do.

170
00:18:21,890 --> 00:18:24,570
格倫  米瓊恩和羅西塔追著達里爾出去了
Glenn, Michonne, and Rosita just took off after Daryl.

171
00:18:24,840 --> 00:18:25,900
我要多輪一班
I'm taking an extra shift.

172
00:18:25,900 --> 00:18:28,290
先來把午餐打包帶走
Just packing a lunch before I go back out.

173
00:18:32,320 --> 00:18:34,150
-回見  -你要去哪
- See you later. - Where are you going?

174
00:18:34,160 --> 00:18:35,760
在你休息時幫你輪班
Take your shift while you rest.

175
00:18:35,760 --> 00:18:36,720
伊妮德
Enid...

176
00:18:38,200 --> 00:18:39,660
就幾個小時而已
Just for a few hours.

177
00:18:42,080 --> 00:18:43,180
讓我幫忙吧
Let me help.

178
00:18:43,700 --> 00:18:46,190
好好休息  吃點泡菜
Put up your feet and eat some pickles.

179
00:18:57,650 --> 00:18:59,490
你用不著跟來的
You didn't have to come.

180
00:19:00,660 --> 00:19:04,360
我們必須試試  就算機會渺茫
We have to try, even if it's a long shot,

181
00:19:04,360 --> 00:19:06,120
就算危機四伏
even if it's dangerous.

182
00:19:08,270 --> 00:19:10,340
輪胎印是向東的
Tire tracks pointed east...

183
00:19:11,940 --> 00:19:13,260
我們去東面
we go east.

184
00:19:14,060 --> 00:19:19,240
你和隊伍去的地方  那個救世軍的基地
Saviors' compound that you and the group-- that you went to,

185
00:19:20,290 --> 00:19:21,620
那是西面
that was west.

186
00:19:26,660 --> 00:19:28,510
看起來她去了東面
Seems like she went east.

187
00:19:35,820 --> 00:19:38,100
你一點都不了解卡蘿爾
You don't even know Carol.

188
00:19:39,500 --> 00:19:40,760
我了解的
Oh, I got to.

189
00:19:41,730 --> 00:19:42,760
了解一點
A little.

190
00:19:48,540 --> 00:19:50,290
你為什么這么做
Why are you doing this?

191
00:19:54,740 --> 00:19:58,320
我所信仰的  未必正確
What I believe-- I'm not right.

192
00:19:59,520 --> 00:20:02,310
不存在所謂的正確
There is no right.

193
00:20:03,190 --> 00:20:05,640
只存在沒有拖垮你的錯誤
There's just the wrong that doesn't pull you down.

194
00:20:12,090 --> 00:20:13,810
它還沒有拖垮我
It hasn't pulled me down.

195
00:20:16,910 --> 00:20:18,250
我想它會的
I think it will.

196
00:20:21,270 --> 00:20:22,710
因為我了解你
'Cause I know you.

197
00:20:34,160 --> 00:20:35,500
該死的
God dang--!

198
00:20:42,490 --> 00:20:43,860
天啊
Oh, man.

199
00:21:08,230 --> 00:21:11,230
放棄吧伙計  別掙扎了
Just let it go, man. Just let go.

200
00:21:24,620 --> 00:21:25,380
天啊
God.

201
00:21:40,920 --> 00:21:41,850
在那
There.

202
00:21:42,300 --> 00:21:43,410
我看到了
I see it.

203
00:22:00,980 --> 00:22:02,580
那是她的車
That's her car.

204
00:22:05,880 --> 00:22:06,850
看到她了嗎
You see her?

205
00:22:12,510 --> 00:22:13,310
沒有
No.

206
00:22:24,490 --> 00:22:25,770
她在哪
Where is she?

207
00:22:49,320 --> 00:22:53,050
救世軍之前從山頂寨鐵匠那拿過武器
The Saviors were getting weapons from the Hilltop's blacksmith.

208
00:22:53,050 --> 00:22:54,710
這些人是救世軍
These men were Saviors.

209
00:23:10,040 --> 00:23:11,270
這里有血
There's blood here.

210
00:23:12,960 --> 00:23:14,380
她可能中槍了
She could've been hit.

211
00:23:20,050 --> 00:23:21,620
我為她感到驕傲
I'm proud of her.

212
00:23:22,540 --> 00:23:23,520
為什么
How's that?

213
00:23:25,410 --> 00:23:27,470
她干掉了四個人
She took four of them down.

214
00:23:28,720 --> 00:23:30,970
那個女人  她非常強大
That woman, she's a force of nature.

215
00:23:30,970 --> 00:23:33,270
她離開是因為她不能再殺人了
She left because she can't anymore.

216
00:23:33,640 --> 00:23:35,240
她信里是這么說的
That's what her letter said.

217
00:23:35,240 --> 00:23:37,390
她能的  因為她必須這樣做
She could because she had to.

218
00:23:38,540 --> 00:23:40,200
有些時候你必須這樣做
Sometimes you have to.

219
00:23:43,000 --> 00:23:46,450
對面有更多的血
There's more blood opposite these men

220
00:23:46,450 --> 00:23:48,310
一直到田地里
that leads into the field.

221
00:23:48,520 --> 00:23:50,960
可能是卡蘿爾留下的蹤跡
It's a trail. Could be Carol's.

222
00:23:50,960 --> 00:23:52,600
她可能還活著
She could still be alive.

223
00:23:52,870 --> 00:23:54,160
她不在這
She's not here.

224
00:23:54,650 --> 00:23:56,720
他們的槍很多都不見了
Most of their guns are gone.

225
00:23:57,210 --> 00:23:59,280
-估計她拿走了  -還有這些
- She might've taken them. - Those, too.

226
00:24:02,690 --> 00:24:04,480
也有可能她死在這了
Or she could've died here,

227
00:24:06,270 --> 00:24:08,140
即便她現在不在這
even if she isn't here.

228
00:24:10,100 --> 00:24:11,420
蹤跡向這邊去了
Trail goes this way.

229
00:24:17,970 --> 00:24:20,100
他們離亞歷山大很近
They were close to Alexandria.

230
00:24:21,920 --> 00:24:23,510
他們還有更多人
There's even more of them.

231
00:24:25,250 --> 00:24:26,450
我們沒能斬草除根
We didn't end it.

232
00:24:27,050 --> 00:24:27,860
不
No.

233
00:24:29,480 --> 00:24:31,070
你挑起了事端
You started something.

234
00:25:48,710 --> 00:25:50,030
她就死在這里
That's where she died.

235
00:25:54,610 --> 00:25:56,490
好吧  那他肯定是從這里開始的
All right, so he had to start from here.

236
00:26:02,080 --> 00:26:03,060
沒錯
He did.

237
00:26:04,580 --> 00:26:05,920
德懷特往哪邊跑的
Which way did Dwight run?

238
00:26:10,140 --> 00:26:11,150
羅西塔
Rosita?

239
00:26:14,880 --> 00:26:16,260
我們該讓他放手去干
We should let him do this.

240
00:26:17,980 --> 00:26:19,900
但他不知道他在干什么
But he doesn't know what he's doing.

241
00:26:21,110 --> 00:26:22,140
我們也不知道
We don't.

242
00:26:23,730 --> 00:26:26,430
或許他這么做  現在是會讓你心里好受點
Maybe him trying this makes you feel better about it right now.

243
00:26:26,600 --> 00:26:29,890
或許這會讓敵人對我們的了解越來越多
Maybe they keep knowing more about us than we know about them.

244
00:26:30,620 --> 00:26:34,630
或許達里爾會害死自己
Or maybe Daryl's gonna get himself killed.

245
00:26:38,050 --> 00:26:39,710
德懷特往哪邊跑的
Which way did Dwight run?

246
00:27:29,280 --> 00:27:30,810
你看清楚點人  混蛋
Watch the hell out, asshole.

247
00:27:30,810 --> 00:27:32,450
我看清楚了  你們不該來的
I did. You shouldn't have come.

248
00:27:32,450 --> 00:27:34,030
你不該離開的
You shouldn't have left.

249
00:27:36,710 --> 00:27:38,730
我之前跟薩沙和亞伯拉罕分開時
When I split off from Sasha and Abraham,

250
00:27:39,000 --> 00:27:40,090
他和那幫女的
he was out there in the woods,

251
00:27:40,090 --> 00:27:41,610
就在那片燒毀的森林里
in that burned-out forest with them girls,

252
00:27:41,610 --> 00:27:44,910
拿槍抵著我頭  把我綁起來
put a gun to my head, tied me up.

253
00:27:46,780 --> 00:27:48,190
我當時竟然想去幫他
I even tried to help him.

254
00:27:48,280 --> 00:27:49,760
所以你覺得是你的錯嗎
So, you think it's your fault?

255
00:27:50,890 --> 00:27:52,200
是啊  我知道就是的
Yeah, I know it is.

256
00:27:53,360 --> 00:27:54,920
我要去做我一開始就該做的事
I'm gonna go do what I should've done before.

257
00:27:54,920 --> 00:27:55,970
怎么  為了她嗎
What, for her?

258
00:27:57,790 --> 00:27:59,220
她已經死了
She's gone, man.

259
00:28:00,360 --> 00:28:01,850
你是為了自己才這么做
You're doing this for you.

260
00:28:02,800 --> 00:28:04,200
我不在乎
Man, I don't give a shit.

261
00:28:04,200 --> 00:28:05,250
達里爾
Daryl...

262
00:28:07,530 --> 00:28:10,580
我們得回家  再考慮這些事
we need to get back there and figure this out from home.

263
00:28:11,640 --> 00:28:13,230
我們的家
Our home.

264
00:28:14,310 --> 00:28:18,210
我們需要你  現在家里的人需要我們的保護
We need you, and everyone back there needs us right now.

265
00:28:20,720 --> 00:28:23,300
外面形勢不妙
It's-- it's gonna go wrong out here.

266
00:28:24,720 --> 00:28:27,740
我們會報這個仇的  我會的
We'll square it. I will.

267
00:28:28,420 --> 00:28:30,020
我向你保證
I promise you.

268
00:28:31,330 --> 00:28:32,820
回家吧
Just come back.

269
00:28:37,870 --> 00:28:39,370
我做不到
I can't.

270
00:28:39,970 --> 00:28:41,600
-達里爾  -我做不到
- Daryl. - Man, I can't!

271
00:28:49,510 --> 00:28:51,150
我也做不到
I can't either.

272
00:29:10,270 --> 00:29:13,930
問題是  那些人現在可能正往亞歷山大去
Thing is, those men could be back in Alexandria right now.

273
00:29:14,440 --> 00:29:15,860
要是他們真去了  就死定了
If they are, they're dead.

274
00:29:16,140 --> 00:29:17,340
但愿不會
I hope not.

275
00:29:18,540 --> 00:29:20,170
我們需要留他們活口
We need them alive.

276
00:29:20,180 --> 00:29:21,940
我們得了解更多情報
We need to find out more.

277
00:29:21,940 --> 00:29:24,310
是啊  沒錯
Yeah, we do.

278
00:29:32,420 --> 00:29:34,320
我們遇到了彼此
We just got stuck with each other.

279
00:29:35,320 --> 00:29:36,860
算我們走運
We were lucky.

280
00:29:40,930 --> 00:29:42,620
我們一起想辦法度難關
We figured it all out together.

281
00:29:44,630 --> 00:29:46,050
我以為我們做到了
I felt like we did.

282
00:29:46,590 --> 00:29:49,320
經歷了這么多  真的以為做到了
After everything, we did.

283
00:29:56,380 --> 00:29:58,520
可這個世界與我們想象的不同
The world's not what we thought it was.

284
00:30:01,820 --> 00:30:03,730
山頂寨  救世軍  更加復雜
Hilltop, the Saviors, it's bigger.

285
00:31:02,390 --> 00:31:03,910
血跡不多
It's not much.

286
00:31:05,640 --> 00:31:06,710
但如果這是卡蘿爾的血  
But if it's Carol's,

287
00:31:06,710 --> 00:31:08,730
那她失血有好一會兒了
then she's been bleeding for a while.

288
00:31:14,610 --> 00:31:17,110
你來這兒是因為卡蘿爾是你的朋友嗎
So, you out here because Carol is your friend?

289
00:31:18,290 --> 00:31:21,690
我來這兒是因為她是我的家人
I'm out here 'cause she's my family.

290
00:31:24,220 --> 00:31:26,240
我在社區找人聊過
I've talked to people back there.

291
00:31:26,490 --> 00:31:29,170
我知道在監獄里發生了什么
I found out about what happened at the prison.

292
00:31:30,430 --> 00:31:32,320
你為什么要驅逐她
How you sent her away.

293
00:31:34,070 --> 00:31:35,820
她殺了你的兩個同伴  對嗎
She killed two of your people, right?

294
00:31:35,820 --> 00:31:37,370
燒掉了他們的尸體
Burned their bodies.

295
00:31:39,640 --> 00:31:41,750
如果這件事發生在今天
What if that had happened today?

296
00:31:42,570 --> 00:31:43,950
你會殺了她嗎
Would you kill her?

297
00:31:44,180 --> 00:31:46,290
如果發生在今天  我會謝謝她
If it happened today, I'd thank her.

298
00:31:47,280 --> 00:31:49,680
或者我會親自殺了他們
Or I would've killed them myself.

299
00:31:49,680 --> 00:31:51,250
她那樣做是對的
She was right to do it.

300
00:31:52,350 --> 00:31:54,450
他們當時病了  散播病毒
They were sick, spreading a disease.

301
00:31:54,450 --> 00:31:56,150
他們撐不下去的
They weren't gonna make it.

302
00:31:57,190 --> 00:31:58,900
是啊  但那時候與現在不同
Yeah, but this was back then.

303
00:31:59,330 --> 00:32:01,290
你也沒有殺她
And you didn't kill her.

304
00:32:02,330 --> 00:32:06,130
你把她逐走了  瑞克  然后她回來了
You sent her away, Rick, and she came back.

305
00:32:06,130 --> 00:32:08,670
她回來了  救了你們所有人
And she came back and she saved all y'all.

306
00:32:11,500 --> 00:32:13,420
人是可以回頭的  瑞克
People can come back, Rick.

307
00:32:35,310 --> 00:32:36,680
不是她
It's not her.

308
00:32:46,930 --> 00:32:49,260
她才死了不到一天
She couldn't have been dead more than a day.

309
00:33:19,680 --> 00:33:21,460
別緊張  我不會惹什么麻煩
It's okay. I'm not trouble.

310
00:33:21,460 --> 00:33:22,550
我不想惹什么麻煩
I don't want any trouble.

311
00:33:22,550 --> 00:33:25,240
出來  放下你的武器
Come out, drop your weapons.

312
00:33:25,240 --> 00:33:26,510
我做不到
I can't do that.

313
00:33:27,110 --> 00:33:29,080
那些行尸太近了
The wasted are too close.

314
00:33:29,080 --> 00:33:31,830
我只是在找我的馬  你看到了嗎
I'm just looking for my horse. Have you seen him?

315
00:33:32,290 --> 00:33:33,550
沒有
No.

316
00:33:35,120 --> 00:33:37,580
我們在找朋友  你看到她了嗎
We're looking for our friend. Have you seen her?

317
00:33:38,650 --> 00:33:40,270
你看到她了嗎
Have you seen her?

318
00:33:40,290 --> 00:33:41,470
它們來了
They're coming!

319
00:33:41,770 --> 00:33:44,290
走吧  走吧
Just go! Just go!

320
00:33:49,230 --> 00:33:50,310
站住
Stop!

321
00:34:13,620 --> 00:34:14,760
瑞克
Rick.

322
00:34:15,160 --> 00:34:16,820
我們不知道他是誰
We didn't know who he was.

323
00:34:17,760 --> 00:34:21,120
沒錯  是山頂寨的武器
Yeah, it's one of the Hilltop's.

324
00:34:21,230 --> 00:34:22,920
就像路上的那根
Like the one on the road.

325
00:34:23,740 --> 00:34:25,190
也許他是救世軍的人
Maybe he's one of them.

326
00:34:26,340 --> 00:34:28,020
也許他也在找卡蘿爾
Maybe he's looking for Carol, too.

327
00:34:28,020 --> 00:34:30,040
也許那個人只是在找一匹馬
Maybe the man is just looking for a horse.

328
00:34:30,040 --> 00:34:33,180
也許他是山頂寨的人  也許他是其他地方的人
Maybe he is from Hilltop. Maybe he's from somewhere else.

329
00:34:38,450 --> 00:34:42,520
我現在不會再冒險了
I don't take chances anymore.

330
00:34:53,130 --> 00:34:54,510
那些人
Those people...

331
00:34:56,300 --> 00:34:57,620
那些狼群
the Wolves...

332
00:35:00,200 --> 00:35:02,510
他們襲擊后  我找到了其中一人
after they attacked, I found one of them.

333
00:35:05,010 --> 00:35:07,250
我之前去找你的時候
He had attacked me on the road before,

334
00:35:07,480 --> 00:35:09,320
他在路上襲擊過我
when I was trying to find you.

335
00:35:09,610 --> 00:35:10,890
我阻止了他
And I stopped him.

336
00:35:14,030 --> 00:35:15,550
但我放他走了
But I let him live.

337
00:35:16,760 --> 00:35:19,270
襲擊過后  他又出現在亞歷山大
And then he was there in Alexandria after the attack,

338
00:35:19,270 --> 00:35:22,250
躲在某個褐石屋里  我又阻止了他
hiding in one of the brownstones, so I stopped him again.

339
00:35:22,250 --> 00:35:25,510
我把他擊暈了  本來可以殺了他
I knocked him out and I could have killed him.

340
00:35:29,660 --> 00:35:31,320
但所有生命都是寶貴的
But all life is precious.

341
00:35:40,610 --> 00:35:43,050
我把他關在褐石屋的地下室中
Put him in the cell of the brownstone basement.

342
00:35:44,770 --> 00:35:46,490
因為我知道他會改變
'Cause I knew he could change.

343
00:35:47,620 --> 00:35:48,910
我們都會改變
We all can change.

344
00:35:48,910 --> 00:35:52,100
-你在社區里關了一個活的  -是的
- You had one of them alive in the community? - Oh, yeah.

345
00:35:53,140 --> 00:35:56,830
當墻倒下行尸進來時  卡蘿爾發現了這事
And when the walls came down and the walkers broke in, Carol found out.

346
00:35:57,400 --> 00:35:59,480
我們打斗了  那個人逃走了
We fought and that man escaped,

347
00:35:59,780 --> 00:36:00,920
而丹妮斯
and Denise...

348
00:36:03,720 --> 00:36:05,540
她來牢房治療他
she had come to the cell to try and help him

349
00:36:05,540 --> 00:36:07,620
被他抓做人質
and he took her hostage.

350
00:36:08,730 --> 00:36:12,980
然后她和那只狼被行尸包圍了
And then she and that Wolf, they got swarmed,

351
00:36:13,730 --> 00:36:16,110
那個人  那個殺人兇手
and that man, that killer,

352
00:36:16,110 --> 00:36:18,120
他救了她的命
he saved her life.

353
00:36:19,320 --> 00:36:22,230
然后丹妮斯才能救了卡爾的命
And then Denise was there to save Carl.

354
00:36:22,490 --> 00:36:23,640
這
It--

355
00:36:25,220 --> 00:36:26,600
這是一場輪回
it's all a circle.

356
00:36:28,340 --> 00:36:30,230
一切都有因果
Everything gets a return.

357
00:36:38,800 --> 00:36:40,260
但事實就是事實
But the fact is the fact.

358
00:36:41,840 --> 00:36:43,370
我確實那樣做了
I did what I did.

359
00:36:44,480 --> 00:36:45,800
我留了他一命
I let him live.

360
00:36:53,820 --> 00:36:55,430
你回家吧  瑞克
You go home, Rick.

361
00:36:56,910 --> 00:36:59,750
你開上車  家里需要你
You take the car. You're needed back there.

362
00:36:59,750 --> 00:37:02,140
你不該在外面冒險
You shouldn't be out here taking any more chances.

363
00:37:02,140 --> 00:37:03,690
我不走
I'm not leaving.

364
00:37:03,970 --> 00:37:06,570
-卡蘿爾還在外面  -我會找到她
- Carol's still out here. - And I will find her.

365
00:37:07,260 --> 00:37:08,500
總會找到的
Somehow.

366
00:37:11,670 --> 00:37:12,700
你走吧
You go.

367
00:37:16,980 --> 00:37:18,210
你會回來的
You're coming back.

368
00:37:22,140 --> 00:37:23,220
是的
Yeah.

369
00:37:24,600 --> 00:37:26,460
但如果我沒回來  別來找我
But if I don't, don't come looking.

370
00:37:31,800 --> 00:37:32,980
拿著
Take it.

371
00:37:34,270 --> 00:37:36,210
-不  我...  -拿著
- No, I-- - Take it.

372
00:37:46,540 --> 00:37:47,600
摩根
Morgan?

373
00:37:55,790 --> 00:37:58,430
那根蛋白棒的確是米瓊恩偷的
Michonne did steal that protein bar.

374
00:38:01,730 --> 00:38:02,930
我知道
Oh, I know.

375
00:38:26,820 --> 00:38:28,550
摩根還在外面找
Morgan's still out there looking.

376
00:38:30,450 --> 00:38:31,650
米瓊恩回來了嗎
Is Michonne here?

377
00:38:33,420 --> 00:38:35,000
她也還在外面
She's still out there, too.

378
00:38:47,400 --> 00:38:48,750
你害怕
You afraid...

379
00:38:50,110 --> 00:38:51,670
回到過去嗎
to go back to it?

380
00:38:54,910 --> 00:38:56,720
跟某人太親近
Let somebody close?

381
00:39:04,320 --> 00:39:07,370
是的  是的
Yeah. Yeah.

382
00:39:13,160 --> 00:39:14,540
我也是
Me, too.

383
00:39:15,860 --> 00:39:17,800
但是現在
But now...

384
00:39:21,340 --> 00:39:22,770
我已經準備好
I think I'm that much more ready

385
00:39:22,770 --> 00:39:24,870
把這世界再捅個窟窿了
to tear the world a brand-new asshole.

386
00:39:37,450 --> 00:39:38,850
快回來了
Any second now.

387
00:39:41,660 --> 00:39:43,010
是啊
Yeah.

388
00:39:45,260 --> 00:39:47,000
快回來了
Any second.

389
00:40:11,150 --> 00:40:12,470
斯科特說你在找我
Scott said you were looking for me?

390
00:40:13,360 --> 00:40:14,390
什么事
What's up?

391
00:40:17,520 --> 00:40:18,710
我需要幫忙
I need some more help.

392
00:40:35,780 --> 00:40:36,920
我喜歡
I like it.

393
00:40:37,830 --> 00:40:39,030
但是為什么
But why?

394
00:40:42,850 --> 00:40:44,480
我必須繼續下去
I have to keep going.

395
00:40:47,970 --> 00:40:50,480
我不能讓任何東西妨礙我
And I don't want anything getting in my way.

396
00:40:58,190 --> 00:40:59,800
怎么  我剪太短了嗎
Man, did I go too short?

397
00:41:00,280 --> 00:41:02,260
我只給我爸爸剪過
I-I only used to cut my dad's.

398
00:41:02,620 --> 00:41:04,430
不  不是因為那個
No, it's not that.

399
00:41:06,460 --> 00:41:07,490
瑪姬
Maggie?

400
00:41:12,460 --> 00:41:13,700
瑪姬
Maggie.

401
00:41:14,800 --> 00:41:16,800
瑪姬
Maggie!

402
00:41:53,750 --> 00:41:54,930
達里爾
Hi, Daryl.

403
00:42:08,890 --> 00:42:10,020
你死不了
You'll be all right.

