[Script Info]
; // The sub is created by AssToolkit
; // AssToolkit is an ASS Converter designed by David C.
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.18,0:00:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《行尸走肉》前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.62,0:00:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.44,0:00:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里的人  
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.26,0:00:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.83,0:00:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你輸了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.74,0:00:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的生活本可以變得好很多
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.12,0:00:16.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去他媽的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.74,0:00:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你聽我號令
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.52,0:00:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你向我上貢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.82,0:00:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向你上貢
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.39,0:00:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你屬于我  對嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.46,0:00:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.21,0:03:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.59,0:03:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來  瞧瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.46,0:03:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,噓
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.73,0:03:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能開門嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.80,0:03:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.41,0:03:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.43,0:03:41.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開門
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.66,0:03:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們出去看看能不能找到一些物資  
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.35,0:03:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等他們來時給他們
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.78,0:03:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想幫忙嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.20,0:03:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認為我無法勝任
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.14,0:03:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽起來一點不奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.16,0:04:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在為他們修這個便攜式音頻系統
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.07,0:04:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們來時   我們會有一個很體面的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.76,0:04:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,音樂播放器
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.55,0:04:07.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在做有把握的事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.82,0:04:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在盡力提供他們想要的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.34,0:04:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*當當當當*
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.14,0:04:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小豬  小豬  讓我進去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.43,0:05:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.19,0:05:20.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是哪位
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.03,0:05:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好是在開玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.61,0:05:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根  露西爾
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.48,0:05:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我得留下深刻的第一印象	
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.51,0:05:37.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.57,0:05:45.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別逼我開口問
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.16,0:05:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說的是一周
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.12,0:05:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你來早了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.55,0:06:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.79,0:06:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克  過來
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.52,0:06:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.27,0:06:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歸我了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.61,0:06:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是輕而易舉
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.82,0:06:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了   各位
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.24,0:06:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們開始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.38,0:06:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大日子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.79,0:06:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克  你看見我剛做的事了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.24,0:06:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是上好服務
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.97,0:06:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們差點被拒之門外了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.16,0:06:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那人是誰啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.96,0:06:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我生氣了嗎  發脾氣了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.29,0:06:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我砸了哪個紅毛的頭嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.27,0:07:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.89,0:07:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是干掉了一個
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.77,0:07:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能殺死你們的行尸
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.37,0:07:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,服務  
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.29,0:07:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿著
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.87,0:08:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.96,0:08:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這地方真是了不起
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.47,0:08:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如俗話說  富得流油
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.34,0:08:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生  我相信你們肯定有許多
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.86,0:08:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可提供的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.63,0:08:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,達里爾
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.87,0:08:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.34,0:08:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.07,0:08:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是幫手
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.20,0:08:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不準看他
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.46,0:08:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不準跟他說話
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.60,0:08:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否則我要你砍掉他身體的某個部位
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.51,0:08:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.44,0:08:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.71,0:09:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛才懸念很多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.07,0:09:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她都不知道有多少
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.16,0:09:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  開始行動吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.30,0:09:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你們櫥柜里藏了什么好東西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.46,0:09:26.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們分好了一半補給
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.15,0:09:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.78,0:09:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.71,0:09:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你無權決定我們拿走什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.56,0:09:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來決定
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.32,0:09:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿拉特
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.12,0:09:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們聽到老大的話了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.39,0:09:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出發
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.46,0:10:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們就搜一搜房子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.82,0:10:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走走過程
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.71,0:10:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.16,0:10:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要帶我在這里轉轉嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.94,0:10:19.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么樣
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.87,0:10:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羅西塔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.14,0:10:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟你的朋友去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.38,0:10:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們打算去...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.90,0:10:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道嗎  我不在乎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.03,0:11:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些事搞定了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.81,0:11:24.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有份工作給你做
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.90,0:11:28.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把達里爾的摩托弄過來
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.72,0:11:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在這里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.46,0:11:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不在這里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.51,0:11:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你知道它在哪里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.09,0:11:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我倆都清楚你是知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.23,0:11:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在你可以走了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.74,0:12:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.92,0:12:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別花太長時間
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.64,0:13:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.49,0:14:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧見了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.25,0:14:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種場景讓我滿意極了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.07,0:15:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一點點合作
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.77,0:15:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓一切都特別舒心
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.88,0:15:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你瞧  一旦你們了解了我們
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.38,0:15:08.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就會發現我們真的特別講道理
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.61,0:15:10.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很誠信
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.98,0:15:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.24,0:15:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-靠  我真愛這地方  -尼根
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.00,0:15:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可能會想看看這玩意
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.64,0:15:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我瞧瞧這是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.86,0:15:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望是什么變態小視頻
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.24,0:15:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...了解我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.88,0:15:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我殺過人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.68,0:15:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-數都數不清  -老天爺
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.08,0:15:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我知道為什么他們都死了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.00,0:15:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你嗎  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.07,0:15:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那張胡子拉碴的臉  -只有他們死了  我的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.86,0:16:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-和外面那些人才能活下去  -我靠
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.63,0:16:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不敢惹那個人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.33,0:16:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你已經不是那個人了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.46,0:16:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.43,0:16:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.34,0:16:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真得刮刮胡子了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.79,0:16:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個生病的姑娘怎么樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.00,0:16:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那晚對她而言壓力可大了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.69,0:16:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她當時那哭鬧的樣子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.93,0:16:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來她是二號的老婆  是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.78,0:16:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意點
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.00,0:16:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意自己看我的眼神  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.75,0:16:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寡婦  特別是長成她那樣的...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.48,0:16:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她們...很特別
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.85,0:16:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愛她們
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.45,0:16:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她們的丈夫去世之后  她們...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.03,0:17:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心里很空虛
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.61,0:17:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過通常這種情況不會持續太久
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.93,0:17:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.50,0:17:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想見見她
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.40,0:17:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想去祭奠她嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.89,0:17:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我靠
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.33,0:17:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太他媽滲人了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.06,0:17:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悄悄摸摸地靠近我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.02,0:17:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴著羅馬領  臉上掛著詭異的微笑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.71,0:17:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.52,0:17:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是加百利神父
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.48,0:17:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她沒挺過來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.86,0:17:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是悲劇
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.33,0:17:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是場悲劇
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.29,0:17:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們一定很難過吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.48,0:17:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一號的死
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.53,0:18:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算在我頭上  我當時別無選擇
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.36,0:18:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須給你們個教訓
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.80,0:18:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是二號
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.12,0:18:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是必須得死的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.56,0:18:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,達里爾  是他逼我的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.01,0:18:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那大概把她壓垮了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.95,0:18:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.70,0:18:19.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本想讓她和我一起回去的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.27,0:18:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你在想什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.51,0:18:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么可能贏得她的芳心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.47,0:18:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我這個把她丈夫的頭打碎了的人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.00,0:18:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你絕對想不到的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.53,0:18:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人啊  他們...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.01,0:18:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放一些回去  不然下一顆就打你身上了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.26,0:18:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.30,0:18:55.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得接下來會發生什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.48,0:18:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會死
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.52,0:19:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡爾  卡爾  把槍放下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.78,0:19:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  他拿走了我們所有的藥品
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.60,0:19:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們說好了只拿一半的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.65,0:19:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.36,0:19:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真要這樣嗎  小子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.70,0:19:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們該走了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.79,0:19:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁你們還沒領教到我們是多危險的人之前
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.90,0:19:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說什么  年輕人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.42,0:19:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思我他媽爆粗了  但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.75,0:19:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你剛是威脅了我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.92,0:19:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著  我理解你為什么威脅戴維
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.12,0:19:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不能容忍
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.32,0:19:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能威脅他  不能威脅我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.58,0:19:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卡爾  放下槍  -別無禮  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.53,0:19:39.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們正在談話呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.57,0:19:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子  我們說到哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.54,0:19:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.82,0:19:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是膽大包天
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.72,0:19:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別威脅我們
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.90,0:19:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著  我喜歡你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.78,0:19:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不想用暴力證明什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.39,0:19:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不想那樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.39,0:20:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說過只拿一半
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.78,0:20:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但哪一半是我說了算
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.08,0:20:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很認真
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.27,0:20:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想讓我證明我有多認真嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.67,0:20:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再一次嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.02,0:20:31.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道嗎瑞克  這一切都在提醒我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.02,0:20:34.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們的槍太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.86,0:20:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有你們從我的哨站搶來的一批槍
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.07,0:20:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有你們用來干掉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.70,0:20:41.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哨站守衛的一大批自己的槍
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.91,0:20:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敢打賭你們還有更多槍
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.60,0:20:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加起來一共...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.58,0:20:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是超他媽多的槍
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.74,0:20:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而這種情緒小失控
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.20,0:20:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已經明確地證明了...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.04,0:20:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這我不能允許
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.98,0:21:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在槍都歸我了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.51,0:21:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么告訴我  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.93,0:21:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的槍在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你們會來的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.17,0:21:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶他去看槍  奧利維亞
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.34,0:21:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武器庫在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.99,0:21:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你負責管這里嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.04,0:21:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.76,0:21:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只負責記錄所有東西  配給口糧  槍支
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.33,0:21:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  聰明
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.60,0:21:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別讓我耽誤你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.24,0:21:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶她去  小伙子們  看看物資
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.24,0:22:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.36,0:22:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他們忙的同時
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.31,0:22:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想對你說明
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.82,0:22:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會拿一丁點你的食物
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.26,0:22:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這里不會多拿
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.90,0:22:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且肯定不只有我注意到了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.63,0:22:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你讓一個胖女人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.78,0:22:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,負責管理口糧 對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.17,0:22:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,總之  你們餓死了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.25,0:22:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么也得不到
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.45,0:22:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以目前呢  你可以保留所有食物
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.80,0:22:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看怎么樣
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.17,0:22:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想讓我說什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.59,0:22:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.16,0:22:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道聲謝怎么樣
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.93,0:22:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得不該這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.41,0:22:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這要求過分嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.16,0:23:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  我們起了個壞頭
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.86,0:23:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我又能說什么呢  是你逼我的  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.02,0:23:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我一直努力想讓你明白
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.86,0:23:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你和我合作  我還是很講道理的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.27,0:23:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我來問你個問題  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.26,0:23:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在和我合作嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.41,0:23:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這看起來像什么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.74,0:23:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道這看起來像什么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.77,0:23:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我真正想知道的是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.91,0:23:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們能否在后面找到所有槍支
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.01,0:23:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是說你私藏了一些  在等待時機
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.41,0:23:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像我的露西爾一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.65,0:23:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,槍都在這里了  就我所知
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.56,0:23:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望如此  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.73,0:24:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還在
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.80,0:25:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著  我知道這樣做很遜  但你也看到局面了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.15,0:25:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到他們今天來了多少人
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.97,0:25:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣了  都結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.15,0:25:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是我們的命運
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.57,0:25:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克把我們帶上了這條路
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.97,0:25:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許如果瑞克能深思熟慮
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.98,0:25:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都會不同
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.38,0:25:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些人也許還活著
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.20,0:25:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們現在就這樣了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.92,0:26:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須學會接受
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.09,0:26:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羅西塔
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.55,0:26:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道嗎  瑞克  今天是個大日子
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.39,0:26:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.33,0:26:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認為咱倆的小協議
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.67,0:26:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定能行得通
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.00,0:26:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.45,0:26:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你有沒有好好保養我的槍
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.36,0:26:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.38,0:26:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽起來也不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.57,0:26:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信露西爾會有點嫉妒
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.74,0:26:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.25,0:27:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看這個
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.56,0:27:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你們把蒂米和迪克小隊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.66,0:27:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干掉的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.42,0:27:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.34,0:27:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后過把癮啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.44,0:27:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這會讓我有不少樂趣
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.84,0:27:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  我不知道...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.85,0:27:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿拉特  不要那么粗魯
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.83,0:27:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非他們罪有應得
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.96,0:27:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我們查了庫存單
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.83,0:27:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了武器庫里的槍
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.60,0:27:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,墻邊的槍  還少幾把
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.18,0:27:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格洛克9和一支點22山貓
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.66,0:27:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.29,0:27:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們有人離開了這里
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.66,0:27:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們可能帶著那些槍
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.69,0:27:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以奧利維亞搞砸了她的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.61,0:27:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是想說這個嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.59,0:27:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我沒有這么說
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.77,0:27:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庫存單應該統計完整  對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.84,0:27:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不遺巨細
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.69,0:28:02.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我說的對嗎  -不
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.19,0:28:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是說  對
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.25,0:28:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庫存單是對的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.46,0:28:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.96,0:28:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也不好
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.90,0:28:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  上面記的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.63,0:28:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卻不在里面  少了兩把手槍
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.97,0:28:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道在哪嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.01,0:28:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  我...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.83,0:28:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真令人沮喪  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.15,0:28:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以為我們已經達成共識了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.61,0:28:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但這事  說明有人有異議
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.59,0:28:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這我不能允許
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.18,0:28:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜歡殺女人
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.49,0:28:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人  我想殺多少殺多少
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.89,0:28:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但歸根結底  親愛的奧利維亞
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.82,0:29:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-這是你的責任  -這個我們可以解決
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.47,0:29:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們當然可以
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.82,0:29:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且現在我正要去解決
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.44,0:29:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是你的工作  而你搞砸了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.40,0:29:18.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,記錄槍支情況
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.36,0:29:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那玩意兒
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.38,0:29:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事關生死
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.00,0:29:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想過藏一些槍
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.74,0:29:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前藏過
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.73,0:29:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想過可以埋一些在外面
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.88,0:29:50.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許我們很多年都不會碰
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.13,0:29:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多年
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.56,0:29:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.69,0:29:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果救世軍發現了那些槍
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.35,0:30:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我們帶著那些槍遇到他們
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.88,0:30:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們中一個就會死
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.03,0:30:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許還不止一個  也許會死很多人
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.63,0:30:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管我們有多少子彈
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.46,0:30:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是不夠的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.09,0:30:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們贏了  事實就是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.06,0:30:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藏槍不是解決方法  再也不是了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.95,0:30:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不必心甘情愿
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.02,0:30:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我們得把槍交給他們
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.87,0:30:41.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一把格洛克9和一把點22
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.99,0:30:43.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是他們在找的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.82,0:30:46.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在誰那
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.10,0:30:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人知道在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.43,0:30:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者知道在誰那嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.20,0:30:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我們找不到  他們就會殺了奧利維亞
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.55,0:31:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們干得出來
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.52,0:31:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們為什么關心
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.18,0:31:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩把槍又不能威脅到他們
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.51,0:31:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那些槍可以保護我們
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.18,0:31:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免受外來人的攻擊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.48,0:31:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,槍在你那嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.77,0:31:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒希望在我這
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.48,0:31:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分人當時不在場
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.20,0:31:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們不必看著
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.46,0:31:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你們現在可以無視他人的死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.49,0:31:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者你們可以幫忙解決這個問題
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.05,0:31:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給他們想要的  我們就能和平地生活
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.78,0:31:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:31:41.68,0:31:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在不是時候
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.83,0:31:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是時候了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.67,0:31:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假設我們找到了槍
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.79,0:31:54.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后我們該怎么擺脫這困境  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.84,0:31:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擺脫不了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.10,0:32:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我來給你們明確說一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.33,0:32:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管事的不再是我了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.14,0:32:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是尼根
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.23,0:32:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在  槍在誰那
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.89,0:32:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是所有人都來了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.15,0:33:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羅西塔
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.61,0:33:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.94,0:33:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羅西塔
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.98,0:34:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你出來就是為了這個嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:34:03.78,0:34:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們殺了丹妮斯
Dialogue: 0,0:34:08.45,0:34:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是空的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.22,0:34:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是滿的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.28,0:34:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.31,0:34:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不懂嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.80,0:34:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里那個混蛋收走我們的槍
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.45,0:34:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因為他要收走我們所有的槍
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.98,0:34:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.13,0:34:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎么做  告訴他們嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.31,0:34:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是我們的命運
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.62,0:35:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒找到
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.86,0:35:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.59,0:35:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.57,0:35:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.36,0:35:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道會順利過去的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:32.74,0:35:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么過去
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.18,0:35:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會找到槍
Dialogue: 0,0:35:36.47,0:35:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會熬過今天
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.82,0:35:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后找到繼續前進的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.73,0:35:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何抗爭
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.74,0:35:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有辦法抗爭的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.11,0:35:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的  總有辦法的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.00,0:35:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對我們有信心
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.31,0:35:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對你有信心
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.23,0:35:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情會變的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.85,0:35:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.69,0:35:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.80,0:36:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并非一直是朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.74,0:36:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米瓊恩呢  她有沒有可能...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.31,0:36:10.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她手上沒有他們要的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.85,0:36:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你挖的那個墳墓  很機智
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.28,0:36:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.74,0:36:22.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高興挖一個沒人睡的墳墓
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.60,0:36:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒找到嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.17,0:36:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們搜了羅西塔的房子
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.91,0:36:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.17,0:36:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們現在怎么辦
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.37,0:36:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,槍最有可能藏在這里
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.46,0:36:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯賓塞干過類似的事
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.01,0:36:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們繼續找
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.16,0:36:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許今天會找到
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.80,0:36:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去搜搜車庫
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.68,0:36:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再去看看迪安娜的辦公室
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.87,0:37:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,氣球嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.48,0:38:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去派對嗎  小姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.29,0:38:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能留著嗎  拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.01,0:38:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.14,0:38:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我留下這些吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.56,0:38:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再說一遍拜托  小姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.42,0:38:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.40,0:38:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  再說一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.63,0:38:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.19,0:38:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心點  小姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.01,0:38:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們很快就走了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:47.24,0:38:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你給我帶了什么  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.33,0:38:57.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧這
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.81,0:39:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該來的還是來了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.74,0:39:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是有意思  一句"我的天  有人會死"
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.75,0:39:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能刺激所有人
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.27,0:39:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我  瑞克  你們中哪一位
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.01,0:39:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差點要了奧利維亞的命
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.88,0:39:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-這不重要  -不  這很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.25,0:39:22.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得讓所有人都同意
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.49,0:39:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人  不然
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.73,0:39:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們又要回到原點了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.26,0:40:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這地方真不錯啊  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:40:29.73,0:40:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我點時間
Dialogue: 0,0:40:38.76,0:40:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.34,0:40:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  你能...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.83,0:40:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我點時間嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.30,0:41:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他讓我拿著的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.54,0:41:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,步槍給我
Dialogue: 0,0:41:27.62,0:41:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.97,0:41:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道在包里裝著
Dialogue: 0,0:41:36.05,0:41:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你在外面做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.57,0:41:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在外面做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.13,0:41:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在練槍
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.78,0:41:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們得把槍都交出去  所有槍
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.55,0:41:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:41:47.57,0:41:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你把槍藏起來  讓他們找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.82,0:41:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人會死的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.17,0:41:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要失去你  或者卡爾  或者其他任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.80,0:41:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要再失去任何人了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.20,0:42:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把槍交給他們  你讓我做嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.79,0:42:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧這個
Dialogue: 0,0:42:29.06,0:42:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以為她去找補給了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:30.43,0:42:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她其實是去打獵了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:32.87,0:42:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這支槍沒入過庫  我們一直在防線上用
Dialogue: 0,0:42:37.57,0:42:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:42:40.22,0:42:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關系就該這么建起來
Dialogue: 0,0:42:44.90,0:42:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得好  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:42:47.53,0:42:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是聽進去讀懂了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:51.21,0:42:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前說過  我要再說一次
Dialogue: 0,0:42:53.90,0:42:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這個人呢  很特別
Dialogue: 0,0:43:00.05,0:43:02.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在你知道了我們會守規矩
Dialogue: 0,0:43:02.10,0:43:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢
Dialogue: 0,0:43:07.39,0:43:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想求你留下達里爾
Dialogue: 0,0:43:10.12,0:43:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:43:15.03,0:43:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道嗎  我也不確定
Dialogue: 0,0:43:19.72,0:43:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許達里爾可以自己求我
Dialogue: 0,0:43:21.85,0:43:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許他會說動我
Dialogue: 0,0:43:32.61,0:43:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,達里爾
Dialogue: 0,0:43:41.49,0:43:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  你試過了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:43.91,0:43:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在你要做的是
Dialogue: 0,0:43:45.84,0:43:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻過你們的高墻
Dialogue: 0,0:43:49.25,0:43:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在外面加倍努力
Dialogue: 0,0:43:51.62,0:43:53.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為我工作
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.99,0:43:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我們很快就會回來的  到那時候
Dialogue: 0,0:43:57.19,0:44:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好拿出點能讓我們感興趣的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:44:00.20,0:44:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否則  露西爾會按她的方式來
Dialogue: 0,0:44:04.52,0:44:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再提醒你一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:44:07.17,0:44:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你沒有拿出讓我們感興趣的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:44:12.91,0:44:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人就要死了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:15.69,0:44:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再出現神奇的槍了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.15,0:44:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿拉特  帶上鹿  天色晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:23.30,0:44:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們回家
Dialogue: 0,0:44:29.89,0:44:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就喜歡請我吃飯
Dialogue: 0,0:44:33.59,0:44:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不用我費心的姑娘了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:43.80,0:44:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,歸我了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:47.54,0:44:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羅西塔
Dialogue: 0,0:44:50.98,0:44:52.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給你準備了個小感謝禮物
Dialogue: 0,0:44:57.01,0:44:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是你們得到的
Dialogue: 0,0:44:59.36,0:45:02.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們拿走了全部的槍  大部分床墊
Dialogue: 0,0:45:05.25,0:45:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你美麗的小腦袋能找到地方躺下
Dialogue: 0,0:45:11.57,0:45:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在外面找到其他東西了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:45:15.67,0:45:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有你死去的朋友們
Dialogue: 0,0:45:38.77,0:45:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以還給你
Dialogue: 0,0:45:42.62,0:45:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你說那句話
Dialogue: 0,0:45:57.04,0:45:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天沒人死
Dialogue: 0,0:46:00.02,0:46:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道我怎么想的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:46:02.27,0:46:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得咱倆加強了彼此的理解
Dialogue: 0,0:46:07.69,0:46:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我問問你  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:46:10.55,0:46:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想讓我走嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:46:17.86,0:46:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再好不過了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:19.80,0:46:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就說那兩個神奇的字吧
Dialogue: 0,0:46:31.41,0:46:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:46:35.32,0:46:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別搞笑了  應該我謝謝你
Dialogue: 0,0:46:46.60,0:46:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又一個
Dialogue: 0,0:46:49.95,0:46:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你需要我們的幫助
Dialogue: 0,0:46:52.31,0:46:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴維  把那個燭臺給我
Dialogue: 0,0:46:57.56,0:46:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我怎么想的嗎  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:46:59.71,0:47:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得我們各取所需  都會是贏家
Dialogue: 0,0:47:04.21,0:47:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看好了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:36.72,0:47:38.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:47:40.29,0:47:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雙贏
Dialogue: 0,0:47:44.92,0:47:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把它洗好等我下次用
Dialogue: 0,0:47:49.27,0:47:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:47:54.41,0:47:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:48:00.27,0:48:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太粗心了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:03.55,0:48:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不會以為我要丟下露西爾吧
Dialogue: 0,0:48:06.30,0:48:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她做了那些事
Dialogue: 0,0:48:10.66,0:48:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么會想要她呢
Dialogue: 0,0:48:13.54,0:48:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感謝你這么配合  我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:48:21.36,0:48:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防萬一你不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:48:24.93,0:48:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我剛剛把雞巴塞進了你的嘴里
Dialogue: 0,0:48:28.15,0:48:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還為此感謝了我
Dialogue: 0,0:49:20.83,0:49:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}歡迎來到亞歷山大安全區\N迷途者的天堂  掠奪者的地獄
Dialogue: 0,0:49:55.82,0:49:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯賓塞
Dialogue: 0,0:49:58.23,0:50:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們拿走了你屋里的槍
Dialogue: 0,0:50:01.55,0:50:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救世軍想要我們全部的槍
Dialogue: 0,0:50:05.30,0:50:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,庫存單上有兩把不見了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:09.04,0:50:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們要殺了奧利維亞
Dialogue: 0,0:50:14.38,0:50:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯賓塞
Dialogue: 0,0:50:18.02,0:50:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你進了我屋子
Dialogue: 0,0:50:20.96,0:50:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們要殺了奧利維亞啊
Dialogue: 0,0:50:24.52,0:50:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著  我不怪你藏槍
Dialogue: 0,0:50:27.38,0:50:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也藏過  但是食品和酒
Dialogue: 0,0:50:33.05,0:50:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因為你很卑鄙  斯賓塞
Dialogue: 0,0:50:35.49,0:50:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很脆弱
Dialogue: 0,0:50:37.23,0:50:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在墻里算你走運
Dialogue: 0,0:50:39.04,0:50:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有我們算你走運
Dialogue: 0,0:50:44.31,0:50:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們應該趁有機會的時候和他們談協議
Dialogue: 0,0:50:49.16,0:50:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我們真走運
Dialogue: 0,0:50:51.21,0:50:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你帶我們來到了樂土
Dialogue: 0,0:50:52.99,0:50:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對不對  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:50:54.28,0:50:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們到了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:56.95,0:51:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜格倫和亞伯拉罕也很走運吧
Dialogue: 0,0:51:06.98,0:51:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再敢對我說類似的話
Dialogue: 0,0:51:10.52,0:51:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就打爛你的臭嘴  敲掉你的牙齒
Dialogue: 0,0:51:14.61,0:51:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:51:17.67,0:51:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說明白
Dialogue: 0,0:51:20.35,0:51:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:51:36.94,0:51:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有槍
Dialogue: 0,0:51:38.74,0:51:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:51:40.02,0:51:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前為什么不告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:51:43.31,0:51:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到我為拿到一把槍做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:51:46.15,0:51:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒有子彈
Dialogue: 0,0:51:47.06,0:51:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我藏了有段時間了
Dialogue: 0,0:51:49.07,0:51:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我不信任瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:51:53.73,0:51:55.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他管事讓我擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:51:57.97,0:51:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道嗎  你說的對
Dialogue: 0,0:52:00.30,0:52:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是我們的命運
Dialogue: 0,0:52:57.03,0:53:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們拿走了我們的床墊  大部分都拿走了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:06.61,0:53:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那把步槍
Dialogue: 0,0:53:08.69,0:53:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是從他們哨站搶的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:10.59,0:53:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,單子上沒有吧
Dialogue: 0,0:53:14.36,0:53:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:53:17.13,0:53:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本可以藏更多的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:18.52,0:53:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你藏了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:53:28.32,0:53:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:53:43.72,0:53:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們得到的一切  都是抗爭得來的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:46.29,0:53:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做出選擇了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:49.96,0:53:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們人不夠  這是人數問題
Dialogue: 0,0:53:52.16,0:53:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有山頂寨啊
Dialogue: 0,0:53:53.17,0:53:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們人數依然更多
Dialogue: 0,0:53:59.04,0:54:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們遵守他們的規則  就能活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:54:02.89,0:54:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么個活法
Dialogue: 0,0:54:10.56,0:54:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾有個朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:54:16.85,0:54:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒提起過他
Dialogue: 0,0:54:20.30,0:54:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我搭檔
Dialogue: 0,0:54:23.04,0:54:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,災變后  他把洛莉和卡爾帶到了安全地
Dialogue: 0,0:54:31.01,0:54:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒法做到  我當時在醫院
Dialogue: 0,0:54:32.60,0:54:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道發生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:54:37.49,0:54:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:54:40.49,0:54:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他名字叫肖恩
Dialogue: 0,0:54:46.30,0:54:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他和洛莉
Dialogue: 0,0:54:50.41,0:54:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們在一起了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:54.21,0:54:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們以為我死了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:58.59,0:55:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道朱迪思不是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:55:03.42,0:55:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:55:08.64,0:55:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愛她
Dialogue: 0,0:55:10.06,0:55:11.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是我女兒
Dialogue: 0,0:55:13.75,0:55:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她不是我骨肉
Dialogue: 0,0:55:16.89,0:55:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必須接受這點
Dialogue: 0,0:55:19.77,0:55:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我接受了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:22.01,0:55:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣我就能保護她
Dialogue: 0,0:55:28.72,0:55:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不死她就不會死
Dialogue: 0,0:55:30.31,0:55:32.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望那會是很久以后的事
Dialogue: 0,0:55:32.38,0:55:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣我可以
Dialogue: 0,0:55:34.50,0:55:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撫養她長大  保護她  教她求生
Dialogue: 0,0:55:42.18,0:55:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是我們現在的生存方式
Dialogue: 0,0:55:45.65,0:55:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也必須接受這點
Dialogue: 0,0:55:47.08,0:55:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以保護所有人活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:55:49.35,0:55:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人死不是你的錯
Dialogue: 0,0:55:52.74,0:55:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不總是  但是有時候是的
Dialogue: 0,0:55:59.01,0:56:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必須接受
Dialogue: 0,0:56:02.48,0:56:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都要接受
Dialogue: 0,0:56:04.04,0:56:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然行不通的
Dialogue: 0,0:56:31.40,0:56:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會試試
Dialogue: 0,0:58:53.93,0:58:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我做顆子彈
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.69,0:07:58.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第七季  第四集』
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.81,0:01:27.66,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx2300\fscy200\alpha&AA\pos(129.2,218.4)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.80,0:01:07.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻譯:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}冰藍 Reginamoon CS小明漫畫家
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.77,0:01:12.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻譯:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}自然卷 艾瑞卡 蘑菇 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.73,0:01:17.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}校對:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.70,0:01:22.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}時間軸:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}雪妞 濤濤 加森
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.66,0:01:27.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}后期:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小哥  拉圖    {\c&H008AFF&}總監： {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小孩
