[Script Info]
; // The sub is created by AssToolkit
; // AssToolkit is an ASS Converter designed by David C.
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.18,0:00:03.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《行尸走肉》前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.62,0:00:05.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.44,0:00:07.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里的人  
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.26,0:00:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.83,0:00:11.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你输了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.74,0:00:14.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的生活本可以变得好很多
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.12,0:00:16.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去他妈的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.74,0:00:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听我号令
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.52,0:00:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你向我上贡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.82,0:00:23.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我向你上贡
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.39,0:00:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你属于我  对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.46,0:00:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.21,0:03:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.59,0:03:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来  瞧瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.46,0:03:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘘
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.73,0:03:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能开门吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.80,0:03:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.41,0:03:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.43,0:03:41.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开门
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.66,0:03:47.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们出去看看能不能找到一些物资  
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.35,0:03:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等他们来时给他们
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.78,0:03:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想帮忙吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.20,0:03:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为我无法胜任
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.14,0:03:57.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来一点不奇怪
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.16,0:04:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在为他们修这个便携式音频系统
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.07,0:04:04.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们来时   我们会有一个很体面的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.76,0:04:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,音乐播放器
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.55,0:04:07.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在做有把握的事
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.82,0:04:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在尽力提供他们想要的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.34,0:04:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*当当当当*
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.14,0:04:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小猪  小猪  让我进去
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.43,0:05:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.19,0:05:20.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是哪位
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.03,0:05:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好是在开玩笑
Dialogue: 0,0:05:23.61,0:05:25.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根  露西尔
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.48,0:05:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我得留下深刻的第一印象	
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.51,0:05:37.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.57,0:05:45.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别逼我开口问
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.16,0:05:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说的是一周
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.12,0:05:51.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来早了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.55,0:06:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.79,0:06:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克  过来
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.52,0:06:10.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.27,0:06:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,归我了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.61,0:06:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是轻而易举
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.82,0:06:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了   各位
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.24,0:06:28.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们开始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.38,0:06:33.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大日子啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.79,0:06:44.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克  你看见我刚做的事了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.24,0:06:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是上好服务
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.97,0:06:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们差点被拒之门外了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.16,0:06:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那人是谁啊
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.96,0:06:56.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我生气了吗  发脾气了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.29,0:06:58.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我砸了哪个红毛的头吗
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.27,0:07:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.89,0:07:02.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是干掉了一个
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.77,0:07:04.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能杀死你们的行尸
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.37,0:07:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,服务  
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.29,0:07:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿着
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.87,0:08:02.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.96,0:08:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这地方真是了不起
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.47,0:08:09.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如俗话说  富得流油
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.34,0:08:13.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,先生  我相信你们肯定有许多
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.86,0:08:15.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可提供的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.63,0:08:19.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.87,0:08:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.34,0:08:22.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.07,0:08:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是帮手
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.20,0:08:29.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不准看他
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.46,0:08:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不准跟他说话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.60,0:08:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则我要你砍掉他身体的某个部位
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.51,0:08:48.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都一样
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.44,0:08:54.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.71,0:09:14.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刚才悬念很多啊
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.07,0:09:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她都不知道有多少
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.16,0:09:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  开始行动吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.30,0:09:24.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你们橱柜里藏了什么好东西
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.46,0:09:26.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们分好了一半补给
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.15,0:09:27.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.78,0:09:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.71,0:09:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你无权决定我们拿走什么
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.56,0:09:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来决定
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.32,0:09:41.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿拉特
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.12,0:09:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们听到老大的话了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.39,0:09:47.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出发
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.46,0:10:01.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们就搜一搜房子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.82,0:10:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走走过程
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.71,0:10:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.16,0:10:13.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要带我在这里转转吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.94,0:10:19.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.87,0:10:31.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗西塔
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.14,0:10:35.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟你的朋友去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.38,0:10:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们打算去...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.90,0:10:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗  我不在乎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.03,0:11:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些事搞定了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.81,0:11:24.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有份工作给你做
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.90,0:11:28.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把达里尔的摩托弄过来
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.72,0:11:29.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.46,0:11:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果不在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.51,0:11:33.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你知道它在哪里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.09,0:11:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我俩都清楚你是知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.23,0:11:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你可以走了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.74,0:12:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.92,0:12:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别花太长时间
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.64,0:13:50.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.49,0:14:55.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧见了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.25,0:14:59.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种场景让我满意极了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.07,0:15:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点点合作
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.77,0:15:03.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让一切都特别舒心
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.88,0:15:06.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你瞧  一旦你们了解了我们
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.38,0:15:08.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会发现我们真的特别讲道理
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.61,0:15:10.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很诚信
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.98,0:15:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爽
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.24,0:15:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-靠  我真爱这地方  -尼根
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.00,0:15:33.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可能会想看看这玩意
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.64,0:15:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我瞧瞧这是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.86,0:15:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望是什么变态小视频
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.24,0:15:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,...了解我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.88,0:15:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我杀过人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.68,0:15:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-数都数不清  -老天爷
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.08,0:15:54.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是我知道为什么他们都死了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.00,0:15:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你吗  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.07,0:15:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那张胡子拉碴的脸  -只有他们死了  我的家人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.86,0:16:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-和外面那些人才能活下去  -我靠
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.63,0:16:04.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不敢惹那个人
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.33,0:16:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你已经不是那个人了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.46,0:16:13.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.43,0:16:17.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.34,0:16:21.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真得刮刮胡子了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.79,0:16:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个生病的姑娘怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.00,0:16:31.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那晚对她而言压力可大了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.69,0:16:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她当时那哭闹的样子
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.93,0:16:36.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看来她是二号的老婆  是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.78,0:16:38.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意点
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.00,0:16:42.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意自己看我的眼神  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.75,0:16:49.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寡妇  特别是长成她那样的...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.48,0:16:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们...很特别
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.85,0:16:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱她们
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.45,0:16:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们的丈夫去世之后  她们...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.03,0:17:00.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,心里很空虚
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.61,0:17:04.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过通常这种情况不会持续太久
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.93,0:17:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.50,0:17:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想见见她
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.40,0:17:12.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想去祭奠她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.89,0:17:15.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我靠
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.33,0:17:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你太他妈渗人了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.06,0:17:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,悄悄摸摸地靠近我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.02,0:17:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴着罗马领  脸上挂着诡异的微笑
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.71,0:17:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.52,0:17:27.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是加百利神父
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.48,0:17:36.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她没挺过来吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.86,0:17:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是悲剧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.33,0:17:49.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是场悲剧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.29,0:17:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们一定很难过吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.48,0:17:57.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一号的死
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.53,0:18:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那算在我头上  我当时别无选择
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.36,0:18:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须给你们个教训
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.80,0:18:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是二号
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.12,0:18:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不是必须得死的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.56,0:18:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔  是他逼我的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.01,0:18:13.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那大概把她压垮了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.95,0:18:15.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.70,0:18:19.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本想让她和我一起回去的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.27,0:18:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你在想什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.51,0:18:23.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我怎么可能赢得她的芳心呢
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.47,0:18:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这个把她丈夫的头打碎了的人
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.00,0:18:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你绝对想不到的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.53,0:18:31.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人啊  他们...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.01,0:18:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放一些回去  不然下一颗就打你身上了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.26,0:18:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.30,0:18:55.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得接下来会发生什么
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.48,0:18:56.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会死
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.52,0:19:00.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡尔  卡尔  把枪放下
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.78,0:19:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  他拿走了我们所有的药品
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.60,0:19:05.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们说好了只拿一半的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.65,0:19:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.36,0:19:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真要这样吗  小子
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.70,0:19:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们该走了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.79,0:19:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁你们还没领教到我们是多危险的人之前
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.90,0:19:21.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么  年轻人
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.42,0:19:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思我他妈爆粗了  但是...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.75,0:19:27.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚是威胁了我吗
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.92,0:19:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我理解你为什么威胁戴维
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.12,0:19:32.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不能容忍
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.32,0:19:33.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能威胁他  不能威胁我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.58,0:19:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卡尔  放下枪  -别无礼  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.53,0:19:39.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们正在谈话呢
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.57,0:19:44.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子  我们说到哪了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.54,0:19:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.82,0:19:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真是胆大包天
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.72,0:19:52.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别威胁我们
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.90,0:19:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我喜欢你
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.78,0:19:58.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不想用暴力证明什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.39,0:19:59.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不想那样的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.39,0:20:00.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过只拿一半
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.78,0:20:03.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但哪一半是我说了算
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.08,0:20:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很认真
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.27,0:20:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让我证明我有多认真吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.67,0:20:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再一次吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.02,0:20:31.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗瑞克  这一切都在提醒我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.02,0:20:34.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的枪太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.86,0:20:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有你们从我的哨站抢来的一批枪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.07,0:20:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有你们用来干掉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.70,0:20:41.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哨站守卫的一大批自己的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.91,0:20:44.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敢打赌你们还有更多枪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.60,0:20:47.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加起来一共...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.58,0:20:49.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是超他妈多的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.74,0:20:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而这种情绪小失控
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.20,0:20:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经明确地证明了...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.04,0:20:56.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这我不能允许
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.98,0:21:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在枪都归我了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.51,0:21:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么告诉我  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.93,0:21:12.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的枪在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.16,0:21:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你们会来的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.17,0:21:34.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带他去看枪  奥利维亚
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.34,0:21:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武器库在里面
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.99,0:21:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你负责管这里吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.04,0:21:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.76,0:21:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只负责记录所有东西  配给口粮  枪支
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.33,0:21:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  聪明
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.60,0:21:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别让我耽误你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.24,0:21:56.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带她去  小伙子们  看看物资
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.24,0:22:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.36,0:22:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他们忙的同时
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.31,0:22:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想对你说明
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.82,0:22:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会拿一丁点你的食物
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.26,0:22:17.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在这里不会多拿
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.90,0:22:20.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且肯定不只有我注意到了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.63,0:22:22.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让一个胖女人
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.78,0:22:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,负责管理口粮 对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.17,0:22:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  你们饿死了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.25,0:22:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么也得不到
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.45,0:22:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以目前呢  你可以保留所有食物
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.80,0:22:38.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.17,0:22:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想让我说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.59,0:22:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.16,0:22:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,道声谢怎么样
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.93,0:22:50.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得不该这样吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.41,0:22:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这要求过分吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.16,0:23:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道  我们起了个坏头
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.86,0:23:10.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可我又能说什么呢  是你逼我的  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.02,0:23:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我一直努力想让你明白
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.86,0:23:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你和我合作  我还是很讲道理的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.27,0:23:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么我来问你个问题  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.26,0:23:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在和我合作吗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.41,0:23:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这看起来像什么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.74,0:23:34.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道这看起来像什么
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.77,0:23:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我真正想知道的是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.91,0:23:40.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能否在后面找到所有枪支
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.01,0:23:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是说你私藏了一些  在等待时机
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.41,0:23:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像我的露西尔一样
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.65,0:23:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,枪都在这里了  就我所知
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.56,0:23:59.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望如此  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.73,0:24:54.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.80,0:25:17.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我知道这样做很逊  但你也看到局面了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.15,0:25:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到他们今天来了多少人
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.97,0:25:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样了  都结束了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.15,0:25:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我们的命运
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.57,0:25:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克把我们带上了这条路
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.97,0:25:37.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许如果瑞克能深思熟虑
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.98,0:25:40.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都会不同
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.38,0:25:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些人也许还活着
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.20,0:25:58.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在就这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.92,0:26:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必须学会接受
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.09,0:26:06.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗西塔
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.55,0:26:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗  瑞克  今天是个大日子
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.39,0:26:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.33,0:26:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为咱俩的小协议
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.67,0:26:18.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定能行得通
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.00,0:26:20.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.45,0:26:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你有没有好好保养我的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.36,0:26:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感觉不错
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.38,0:26:50.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听起来也不错
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.57,0:26:53.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信露西尔会有点嫉妒
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.74,0:26:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.25,0:27:04.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看这个
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.56,0:27:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是你们把蒂米和迪克小队
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.66,0:27:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干掉的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.42,0:27:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.34,0:27:13.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后过把瘾啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.44,0:27:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这会让我有不少乐趣
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.84,0:27:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  我不知道...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.85,0:27:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿拉特  不要那么粗鲁
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.83,0:27:27.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非他们罪有应得
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.96,0:27:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我们查了库存单
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.83,0:27:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了武器库里的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.60,0:27:33.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,墙边的枪  还少几把
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.18,0:27:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格洛克9和一支点22山猫
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.66,0:27:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.29,0:27:48.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有人离开了这里
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.66,0:27:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们可能带着那些枪
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.69,0:27:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以奥利维亚搞砸了她的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.61,0:27:53.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是想说这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.59,0:27:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我没有这么说
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.77,0:27:57.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,库存单应该统计完整  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.84,0:27:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不遗巨细
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.69,0:28:02.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我说的对吗  -不
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.19,0:28:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  对
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.25,0:28:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,库存单是对的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.46,0:28:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.96,0:28:13.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也不好
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.90,0:28:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看  上面记的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.63,0:28:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,却不在里面  少了两把手枪
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.97,0:28:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道在哪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.01,0:28:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  我...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.83,0:28:31.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真令人沮丧  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.15,0:28:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为我们已经达成共识了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.61,0:28:38.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这事  说明有人有异议
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.59,0:28:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这我不能允许
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.18,0:28:49.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不喜欢杀女人
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.49,0:28:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人  我想杀多少杀多少
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.89,0:28:57.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但归根结底  亲爱的奥利维亚
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.82,0:29:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这是你的责任  -这个我们可以解决
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.47,0:29:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们当然可以
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.82,0:29:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且现在我正要去解决
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.44,0:29:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你的工作  而你搞砸了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.40,0:29:18.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,记录枪支情况
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.36,0:29:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那玩意儿
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.38,0:29:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事关生死
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.00,0:29:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想过藏一些枪
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.74,0:29:42.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前藏过
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.73,0:29:46.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想过可以埋一些在外面
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.88,0:29:50.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我们很多年都不会碰
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.13,0:29:51.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多年
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.56,0:29:53.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.69,0:29:58.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果救世军发现了那些枪
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.35,0:30:03.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们带着那些枪遇到他们
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.88,0:30:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们中一个就会死
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.03,0:30:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许还不止一个  也许会死很多人
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.63,0:30:14.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管我们有多少子弹
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.46,0:30:17.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是不够的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.09,0:30:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们赢了  事实就是如此
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.06,0:30:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藏枪不是解决方法  再也不是了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.95,0:30:31.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不必心甘情愿
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.02,0:30:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们得把枪交给他们
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.87,0:30:41.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一把格洛克9和一把点22
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.99,0:30:43.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是他们在找的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.82,0:30:46.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在谁那
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.10,0:30:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人知道在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.43,0:30:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者知道在谁那吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.20,0:30:59.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们找不到  他们就会杀了奥利维亚
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.55,0:31:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们干得出来
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.52,0:31:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们为什么关心
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.18,0:31:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两把枪又不能威胁到他们
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.51,0:31:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那些枪可以保护我们
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.18,0:31:13.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免受外来人的攻击
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.48,0:31:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,枪在你那吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.77,0:31:19.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,倒希望在我这
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.48,0:31:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大部分人当时不在场
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.20,0:31:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不必看着
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.46,0:31:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你们现在可以无视他人的死亡
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.49,0:31:33.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者你们可以帮忙解决这个问题
Dialogue: 0,0:31:34.05,0:31:38.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给他们想要的  我们就能和平地生活
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.78,0:31:40.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要
Dialogue: 0,0:31:41.68,0:31:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不是时候
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.83,0:31:45.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是时候了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.67,0:31:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假设我们找到了枪
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.79,0:31:54.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后我们该怎么摆脱这困境  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.84,0:31:58.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摆脱不了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.10,0:32:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我来给你们明确说一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.33,0:32:07.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管事的不再是我了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.14,0:32:13.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是尼根
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.23,0:32:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  枪在谁那
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.89,0:32:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是所有人都来了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.15,0:33:00.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗西塔
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.61,0:33:01.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.94,0:33:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗西塔
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.98,0:34:03.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你出来就是为了这个吗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:03.78,0:34:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们杀了丹妮斯
Dialogue: 0,0:34:08.45,0:34:09.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是空的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.22,0:34:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是满的呢
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.28,0:34:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.31,0:34:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不懂吗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.80,0:34:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,家里那个混蛋收走我们的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.45,0:34:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为他要收走我们所有的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.98,0:34:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.13,0:34:24.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想怎么做  告诉他们吗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.31,0:34:34.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我们的命运
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.62,0:35:17.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没找到
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.86,0:35:19.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.59,0:35:22.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.57,0:35:25.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.36,0:35:31.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道会顺利过去的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:32.74,0:35:33.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么过去
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.18,0:35:35.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会找到枪
Dialogue: 0,0:35:36.47,0:35:38.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会熬过今天
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.82,0:35:40.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后找到继续前进的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.73,0:35:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何抗争
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.74,0:35:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有办法抗争的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.11,0:35:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有的  总有办法的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.00,0:35:48.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对我们有信心
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.31,0:35:51.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我对你有信心
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.23,0:35:54.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事情会变的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.85,0:35:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.69,0:35:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.80,0:36:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并非一直是朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.74,0:36:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米琼恩呢  她有没有可能...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.31,0:36:10.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她手上没有他们要的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.85,0:36:16.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你挖的那个坟墓  很机智
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.28,0:36:18.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.74,0:36:22.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高兴挖一个没人睡的坟墓
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.60,0:36:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没找到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.17,0:36:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们搜了罗西塔的房子
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.91,0:36:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么都没有
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.17,0:36:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.37,0:36:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,枪最有可能藏在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.46,0:36:41.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯宾塞干过类似的事
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.01,0:36:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们继续找
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.16,0:36:46.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许今天会找到
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.80,0:36:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去搜搜车库
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.68,0:36:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再去看看迪安娜的办公室
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.87,0:37:58.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,气球吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.48,0:38:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要去派对吗  小姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.29,0:38:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能留着吗  拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.01,0:38:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.14,0:38:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我留下这些吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.56,0:38:14.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说一遍拜托  小姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.42,0:38:19.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.40,0:38:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  再说一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.63,0:38:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.19,0:38:32.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心点  小姑娘
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.01,0:38:40.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们很快就走了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:47.24,0:38:48.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我带了什么  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.33,0:38:57.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧这
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.81,0:39:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该来的还是来了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.74,0:39:03.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是有意思  一句"我的天  有人会死"
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.75,0:39:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能刺激所有人
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.27,0:39:12.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我  瑞克  你们中哪一位
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.01,0:39:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差点要了奥利维亚的命
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.88,0:39:18.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-这不重要  -不  这很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.25,0:39:22.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得让所有人都同意
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.49,0:39:24.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人  不然
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.73,0:39:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们又要回到原点了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.26,0:40:20.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这地方真不错啊  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:40:29.73,0:40:30.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我点时间
Dialogue: 0,0:40:38.76,0:40:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.34,0:40:46.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托  你能...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.83,0:40:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我点时间吗
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.30,0:41:20.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他让我拿着的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.54,0:41:25.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,步枪给我
Dialogue: 0,0:41:27.62,0:41:28.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.97,0:41:34.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道在包里装着
Dialogue: 0,0:41:36.05,0:41:37.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你在外面做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.57,0:41:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在外面做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.13,0:41:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在练枪
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.78,0:41:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得把枪都交出去  所有枪
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.55,0:41:47.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:41:47.57,0:41:50.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你把枪藏起来  让他们找到了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.82,0:41:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人会死的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.17,0:41:55.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要失去你  或者卡尔  或者其他任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.80,0:41:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要再失去任何人了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.20,0:42:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要把枪交给他们  你让我做吗
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.79,0:42:25.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧这个
Dialogue: 0,0:42:29.06,0:42:30.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为她去找补给了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:30.43,0:42:31.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她其实是去打猎了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:32.87,0:42:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这支枪没入过库  我们一直在防线上用
Dialogue: 0,0:42:37.57,0:42:39.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看啊
Dialogue: 0,0:42:40.22,0:42:44.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,关系就该这么建起来
Dialogue: 0,0:42:44.90,0:42:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做得好  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:42:47.53,0:42:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是听进去读懂了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:51.21,0:42:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前说过  我要再说一次
Dialogue: 0,0:42:53.90,0:42:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这个人呢  很特别
Dialogue: 0,0:43:00.05,0:43:02.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你知道了我们会守规矩
Dialogue: 0,0:43:02.10,0:43:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢
Dialogue: 0,0:43:07.39,0:43:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想求你留下达里尔
Dialogue: 0,0:43:10.12,0:43:11.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能
Dialogue: 0,0:43:15.03,0:43:17.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗  我也不确定
Dialogue: 0,0:43:19.72,0:43:21.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许达里尔可以自己求我
Dialogue: 0,0:43:21.85,0:43:26.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他会说动我
Dialogue: 0,0:43:32.61,0:43:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔
Dialogue: 0,0:43:41.49,0:43:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  你试过了
Dialogue: 0,0:43:43.91,0:43:45.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你要做的是
Dialogue: 0,0:43:45.84,0:43:48.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,翻过你们的高墙
Dialogue: 0,0:43:49.25,0:43:51.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在外面加倍努力
Dialogue: 0,0:43:51.62,0:43:53.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为我工作
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.99,0:43:57.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们很快就会回来的  到那时候
Dialogue: 0,0:43:57.19,0:44:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好拿出点能让我们感兴趣的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:44:00.20,0:44:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,否则  露西尔会按她的方式来
Dialogue: 0,0:44:04.52,0:44:06.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再提醒你一遍
Dialogue: 0,0:44:07.17,0:44:11.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你没有拿出让我们感兴趣的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:44:12.91,0:44:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人就要死了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:15.69,0:44:18.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要再出现神奇的枪了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:20.15,0:44:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿拉特  带上鹿  天色晚了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:23.30,0:44:24.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们回家
Dialogue: 0,0:44:29.89,0:44:33.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就喜欢请我吃饭
Dialogue: 0,0:44:33.59,0:44:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又不用我费心的姑娘了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:43.80,0:44:45.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,归我了
Dialogue: 0,0:44:47.54,0:44:48.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗西塔
Dialogue: 0,0:44:50.98,0:44:52.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你准备了个小感谢礼物
Dialogue: 0,0:44:57.01,0:44:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是你们得到的
Dialogue: 0,0:44:59.36,0:45:02.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们拿走了全部的枪  大部分床垫
Dialogue: 0,0:45:05.25,0:45:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你美丽的小脑袋能找到地方躺下
Dialogue: 0,0:45:11.57,0:45:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在外面找到其他东西了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:45:15.67,0:45:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有你死去的朋友们
Dialogue: 0,0:45:38.77,0:45:40.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以还给你
Dialogue: 0,0:45:42.62,0:45:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你说那句话
Dialogue: 0,0:45:57.04,0:45:58.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天没人死
Dialogue: 0,0:46:00.02,0:46:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道我怎么想的吗
Dialogue: 0,0:46:02.27,0:46:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得咱俩加强了彼此的理解
Dialogue: 0,0:46:07.69,0:46:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我问问你  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:46:10.55,0:46:12.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想让我走吗
Dialogue: 0,0:46:17.86,0:46:19.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那再好不过了
Dialogue: 0,0:46:19.80,0:46:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就说那两个神奇的字吧
Dialogue: 0,0:46:31.41,0:46:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:46:35.32,0:46:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别搞笑了  应该我谢谢你
Dialogue: 0,0:46:46.60,0:46:48.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,又一个
Dialogue: 0,0:46:49.95,0:46:51.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你需要我们的帮助
Dialogue: 0,0:46:52.31,0:46:55.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴维  把那个烛台给我
Dialogue: 0,0:46:57.56,0:46:59.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我怎么想的吗  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:46:59.71,0:47:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们各取所需  都会是赢家
Dialogue: 0,0:47:04.21,0:47:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看好了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:36.72,0:47:38.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不错
Dialogue: 0,0:47:40.29,0:47:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,双赢
Dialogue: 0,0:47:44.92,0:47:47.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把它洗好等我下次用
Dialogue: 0,0:47:49.27,0:47:50.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:47:54.41,0:47:56.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:48:00.27,0:48:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太粗心了
Dialogue: 0,0:48:03.55,0:48:06.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会以为我要丢下露西尔吧
Dialogue: 0,0:48:06.30,0:48:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她做了那些事
Dialogue: 0,0:48:10.66,0:48:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么会想要她呢
Dialogue: 0,0:48:13.54,0:48:17.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感谢你这么配合  我的朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:48:21.36,0:48:23.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防万一你不明白
Dialogue: 0,0:48:24.93,0:48:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚刚把鸡巴塞进了你的嘴里
Dialogue: 0,0:48:28.15,0:48:30.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还为此感谢了我
Dialogue: 0,0:49:20.83,0:49:25.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}欢迎来到亚历山大安全区\N迷途者的天堂  掠夺者的地狱
Dialogue: 0,0:49:55.82,0:49:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯宾塞
Dialogue: 0,0:49:58.23,0:50:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们拿走了你屋里的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:50:01.55,0:50:04.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救世军想要我们全部的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:50:05.30,0:50:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,库存单上有两把不见了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:09.04,0:50:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们要杀了奥利维亚
Dialogue: 0,0:50:14.38,0:50:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯宾塞
Dialogue: 0,0:50:18.02,0:50:19.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你进了我屋子
Dialogue: 0,0:50:20.96,0:50:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们要杀了奥利维亚啊
Dialogue: 0,0:50:24.52,0:50:27.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我不怪你藏枪
Dialogue: 0,0:50:27.38,0:50:30.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也藏过  但是食品和酒
Dialogue: 0,0:50:33.05,0:50:35.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是因为你很卑鄙  斯宾塞
Dialogue: 0,0:50:35.49,0:50:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很脆弱
Dialogue: 0,0:50:37.23,0:50:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在墙里算你走运
Dialogue: 0,0:50:39.04,0:50:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有我们算你走运
Dialogue: 0,0:50:44.31,0:50:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该趁有机会的时候和他们谈协议
Dialogue: 0,0:50:49.16,0:50:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我们真走运
Dialogue: 0,0:50:51.21,0:50:52.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你带我们来到了乐土
Dialogue: 0,0:50:52.99,0:50:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不对  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:50:54.28,0:50:55.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们到了
Dialogue: 0,0:50:56.95,0:51:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜格伦和亚伯拉罕也很走运吧
Dialogue: 0,0:51:06.98,0:51:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再敢对我说类似的话
Dialogue: 0,0:51:10.52,0:51:13.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就打烂你的臭嘴  敲掉你的牙齿
Dialogue: 0,0:51:14.61,0:51:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白吗
Dialogue: 0,0:51:17.67,0:51:19.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说明白
Dialogue: 0,0:51:20.35,0:51:21.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白
Dialogue: 0,0:51:36.94,0:51:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有枪
Dialogue: 0,0:51:38.74,0:51:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:51:40.02,0:51:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前为什么不告诉我
Dialogue: 0,0:51:43.31,0:51:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到我为拿到一把枪做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:51:46.15,0:51:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还没有子弹
Dialogue: 0,0:51:47.06,0:51:48.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我藏了有段时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:51:49.07,0:51:51.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我不信任瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:51:53.73,0:51:55.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他管事让我担心
Dialogue: 0,0:51:57.97,0:51:59.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗  你说的对
Dialogue: 0,0:52:00.30,0:52:02.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是我们的命运
Dialogue: 0,0:52:57.03,0:53:00.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们拿走了我们的床垫  大部分都拿走了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:06.61,0:53:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那把步枪
Dialogue: 0,0:53:08.69,0:53:10.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是从他们哨站抢的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:10.59,0:53:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,单子上没有吧
Dialogue: 0,0:53:14.36,0:53:15.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:53:17.13,0:53:18.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本可以藏更多的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:18.52,0:53:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你藏了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:53:28.32,0:53:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:53:43.72,0:53:46.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得到的一切  都是抗争得来的
Dialogue: 0,0:53:46.29,0:53:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做出选择了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:49.96,0:53:52.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们人不够  这是人数问题
Dialogue: 0,0:53:52.16,0:53:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有山顶寨啊
Dialogue: 0,0:53:53.17,0:53:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们人数依然更多
Dialogue: 0,0:53:59.04,0:54:02.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们遵守他们的规则  就能活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:54:02.89,0:54:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么个活法
Dialogue: 0,0:54:10.56,0:54:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾有个朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:54:16.85,0:54:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没提起过他
Dialogue: 0,0:54:20.30,0:54:21.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他是我搭档
Dialogue: 0,0:54:23.04,0:54:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灾变后  他把洛莉和卡尔带到了安全地
Dialogue: 0,0:54:31.01,0:54:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没法做到  我当时在医院
Dialogue: 0,0:54:32.60,0:54:35.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:54:37.49,0:54:38.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:54:40.49,0:54:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他名字叫肖恩
Dialogue: 0,0:54:46.30,0:54:47.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他和洛莉
Dialogue: 0,0:54:50.41,0:54:51.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在一起了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:54.21,0:54:55.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们以为我死了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:58.59,0:55:00.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道朱迪思不是我的
Dialogue: 0,0:55:03.42,0:55:04.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:55:08.64,0:55:09.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我爱她
Dialogue: 0,0:55:10.06,0:55:11.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是我女儿
Dialogue: 0,0:55:13.75,0:55:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她不是我骨肉
Dialogue: 0,0:55:16.89,0:55:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须接受这点
Dialogue: 0,0:55:19.77,0:55:20.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我接受了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:22.01,0:55:23.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样我就能保护她
Dialogue: 0,0:55:28.72,0:55:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不死她就不会死
Dialogue: 0,0:55:30.31,0:55:32.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望那会是很久以后的事
Dialogue: 0,0:55:32.38,0:55:33.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样我可以
Dialogue: 0,0:55:34.50,0:55:38.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抚养她长大  保护她  教她求生
Dialogue: 0,0:55:42.18,0:55:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我们现在的生存方式
Dialogue: 0,0:55:45.65,0:55:47.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也必须接受这点
Dialogue: 0,0:55:47.08,0:55:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以保护所有人活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:55:49.35,0:55:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人死不是你的错
Dialogue: 0,0:55:52.74,0:55:55.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不总是  但是有时候是的
Dialogue: 0,0:55:59.01,0:56:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须接受
Dialogue: 0,0:56:02.48,0:56:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都要接受
Dialogue: 0,0:56:04.04,0:56:05.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然行不通的
Dialogue: 0,0:56:31.40,0:56:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会试试
Dialogue: 0,0:58:53.93,0:58:55.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我做颗子弹
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.69,0:07:58.90,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第七季  第四集』
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.81,0:01:27.66,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx2300\fscy200\alpha&AA\pos(129.2,218.4)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.80,0:01:07.80,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻译:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}冰蓝 Reginamoon CS小明漫画家
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.77,0:01:12.77,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻译:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}自然卷 艾瑞卡 蘑菇 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.73,0:01:17.73,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}校对:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.70,0:01:22.70,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}时间轴:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}雪妞 涛涛 加森
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.66,0:01:27.66,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}后期:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小哥  拉图    {\c&H008AFF&}总监： {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小孩
