[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Subtitles
Original Script: Subtitles
website: www.zimuzu.tv
Sina Weibo: @zimuzu
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134
Style: LOGO,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.92,0:00:08.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.43,0:00:10.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到20英里了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's 20?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.07,0:00:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快了  还有1英里就到642号公路了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It will be. 642 is a mile ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.31,0:00:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得在岔道前跟它们拉开距离\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We gotta put distance between us and them before the turnoff.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.17,0:00:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加速吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So floor it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.92,0:00:19.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  努力跟上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, try to keep up.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.62,0:00:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔  你看过这辆车吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Daryl, have you looked at this car?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.13,0:00:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我  我们也想尽快回去的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Believe me, we want to get back there, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.76,0:01:57.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别管了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Leave it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.15,0:02:01.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打算最后给它"美化"一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just gonna give it a last little polish.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.28,0:02:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你笑什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What the hell you got to grin about?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.12,0:02:06.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们赢了  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We won, darlin'.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.34,0:02:09.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能还有更多人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There could be more.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.32,0:02:14.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Screw it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.95,0:02:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\p1\bord0\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,200,\fscx206\fscy266\t(200,400,\fscx103\fscy133\t(29600,29800,\fscx206,fscy266\t(29800,30000,\fscx0\fscy0))))\c&H573E00&\pos(39.5,211)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10m -13 -14 l 13 -14 l 13 12 l -13 12 l -13 -14 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.95,0:02:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,200,\fscx206\fscy266\t(200,400,\fscx103\fscy133\t(29600,29800,\fscx206,fscy266\t(29800,30000,\fscx0\fscy0))))\c&HEBAE00&\bord0\shad0\fad(0,330)\pos(51.4,231.16)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.95,0:02:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,200,\fscx206\fscy266\t(200,400,\fscx103\fscy133\t(29600,29800,\fscx206,fscy266\t(29800,30000,\fscx0\fscy0))))\c&HEBAE00&\bord0\shad0\frz180\t(0,500,\clip(-1,0,386,289))\pos(27.7,188.26)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.95,0:02:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\alpha&B0\c&H000000&\t(0,200,\fscx2000\fscy600\t(200,400,\fscx2500\fscy300\t(29800,30200,\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\alpha&AA\fscy400\fscx400)))\move(158,211.2,46.5,211.2,29800,30200)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.95,0:02:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\fs16\fn方正大黑_GBK\move(-150,211,56,211,400,600)\clip(54.24,192,230.88,228.48)}本字幕首发于{\c&HEBAE00&}字幕组{\c&HFFFFFF&}网站\N{\c&H00C0FF&}www.ZiMuZu.tv {\c&HFFFFFF&}欢迎交流
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.95,0:02:27.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,281,227))}翻译  33来了 送小孩 小十三 自然卷
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.95,0:02:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,291,227))}翻译  冰蓝 CS小明漫画家 辰星晓Reginamoon
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.95,0:02:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\frx-630\t(0,500,\frx0\t(4500,5000,\clip(40,213,40,248)))\pos(57.12,210.56)}校对 送小孩 冰蓝
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.95,0:02:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,0)\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\move(57.12,210.56,400,210.56,4500,5000)\clip(54.24,193.92,284.24,228.48)}时间轴  加森 雪贵人 涛涛
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.95,0:02:47.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(300,300)\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs17\bord0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&HEDB425&\4c&H9EF6FF&\shad0\bord0\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))\pos(57.12,210.56)}后期 送小哥 拉图  总监 送小孩喝稠酒
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.73,0:03:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs21}本蓝光版外挂字幕由  {\c&H9B30FF&}风吹来的那片云{\c&HFFFFFF&}  用WEB版调轴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.73,0:03:53.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第六季  第六集』
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.89,0:04:42.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨沙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sasha?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.73,0:04:44.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚伯拉罕  你在吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Abraham, are you there?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.78,0:06:28.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找到我们了  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You found us, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.25,0:06:29.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here we are.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.12,0:06:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们拿走的都是应得的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We earned what we took.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.57,0:06:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许只是某个前哨站的一个士兵\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Probably just another soldier from one of the outposts.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.39,0:06:41.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许也讨厌他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Probably hates him, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.00,0:06:46.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道怎么用吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know how to use one?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.36,0:06:48.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.25,0:06:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从来不喜欢用这东西捕猎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Never liked using them to hunt.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.04,0:06:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去接帕蒂  然后就走  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We pick up Patty and we're gone, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.12,0:06:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们最后一天这样过活了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is the last day we gotta live like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.76,0:07:09.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get up.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.62,0:07:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, get up.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.55,0:07:20.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要走了  是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're moving. Here's the deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.82,0:07:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不说话  我就不杀你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't say shit and I don't kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.72,0:07:25.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是你以为的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I ain't who you think.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.09,0:07:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再说一句试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Say something else.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.10,0:07:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.43,0:07:37.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟着她们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Follow them.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.75,0:07:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给  喝了剩下的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here, drink the rest.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.96,0:07:53.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们该省着喝  -我们会找到更多的水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- We should save it. - We'll find some more.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.71,0:07:54.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Drink.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.78,0:07:56.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你该保持水分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're supposed to stay hydrated.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.11,0:07:58.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都会好的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It all works together.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.88,0:07:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, it does.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.35,0:08:15.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.43,0:08:18.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能让你倒下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We don't need you falling down.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.27,0:08:20.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喝\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Drink.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.64,0:08:27.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果他们找到我们  也许我们会交出你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They find us, maybe we give you to them,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.65,0:08:29.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样就扯平了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}they let us call it even.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.59,0:08:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是讲理的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You see, we're reasonable people.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.81,0:08:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都有自己的原则\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everybody's got their code.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.21,0:08:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你愿意下跪  那可以\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You feel you gotta kneel, that's fair enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.74,0:08:39.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不愿意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.92,0:08:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.67,0:08:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不敢相信我们回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't believe we're back.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.38,0:08:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里不再是家了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not home anymore,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.27,0:08:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但总比我们之前待的地方好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but it's better than where we were.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.24,0:09:00.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只在这里停留一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is a pit stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.28,0:09:03.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们接走帕蒂  仅此而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We pick up Patty, nothing more than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.31,0:09:07.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是怎么做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How'd you do it?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.86,0:09:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看见我们停卡车的地方了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You saw where we left the truck?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.95,0:09:12.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把汽油阀门打开了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We opened the valve
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.78,0:09:15.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从农景路一路开过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and drove all the way in from Farmview Road.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.23,0:09:18.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在树林里穿梭  直到我们开上路面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ran from the tree line till we got to the pavement.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.21,0:09:22.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,点燃了从斯威特沃特拿来的纸板火柴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lit up a matchbook from the Sweetwater
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.02,0:09:23.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把它扔到油迹上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and dropped it in on the trail.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.32,0:09:25.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们冲向车子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then we just ran for the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.47,0:09:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爬了进去  车边全是行尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Got in and the dead ones were there.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.95,0:09:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们撞在引擎盖上  然后...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They were beating on the hood, and then--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.11,0:09:34.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后  "轰"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and then boom!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.05,0:09:36.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们全翻了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Knocked 'em on their asses
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.95,0:09:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我再用斧子一个个解决了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I took an axe to each one.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.99,0:09:41.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我们就看着火焰渐起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then we just watched it go up.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.53,0:09:45.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再也听不见那些吼声和哀嚎\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No more moans, no more of that wailing.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.06,0:09:48.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有大火在燃烧  将它们全部烧成灰烬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was just the fire, just burning them all away.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.20,0:09:52.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这都是你们干的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You did all this?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.00,0:09:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时一切才刚刚开始\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was right at the start.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.78,0:09:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都停了  电视  广播\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everything stopped-- the TV, the radio.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.63,0:09:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就在这里  树林里全是行尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We were here. The forest was full of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.25,0:10:01.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,城里的行尸也被吸引了过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And the other ones in town, they were drawn to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.95,0:10:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,径直走进了火中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They just walked right into the flames.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.83,0:10:07.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们干掉了它们中的大部分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We got most of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.52,0:10:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以为我们这边搞定了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thought we ended it for us,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.85,0:10:10.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而她当时在华盛顿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and she was in DC.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.78,0:10:13.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们以为无论在哪里  大家都在和它们抗争\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We thought everyone was fighting them wherever they were.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.51,0:10:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  我们以为大家都在这样做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, we thought that was what everybody was doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.66,0:10:18.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在抗争它们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fighting it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.50,0:10:20.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以为我们会一起取得胜利\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That we'd all win together.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.06,0:10:24.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们当时太蠢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We were stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.58,0:10:27.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不觉得你们现在也是在犯蠢吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Y'all don't think you're being stupid right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.04,0:10:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说我应该杀了你吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you saying I should kill you?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.73,0:10:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是认真的  你会害我们吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean it, are you gonna try and pull something on us?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.54,0:10:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们手下留情是在犯蠢吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are we just being thick here by not removing all doubt?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.98,0:10:49.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,此时此刻  我没有扣下扳机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right now, by me not pulling this trigger,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.64,0:10:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个错误吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is that a mistake?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.53,0:10:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是认真的  我真的想知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm serious. I really wanna know.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.50,0:10:57.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你选择为其他人当杀手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You made a choice to kill for someone else,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.60,0:11:00.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了能有个三尺之地遮风避雨就出卖自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to have them own you for a roof over your head and three squares,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.86,0:11:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以也许我没有考虑周全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so maybe I'm not considering all aspects here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.57,0:11:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你告诉我  我是在犯蠢吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You tell me, am I being stupid?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.70,0:11:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.96,0:11:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  我得去个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, I got somewhere to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.80,0:11:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以做笔交易  我能帮你一把\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can make a deal. I can help you out.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.20,0:11:19.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和他们是一伙的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're one of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.94,0:11:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你受伤了  孤身一人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're hurt and you're alone
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.91,0:11:24.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了活命什么话都说得出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you'd say anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.97,0:11:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一开始就不该相信你们的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We should've never trusted you people to begin with.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.90,0:11:32.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go on.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.43,0:11:34.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Keep moving.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.76,0:11:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.06,0:12:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帕蒂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Patty.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.29,0:12:10.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她可能...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She could be...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.81,0:12:15.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}帕特里克燃料公司
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.80,0:12:18.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  她不见了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, she's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.44,0:12:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只能另定计划了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then we make another plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.53,0:12:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们离开这里  这就是计划\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, we get out of here, that's the plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.82,0:12:30.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就这样吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then that's the plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.95,0:12:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们没必要为我冒险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You guys didn't have to do this for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.33,0:12:35.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这样做是正确的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was the right thing for all of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.60,0:12:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是正确的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This was the right thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.54,0:12:41.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们现在回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even if just you guys went back now,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.83,0:12:43.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说一切都因我而起...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if you just told them that it was me...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.30,0:12:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  总会有办法的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, we'll find a way.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.73,0:12:47.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你们考虑一下  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Just think about it. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.36,0:12:49.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着  或许我们走不了那么远  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look, maybe we don't get as far,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.52,0:12:50.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们会...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but we'll get-- hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.47,0:12:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒂娜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tina, hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.15,0:12:52.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹  看着我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, baby sister, look at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.73,0:12:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跑  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, stop! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.33,0:12:57.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跑  我们需要那东西  求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't! We need that, please!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.22,0:13:21.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,萨沙  亚伯拉罕  能收到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sasha, Abraham, are you there?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.58,0:14:26.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}胰岛素  需冷藏
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.42,0:14:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There, it's clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.24,0:14:38.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的摩托不见了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}His bike's gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.60,0:14:44.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些是弹壳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}These are shells.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.45,0:14:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也有还击  逃走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He fired at 'em, got away.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.61,0:14:51.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他受伤不轻\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He caught a good bounce.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.73,0:14:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在本来就人烟稀少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There aren't enough people around
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.71,0:14:57.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,难道还会有人故意埋伏吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to just wait around for somebody to ambush.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.18,0:14:59.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们也不可能跟踪我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And they couldn't have just been watching us,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.62,0:15:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们做的事很难被跟踪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}not with what we were doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.87,0:15:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  他们想干掉某些特别的人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nah, they were looking to chew up someone in particular.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.09,0:15:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管这帮人是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whoever the hell they were.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.04,0:15:13.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔  能收到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Daryl, you copy?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.50,0:15:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Daryl?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.94,0:15:21.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我敢打包票  他肯定回亚历山大了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dollars to doughnuts, he's on his way back to Alexandria now.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.56,0:15:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他不会丢下我们的  -他这样做过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- He wouldn't leave us behind. - He already did.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.22,0:15:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是他回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But he came back.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.20,0:15:30.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们去找他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So we go look for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.34,0:15:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,寻找追踪者的最好办法是原地等待\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The best way to find a tracker is to stay put.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.37,0:15:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让他来找你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let him find you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.87,0:15:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想一直待在这里坐以待毙吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You just want us to sit here with our precious leathers in our hands?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.94,0:15:40.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.12,0:15:50.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}日出车险
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.03,0:16:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.13,0:16:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.26,0:16:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没那么蠢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're smarter than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.72,0:16:17.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没必要暴露行踪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We don't need to leave bread crumbs.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.82,0:16:27.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}迪克森
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.41,0:17:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么不干掉这个帅哥呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How come gorgeous over here is still standing?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.22,0:17:33.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它出不来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He can't get out.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.31,0:17:38.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,门锁了  我们没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's locked. We're fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.21,0:17:47.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放哨或睡觉  随你选\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stand watch or sleep? Your choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.48,0:17:52.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我选前者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll take the former.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.21,0:17:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不定再搜刮点东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do a little shopping, maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.09,0:18:34.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}为曾做出贡献而骄傲\N我为世界祈祷\N坚持下去  保持乐观\N咬伤会致死...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.18,0:18:41.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,睡不着吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can't sleep?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.94,0:18:45.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你这不废话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What does it look like?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.27,0:18:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想知道你是不是故意不睡的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just wanted to know if it was a choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.57,0:18:51.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have no idea how much
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.86,0:18:55.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有多想消灭那家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want to release that thing from this plane of existence.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.94,0:19:06.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们的新家了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This our new home?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.82,0:19:12.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咱们应该给它起个名字吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Should we give him a name?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.30,0:19:16.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都是你自己选择的结果\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You got yourself into this.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.97,0:19:20.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来该我独自开车  但你却要跟来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was driving that car solo until you chose to come with.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.28,0:19:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时我别无选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I didn't have a choice there.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.57,0:19:25.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell me why.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.56,0:19:27.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你一个人去根本不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You going stag was not an option.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.77,0:19:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell me why.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.24,0:19:37.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那时你失控了好一阵子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were out of control for a good while there.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.75,0:19:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差点在去天堂的路上把我的胳膊卸下来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just about took my arm off on the road to paradise.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.98,0:19:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-记得吗  -记得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You remember that? - I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.66,0:19:48.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我现在理智了  -我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I'm in control now. - Me, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.13,0:19:50.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你想杀了那只行尸吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's why you wanna kill that walker?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.40,0:19:52.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,街上那只\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The one down the street?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.53,0:19:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有车里那些人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The guys in the car?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.60,0:19:56.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你很理智\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'Cause you're in control.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.79,0:20:00.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为不了结一件事  让我如坐针毡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'Cause loose ends make my ass itch.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.23,0:20:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我心态不稳\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If I have not gotten my psyche situated straight,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.91,0:20:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也是因为麻烦始终不断地出现\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it's because the shit's continually been hitting the fan without respite.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.44,0:20:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,偶尔有间断  我们还开过派对呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, there's been respite. There was a party.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.79,0:20:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I remember that.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.60,0:20:17.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那时很"享受"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You had the time of your life there.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.41,0:20:23.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没必要跳出行驶着的车子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't have to throw yourself out of a moving car...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.61,0:20:26.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来让自己觉得在掌控中\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to feel like you're calling the ball.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.63,0:20:28.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那很容易的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.01,0:20:30.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跳下飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You jump out of an airplane,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.07,0:20:31.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后就没有选择了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you don't have choices after that.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.64,0:20:34.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你可以挑战一下地面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe you play some chicken with the ground,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.07,0:20:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可你拉开伞绳  就能活下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but you pull the rip cord, you live.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.94,0:20:42.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果你头顶有屋顶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But if you have a roof over your head,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.78,0:20:45.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有食物  有高墙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you have food, you have walls...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.51,0:20:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就有选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you have choices.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.71,0:20:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有行尸  子弹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And without walkers and bullets
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.39,0:20:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and shit hitting the fan,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.04,0:21:00.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就得负责\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you're accountable for them.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.44,0:21:05.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  该死  你一直都得负责\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, hell, you're always accountable.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.43,0:21:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是有那么多噪音干扰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's just with all that other noise,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.43,0:21:12.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道人们不会注意到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you know people won't notice.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.91,0:21:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么放哨  要么睡觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stand watch or sleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.42,0:21:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我选前者\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The former.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.87,0:21:38.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,守一整夜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Straight through the night.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.97,0:21:41.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们早上再商讨\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll reassess in the morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.57,0:21:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,商讨什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.24,0:21:45.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还待在这干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What the hell we're doing here.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.61,0:22:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放下枪  放下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Drop the gun. Drop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.92,0:22:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give it to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.20,0:22:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我大老远过来  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I came all this way.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.64,0:22:24.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你拿什么交换这个包\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What you got for the duffel?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.10,0:22:28.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让我受了太多罪  不能轻易给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You put me through too much shit just to give it back.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.11,0:22:30.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我的原则\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Principle of the thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.84,0:22:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你除了这把枪还有什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What you got besides this gun?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.12,0:22:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.11,0:22:38.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在刻什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What was that thing you were carving?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.50,0:22:47.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我外公教过我...  -我不在乎  就它了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- My grandfather taught me how... - Don't care. It'll do.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.59,0:22:54.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿走吧  都在里面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take it. It's all there.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.50,0:22:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你们好运  你们会需要好运的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good luck. You're gonna need it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.48,0:23:22.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一了百了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's end this.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.03,0:23:25.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我们的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's ours.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.56,0:23:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们拿走的都是应得的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We earned what we took.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.26,0:23:29.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们拿走的都得还回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna return what you took.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.89,0:23:32.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来这里消耗的汽油以及\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna pay for the gas it took to come out here
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.65,0:23:34.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家所费的时间也由你们买单\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and for all the time these men took out.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.08,0:23:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结束了  你们知道规矩的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's over. You know the rules.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.71,0:23:39.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狗屁规矩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your rules are batshit!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.81,0:23:43.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们才不回去  韦德  我们再也不下跪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're not going back, Wade. We're done kneeling!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.44,0:23:45.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别转移话题  混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't change the subject, asshole.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.77,0:24:00.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走  那边\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on. Hey, that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.62,0:24:03.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走  快  快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on. Go, go, go. Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.44,0:24:05.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get up.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.31,0:24:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.94,0:24:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Eyes open.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.11,0:24:38.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,管好自己的区域  切换到A频道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You cover your quadrant. Go to alpha channel.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.69,0:24:51.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爱你  谢尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Love you, Sher.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.06,0:24:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不用为我冒险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You didn't have to for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.59,0:25:16.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,韦德  我被咬了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wade, I'm bit!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.37,0:25:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,韦德  我被咬了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wade, I'm bit!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.32,0:25:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-帮我砍了  -该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Take it off me. - Damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.91,0:25:24.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动手  砍掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do it! Just take it off!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.55,0:25:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后你的手表归我了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll get your watch after.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.30,0:25:42.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  就这样吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, that's it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.90,0:25:43.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该回家了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Time to go home.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.76,0:25:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡姆受伤了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Cam got a boo-boo.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.64,0:25:47.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你确定吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Are you sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.82,0:25:51.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  他不想继续了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, yeah. He only wanted to take this so far.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.20,0:25:54.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他觉得强扭的瓜不甜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And he only wants ass that's willing, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.29,0:26:03.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  卡姆  走两步就好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, Cam. Let's walk it off.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.17,0:26:19.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们以为你和他们是一伙的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We thought you were with them.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.73,0:26:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把你打晕  绑起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We knock you over the head, tie you up,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.07,0:26:26.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还威胁说要杀你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}threaten to kill you...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.53,0:26:30.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么要回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}why the hell did you come back?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.85,0:26:35.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我也蠢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe I'm stupid, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.52,0:27:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们好啊  先生们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, howdy, gentlemen.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.12,0:28:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}唐娜·玛利亚
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.50,0:28:28.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,火箭弹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rpg.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.59,0:31:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你从哪里弄来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where do you get that?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.87,0:31:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些都是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It is the fruit
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.53,0:31:34.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我蠢得无可救药\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of some off-the-chart stupidity.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.73,0:31:39.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去做傻事的时候得来的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Some grade-A, butt steak idiocy.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.58,0:31:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自知之明真是个好东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Self-awareness is a beautiful thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.60,0:31:45.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.00,0:31:49.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我了解这个团队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You see, I know this group
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.05,0:31:51.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我了解瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I know Rick.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.14,0:31:54.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管家里发生了什么事  肯定都得到了处理\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And whatever happened back there is being managed
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.64,0:31:56.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正始作俑者没有好果子吃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and kicked right up into its own ass one way or another.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.47,0:31:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这点我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.48,0:32:01.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有啤酒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We got beer...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.23,0:32:05.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,空调\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and air conditioning...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.63,0:32:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有高墙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and walls.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.44,0:32:14.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这辈子都安排好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The table is set for the rest of our lives,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.41,0:32:17.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但愿我们过得长久殷实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I hope those years to be long and fruitful.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.20,0:32:20.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到那样的时光...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I see that time before me...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.27,0:32:25.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我一直有冲动想做点什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I've been feeling the urge to make some plays...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.57,0:32:30.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在死神随意夺走我的性命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}before the great cosmic Pete comes to cut my throat unceremoniously
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.47,0:32:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我咽下最后一口气之前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I gurgle my last breath.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.08,0:32:36.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但在此之前生活还要继续\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, things are gonna go on for a while before that,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.68,0:32:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前从来没有想过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and that hadn't occurred to me before.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.59,0:32:43.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前一直是走一步算一步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been kind of living check to check on that point.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.36,0:32:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你看穿我的样子  萨沙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I like the way you call bullshit, Sasha.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.21,0:32:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想更深入地了解你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I believe I'd like to get to know you a whole lot better.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.20,0:33:02.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那也是你想做的事之一吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That one of your plays?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.78,0:33:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是什么让你觉得我想要被理解的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What makes you think I want that?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.28,0:33:17.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人的直觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A man can tell.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.32,0:33:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:27.24,0:33:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你得先处理好自己的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}...you got some stuff to take care of.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.49,0:33:32.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.87,0:33:35.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,确实\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.39,0:33:50.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你认识他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So you knew 'em?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.53,0:33:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还觉得我是他们一员吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Still you thought I was one of them?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.88,0:33:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽管我们一开始就在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where we were-- we were there since the beginning.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.38,0:33:55.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但依旧认不全所有人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We still didn't know everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.08,0:33:58.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们刚加入那会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Back when we first threw in with them,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.12,0:33:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是个不错的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}it was as good as a place as any.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.91,0:34:02.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后生活变得艰苦  人们变得凶恶\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then things got harder, people got harder.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.85,0:34:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家开始显露人性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Human nature kicked in and it became
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.29,0:34:08.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上演了一出特别的闹剧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a truly unique kind of shitshow.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:08.02,0:34:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们为了安全愿意交换任何东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}People will trade anything for safety,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:11.27,0:34:12.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了知道他们是安全的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for knowing that they're safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.90,0:34:14.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.56,0:34:16.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后他们一无所有  仅仅是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So they got nothing left except just...
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.50,0:34:18.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活着\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}existing.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.52,0:34:21.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再也没人是安全的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, nobody's safe anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.10,0:34:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不能跟人们那样保证\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can't promise people that anyhow.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.44,0:34:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以跟想听到那话的人保证\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You could promise the people who want to hear it.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.98,0:34:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蒂娜  等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, Tina, hold up.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.13,0:34:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡拉和德伊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Carla and Delly.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.47,0:34:47.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's them.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.13,0:34:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和蒂娜在他们小的时候照看过他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Me and Tina used to babysit them when they were kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.67,0:34:59.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人都说灾变发生时他们去北边了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everyone said that they went out north when it all started.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.74,0:35:01.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We didn't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.52,0:35:11.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I did this.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.69,0:35:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是我们做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We did this.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.18,0:35:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.69,0:35:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉  宝贝  我们必须试试 \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm so sorry, baby. We had to try.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.32,0:35:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须试试  我们必须那样做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We had to try. We had to.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.95,0:36:01.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.79,0:36:03.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.27,0:36:05.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.52,0:36:23.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.09,0:36:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀过多少行尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How many walkers you killed?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.46,0:36:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-回答问题  -很多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Just answer the question. - A lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.90,0:36:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少几十只\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A couple dozen at least.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.37,0:36:38.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀过多少活人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How many people you killed?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.49,0:36:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没杀过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}None.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.13,0:36:42.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.35,0:36:47.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我为什么没杀过活人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why haven't I killed anybody?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.98,0:36:51.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为如果我杀了  就没有回头路了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because if I did, there'd be no going back.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.25,0:36:55.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就永远无法回到过去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There'd be no going back to how things were.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:57.56,0:36:58.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来自的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm from a place
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.67,0:37:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们依然没变\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}where people are still like they were...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.26,0:37:06.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,基本没变  不论好坏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}more or less, better or worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.39,0:37:26.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们从这里步行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can walk it from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:27.42,0:37:29.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到遇见我的朋友们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Till we meet up with my friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.17,0:37:31.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们有车  你们可以坐他们的车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They got a car. You can ride with them.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.39,0:37:34.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说你有多少朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How many friends you say there were?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.98,0:37:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没说  他们有两个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't. There's two of 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.79,0:37:40.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where are they?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.02,0:37:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去找找\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're gonna find out.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.50,0:37:46.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道他们逃掉了  没被抓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How do you know they even got away? That they didn't get taken?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:46.51,0:37:47.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.53,0:37:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.67,0:38:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.66,0:38:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把弩给她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give her the crossbow.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:14.01,0:38:15.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要回去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You gonna go back?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.33,0:38:18.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你要安全吗  -闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You gonna be safe? - Shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.50,0:38:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再也没有安全的地方了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ain't nowhere safe no more.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.47,0:38:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把弩给她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give her the crossbow.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.57,0:38:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要下跪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You gonna kneel?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.20,0:38:58.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,包扎一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Patch yourself up.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.38,0:39:04.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.11,0:39:07.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna be.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.87,0:40:05.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}帕特里克燃料公司
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.24,0:40:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}帕特里克燃料公司
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.23,0:40:38.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}车牌号  帕蒂002
Dialogue: 0,0:40:56.99,0:40:58.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look at this.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.53,0:41:05.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:08.60,0:41:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.82,0:42:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克  能收到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick, you copy?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:03.83,0:42:05.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Anybody?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:10.94,0:42:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重复一遍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Say it again?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.12,0:42:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Help.
