Captioning made possible by
comedy central
? I'm going down
to south park?
? Gonna have
myself a time?
? Friendly faces
everywhere?
? Humble folks
without temptation?
? Going down
to south park?
? Gonna leave my
woes behind?
? Ample parking
day or night?
? People spouting
"howdy neighbor"?
? Headed on up
to south park?
? Gonna see if
i can't unwind?
? So come on down
to south park?
? And meet some
friends of mine?
Dude, did you do all
your homework last night?
Yeah, but there was
so much of it,
I was up until
two in the morning.
I know.
Okay, children, i hope you all
did your homework last night
Because we're going to
talk about pages 42 through 612.
First of all,
who can tell me
What year the founding fathers
got together?
Let's see, how about...
Please don't call me,
please don't call on me.
Wendy.
Whew!
1776.
Good job, wendy, and what
was that document called?
Oh, please god, don't
let him call on me.
Father in
heaven i beg you.
Kyle.
Oh, thank you lord,
praise jesus!
The declaration
of independence.
Very good, kyle.
Now, who can tell me
what famous person
Wrote the declaration
of independence?
Let's see...
Oh, i know, how about
the new student, timmy.
Timmy!
No, it wasn't you, timmy,
try again.
Hee-Yah...!
Timmy, did you not
do your homework?
Timmy!
Ah, mr. Garrison,
haven't you figured it out?
Timmy's retarded.
Don't call
people names, stanley.
But he is.
Now, timmy, you need to
work on your study skills.
Duh...
Are you mocking me?
Because if you are, i have no
problem sending your butt
To the
principal's office.
Liv-A-Laa...
liv-A-La timmar!
That does it!
Well, timmy, i just don't
know what to do with you.
You're getting
very poor marks in school,
And the teachers are complaining
you aren't paying attention.
Ah.
Young man, if you don't
want to be held back a grade,
I suggest you start
cooperating, m'kay.
Timmy!
Well, that does it,
i'm suspending you, timmy,
Until you can learn
to respect your elders.
Hold on there just a second,
principal victoria.
I think i may know
what the problem is.
Timmy.
Yes, of course.
What?
I think maybe timmy
is suffering from
Something called
"attention deficit disorder"
Or a.D.D.
It's very common
in kids his age.
Oh!
Timmy!
Well, that certainly
would explain it.
It's should be
easy enough to find out,
They have tests for
that kind of thing now.
Liv-A-Lar
timmy!
All right this is
a very simple test
Which should determine,
without a doubt
Whether or not timmy has
attention deficit disorder.
Good.
M'kay.
Now, timmy, i'm going to
read you a book called
"The great gatsby"
by f. Scott fitzgerald,
At the end of the novel,
i'll ask you a few questions,
Are you ready?
Him-My!
Okay, here we go.
"In my younger and more
vulnerable years,
"My father gave me some advice that i've
been turning over in my mind ever since...
"So, we beat on,
boats against the current,
Born back ceaselessly
into the past."
Ah-Ahhh.
Okay, now timmy, can you
tell me, in chapter seven,
What kind of car
did gatsby drive?
Timmy!
Well, that settles it!
This young man definitely has
attention deficit disorder.
Oh-Oh, i knew it.
What can we do
for him, doctor?
Well, a.D.D. Is
fairly common in kids today,
I'm going to prescribe
someritalin.
And we'll see how that
goes for little timmy.
Timmy...
Hurry up children,
let's take our seats.
You better have done
your homework last night, timmy.
What's this?
Timmy.
A note
from the principal.
"Please excuse timmy from all
questions and all homework,
As he has been diagnosed with
attention deficit disorder."
Oh, brother!
He doesn't have to
do homework?
That's just swell, timmy.
Looks like you've outsmarted the
principal and the counselor.
Timmy.
Very well, i guess you're
excused from homework.
Hey wait, i think maybe i have
attention defunction disorder.
Yeah, me too,
i've got a.D.D.
Me too.
I've got it. Me too!
"After a while i went out
and left the hospital
And walked back to the
hotel in the rain."
All right now, in chapter 12, what kind
of bottles did ms. Van campen talk about?
Anybody?
My god, these children
all have a.D.D.
Hooray.
Hooray. Hooray.
It's ritalin
for all of you!
Dude, we suck.
Hey that's not
the right attitude, jonesy.
The battle of the bands
is tomorrow night.
Dude, we'd never win the
battle of the bands.
There's no big deal.
Not a big deal!
This year's winner gets
to open for phil collins
At lollapaloobooza and
that's no big deal.
Hey guys, you better
stop fighting.
We just got to
practice more.
Dude, we've been practicing
for eight years, skylar.
Hey, am i the leader
of this band or not?
Now, let's
do it from the top.
Tim-Mah!
What was that?
I don't know, man.
Whoa!
Who is that?
Timmy!
Are you a
singer, man?
La-La-Timmy.
Timmy!
Dude, that's hot!
Yeah.
There's your prescription ms. Mccormick,
$100 worth of ritalin.
Then he won't have attention
deficit disorder anymore?
We can only hope so.
Next!
Oh, hi sheila.
Sharon, your son has attention
deficit disorder, too?
Yes, i should have known,
it all makes sense now.
I could never get stanley
to pay attention
When his grandfather told
him stories about the '30s.
I know what you mean,
kyle gets so hyper sometimes
He runs around and screams
like a little eight-Year-Old.
I am eight.
Next, please.
What do we have here-
Oh, ritalin.
Yes.
That's right i've got
a bad case of a.D.D.
No homework for me.
Mr. Pharmacist, this ritalin doesn't
have any side-Effects does it?
No, your son may experience
a small lack of energy,
But that's all.
And he might start seeing little
christina aguillera monsters
But that's
to be expected.
Oh, my!
? Would you like to be
laughing in fields of light?
? Laughing in fields of light?
Boo!
You suck. Boo!
All right, that was
"Sinisters of mercy, hold no
pain against the dark lord"
With their song
"Spilt blood on the footsteps
of my mind revisited".
We got the best response,
We'll be opening for
phil collins for sure.
And now it's time
for our final band.
Thank god!
Ha ha!
Ha ha! Ha ha!
Give it up for,
"Timmy and
the lords of the underworld".
One, two, three, four!
Timmy!
Yimmy, yeah!
That handicapped
dude, rules!
Yeah.
You guys are terrible, how
can you laugh at that poor kid?
Timmy, timmy!
? The lords of
the underworld?
? Darkness fills
my heart with pain?
Timmy, timmy!
Dude, it's timmy.
No way!
Da... da... da...
They're ridiculing that singer,
come on let's get out of here.
Timmy, timmy.
? And the lords
of the underworld?
Timmy!
? Darkness fills my
heart with pain?
Timmy!
That was awesome!
Yeah, timmy rules!
Boys, you shouldn't laugh
at him he's handicapped.
But, he's funny.
How, would you like
to be handicapped?
Do you think that
would be funny?
You're making
him feel bad.
He looks pretty
happy to me.
Oh, you people
make me sick!
Dude, this is
a no-Brainer!
This year battle
of the bands winner
And the band that gets to open for
phil collins at lullapolooza istimmy.
We did it, dude.
Listen to them,
they really love me.
Woo!
Woo! Woo! Woo!
Yes, i'm a rocker!
Tonight we analyze
the new rock sensationtimmy,
The controversial new band
that's taken the country by storm.
Already playing at
several large venues this month.
The band prepares for it's
biggest gig, lollapaloozaza.
Where they will open
for phil collins.
But, phil collins
is not happy.
Well, i think it's a
horrible tragedy, isn't it?
I mean, people aren't going to
see timmy for his musical skills
They're laughing at him.
And i think you shouldn't laugh
at people with disabilities.
Ha, heh-Heh.
Society has to learn
to be more compassionate.
This is going to stop,
if i have to stop it myself.
Dude, did you
see that stuff
Phil collins was
saying about timmy?
Yeah, what a dick, timmy's five
times more talented than he is.
Hey, guys, have you been
taking your ritalin?
No we're not actually
going totakethat stuff.
No dude, you got to try it,
it makes you feel good.
Good...
Hello, there children.
Hello, chef.
Hello, chef.O, chef.
How's it going?
Very well, thank you.
Everything's fine, why?
Because we're
on ritalin.
What?
We all have
attention deficit disorder
So we all started
taking ritalin.
It really takes the edge off,
man, you should try it.
So,that'swhy all you children
are acting so damn boring.
That's correct, chef.
Dammit, children,
you don't need drugs
To make you pay
attention in school.
In my day, if we
didn't pay attention
We got a belt
to the bottom.
Now they try to
cure everything with drugs.
Yes, but now we don't
have any homework,
So we can go see timmy play
downtown at mile high stadium.
Oh, boy, oh, boy.
Oh, boy.
Oh, it makes me sick!
Those damn psychologists prescribe
all kind of medicine to you children,
Without even caring
about the side-Effects.
But there are no
side-Effects, chef.
No, none at all.
Reoww!
Did you guys see that?
See what?
You're watchingmtv.
The cool brainwashing
12-Year-Old and younger station
That hides behind
a slick image.
We're so cool,
that we decide what's cool.
And nowmtv news.
The news that is single-Handedly
dumbing down our country,
Which is cool.
Here's your host,
kurt loder.
Why am i
still doing this?
I've got to be to the oldest person
on this network by at least 40 years.
Kurt loder didn't
just say that.
No wait, he did just say it,
but just to be cool.
That's what
makes him cool.
You think kurt loder is cool
and now the news that's cool.
Well, it's only two weeks
until lollapaloobuba
And the headlining band
has changed,
Now the headlining the event
istimmy,
The new hit sensation
out of colorado.
This news came as a shock
to the performer
That was going to headline
lalapulubla, phil collins.
Well, i think the
sad question is,
Where are the parents
in all this?
I mean, that kid's parents is
letting them be exploited
And they don't even
seem to care.
And so phil collins
decided to travel to south park
And personally pay
timmy's parents a visit.
Well, i mean,
Why are you letting them
do this to your son?
Don't you see that everyone
is just laughing at them.
Richard!
Helen!
Hey.
Phil collins warns that a novelty
band that makes fun of the handicapped
Should not be allowed
to play at lollapoolula.
And vows to do everything
in his power to stop it.
Phil collins, by the way,
divorced his wife by fax
And then married
a 27-Year-Old.
I'm kurt loder
and that's the news.
Okay, children,
let's settle down.
I mean it,
i want quiet.
My god, mr. Hat,
These children are
so boring on ritalin.
All right, children,
today we're going to learn about
Human reproduction!
What do you
think about that?
Vaginas and penises...
Butt sex.
Damn it, eric, don't you have
some smart-Ass thing to say?
What kind of smart-Ass thing
would i say, mr. Garrison?
This is driving me crazy!
I can't handle you little
bastards being so mellow.
Gee, you seem
a little stressed mr. Garrison,
Why don't you
try some ritalin?
Ah...
There you go.
Reow!
Ahh!
Thank you, baltimore.
Good night!
Alright, let's
rock this house.
Hello miami!
Timmy!
Excuse me, skylar.
Yeah.
Nice to meet you,
i'm phil collins.
Oh, yeah, you're opening
for us at lollapaluzava.
I just want to
tell you well,
That i think you're a great
guitar player and songwriter.
Oh, thanks a lot,
i appreciate that.
Gotta run.
It's too bad those other guys
are holding you back.
Huh?
Well, i mean,
it's obvious
All the talent and artistic
vision in the band comes from you.
Strange how everyone
focuses on timmy, isn't it?
I mean even the name
of the band is timmy.
The name of the band is "timmy
and the lords of the underworld."
Look, i used to be
in a band too, genesis.
But all those bastards did was
hold me back, and hold me back,
But then finally
i went solo.
And that's when i started
writing really great songs.
But, look if you you're
happy being on the sidelines,
Being more of a cheerleader
than a player,
Well then i guess you should
stay on as timmy's shadow.
Oh, thanks man,
see you.
That should just about put an
end to all this timmy nonsense.
Timmy, timmy, timmy!
Another great show, man.
There must have been
100,000 people out there.
Yeah, all of them
chanting, "timmy, timmy".
Timmy!
What's the matter, skylar?
The name of the band is "timmy
and the lords of the underworld",
Not just "timmy".
Timmy.
And the lords
of the underworld.
Timmy!
It's all about
you, isn't it?
I'm sick of it!
Timmy gets all
the applause.
the chicks.
Well, you know what,
forget you, man.
But, timmy is what
made our band famous.
Shut up, malsey.
You can stay and deal with
mr. Egomaniac here,
But i'm moving on.
I don't need timmy,
i'm going solo.
Timmy.
No, don't try
and stop me, man.
I'll see you
on fame's backside.
Liba-La!
Hey, terrence, what brand
of pants am i wearing?
Let me see.
Ha ha!
Let's watch
something else.
Yes, let's.
You're watchingvh-1.
Ah...
ah... ah...
Here's lollapala's news, the
hit group, timmy has broken up.
Oh, dear,
timmy's band broke up.
And so phil collins
is back on as headliner.
The opening band now will be timmy's
guitarist skylar's new solo project,
"Reach for the skylar".
You know something,
i think that's good.
It was wrong to
make timmy a singer.
Yeah, phil collins
was right.
People laughed
at timmy.
And timmy should be at home where
he's protected from laughter.
I agree.
You know what, you guys, we
should go to the concert anyway,
And see phil collins.
Yeah, i think phil collins
rocks the house.
Sounds good,
so it's decided,
Phil collins' concert
for all of us.
Hoo-Ray.
Oh, oh,
hold still kenny.
Oh, my goodness,
you killed kenny.
Bastard.
Parents, i called
all you guys together,
Because i think you
might be making a mistake
Putting your children
on ritalin.
But, our kids have
attention deficit disorder,
Chef, they can't pay attention
in school without it.
I know you want
to help your kids,
But i brought over
a videotape to show you
That there are
alternatives to ritalin.
There is this doctor
in northern california
Who is doing really amazing
things with kids who have a.D.D.
I want you
watch this tape.
Hello, i'm dr. Richard shay,
Here to tell you about my
exciting new drug-Free treatment
For children with
attention deficit disorder.
Ya-Ya...
ya-Ya... ya-Ya...
This treatment is
fast and effective
And doesn't use
harmful drugs.
Watch closely as i apply
treatment to the first child.
I want a horse-
I want a
big brown horse
With a fluffy black tail-
Sit down and study!
Oh, let's go race-
Wahhh, aah-
Stop crying and
do your schoolwork!
If you would like more information
on my bold new treatments,
Please send away for
this free brochure entitled,
"You can either calm down, or i
can pop you in the mouth again."
Well, what do you think.
I can have dr. Shay come to
south park for a small fee.
That video had
pretty colors.
It sure did.
What the-?
Dammit, have you all been taking
your children's ritalin too?
Yes.
Yes. Yes.
Oh, fudge it.
Chef, are you going to the
phil collins concert tomorrow?
The what?
Phil collins is playing
lollapalalas
And because we're all doing
so well in school now
Our parents said
they would take us.
Yes.
Yes. Yes.
Hold on a second, you children,
wantto go see phil collins.
Yes, his flowing melodies
are really enjoyable to us.
Oh, my god!
Come, see him with us.
Yes, come with us,
come with us.
Ahhh, it's christina aguillera
again, she's on my back.
That does it, the ritalin has affected
your little cracker brains too deeply.
I'm going to see
that damn pharmacist.
Look at that, ritalin stocks
are up ten points.
That's easily another
20 grand apiece.
Hey, open
this damn door!
Can i help you?
Yes, you can.
What the hell are
you two doing
Prescribing all
the children ritalin.
Well, they've all been
diagnosed with a.D.D.
That's attention deficit-
I know what it is,
but now you've got
A town full of
zombie children
From the planet zandor.
Huh?
All around the country,
You bastard doctors are
giving children ritalin,
And for every one child
that actually needs it
You give it to
50,000 that don't.
Hey now, don't tell us
our business, mr. Chef-
You damn right i'll
tell you your business,
Because you two have
your heads up your asses.
Thanks to you we have children in
our town that like phil collins.
What?!
That's right, you made them
so dull and boring
That they're actually going to
go to a phil collins concert.
My god,
what have we done?
But, if i'd known.
I mean, phil collins, my god.
Well, how do we
reverse the ritalin?
We have to convince
them not to take it,
But it'll be hard
to get it away from them.
Then we need
an antidote.
Yes, of course.
What's the antidote
for ritalin?
I have some right here,
it's a compound calledritalout.
We've got to get the antidote
to all the children, quick!
? That's not a word?
? Oh, boo boo?
? Boo, boo, yo?
Here, we can put the ritalin
antidote in these drinks
And hand them out
to the children.
? Boo boo boo-Dio?
Oh, wasn't
that great son?
It sure was, dad.
It's so wonderful to be on the
same wavelength as our kids.
Here you go, stan and
kyle, free drinks on me.
Oh, thank you, chef,
how nice.
And now, i'd like to sing the complex
and amazing song that won me the oscar.
A song entitled,
you be in me.
? You're inside of me?
? Deep inside of me?
? So deep in inside, i can feel
you pushing against my heart?
Come on drink
it down, it's free.
? You be inside of me?
Arr...
oh noo!
Get off me,
get off me!
Somebody help.
I feel... different.
Yeah.
Get off me
christina aguillera.
Drink this, eric.
God, help me.
She's gone.
Thank god.
What makes...
Wait a minute,
phil collin sucks ass!
Yeah, what the hell
were we thinking?
Boo!
I think
it's working.
Boo!
Boo! Boo!
Shut your filthy holes
you little bastards!
Get off the stage
phil collins!
We want timmy!
Yeah.
You just want to
laugh at him.
No, you see we learned
something today.
Yeah sure,
we laughed at timmy,
But what's wrong
with laughter?
Just because
we laugh at something
Doesn't mean we don't
care about it.
Timmy made us smile and
playing made timmy smile,
So where was
the harm in that?
The people in the wrong, are the people
who think timmy should be protected
And kept out of the
public's eye.
The cool thing about
timmy being in a band
Was that he was in your face,
and you had to deal with him.
Whether you laughed
or cried or felt nothing.
That's why
timmy rules.
Yeah.
Timmy, timmy!
Timmy! Timmy! Timmy!
Timmy!
Timmy! Timmy!
Man it sucks not being
part of lollapalabala.
Yeah.
Hey dudes.
Skylar, what are
you doing here?
Isn't "reach for the skylar"
supposed to play soon?
They booed phil collins
off the stage.
Everyone is
chanting for
"Timmy and the
lords of the underworld".
So now that they want us
you think you can just
Waltz back into our lives
and be in the band again?
I don't expect
anything.
Timmy, i just
wanted to say
We had some pretty
rocking times, dude.
And maybe i let fame and
phil collins go to my head.
Timmy! Timmy! Timmy!
Timmy!
Timmy! Timmy!
Wow, they really are
chanting for us.
They want us back.
What do you say, timmy?
Timmy.
All right!
Ladies and gentlemen,
without further ado
It is my pleasure to introduce
the reunion tour oftimmy.
Timmy and the lords
of the underworld.
Timmy!
Yimmy- Yah!
Timmy-Timmy.
? And the lords of
the underworld?
Put me down
you filthy bastards!
Ah... arrr!
Timmy, liv-A-Lar!
Boo cha ka...
Timmy, timmy, timmy.
Timmy.
? And the lords of
the underworld?
? Darkness fills
my heart with pain?
Captioning made possible by
comedy central
Captioned by
soundwriters™
www.tvsubtitles.net