Captioning made possible by
comedy central
? I'm going down
to south park?
? Gonna have
myself a time?
? Friendly faces
everywhere?
? Humble folks
without temptation?
? Going down
to south park?
? Gonna leave my
woes behind?
? Ample parking
day or night?
? People spouting
"howdy neighbor"?
? Headed on up
to south park?
? Gonna see if
i can't unwind?
? So come on down
to south park?
? And meet some
friends of mine?
Okay, is everyone
ready to go?
Oh, i'm so excited.
I've always wanted to see
"cirque du cheville".
Me too, we were lucky
to get tickets.
Come on boys,
we're gonna be late!
Oh, don't they
look precious!
Why do we have to
dress up?
Isn't this just a circus with
elephants and lions and stupid clowns?
No stanley, cirque du cheville
is french canadian.
They get acrobats and singers
from all over the world
And do very
artistic things.
Ahh...!
Why the hell do you wanna
take these boys
To see that "fufu"
french theater crap?!
You're gonna turn them
into "poofters".
Dad, stanley needs
to see the arts.
Well, he, doesn't need
to see a bunch of frogs
Prance around in
tights and makeup
Wrapping their peckers
around each other's faces!
Come on everybody,
let's go.
Close your eyes and
cover your ears, billy!
Remember, you're a man!
Oh, this is so exciting.
Oh, look at the
funny clown, stanley.
Where?
Oh, no.
Ah, very funny,
thank you, goodbye.
No, thank you.
Go away, please.
He doesn't want your dumb-Ass
umbrella, clown, beat it!
Ow!
You didn't know that was
gonna happen, did you, stanley?
Oh god,
that was so funny!
Oh man, somebody stop my guts
from bursting out of my sides.
Ladies and gentlemen,
please no smoking
And no flash photography
duringcirque du cheville.
Cirque du che-Blehh.
Ooh-Ho, we've reached
fagtrack and bob, captain.
Eric, shh!
How long does
this thing last?
Two hours.
Awww!
Ooh, these are the contorting
quintuplets from romania.
Woo hoo!
What, what- Another
gay guy in feathers?
Wow!
Damn, dude!
Oh, yay!
Oh, that was
wonderful.
Yes, too bad that was their
last show or i'd go see it again.
Those contorting
romanian chicks ruled.
Yeah, especially that
second one from the left,
She was fine.
Cartman, what the hell
you're talking about?
They're identical!
Not that second one from the
left, she had it going on!
Don't forget to buy
your souvenirs, folks.
Damn, dude, you see how much
money this place is raking in?
Yeah, i could prance around
in tights and sing opera too
For that kind of cash.
Hey, we should start our own
cirque du cheville.
Yeah, this one's moving out
of town, so we could take over.
Let's go practice.
Hurry up, girls.
We must bundle up
against the cold.
Did we do good
final show, grandmama?
Very good, my girls.
I only wish it weren't
your last show.
I love this country
so very much.
Mrs. Vladchik,
it is time.
It is time
to return to romania.
Yes, yes, of course.
Just give me one second
to finish getting them ready.
This way, girls, quickly.
Why are we going out
the window, grandmama?
Your mother did not want you
to grow up in romania.
This is our only chance.
Mrs. Vladchik?
They're trying to defect!
We need a boat.
Where to, mack?
Follow that boat.
Ow!
Heh-Heh, heh-Heh...
Ahhh!
Dude, this isn't working.
It's kenny's singing.
Huh?
Yeah, kenny,
you have to sing better.
I'm singing
as good as i can!
Well, it's not
good enough, kenny.
You have to get better,
try again!
Aha, i knew it.
They turned you
into poofters.
There's nowhere to go,
mrs. Vladchik, pull over!
Okay, girls,
Did we do good,
grandmama?
Very good, gracas.
I'm tired, grandpa.
No, billy, you're gonna stay
here and watch more "macgyver".
We're gotta get all the
frenchy-Fu fag nasties outta ya.
Who the hell would be
ringing the doorbell
This time of night?
I don't know...
Whoa!
We are very sorry
to disturb you.
My granddaughters
are cold and tired.
Is there any possibility we could
pay you for a place to sleep?
You're from
cirque du cheville.
Yes, we...
missed our train.
If we could shelter here,
it would only be for one night.
Well...
Well, of course you can,
come in out of the snow.
Oh, thank you
so much!
There's some spare
bedrooms upstairs, mrs...
Vladchik.
That grandma's not
a bad piece of ass.
Eww, dad, not
in front of stanley.
Well, it's good for him.
Hello and welcome to "singing
like bocelli for dummies".
Lesson one:
Lesson two:
Good.
And now we'll do the
entire piece conte partiro.
Conte partiro?
Got everything
you need there, do you?
Yes, you've all been so kind
to my little granddaughters.
They're quite agile
little things, aren't they?
Yes, as i was
back in my day.
I was a
contortionist too.
You don't say?
Yes.
You... remember any of
that stuff, do ya?
Oh... man.
Ohhh...
And now lesson four, the
complete works of mozart.
Let's begin.
Gah!
What should we do,
randy?
I like these
romanians, fine,
But i hope that old woman isn't
planning on staying here much longer.
Yeah, it's 11:00 and
she's still sleeping.
Poor, dear,
must be tired.
You're damn right
she's tired.
Huh?
Oh nothin', she's just gonna
have a little trouble
Walkin' today is all.
Hurry up, you guys.
What's going on?
Dude, you're not
gonna believe this.
What?
Hello.
Hi.
No way, the bitches from
cirque du che-Blah!
Yeah, they're quintuplets
from romania.
What's a quintuplet?
We are twins, except there are
five of us instead of two.
But, there's only
four of you.
No no, natalia is just playing
mirror buddies with nadia.
Hello!
So, if you're identical, does
that mean you all think alike?
No, don't be ridiculous!
Will you guys be
in our cirque du cheville?
You have your own?
Kenny has to get
better at singing first.
Hey!
But, as soon as he
starts singing better,
We're all gonna
make bank!
Okay.
Sounds good.
Count me in.
Okay.
Oh, and me.
Alright!
Alright, we've gotta
figure out what to do.
I'm gonna go
wake her up.
Hello, mrs...
mrs. Old romanian woman...
Ma'am?
A little tuckered, is she?
No, dad.
A little cottony
in the crotch?
No dad, she's dead!
What?
Oh, dear jesus!
It looks like she
had a heart attack.
No wonder she didn't
say goodnight.
Eww!
Okay, hold it,
hold it.
Ow!
I don't know how to
tell them, you tell them.
Uh, girls,
we have some bad news.
What?
Umm... everyone who has
a grandma, step forward.
Uh, not so fast girls.
Randy!
Grandmama is dead?
What are we
going to do now?
Hey guys, come here.
This is
totally awesome.
What?
How can
you say that?
Because now we can
convince them to stay here
And now our circus
will kick ass.
Oh yeah!
Mom, dad, can the quints stay
with us, please, can they?
Well, stanley,
it's not really-
They have nowhere
else to go, please!
Well, for the time being,
i, i mean...
Of course
they can stay.
Hooray!
Tom, i'm standing
at the home in south park
Where five precious little girls
have been rescued from romania.
Their mother passed away
some months ago
And then their grandmother died
trying to bring them here.
But all is well now
and people are coming
From all over the country
to view the little tykes.
If you'd like to come down
and see the quintuplets
Admission is only
five dollars.
And for a few dollars more,
you can feed them fish sticks.
Mmm!
Tom, it looks like
these cute little girls
Have made it out of that armpit
of a country they call romania.
Yes, luckily for them,
these quintuplets no longer
Have to live in romania,
the asshole of the world.
Back to you, tom.
This is not good.
It makes our country
look poor and stupid.
This could kill
our tourism.
You know what to do.
Alright, kenny, let's start
with some warm-Up exercises.
Well, what do you think?
Can you help him
become a better singer?
Well, he's got potential.
Depends on how good
he wants to be.
Very, very good!
Well, if you want
to be arealsinger
You need to go to
a conservatory in europe,
There's just
no other alternative.
Europe?
We can't
afford that.
Well, then i'm afraid your
son will always be a hack.
Nnn...
Well, kenny, if it
means that much to you,
Maybe we can bus it to europe and
you can sing on the way to make money.
Yeah!
Randy, randy, you better
have a look at this.
What?
...until the u.S. Government
received this video
Which was sent from romania
just hours ago.
Hello, this is
romanian father.
I am desperate to have my
girls returned to me in romania.
Uh-Oh.
That's your dad?
Maybe.
We haven't seen papa
for more than five years.
How i miss them all-
Little nada-
Nadia!
Nadia,
my sweet barsca.
Bartonia!
Bartonia- Anyway, my heart
is aching for their return.
I know the american government
will do us right, thank you.
Oh no, dude, if he they get
sent back to romania,
We'll never get our
cirque du cheville going!
Mom, dad, you're not gonna
send them back, are you?
Well, i think
we... have to.
Don't we?
I don't know.
You don't wanna go back
to stinky romania, do you?
It sucks there!
Yeah, america
is so much cooler.
In romania they just oppress
you and try to bring you down.
We'll have to call the police
and see what they want us to do.
Damn, we might be
screwed.
No, we've just gotta convince these
chicks that america kicks the ass
Out of every
other country.
Come on!
You see in america,
we have log rides...
Bacon double cheeseburgers!
Sheep shearing contests.
Yeah, woo hoo!
And shopping malls!
Yay!
Woo hoo!
Mrs. Janet reno,
You must understand the father
has right to his children.
Yes, but the girls seem
to wanna stay here.
Why don't you all
stay here in america
And this whole thing
can go away?
Okay.
Our home is romania.
We love it there!
Ah, yes,
we love it there.
If daughters will not
return on their own
You must force them
to return.
Gentlemen, this has to be
handled very delicately.
You don't understand
americans' power to protest.
Protest?
Look, people have it
so good in america
That they get bored
very easily.
And when people get bored
they start protesting things.
Ohh!
But i want to assure you
and the romanian people
That we're going to do
everything in our power
To make this all
as confusing as possible.
Let the quints stay!
Romania is gay!
Let the
quints stay!
Romania is gay!
Fur is murder,
fur is murder!
Oh, what are we
protesting here?
Romania sucks.
Oh, let's see...
Here we go.
Romania sucks,
romania sucks...!
Oh my god...
I didn't know this was going
to become such a big deal.
That'll teach us for taking an
old lady and her granddaughters
Out of the cold.
Attention people
inside the house:
You must return the quintuplets
to their father.
You have until...
Oh yeah, that's good.
You have until
easter sunday to comply.
Boo.
Boo!
What?
Get em!
Okay,
let's try it again.
Hup!
Alright!
Stan, we-
Stanley, we have
some bad news.
The courts have decided the
girls must go back to romania.
No, they can't!
We've convinced them that
they want to stay in america.
Yeah, we showed them
amusement parks and malls.
How can you expect them
to go back now?
I'm sorry, boys,
But janet reno is having them
taken away on easter sunday.
We don't have a choice.
Sorry, girls.
Now what do we do?
Tom, it is now
easter morning
And as the u.S. Government
promised,
They are here to take the girls
back to their father in romania.
Rumor has it that janet reno herself
will be extraditing the quintuplets.
Alright, miss reno,
let's go over the plan.
Right!
We'll drop you in the northwest
corner of the backyard.
You hop into the back of the
house and find the quintuplets.
When you see them,
you say:
Hello, girls,
i'm the easter bunny.
Good, and then hand them the
easter eggs filled with tear gas.
Are you ready?
Ready.
Go blue!
Yes, we would like very much to have
you here at the romanian music school.
Woo hoo!
How much is all this
gonna cost?
Don't worry, miss mccormack,
romania is very poor country.
Apartments are cheap,
food is cheap.
Everything is cheap because
we are so goddamn poor.
Yes, your 200 american dollars
will last months here.
Wow, what a great country.
Everybody's poor like us.
Yeah!
Hello, girls,
i'm the easter bunny.
Happy easter, kids.
Come see what
i brought for ya.
Hey, terence,
i think i have to fart.
Wait, before you do...
Oh, look,
an easter egg!
Oh, sh-
That's it,
let's move move move!
Give us the kid now!
Now!
Down on the floor,
down on the goddamn floor!
Find them!
This is a bust,
hand over the quints!
Hand over the children-
Happy easter-
Hand over the children!
What the hell's
goin' on?
Freeze, asshole.
Oh, go ahead and shoot me,
i dare ya!
Don't push me, man.
Pull the trigger,
you little pussy.
Dahhh!
Gun, gun!
Down, down!
Riot, riot!
Pepper spray,
pepper spray!
Dammit, now i'm never gonna
have my own circus.
Oh, your son is so
talented miss mccormack.
The people of romania
love him.
Good job, kenny.
Miss mccormack, we would love
for you and your son
To stay here in romania...
with us.
Will you consider it?
What do you think, kenny?
You'd have to leave your
friends and family behind.
Sure!
Alright!
Oh, randy, it's gone.
It's all gone.
Dude, what the
hell happened?
Government came
and got the quintuplets.
No more cirque
du cheville for us.
Dammit, how come every time
we get a sweet idea
The government has to
screw it up?
Yeah, well not this time.
Huh?
We just gotta get that
angry mob back on our side.
Alright, everybody,
listen up!
Those bastards broke in here
and took those poor quintuplets
To the mayor's office
downtown.
But they haven't won yet.
I say we all go over
to the mayor's office
And demand to see
the quintuplets right now!
Hmm... yeah...
I don't know, i usually like
to stop protesting by 5:30.
Yeah, do we get
overtime for this?
Uh sure,
you all get overtime.
Alright!
Yeah!
Down with japan!
Get 'em!
Alright, we just need to get a few more
pictures of the girls reunited with their father
So that everyone
knows they're happy.
Come on girls, smile.
We want you
to look happy, smile.
Look at the silly frog.
Who's got the silly frog,
look at him, i've got-
Look at him,
it's so silly, i'm so silly.
Ah, hello, this is kenny's dad
back in america.
I miss my son
very much.
I would like to see him
returned to me
So that the u.S. Government
will buy me a new car and-
Ow!
I mean, because i miss
my son very much.
Man.
Hey, we wanna
see the quintuplets.
You can't see them, boys.
They're happily reunited
with their father.
Come on, angry mob.
Ahhh!
Alright, it is time for us
to return to romania.
What is that?
It's the protestors,
they're back.
Goddammit.
We'll take care
of them, come on!
Let's move, move!
C'mon, c'mon!
This is government
property.
You ruined my house!
What are you
doing, nadia?
I'm calling the only person
in the world who can help us.
Take that.
Stop it, stop it,
stop it!
All of you are
acting like idiots.
Yeah!
None of you
care about us.
You only care about
yourselves.
Look at you, father.
You walked out on us
five years ago
And now you act like
you miss ussomuch.
You are a liar
and a fake.
Yeah, you suck, dude.
And you romanian leaders-
You don't care about us!
All you care about is making
america look stupid.
Yeah, you guys
are dicks.
And you protestors
- Don't you have anything better to do?
Get a life!
Yeah!
And you boys
are the worst of all.
Huh? Huh?
You know nothing
about romania
And yet you assume
america is so much better.
Maybe romania isn't as nice
as america, but it is our home.
We are romanian.
All you care about
is your own stupid circus.
Where are you going, girls?
The only
place we can go.
We are going on oprah
and then a book tour.
Yes, you can all kiss our
little white romanian asses.
Oh well, doing our own circus
was a dumb idea anyways.
Yeah, screw them!
Kenny was never gonna
get his singing right anyway.
Whatever happened
to kenny?
Let kenny stay,
let kenny stay...!
Alright people, the father
wants his son returned to him.
Hand him over to us.
Boo!
Shut up, romanians.
Alright, let's go.
Move move move!
Hand over the boy, now!
Okay, okay.
I mean it, lady,
you've got about-
Whoops.
Captioning made possible by
comedy central
Captioned by
soundwriters™
www.tvsubtitles.net