Captioning made possible by
comedy central
? I'm going down
to south park?
? Gonna have
myself a time?
? Friendly faces
everywhere?
? Humble folks
without temptation?
? Going down
to south park?
? Gonna leave my
woes behind?
? Ample parking
day or night?
? People spouting
"howdy neighbor"?
? Headed on up
to south park?
? Gonna see if
i can't unwind?
? So come on down
to south park?
? And meet some
friends of mine?
? I walk hand-In-Hand
with je-Sus?
? Over at the park
by where he lives?
? I tell him
all my problems?
? And sometimes
he tells me his?
? What a friend
i have in je-Sus?
? I can say that
honestly?
? He's not like all
my other friends?
? Who really don't care
about me?
? A-Amen?
Bor-Ring!
And now, mr. Mackey will read his
favorite psalm for us, psalm 46.
Uh, god is our refuge
and strength, m'kay.
A very present help
in trouble, m'kay.
Hey, you guys, you know what
my favorite psalm is?
"It's a man's obligation
"To stick his boneration
in a woman's separation
This sort of penetration will increase
the population of the younger generation."
God is in the midst of her,
m'kay.
She shall
not be moved, m'kay.
Wait, wait, wait!
"It's a man's obligation to stick
his boneration in the woman's-
his boneration in a woman's separation
To increase the population
of the younger generation."
"Mrph rm rmph rmhrmh
rmhr rmhph rm rmhpr-
No, no, no,
"separation".
"It's a man's obligation to stick
his boneration in a woman's-M"
Boys, you are
in church!
Ah!
The god of jacob
is our refuge, m'kay.
Thank you, mr. Mackey,
hello, everyone.
Today, we are going
to talk about...
Hell!
Hell is not
a very nice place.
Burning, searing,
flames,
Screaming, torture...
for eternity!
Once you are in hell,
you cannot escape.
You live forever
in horrible pain.
In burning agony!
All sinners
are there in misery,
Dying over
and over and over!
If you be cast down into
this black bog of stench
Then woe is thou!
For satan has made it the most
miserable place in the universe!
And he will be
your ruler!
Your ruler
of pain and agony!
? Are we going
to the hukilau?
? The huki huki huki
huki hukilau?
? Are we going
to the hukilau?
? The huki huki huki
huki huki hukilau?
? Everybody
loves a hukilau?
I do!
? Where the lau lau is
the kau kau at the luau?
? We throw our nets
out into the sea?
? All the ama-Ama
come swimming to me?
? Are we going to
the hukilau?
? The huki huki huki
huki hukilau?
? Are we going
to the hukilau?
? The huki huki huki
huki huki hukilau?
? Everybody
loves a hukilau?
? Where the the lau lau is
the kau kau at the luau?
? We throw our nets
out into the sea?
? All the ama-Ama
come swimming to me?
? Are we going
to the hukilau?
? The huki huki huki
huki hukilau?
? Huki huki lauuuuuuuu?
Yeah!
Oowww!
Heh-Heh!
Great luau, satan!
Thanks,
see ya, gary!
Thanks for coming,
oh, bye, marsha!
Satan, a few of us are gonna go
pound some brews, you wanna join us?
Oh i'd love to,
mr. Matthau, but i can't.
Chris and i just moved
to the west side
And we have to unpack.
Oh well, maybe next time,
great luau!
Bye!
Chris?
Yeah?
Did you, uh, see my "boy
with an umbrella" hummell?
Uh, no, but there's still some
boxes coming from the movers.
Oh, okay, thanks.
Oh, that must be them now.
Just put the boxes
by the-
Hello, satan!
Saddam!
Did you miss me,
buttercup?
No, it can't be,
you're dead.
I killed you.
Yeah,
you killed me, so?
Where was i gonna go,
detroit?
Oh no,
oh god, no!
A place of everlasting
agony and pain!
Hell awaits all sinners and
all who do not accept christ!
Children in this town have not been
attending sunday school after mass.
And adults have not been
coming to confession.
If this does not change,
i promise you,
You will all be going to the
black pit of satan's world!
That is all,
peace be with you.
Well, that was quite
an uplifting sermon. Yeah.
Mom, we're staying
what? For sunday school.
We have to go to sunday school
so we don't burn!
Yeah, i'll see ya
later, mom!
Oh, now look at that,
they're scared to death!
Hell is a very real place,
mr. And mrs. Marsh!
I'm trying to save their souls and
the souls of everyone in this town
From the wretched
lake of fire!
Come on, guy!
Just let me in
so we can talk.
I don't want to
talk to you, saddam!
This isn't what i need
in my life right now!
Is that
the movers, satan?
Uh, yeah, yeah,
it's just the movers.
Oh, well, tell them i'm leaving
their check on the counter.
Okay, chris.
Satan, look, i know our
relationship wasn't perfect.
Okay?
I know that.
I was too busy trying to take over
the world, to give you what you needed!
But i've changed, satan.
Oh, like i haven't heard
thatbefore.
Come on, can't we just
go out for a burrito?
Me gusto burrito mucho.
I can't, saddam,
i'm with chris now.
Who?
Screw him!
He can't pound your ass
like i can!
Goodbye, saddam.
Wait, wait, i'm sorry!
But satan, you can't deny
what's between us.
You can try,
But you know
we belong together.
My life is good now, saddam,
chris treats me well.
You and i are through.
Goodbye.
Hey, come on, guy!
Give me a break!
Hello, children,
i'm sister anne,
And i'll be teaching you, so that you
all can receive your first communion!
Are we gonna
go to hell?
Well, hopefully not.
That's why you're gonna
need to receive communion.
And as long as we get this
communion thing, we're safe?
What if we haven't really done
anything that horribly bad in our lives?
Yeah, whatif
we hadn't?
It doesn't matter, because we
are all born with original sin.
Now let me explain
how communion works.
The priest will give you
this round cracker,
And he will say,
"The body of christ"
and then you eat it.
Jesus was made
no. Of crackers?
But crackers
are his body.
Yes.
What?
In the book of mark, jesus
distributed bread and said,
"Eat this,
for it is my body."
So we won't go to hell,
as long as we eat crackers?
No, no, no, no!
Well, what are
we eatin' then?
The body of christ!
Oh, i get it, jesus wanted
us to eat him,
But he didn't want us
to be cannibals
So he turned himself into crackers
and then told people to eat 'im.
No!
No?
I can't whistle
if i eat too many crackers.
Look, all you have to know is that
when the priest gives you the cracker
You eat it, okay?
Okay.
And then you will drink
a very small amount of wine.
For that is
the blood of christ.
Oh, come on now,
this is just getting silly!
Eric, do you want
to go to hell?
No!
Questioning me!
But now we can have communion
and not go to hell, right?
No, because before you can
take your first communion,
You have to have your first
confession. Confession!
You'll be getting in the
confession box with a priest
And confessing all your sins,
so that god can forgive you.
You kids will all have to go to
your first confession this tuesday.
So i want you all
to go home tonight,
And think long and hard
about all your sins,
So that you can tell
the priesteverything.
Oh, sh-!
Those were some
great pork chops, satan!
Yeah.
Hey you, you've been
acting strange all night.
What's up?
Nothing, why.
Well, it's just that you've washed
that same dish seven times now, silly.
Oh, sorry,
heh-Heh.
Come on, satan, you know
you can tell me anything.
What's up?
Well, chris,
saddam showed up today.
Oh...
Wow, i wasn't ready
for that.
He showed up spouting
all kinds of things
About how he's changed
and he still loves me.
I thought you...
killed him.
Yeah, well, where was
he gonna go, detroit?
Do you still love him?
No, chris.
It's okay if you do.
Well, i mean...
Of course there's a part of me
that will always love him.
But i also know
how abusive he was.
I'm much happier
with you.
You know what
i think we should do?
I think we should all get
together and just talk like adults.
What?
We're all grown men here, satan,
i wanna just go meet this guy.
No, chris, you don't understand,
saddam is ing crazy.
I know he's got the whole
"bad boy" thing going.
I think that's what
you were attracted to.
But i can be a pretty
rough tumbler myself.
Oops!
Aw, butternuts!
Okay, let's see...
Oh yeah, there was the time we threw
a fish into the bus driver's hair
And she didn't find it for
seven days. Oh yeah, okay.
And then there was the time we
held that little first-Grader down
And farted on him
for 28 minutes.
Right, i already
got that one.
Hey dudes,
what are you doing?
We're trying to remember
all our sins.
Sister anne told us we have
to confess all our sins
Or else we're gonna
what? Go to hell!
Have you confessed
no! All your sins yet?
Dude, he's jewish, he doesn't
have to confess his sins.
Oh good, i don't?
No, you're already
going to hell.
I am not!
You are too!
Dude, this lady told us that
if you don't confess your sins
And you don't eat crackers and drink
wine, then you go to hell, period!
I'm gonna go
ask my mom!
Now let's see...
What about the time we set
mr. Garrison's cat on fire?
Oh right, that was mostly
kenny's fault. What?
You guys, you guys! We just
thought of somethin'!
What, butters?
Well, what about
the handicapped kid, timmy?
Timmy!
What'd we do
to timmy?
No, i mean poor timmy's
gonna go to hell!
He can't confess his sins 'cause
all he can say is his name!
Timmy!
Ooh, yeah, you're right,
i guess timmy's pretty screwed.
Oh man, we can't let
timmy go to hell!
We have to do something!
What are we gonna do?
I don't know, i don't know
whatwe're gonna do.
I don't knowwhat
i'm gonna do.
I can't deny my feelings
for saddam,
But my life is so much
better now with chris.
Ee-Aa-Ee-Aa
be-Ya-Ki-Ki-Ki!
Yeah, it's like chris is
so perfect in every way,
But there's just something
about saddam
That i'm much more
attracted to.
Eee-Aaa-Beecha-
Eee-Aa-Beaa!
In what way?
Eee-Aa-Beeea-
Beachaaa!
Yeah, you're right.
Saddamwouldjust
treat me bad again!
I just have to
not see saddam,
Put him out of my mind
and focus on chris.
If i don'tseesaddam,
Then won't have such
strong feelings for him.
Thanks guys!
Goycha!
There you are!
Oh, hi chris!
I've been looking
all over for you.
I have to tell you something
that might make you...
A little mad.
What?
Well, i called saddam hussein and
invited him over for dinner tonight.
You what?!
I just think we all need
to get this out in the open.
Aw, chris, aaaghgh!
Aaghgh!
Come on, satan,
we're all adults here.
He was an important person
in your life,
For better or for worse,
so i want to know him.
If he sees that i'm
a real person too,
Then maybe he'll see
how happy we are together.
No, chris, he'll try to
kill you is what he'll do!
Satan, we're not in
junior high school anymore.
Oh dear god!
Hail mary, full of grace the lord
is with you, blessed art thou among-
How was it?
Oh dude,
you screwed me up! Huh?
The guy in there said
i have to say 54 "hail marys".
Now i can't remember if
i was on number 7 or 8!
Who's in there?
I don't know.
You can't see him,
it's just some anonymous guy.
Well, here goes
everything!
Uh, forgive me, father,
for i have sinned.
Blessed art thou, child.
Now, what do you
have to confess?
Well, let's see...
I'd like to start, if i may,
back when i was two and a half.
It was a cold, april morning
and the dew on the grass
Was frozen like
tiny beads of glass.
Hail mary, full of grace the lord is with thee
- Hey, dude.
God dammit!
What?
Ooh, there's sister anne, come
on we gotta ask her about timmy!
Sister anne!
Oh, hello, children.
We have a question.
Okay, shoot.
Where do handicapped people
go when they die?
The handicapped are just people like
you and me, so the same rules apply.
They need to be baptized, take
communion and confess their sins.
But our friend timmy can't really
talk, all he can do is say his own name,
So he can't really confess his
sins, so is he going to go to hell?
Uh...
This really isn't a question
for me, it's for the priest.
I'll see if
i can find him, bye!
And that was about everything
from first grade,
Then last year, well...
You can't tell anybody
about this stuff, right?
Your confession does not
leave this box.
Okay, because last year,
I took a sandwich that the priest
of this church had been eating.
Oh, well...
I'm sure he would
forgive you,
If he knew.
Yeah, but i'm not
finished yet.
I took a sandwich
that the preist was eating,
Took the piece of ham out of it,
put it between my butt cheeks,
Then put the sandwich back
and watched him eat it.
I see.
Yeah, and then this other time, i
went pee-Pee in the holy water thing
And the priest blessed himself
on the forehead with it
Every day for
about a week.
And then one time,
i was at the park
And the priest was out
walking his dog,
And i went number two
on the sidewalk
And then told officer barbrady
that it was the priest's dog,
And so the priest got fined
like $100 for not cleaning it up.
And then this one time,
I put super glue
all over the priest's bible-
Ah, ah, oh, jesus,
aaghgh!
Aaghh! Aaagh!
Ah, ah, help!
Father, i need
to talk to you.
Father, i have to
ask you a question.
Okay, okay, fine.
Oh, oh!
Dude, what happened?
I felt it, you guys!
I felt
the angry hands of god!
He is an angry god,
you guys.
We all have to start
taking this very seriously!
Oh, hello,
you must be saddam hussein.
And you must be
mr. Ass face!
Just kidding,
you're chris, right?
Thanks for inviting me
to dinner, guy.
Here, i brought you
a potato.
Oh, thank you!
Chris, no,
it's a bomb!
Satan, what the heck
is wrong with you?
Yeah, hey, relax, guy!
We're all here
to act like adults, right?
Oh, gee, i must have
overcooked it.
Well, come on in,
dinner's just about ready.
"And behin da glass
der dusty fowny eye."
Very good, ike!
That's two john steinbeck
books in one day!
Cookie monster!
Oh, he's growing up
so fast!
Mom, dad,
am i going to hell?
Why, what did
you do, kyle?
Nothing,
but the guys said
If i don't confess
my sins and eat crackers,
I'm gonna go to hell!
Oh, no,
that's just catholics.
Us jews don't
believe in hell.
We don't?
But what
if we're wrong?
Well, kyle, they could
be wrong, too.
Yeah, but if they're wrong,
no big deal.
If we're wrong,
we burn in hell!
Oh no!
Kyle, it's all about being
a good personnow.
You see, christians use hell
as a way to scare people
Into believing
what they believe.
But to believe in something, just
because you're afraid of the consequences
If youdon'tbelieve
in something
Is no reason
to believe in something.
Understand?
No.
Well, you guys can
do what you want.
I'm going down to that church to
confess my sins and eat crackers.
And i'm taking
kyle! Ike with me!
So, saddam,
Satan told me all about how you
guys almost took over the world once.
Yeah, those were
the days, boy.
What the hell is this crap
we're eating, anyway?
It's all vegetarian,
saddam,
Chris was a nutritionist
before he died.
Oh, isn't that
fascinating?
So tell me, chris,
how was it that you died?
Oh, well, i actually slipped
down an escalator in a mall.
Those things can be
pretty sketchy.
An escalator?
What kind of pussy way
of dying is that?
Look, saddam, i know that you
and satan had a relationship.
And i just want
youto know,
That i'm totally okay with you
guys staying friends. Uh-Huh.
I think it's important to stay friends
with people you had relationships with.
And i know that satan and my
relationship is strong enough
That it can handle
anything.
Right?
Right!
Father, the children asked me
about their handicapped friend.
I want to explain to them
that he's fine.
Well, has your friend ever
confessed or been baptized?
I don't think so.
Then hell awaits him.
Father, these boys are really worried
because they think they have to-
They should be worried.
Boys, it is your christian dutyto
save the souls of your friends.
Yes, but-
Mr. Father!
We have to
ask you something!
Oh, you're the little
jewish boy, right?
Yeah, if we're jewish,
are we gonna go to hell?
Well, young man,
you can rest assured
That according to
matthew 25,
When you die, you will
stand before god and he will say
"Depart from me, ye cursed,
into the eternal fire
Prepared for the devil
and his angels."
Yes, as a jew, your home
will be the lake of fire.
Oh no!
Father!
I hope to see all of you
in church this sunday!
We will be!
Father, i don't know if i agree
fully with what you're saying.
I think that as long as
jewish people are good,
They will
get into heaven.
Sister, the jews
crucified our savior.
I'm mean, if you don't go
to hell for crucifying a savior,
Then what the hell
doyou go to hell for?
Stan, you've got to help us
become good christians, please!
Alright, alright, alright,
you heard the priest,
The first thing we have to do is
get you guys all baptized, come on!
Wagh-Blagh-Aggh!
Wagh-Ha-Hagh-Blagh!
Okay, you better baptize
kyle some more.
Hallelujah,
wash away the sin! Agh!
Turn around so i can
clean out your ass!
Cartman!
What?
Dude, you said "ass",
that's a sin!
Oh, now you've
said it too!
Oh, sh-, agh!
F- , whoops!
Oh, dude, we gotta get back to
the church and confess again!
But what about them?
Uh, oh, i know!
We can use
"wacky water weasel"!
Agh!
Okay, come on!
Timmy!
Well, i don't know
about you guys,
But all that ginger
made me tired!
Yeah, i guess i should
be getting back.
Good,
i'll show you out.
Nice to meet you, saddam,
have a safe walk back!
Yeah, thanks for the wheatgrass
and twigs and stuff!
Satan, that guy
is a pussy!
He's stable, saddam!
Yeah, that's what i said,
he's a pussy!
Having stability in your life is
a great thing, you should try it!
For some people, maybe,
but you like excitement.
I know you, satan.
I'm very happy
with my life now.
Here.
I'm at the bargain hotel
on mala vista, room 16.
No, saddam,
i won't be needing this.
I know you won't, but just
keep it just in case.
It was good seeing you
again, satan, goodnight.
Goodnight, pussy,
i mean, chris!
G'nite!
Hello, your excellency.
This is sister anne,
the bleeding eyes of jesus,
Calling from
the united states.
Yes, i understand you wish
to speak-A with the pope.
Yes, the priest here has been
telling the children
Some pretty
radical things,
And i just wanted to see
what the church thinks
About jews and
the mentally handicapped.
Yes, well, the pope is here,
but please keep it brief,
He is-A very old-A.
Huh?
Hello, his holiness.
I want to ask you about people
with mental disabilities.
Huh?
Do mentally challenged people
go to hell?
Huh?
Handicap,
mental handicap.
Brdrdrbrdrdrdrdr.
The priest here said that people with
mental handicaps might end up in hell,
Is that true?
Uhhhhhhh...
bdrdrdrdrdrdrr.
Come on, this stupid light
won't change.
Come on, hurry up!
Hey, what are
you guys doing?
We're going to church, we sinned
and so we have to confess again!
Us, too, we saw a picture
of a naked lady.
We could see
her whole beaver!
Yeah, if we died right now, we'd have
unclean souls and we'd burn in hell!
Well come on,
let's go!
Oh my god!
They killed kenny!
He had sins that
he didn't confess!
And he never
took communion!
He'sdoomed.
We gotta get to that church
beforewedie!
Yeah!
Careful.
Yeah.
That's hot.
You take it.
You take it, now.
Chris,
what are you doing?
I'm just...
I'm just trying to be
a little more naughty in bed.
I know that's what you liked
about sex with saddam,
I'm just showing you that
i can be that way too.
Oh boy.
Uh-Huh.
Yeah, you like that,
don't you, bitch?
I'm a bad boy.
Yeah,
take that.
Chris, just don't,
don't do that.
But it turns you on.
When saddam did it,
yeah, but...
But what?
Nothing, i just...
i'm just really tired is all.
Can we just please
go to sleep?
Chris, seriously,
i'm just tired, okay.
Okay,
i love you, satan.
I love you too, saddam.
Wah!
Ah, i'm sorry,
i mean chris!
It's okay, it's okay,
i, uh, oh...
I understand,
i do.
I just need to go
get some air, okay.
I'll be back
really quick.
Yeah, sure, okay.
Come on, hurry up!
Oh no,
it's locked!
What, no, it can't be locked
we have to confess!
We have to confess our sins
before we die!
Hey, there's a window in
the back that's usually open!
The confession box
is over there!
I'm first, i'm first!
Ooh!
What the-
Oh, son of a bitch!
He-He-He!
Uh, kids, uh...
You're a sinner!
You're doing unnatural things
in the house of god!
Oh, uh...
Oh forgive me,
heavenly father!
I have sinned
against you!
Oh, this guy is
sogonna burn!
Mrs. Donovan is
a temptress from hell!
Dude, if this guy's going
to hell, who's gonna save us?
Well, it looks like we're
gonna have to save timmy, kyle
And everyone else in this town from
the angry hand of god ourselves!
Oh the pain!
Ohh, the paaaiin!
No, i can't.
What am i doing?
I know this is
the wrong thing to do.
I could lose chris.
I can't do this,
i can't do this!
We have repeatedly broken
god's commandments-A!
We have lived our lives
for ourselves-A,
Totally ignoring
the lord-A!
"If thy hand offend thee,
cut it off:
It is much better
for thee-
Oh, what the hell
are they doing now?
Oh no!
Into the fire that will
never be quenched!"
Pamphlet?
There is only one answer!
As kids we must abandon this
town of sin and start anew!
I don't want to
go to hell.
It will be a long road,
But at the end of that road
is salvation!
Andiam going to
lead you there!
Captioning made possible by
comedy central
Captioned by
soundwriters™
www.tvsubtitles.net