Captioning made possible by
comedy central
? I'm going down
to south park?
? Gonna have
myself a time?
? Friendly faces
everywhere?
? Humble folks
without temptation?
? Going down
to south park?
? Gonna leave my
woes behind?
? Ample parking
day or night?
? People spouting
"howdy neighbor"?
? Headed on up
to south park?
? Gonna see if
i can't unwind?
? So come on down
to south park?
? And meet some
friends of mine?
Come on, throw
the football, ike!
Dude, you're not gonna believe
what cartman has!
Hepatitis "b"?
No, dickhole.
Four tickets, 28th row,
for theraging pussies.
You got raging
pussies tickets?!
We're going
tomorrow night.
Cartman's got the bus
schedule all figured out.
Hold on,
i'll be right back.
Mom, dad!
Can i go with the guys to see
the raging pussies?
No, kyle.
But all the guys
are going!
Kyle, you're not
old enough.
And those concerts
are dangerous and vile.
But mom, i-
The answer is no, kyle!
Agh!
My parents said
i can't go.
Well, of course your parents
said you can't go!
Dummy! You don't ask
if you can go!
I'm telling my parents
i'm staying at stan's house,
Stan's telling his parent
he's staying at kenny's house,
And kenny's not telling
his parents anything
'Cause they're alcoholics
and they don't care.
Yeah!
Oh... well, now
i already told them.
Well, i guess
you're screwed then.
No, it's all right.
Just give me some time
to work on them.
I'll see you guys later.
But what if i do a bunch of
chores around the house?
Come on,
you're being unfair!
All right, fine, kyle,
You can go to the
raging pussies concert
If you clean out the garage,
shovel the driveway
And bring
democracy to cuba!
What's cuba?
A communist country run by a
dictator named fidel castro.
And do i have to shovel
the whole driveway
Or just the side
the car's on?
The whole thing.
Oh, geez.
Dear, mr. Castro,
my name is kyle.
I am an 8-Year-Old american boy
who lives in south park.
...and if i had
just one wish,
Just one wish
in the whole world...
? If i had one wish
it'd be for cuba to change?
? Because i think that
all the cubans are in pain?
? All the joy in the world
from sea to shining sea?
? Doesn't mean a thing
if cubans aren't free?
? I just can't be very happy
that's certain?
? Not as long as
your cubans are hurtin'?
? Oh, won't you
search your soul?
? And find a way
to change your mind?
? That is my
one and only wish?
Llamada todos junto!
Once again this does mark
the end of communism in cuba!
Cuban dictator fidel castro claims he was
finally convinced by a young boy's letter.
Now the country is again open
to american tourism.
Plans can finally resume for
knott's berry farm, cuba.
I did it!
Now i can go to
the raging pussies!
No, you can't.
What?
Kyle, your mother and i don't want you
going to the raging pussies concert.
We gave you a chore that
we thought was impossible.
You weren't supposed to
actually do it.
But i did,
i brought democracy to cuba.
We know, kyle,
But we just don't want you
going to that concert.
But that's not fair,
you lied to me!
Kyle, perhaps we
handled this wrong,
But you need to
understand that-
What i understand is that you
totally screwed me over!
So why should i have to
listen to you?
Because we're
your parents!
Well, i wish i didn't
have any parents!
Kyle!
It's so unfair!
How could my parents
do that to me?
Parents can be pretty cruel
sometimes, dude.
They get off on it.
They're evil.
I wish i didn't
have any parents!
Well... youcouldmake them
go away for a while. How?
Well, i mean,
youcouldcall the police
And have them
take your parents away.
The police?
Yeah, i saw it on tv.
All you gotta do is
call the police
And say that your parents
both "molestered" you.
What's that?
I don't know, but it works.
When i wanted to get rid of
my mom's last boyfriend
I just called the police,
and said he was molestering me,
And i haven't seen him
for three months.
Wow- Three months
without parents!
But what do the police
do to them?
Who cares? My parents
deserve whatever they get!
They're liars
and cheats!
You have to make it convincing,
though, when you call the police,
You have to be like,
"my parents molestered me!"
My parents molestered me.
No, but you gotta cry,
like this-
My parents molestered me.
And then they'll say something like,
"was it good touch or bad touch?"
And you say,
"it was good touch."
No, wait,
you say it was bad touch.
What's bad touch?
Something about a swimsuit,
i don't remember.
But you definitely answer
"bad touch".
Okay- Molestered,
bad touch.
Yeah, and cry.
Oh, he's ready.
Oh my god,
this isn't happening!
I would never touch
my children like that!
You do have the right
to remain silent, ma'am,
I suggest you
use that right.
Please,
just listen to me!
Heh-Heh, heh-Heh.
What about
my children?
Who will take
care of them?
Oh, now you care?
They're going to live
with their grandmother.
Their grandmother's been
dead for three years!
You're not
listening to me!
Kyle, tell these people
that your...
They'll never be able
to hurt you again.
Cool, thanks.
All right, folks,
our work here is done.
All right!
? Just take those old records
off the shelf?
? I sit and listen to 'em
by myself?
? Today's music ain't
got the same soul?
? I like that old time
rock and roll?
? Don't try to take me
to a disco...?
Dude, having no parents
is awesome!
I'm gonna say my parents
molestered me, too!
Hey, yeah!
We should all say our
parents molestered us!
Yeah, all right.
Woo-Hoo!
?... I like that
old time rock and roll?
? Still like that old time
rock and roll?
? That kind of music
just soothes my soul?
? I reminisce about
the days of old?
? With that old time
rock and roll?
The following hot presentation
is for mature audiences only.
You guys,
come out here!
What's going on?
Notice anything?
Watch...
Nothing.
Yeah, nothing.
There's not an adult
left in town.
They've all been arrested, and
the ones that weren't arrested
Have moved away because they're
scared of being arrested.
Not one adult left?
Then it's ours.
The whole town...
it's ours.
Oh, sweetie, i have
no idea where we are.
I haven't seen
a road marker for miles.
What was the last highway
we were on?
There has to be a town
around here somewhere.
Maybe you're reading
the map wrong.
Hey, it was your idea
to take the back roads!
What the?
Oh no...
no, no, no, no.
What's the matter
with it?
I have no idea.
Oh, we're gonna have to
find some help quick.
We're not gonna make it
more than a couple miles.
Oh, look,
there's a town up ahead!
Smiley town?
That's a strange name.
Well, it'll have to do.
It's probably the only town
for 100 miles.
Hello!
Is anybody here?
Oh, uh-
Can i help you folks?
Yes, we need a mechanic
to look at our car.
Oh, well, uh...
i'm the mechanic, i guess.
What seems to be
the problem?
It's...
just you here?
No, craig's here, too.
Oh, good.
But he's playin'
"spaceman" right now.
Hey, craig!
What?
Look, we're in a bit
of a spot here.
I've got a very important job interview
tomorrow morning in breckenridge
So i have to get
my car fixed fast.
Is there another
garage in town?
Uhh... no.
How about a phone,
can we just use the phone?
Phone here doesn't work.
I'm afraid the only phone
that does work...
Is over in "treasure cove".
Fine, can you
take us there?
You... sure you wanna go
to treasure cove?
Yes!
Oh, really,
are you sure?
Yes!
Oh, all right then,
show 'em where it is.
This is the end of
smiley town.
The only phone is somewhere
in treasure cove.
If you wanna find it, you're
gonna have to cross the white line.
Well, can you help us
find the phone, please?
Hell no, i'm not
crossing the white line.
Why not?
All right,
let's just go, linda,
I don't have time for
"spaceman spiff's" little games.
Craig.
What?
It's spaceman craig.
Carousel.
Nya-Nya,
nya-Nya-Nya!
Look, there's
an elementary school.
Come on, there might be
some teachers inside.
What is that?
Ahh!
What do you
want from us?
Linda, it's a
remote-Controlled car.
It looks like maybe there's
a little camera on it.
Mark, i don't like this.
Relax, linda,
everything's fine.
Ow, ow!
What is it-
Acid?
No, it's lemon juice!
Oh, god,
are you blind?
No, it just really,
really, really hurts!
Mark, mark, look.
Well, hello,
what's your name?
What-What do you want?
We want to play.
Mark, i'm scared.
Don't be scared,
they're just kids.
Where are
your parents?
We already played
with our parents.
Now, we wanna play
with you.
Okay, i'm scared now, too,
that freaked me out.
We want to play
with you!
Get off me!
Oh god, mark, help!
Oh no, they're crossing
the white line!
Ohhh!
Spit wads!
Take that,
kindergartners!
Eww, gross!
What the hell
is going on here?!
Kindergartners
- Treasure cove is full of them.
All right, look kid, we demand
to see an adult this instant.
I got new orders, i'm supposed
to take you to see the mayor.
The mayor, good, finally.
Hello, mr. And mrs. Cotner,
won't you come in, please?
Mr. And mrs. Cotner,
as the mayor of smiley town,
I would like to ask you
a few questions.
You're the mayor?
What the hell is
going on here?
Where are
all your parents?
Parents?
Ah, you mean
the birth-Givers.
They're not around.
No parents
in the entire town?
What happened to them?
Okay, see, i'm the mayor
of smiley town
And so i will ask
the questions around here.
Look, just point us to
a phone, kid, all right?
Heh-Heh, i'm afraid
you'll find all the phones...
Quite out of service.
No phones either?
How do you
communicate?
Butters, i need an e.T.A.
On the car, stat.
All right, we've had
just about enough here.
That's the most ridiculous
thing i've ever seen!
I don't care what little games
you kids wanna play,
We just want
out of here, all right?
It's gonna be
about three days.
So, it appears
that you need me.
Which is good, because,
i need you too.
Ringy-Ding?
I've got the job interview
of my life in breckenridge.
Just tell me how to get
a phone or a car!
Spitball!
Aah!
You sons of bitches!
You see what we're
dealing with here?
Tonight is "carousel",
And they will try to
kill one of us.
You two seem to have the uncanny
ability to cross the white line.
If you help us,
we'll get you what you need.
Mark, are we doing
the right thing?
Look, if getting this stupid book
will get me a cell phone, i don't care!
I just don't know if you're dealing
with these kids the right way.
Well, i told you i can't
deal with kids, linda!
That's why i don't
want to have children!
Hey, i think you'd
make a great father.
Let's not go through
this again, linda.
Look, here's the book they've been
talking about that makes no sense.
My god, mark!
What is it?
It's a boy.
They... killed him.
The bastards...
Oh, mark,
let's get out of here!
Nya-Nya,
nya-Nya-Nya!
Aah!
Oh, no.
Mark!
Uh, the fat kid
told us to take it!
Wha- Ahh!
Mark, mark, wake up!
Nya-Nya, nya-Nya,
nya-Nya!
You guys, stop it!
Sorry about them,
kindergartners are kinda spazzes.
Yeah.
Why are you
doing this?
How come you wanna
help the fat-Ass?
Who?
The fat-Ass, the mayor.
Look, i have the
job interview of my life
In less than...
12 hours.
I just need a phone, and he said
he'd help me if i took your book
So you couldn't
kill them anymore.
You got "foolied",
outlander.
We're the only ones
with a working phone.
And if you'd
taken our book
Then it's one of us
who dies tonight at carousel.
How did this
all happen?
Why do you children
live in this town alone?
Because we do.
It was like this yesterday
and the day before that.
But what about
before that?
You mean
in the before-Time?
In the long, long ago?
Yes!
If we tell you, will you
help us stop the fat-Ass?
I'll do anything
to get to a phone.
All right,
everybody gather around.
We're gonna tell the story
of the before-Time again!
The before-Time!
Story of before-Time.
Way back,
in the long, long ago,
We all lived by the
birth-Givers' laws.
But the birth-Givers
were unfair.
They made us go to bed early
and eat broccoli.
Yuck, yuck, yuck!
And so the fat-Ass came up with a way
to have all the birth-Givers disappear,
By using the magic
"m"- Word.
Mmmmm!
Soon we were without power,
or water or fresh food,
But we tried to survive
under the guidance...
Of the provider.
Provider, provider.
But the fat-Ass and us disagreed
on how to worship the provider.
The fat-Ass tried to make us follow his
way by making himself the school principal.
So we made ourselves the
superintendents of schools.
But then he just
made himself the mayor.
The town split sides, and that's
when the provider got angry.
Boom! Crash!
So every night, the provider
must be appeased at carousel.
We need their book,
so one of ours doesn't die.
Carousel, carousel.
We all know that one day
the provider will set us free,
Make everything like it was
in the before-Time.
In the long, long ago.
Let me
get this straight.
If i go get the fat kid's book on
the other side of the white line
You'll show me where
a cell phone is?
Yes, no foolies.
No foolies.
Let's go, it's,
it's right out here.
Linda, i want you to just go back to
the car and wait for me, all right.
I'll go get that fat kid's book
so i can use their phone.
Mark, i'm scared.
I know, but this will
all be over soon.
Oh, gerald, i haven't
seen you for so long!
Hello, honey.
How has prison been
for you?
Oh, it's awful,
just awful!
All right, parents,
let's all take our seats.
My name is scott evans,
And i am a prison
rehabilitation counselor.
Excuse me,
but my wife and i
Honestly never touched
our child.
Neither did we!
We didn't neither!
Enough, enough!
Look, it's obvious we have
a lot of emotional issues
And personal demons
to face here.
During your prison time, you will
all be spending one hour a day
In therapy
here with me.
What i want you to do, is learn to
control those sick, sexual urges you have.
Now we're gonna
try an exercise.
I'm gonna confront you with
what you lust after most.
All right, parents, now,
i know this is difficult,
But i want you to just
look at this child,
Just try to suppress
your urges to molest him.
Just think about
something else,
Think about clouds
and beaches.
Don't think about his supple,
soft, little body.
Oh, that's disgusting!
Now stop this!
Fight your urges,
mr. Brovlofski!
I don't have any urges!
I can't help you if you won't
admit you need help!
Now, sit down!
Look, i know this is very
difficult for all of you.
Most of you are still in denial
about what you've done.
To you, it seems you never
molested your children at all!
But you did.
Help me... help you.
Now let's
try again.
Look at this young man.
Just look...
don't molest.
Fight it, fight it!
Oh god, god.
Please just let us
get out of this place.
I think i found
the problem, ma'am.
Broken window roller-Upper.
Oh no, no!
Ahh!
Where is
your husband?
Uh...
Seize her!
All right,
i got the book for you.
Awesome!
Now can i please
have the cell phone?
Sure, outlander,
i'll get it.
Outlander!
We have your woman!
She still lives,
outlander!
Outlander,
her blood will spill!
What the heck are you
talking about?
Butters, calm down,
all right.
Okay, so what are some
other things that we can do
Besides molest
our children?
See a movie?
Sure, see a movie's good.
We could see a movie instead of
molesting our children.
What else?
Make a sweater?
Uh-Huh, i'll put
"knitting/sewing".
Who's got another one?
Molest children?
No, no, we're looking
for things to do
Besidesmolesting
our children.
Oh... fishing?
Fishing's good, uh-Huh.
I believe you have something
of ours, outlander.
Give it back
or the female gets it!
Unh!
Heh-Heh.
Give him
the book back!
No, if they have it one of
ours will die for carousel!
We're running
out of time!
Hand our book over,
quick!
Enough of this!
You kids are all
in big trouble!
The provider awakes!
It's time for carousel.
Ha ha, your side doesn't
have its book, fat-Ass!
That means someone on your side
is sacrificed tonight!
God dammit!
All right,
it is decided.
Butters, your turn.
Oh, i'm gonna be sacrificed
to the provider!
Stop right there!
Nobody's killing
anybody tonight!
Be careful, mark, they'll make you disappear with the "m"
- Word!
Yeah, we'll call the police
and say you molestered us too!
What?
I'm here for you,
provider!
Take me!
Is that what happened
to the adults here?!
You lied to the police
and said they molested you?
My god, they were
your parents!
Parents?
The birth-Givers!
Your... birth-Givers.
Don't you remember?
They are your "providers"-
Not some statue!
And they're not off in some
fantastical far away land now...
They're in prison!
Probably crying themselves
to sleep, cold and lonely and...
I'm sure, missing you all
very, very much.
Your birth-Givers
took care of you.
That's what their laws and their
rules were for, because they love you,
And they didn't want you to
end up living like, like this.
Hewon't take care of you.
Your parents,
your... providers, will.
Parents...
Mom, dad.
Oh boy,
here it comes!
If you want things to be the way
they were in the before-Time,
In the long, long ago,
You all need to call the police and
tell them you lied about the m-Word.
He's right, dude.
Things were a lot better
with our parents around.
Yeah, i guess their rules
did have a point.
Things have gotten a lot worse in
the 10 days since they've been gone.
10 days?
It's only been 10 days
since they left?
Take him down.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm ready to give myself
to mr. Elway!
Here's our
cell phone, dude,
Will call the
police for us?
Hey, looks like you're not so
bad with kids after all.
Yeah, i guess you're right.
Maybe we should
have some.
Yeah, right,
after all this?
I'm getting my
tubes tied tomorrow!
Come on, you guys, our parents
are gonna be back any minute.
Do you think they're gonna be pissed
at us for lying that they molested us
And sending them all
to jail for 10 days?
Well, they can't be
too pissed off,
I mean, we made them
a banner.
Hey, kids!
Hey, you guys
came back!
Did you make it to
your job interview?
Yeah, i got the job.
You're looking at the new
manager ofdenny's in breckenridge.
And i got
my tubes tied!
All right!
Well, thanks for
everything, you guys.
You really helped us see
how important parents are.
Yeah!
Hey, here they come!
Mom, dad!
Kids!
Come here, come here.
Oh, kyle,
ike sweetie, you're okay!
Yeah, we're fine.
Kyle, we're so sorry for the
horrible sexual abuse over the years.
But we're all
better now.
But, you didn't
do anything to me.
Ahp- We did.
We've come to terms with it
through therapy
And learned
to admit it.
It won't happen again!
But, you guys, i-
Oh, stanley, i wish we could
take back all the years of abuse,
But we can't.
We've learned to
overcome it, son,
You'll see.
We love you, son,
But we only love you in
a platonic way, from now on!
What the heck are you
talking about?
Kenny, kenny,
we're sorry.
Where is he?
Everything's gonna be
all right now, jenny.
Come on, let's go home.
Huh.
Well, what are you kids
gonna do now?
I dunno.
You guys wanna go
build a snow igloo?
Sure.
Snow igloos
kick ass.
Captioning made possible by
comedy central
Captioned by
soundwriters™
www.tvsubtitles.net