Captioning made possible by
comedy central
? I'm going down
to south park?
? Gonna have
myself a time?
? Friendly faces
everywhere?
? Humble folks
without temptation?
? Going down
to south park?
? Gonna leave my
woes behind?
? Ample parking
day or night?
? People spouting
"howdy neighbor"?
? Headed on up
to south park?
? Gonna see if
i can't unwind?
? So come on down
to south park?
? And meet some
friends of mine?
Okay stan, i'm going
to give you...
A "u.F.O.
Crash-Landing" card,
You can deny it
or cover it up.
Dude, i don't understand
this gameat all.
It's "investigative reports
of bill curtis fun time game",
You have to deny it
or cover it up.
Uh, deny it.
Okay, let's see
what bill curtis says.
Hello, i'm bill curtis.
Many believe that
the u. S. Government
Covered it up,
i'm bill curtis.
All right, cartman,
i'm going to give you...
A "jail time card",
you lose a turn.
Sweet.
Oh yeah, well, i'm
going to give you...
Aids.
What?
I just gave
aids? You aids.
Dude, that's not cool,
don't give kyle aids.
Kyle has aids and now loses
47 turns and 800 points.
Kenny, your dad and i are
thinking about having another baby.
Wouldn't you love to have
another brother or sister?
No.
We just might
work on it later tonight.
Goddammit,
poor people suck!
Your family is
already on welfare
And now you're going to bring
another kid into the world.
Poor people are churning out
babies, adding on to over-Population
And expectingmeto pay
for it with my tax dollars.
You don't pay tax dollars,
cartman, you're 8.
You see, this is just
what i've been talking about!
I can't even relate to you guys
anymore because you're too immature.
What?
Hanging out with friends
That are a little more
intelligent and understand
Politics and stuff.
It's just that i'm up
on this level, up here
And all my friends
are down here.
You don't know what you're
talking about, fat ass!
No, no, no,
me, "nah", you guys, "nah".
Maybe more down,
down "nah".
Screw you guys,
i'm going home!
I'm bill curtis.
I've outgrown
all my friends,
I need to meet more
mature people, cloud frog.
Oh, great idea,
cloud frog!
I can meet new friends
on the internet.
Here's a chat room.
"Men who like young boys",
that's perfect!
Wow, look at all these guys
that want to be my friends!
I'll pick tony316.
Hi, tony.
Oh, you know
the usual stuff.
Smiley face.
Kewl, wanna get together?
Sure, tony,
that would be cool.
Winking smiley face.
Sounds good,
see you then!
Clown hat, curly hair,
smiley face.
You see that
cloud frog!
Tomorrow i'm going to meet
my first mature friend.
Hi, are you tony?
Yeah, you're eric?
Yeah!
I brought you some candy. Wow, cool!
And some books
on kama sutra.
Neato, having older friends kicks ass!
You see i've really
been having a tough time,
I've kind of matured faster
than my other friends,
We don't really
relate anymore and -
Uh, all my friends seem
so childish now, you know.
Do you like having
your back rubbed?
Yeah, that seems
really nice, thanks.
Hold it right
there, scum bag!
Huh?
We monitored your little
"on-Line chat",
Now you're coming with us. No!
What the hell
just happened?
You can't eat kenny, we have
to save food for the baby.
Your mom and i are going out for a few
weeks, kenny, take care of the baby.
Kenny, you have to change
the baby's diapers!
You have to share
your room with the baby!
The baby, the baby,
the baby!
Huuuh!
Stop it.
Come on, let's go try to
get you pregnant again.
Oh, all right.
Dad, i want
to play catch.
Huh?
Oh, i'll play catch
with you later, son.
I want to play now!
Oh, go ahead, we can
make love afterwards.
Oh, all right.
All right, here comes a pop
fly, see if you can catch it.
Good job,
now throw me one.
Oh!
Blech!
What happened?
He smacked me
in the balls.
Oh, oh!
Woo-Hoo!
Blech!
Okay, we'll
try this again.
This one looks good,
"hung daddy".
Hello, hung daddy!
Damn dude, this guy is tiny,
he must be a dwarf.
Sorry, i'm not interested in
being friends with midgets.
Frowny face.
How about this one?
Mr. Hammer head?
Hi, there.
Mr. Garrison!
Ahh, eric!
You want to be my friend? Oh, crap!
That's cool, we can hang out,
what do you want to do first?
Nothing, nothing!
All right, scum bag,
we got you.
Hey, ah!
Good thing
you guys came.
This little boy was trying
to have his way with me.
Nice try, buddy, we monitored
your little "on-Line chat",
Now you're coming with us. No!
Why the hell does the f.B.I.
Keep arresting all my friends?
This has to be the work
of stan and kyle.
God, i hate
those guys!
See, i told you, dude!
Those are
dialysis machines.
Old people have to hook
themselves into it with a tube
And it sucks all
their body fluids out.
Oh, man,
that's terrible!
I know, huh?
Put your mouth against
the glass, like this.
Wah!
Yeah,
haaa!
Bleh-Leh-Leh-Leh!
Wha-La-La-La-La!
All right, just what the hell
do you guys think you're doing?
We're making faces
at sick people.
No! I mean what
the hell are you doing?
Why are all my mature adult friends
being mysteriously arrested, huh?
We don't know.
I'll tell you why!
Because you guys are jealous and can't
handle the fact that you're immature,
So you started a government
conspiracy against me!
We don't know what you're
talking about, lard butt.
Lard butt, oh,
that's so mature.
God, i guess i was wrong
about you guys, huh?
You're not more
mature than us, cartman.
Yes, i am!
I'm telling you this is all a
terrible mistake, officer barbrady.
Well, the f.B.I said
i have to hold you here,
So that's what i'm going
to do, mr. Complainy-Pants.
Oh!
Do you like having
your back rubbed?
Eat me, pervert.
Okay.
We demand you release
these men at once.
Who are you?
We are "nambla",
The north american man-Boy
love association
And we heard about these
political prisoners you're keeping.
Political prisoners?
No, these are child molesters.
Loving young boys has been around
since the time of the romans, pal.
There's nothing
wrong with it!
We are an organization
dedicated to showing
That sex between a man and a
young boy can be a beautiful thing!
Yeah!
Uh, i don't know
who you are,
But these men aren't going any
where until i hear from the f.B.I.
Hate mongerer!
Hate mongerer, yeah.
Okay, people, i think you'd better
move along before i arrest more of you.
All these men wanted
was to love a young boy,
There is nothing
wrong with love.
I did not want love
from a young boy,
I like men
my own age.
Ah! I mean-
I like women,
what did i say?
Oh god,
i love titties!
You haven't heard
the last of us, officer.
Together we are strong.
Come on, men!
Yeah! Yeah!
Well, they got activists
for everything these days.
I've done it, kevin!
I've successfully gene-Spliced this
chipmunk with a piece of provolone cheese.
Do you know what
this means, kevin?
No more will the world have
to look in two different places
For squirrels and
provolone cheese.
No more will mankind
have to pick-
Who could that be?
Why, it's little
eric cartman.
Doctor mefesto,
i need help.
Of course,
come in.
See, unfortunately, i have
matured faster than all my friends.
I want to hang out with older
friends, but i can't find any.
So i was wondering if you can geneticly
engineer some older friends for me.
Oh, eric, i'm afraid
it's not that simple.
Genetic engineering has
not yet evolved to the state
Where i can just
make people.
Damn it, but i want to
hang out with older guys!
Oh, well,i happen to be a member of
an organization that can help you.
It's called "nambla".
"Nambla"?
Yes, i've been a member
for several years.
I'm sure they'll let you join,
you look about right.
Okay, thanks,
sure. Doctor mefesto!
Fellow members
of "nambla",
As you know, we continue
to be discriminated against.
Recently the f.B.I.
Has started to arrest men
Who are doing nothing more
than than trying to start
A sexual relationship
with a young boy.
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
And now that all ethnic groups,
homosexuals and women
Are protected under
civil rights laws,
We want the same!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
What we need isproof that young
boys want to be members of "nambla".
That theywant
love from us.
We need a poster child.
To show the world that it is a
beautiful and wonderful thing-
Ooooh...!
Can we help you?
Yes, i'd like to join your
fine organization, is that cool?
You do?
Sure.
Thank you,
thank you, jesus!
Sweet.
Whah!
Bleh!
Le-Le-Le-Le!
Buh!
Well, kenny,
the doctor confirmed it.
I'm pregnant!
You're going to have
a little brother or sister.
Yup, it's for sure.
And he fixed my shattered
left testicle, too.
Don't be out
too late, kenny.
We need to start moving
stuff out of your room.
Wow, your mom's
pregnant, kenny!
Yeah, now what are
you going to do?
I don't know,
hmm-Hmm-Hmhm-Hm-Hmm.
? Nyah-Nyah-Nyah?
? I got
into "nambla"?
? And you guys didn't?
What are you
talking about, fat ass?
Oh, no big deal, i just
found a group called "nambla"
With adult members and
they all think i'm so mature
They wantmeto be their
new poster child, is all.
It looks like i'm finally going to
have mature friends who i can relate to.
? Nyah-Nyah-Nyah
nyah-Nyah-Nyah?
? I'm too mature
for you guys?
? Nyah-Nyah-Nyah
nyah-Nyah-Nyah?
Can i help you,
young lady?
Oh, you want "morning after"
abortion pills.
Well, they're right over there. Thanks!
I'm sorry,
young lady,
But i can't sell that to you
without permission from your parents.
Well, all righty then,
cash or charge?
Cool.
Look, mom, i made you
something to drink.
Oh, well, that's
very sweet of you kenny,
You made my favorite
drink for me.
Yeah.
But, unfortunately, now that
i'm pregnant i can't drink.
Well, i could still drink. No, daddy.
Oh, that hits
the spot.
Makes me forget all about
my shattered balls.
What, what's
the matter?
Why don't you go
make me another one of-
Oh!
What's the matter?
Uh-Oh!
Oh god, i'm gonna
crap my pants!
Oh, god!
Oh, my balls.
Blech!
Oh, god!
Just a few more
pictures, eric.
You make a perfect
poster child.
Thanks, dude.
Hey eric, we have
a surprise for you.
We want you to have
a big dinner and dance
Honoring you as
our new poster child.
Really, awesome!
Yes, and we want you
to, umm...
Invite all your
young male friends.
Oh, yes.
Aww!
Well, sure, i have some
friends who want to be mature
Excluding stan and kyle,
of course.
Great, now you go and
invite your little friends
And we'll get
the hotel ready.
Kickass!
Kenny, don't forget
to clean out your room,
So we can paint it
for the baby!
Hey, are you feeling down,
you need some excitement!
And north park funland has
just opened its newest ride,
"The john denver experience"!
You'll be "rocky
mountain high" with this,
The most extreme,
insane ride ever built!
It was fun.
Note: people with heart
conditions and expectant mothers
Should not ride "the john
denver", open now, come on down!
Mom!
Are you sure you should be
going on this thing.
Oh, it's all right.
You know, i think kenny's been
a little worried about the baby,
We have to show him that
he's still our little boy.
What'd he say?
Whoa!
Oh god, my nose,
i think i broke my nose.
Come on stuart, let's just
get you to a bathroom.
Oh, i'm not going to make it,
i'm going to be sick.
Oh, my stomach.
Oh, my nose.
Gross.
Oh, stan and kyle, just
the guys i wanted to see,
My "nambla" organization is having
a very important benefit in my honor.
They are?
We're going to have a big
mature party at this hotel
And i can invite all
my mature friends that i want.
And that means i'm going
to invite everybody,
Except for
you guys!
? Nyah-Nyah-Nyah
nyah-Nyah-Nyah?
We don't want to go to some
stupid adult meeting anyway.
Well, that's nice,
because you can't go.
We don't
want to go.
You can't go.
We don'twant
to go.
No, youcan'tgo.
Hey clyde, butters,
check this out!
Dude, maybe wedoneed to
start being more mature.
Yeah, i guess we've got to
try to get in that club, too.
You're doing fine,
ms. Mccormick.
It's all right, kenny.
Come see
the miracle of life.
Ewww!
I can see his head.
You can?
Push now,
push hard!
Oh, my god!
What is it!
It's alive!
Oh, my god!
It killed kenny!
Bad baby, bad!
Hmm?
That does it!
Oh, hi kenny,
what are you doing?
What are you
doing kenny?
Kenny, what are you
going to plunge?
Grrrrr!
Ahhhh!
Kenny, what the
hell are you doing?
What the hell?
Hey, what the hell
are you guys doing here?
This is for
mature people only.
We got invited too,
fat ass.
Well, i guess nowadays they allow
any old schmucks into "nambla".
Fellow nambla members,
It is great to see
you all here.
It seems like we have finally
found a city that won't oppress us!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
First and foremost, i want
to recognize eric cartman
For putting us in touch with
all you pretty young boys.
Thank you,
thank you very much.
Now, i know that many of us have
already found partners in this fine city
And i'd like to take a minute to
hear some testimonials from members.
This is boring.
Yeah.
Hey, when are we going to
get to some action, huh?
Oooh!
Ha-Ha!
Goodness,
what a gift from god.
We'll get to it very soon,
i'll assure you.
But first, i'd just like to hear
from a couple of you on your progress.
Yes, patrick.
I found a little 8-Year-Old
named butters,
He's a beautiful
bright little boy.
Well, i sure am,
i guess.
And his skin is as soft
as fresh linen.
Ooh!
Ooh! Ooh!
That seems
kind of weird.
Well, my skin is
"springtime" soft, i suppose.
Wonderful.
And how about you
mr. Harris?
Well, i want to announce that i may
have found the dream boy of the decade,
He's sexy, sassy
and full of spark.
His name is timmy.
Timmy!
Tim-My?
Well, members, i know
we're all eager
To get acquainted with
our new partners.
So why don't we turn down
the lights and start the dance.
All right, i want these perverted
bastards all taken in, got it?
Got it!
Fellow nambla members,
As the south park
representative-
Hold it right there!
Nobody move!
What's going on?
All right, sickos,
where are the children?
What children?
This is "nambla",
yes. Right?
"The north american
man-Boy love association".
What? No!
We're "the north american
marlon brando look-A-Likes."
Oh crap, we've got
the wrong "nambla".
Oh, damn it, i'm
in the wrong place!
Don't tell me that other "nambla"
is actually in south park.
You know of them?
We've been fighting with them for
years over the rights to "nambla.Com".
Yeah, those
perverted bastards!
Wow, you guys really dolook
a lot like marlon brando.
Thank you.
Now, let's go get those
other "nambla" bastards
Before they hurt any
south park children!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
And let's kick their asses
for stealing our domain name!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
All right, members,
that's enough of that.
It's time for for us all to
retire to our respective rooms
And get to know
our new young boys.
All right!
Dude, being mature is boring. Yeah!
Everyone come up and grab your
room keys and we'll head upstairs.
Ahhh!
Ahhh! Ahahhh!
Dude, i think these guys mean to
have sexual encounters with us!
I know dude, let's get
the hell out of here!
Ah! There's more
of them, quick hide!
Okay, marlon brandos!
They've got to be here
somewhere, let's try this room.
Let's get those perverts.
Ah!
Sacre bleu!
Whoa!
Ahhh!
Kenny, no! Leave me
alone! Mmm-Hmm-Mmm.
Kenny!
This time i will
not drop the food.
Where are
the boys?
Sacre bleu!
I think the boys
went in here.
Ah!
Timmy!
Maybe the boys
are in here, oh boys!
Ah!
All right, you're
under arrest!
No, you've got
the wrong "nambla" again.
Dammit!
Hey, we didn't
try that room.
Sacre bleu.
Dude, we're
surrounded by perverts.
They're all over
the place.
Timmy!
What are we
going to do?
Well, cartman, you got
everybody into this,
You gotta figure a way
to get everybody out.
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
Uhh, that's fine.
I know how
to get us out.
How?
Well, look those perverts
aren't going to rest
Until they've made love
to one of us, right?
So somebody is just going
to have to go out there
And take one
for the team.
And i think in all fairness,
it should be butters.
Huh, well,
why me?
Are you a team player
or not?
Yeah, sure, i'm
a team player, i guess.
Well, butters, there is
no "i" in team.
You mean you expect me to go out
there and let all those horny old men
Have their way with
my fragile person?
Just what team
is this anyway?
Just go, butters,
we're running out of time.
Oh, all right then.
He's such
a dumb ass.
All right, men,
here i come.
I'm ready to
take one for the team.
Kenny, kenny, i've had
enough of your shenanigins!
Ooh, one of the boys
just came in!
I get him first!
What the-?
Oh no!
Ahhhhh!
Are you all right,
stuart?
Don't touch me.
I've had my nuts broken,
body poisoned
And been made love to in the
ass by 3 dozen 40-Year-Old men.
I just want to go home
and take a hot bath.
We've been after you
for a long time, buddy.
Do you know
your rights?
Rights? Does anybody
know their rights?
You see, i've learned
something today,
Our forefathers came to this country
because they believed in an idea.
An idea
called freedom.
They wanted to live
in a place where a group
Couldn't be prosecuted
for their beliefs.
Where a person can live
the way he chooses to live.
You see us as being perverted
because we're different from you.
People are afraid of us
because they don't understand.
And sometimes it's easier to
persecute than to understand.
Dude, you have
sex with children.
We are human.
Most of us didn't evenchooseto
be attracted to young boys,
We were born
that way.
We can't help
the way we are,
And if you all can't
understand that, well,
Then i guess you'll just
have to put us away.
Dude, you have
sexwith children.
Yeah, you know, we believe
in equality for everybody
And all that gay stuff,
but dude,
You.
Seriously.
Alright, that's enough, you're all
going to be put away for a long time.
Well, cartman.
Well, what?
Don't you think you owe everyone an
apology for bringing "nambla" here?
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
All right,
all right.
I'm sorry i almost got
you guys all raped, there.
And now do you still think you need
to hang out with older, mature friends?
No, i guess you guys will
blossom into maturity someday,
Just don't
take too long.
Okay, let's roll.
Coo-Coochie-Coo
coo-Coochie-Coo.
Our little angel,
yes.
Oh, he's so beautiful!
I know it's been hard on
both of us, losing poor kenny.
But this knew baby
kinda reminds me of him.
What should
we name him?
Well, seeing as though
kenny passed away,
Maybe we should
name him...
Kenny.
Yes, kenny is such
a great name.
My little kenny,
a brand-New kenny.
God, this must have been the
50th time this has happened.
52nd.
www.tvsubtitles.net