Captioning made possible by
comedy central
? I'm going down
to south park?
? Gonna have
myself a time?
? Friendly faces
everywhere?
? Humble folks
without temptation?
? Going down
to south park?
? Gonna leave my
woes behind?
? Ample parking
day or night?
? People spouting
"howdy neighbor"?
? Headed on up
to south park?
? Gonna see if
i can't unwind?
? So come on down
to south park?
? And meet some
friends of mine?
He's gonna be here
any minute, ike.
Oh no, poopie.
He might not come if you're too
close to the toilet bowl, ike.
Come sit by me.
It's getting late, boys,
Why don't you
come on up to bed.
Just let us stay up
a little longer, mom,
Mr. Hankey's gotta show up,
he always does.
All right, boobie.
Oh, and boys,
happy chanukah.
Happy chanukah, mom.
Wee, wee.
Go away!
Stan, go get
the other guys
And tell them to meet me
at the bus stop in 10 minutes.
Okay, good,
you're all here.
What's this
all about, kyle?
It's mr. Hankey,
he hasn't shown up yet!
Oh, jesus christ,
i'm going back to bed.
It's only three days until
christmas, you guys.
You know how bad things
have been around here.
I think it might be because
mr. Hankey hasn't come.
Kyle, i have a full day
of watching tv tomorrow,
I don't have time to go on
a poo hunt right now, okay?
If you guys want there
to be a christmas
You better come help me.
Heh-Choo!
Dude, you sneezed
on my back!
Oh sorry, you might
get some germs
While you're walking around
in human feces.
Hey, look!
Hello?
Howww-Dy ho!
Mr. Hankey!
Oh, we were so worried.
I was waiting up for you and you
didn't come so i thought that-
Oh no,
i'm fine, kyle.
But where have you been?
Things aren't the same
without you.
Nobody seems to have
the christmas spirit.
Oh, i know, kyle.
I've just been awful busy
with my family.
Honey!
Family?
Boys, i want you to meet
my wife, autumn.
Howdy hey, kids.
Would you like
a drink?
They're too young
to drink, honey.
Oh hell,
it's christmas.
Oh, and you have to meet
the little nuggets, too.
Kids!
This is our son
cornwallis.
Howww-Dy ho!
Our daughter amber.
Howdy ho!
And our son simon.
Nnn, hey!
Simon's not so smart, he was
born with a peanut in his head.
What's that, pa?
Nothin', simon.
A family!
So that's why you haven't been
able to spread christmas cheer.
It sure has been tough.
Nobody seems that into
christmas up there.
I know, it's like it
doesn't matter anymore.
My mom's barely bought me
any presents so far.
Well, don't worry kids.
I'm sending the nuggets
up tomorrow
To spread christmas cheer.
And if you want,
you can help them.
Sure we'll help!
Anything for more
presents!
Woo hoo,
it's a christmas party!
Hey, you boys.
You boys wanna bet me i won't
take off my clothes?
Honey, please,
you're-You're drunk, okay.
But it's christmas, baby!
Honey, can we go inside
for a second?
Now when people come over...
Well, it's decided, kids,
Tomorrow we're gonna bring back
the spirit of christmas!
Ho, ho, ho!
Merry christmas, you guys.
Only three
shopping days until-
God dammit!
Hey, merry christmas,
asshole!
Nobody's paying
any attention.
Look out!
Eww, i almost
stepped in it!
Well, it was
a good effort, boys,
But i'm gonna have to
close shop.
Nobody's buying anything
and i can't afford
To keep this
furnace runnin'!
Oh, and boys, there's some crap
on the sidewalk there, watch out.
Not one toy.
I guess this year everyone's
content to celebrate
With candles and love.
This is hopeless.
We're just gonna have to face
that the commercialism
Has been sucked
out of christmas.
And in other news tonight,
it appears that everyone
Is officially
sick of christmas!
In anspcpoll, 38% said they were
fed up and tired of the holiday.
5% said they were
indifferent to it.
And a whopping 57%
Said they would kick bon jovi
square in the balls
If given the opportunity.
Well, i think people are just
fed up with the crowded shopping
And the
credit card bills.
I think that the holiday
just has become a joke.
Y'know, it's just that a lot of
people don't really believe
In the whole "jesus" thing
anymore, y'know.
So what's to celebrate?
Oh yeah, right in the
balls, man,
Right square
in the balls.
Well, the holiday spirit
may be gone from south park,
But at least our faith
in each other remains strong.
Oh, really?
Dude, change the channel,
this is too depressing.
Good grief, we need a
christmas tree for our play.
Oh jesus, not
this thing again.
How come everyone in cartoons
has such big heads?
All right, everyone, we've got
to get on with our play.
Jesus, this sucks!
All they keep doing
is dancing around.
Yeah, this thing really falls
apart in the second act.
And why is it- That on
"charlie brown" cartoons-
Everyone talks-
Like this?
My mom could make a better
christmas special than this.
Hey, that's it!
Oh my god,
that's totally it!
It's so simple.
What, dude?
We can get everyone back
into the christmas spirit
By making our very own
animated christmas special
And showing it
to everybody in town.
We don't know anything
about animation.
How hard can it be?
Look at it?
Hey, yeah!
We can make a little animated
santa claus and jesus.
And it can star us instead of
these little round-Headed guys.
Hell yeah, awesome!
Yeah, and we can call it...
"the spirit of christmas."
Oh, this is
terrible, johnson.
Our whole town's economy
is going right in the toilet.
We've got to get everybody
back in the christmas spirit.
Mayor, some adorable children
are here to see you.
Muh- Send them in.
Mayor, we have the solution
to your problem. You do?
We're gonna make make a short animated
christmas card that everyone can watch
And play it at the screen
at the old drive-In.
It'll have everything-
Jesus, santa.
And when people see it they'll
just have to get in the spirit.
All we need is
$300 for our budget.
An animated
christmas card!
Kids, that just might be
Thedumbest idea
i've ever heard, ever!
Aww. Aww.
But at this point
i'm willing to try anything.
Johnson, cut 'em
a check for $300.
All right! All right!
You guys go tell butters
to start making the cutouts.
I'm gonna go tell mr. Hankey
the good news.
You put the vase down!
Put that vase down,
that's an expensive vase!
Don't you
throw that vase!
Uh, mr. Hankey!
Oh, kyle,
howww-Dy ho!
We got the money,
mr. Hankey,
We're gonna make our
animated christmas card.
Oh, that's swell!
Kids, christmas
is back on!
We gotta all get that old
drive-In working again.
Okay! Okay!
That's not only thing
we gotta get working again,
If you know what i mean.
Why, why do you,
why do you have to
Say things like that
in front of people?
Well, i've gotta go
start our animation.
We've only got two days!
Good luck, kyle,
And we'll have that
projector working,
Don't you worry!
Whcornwallis?Ter,
All right, butters,
let's see what you've got.
Oh, well okay.
Now don't expect too much
with the budget you gave me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah-
Just let us see 'em.
Well, all right, here's a little
construction paper santa claus.
"Ho ho ho there, kids.
Would you like some
toys and stuff?"
Ah, and uh,
here's a little jesus.
"Hey there, santa, i'm the light
of the way and stuff."
"Oh, okay, that's good,
i suppose."
And here's the cutout versions
of you guys.
Whoa. Whoa.
Heh-Heh, look,
he made stan all fat.
That's not me, that's you! What!
They kind of
look like us.
I mean, stan's got blue eyes
and i've got a sharper nose,
But they kind of
look like us.
I am not that
goddamn fat!
Good job, butters.
Oh, uh, hey, i made a little
cutout version of me, too.
In case you need it
for your animated film.
No, that's okay.
See ya!
Oh, all right,
all right then.
"Oh, hey there, good-Looking,
what's your name?"
"Ah, butters, ma'am."
"Oh, butters, would you like to
slap my titties around?"
Whoa, well, ah...
No thanks, ma'am,
i'll get in trouble again.
Cornwallis, we've got to go
fix up the drive-In.
I don't want to, dad,
i'm too sad.
Hey, it's all right,
cornwallis,
Those boys' animated movie will
bring back the spirit of christmas.
It's not that father,
it's-
I don't feel like i'm
really a part of christmas.
But son, you're a hankey,
we love christmas.
Come on, it's time to
sit around the tree!
We're having
a talk, honey.
Goddammit,
it's christmas,
And we're gonna be a happy
family around the tree.
Autumn, you're drunk,
all right,
Now just go help
the other kids,
They can't get
their stockings up.
That's not only thing that
can't get up around here.
Now come on, son,
don't be so down.
Why? We're just
pieces of crap.
Christmas isn't for us.
Christmas is about
feeling good.
That's for everybody!
I see the nativity-
There's angels, shepherds
and sheep, but no poo.
All the christmas movies-
Santa, elves, reindeer-
No poo, i'm not
a part of it.
No, you're not
a part of it, cornwallis,
You're all of it,
don't you see?
I'm nothing but crap.
But crap is everything.
? Everything that lives on earth
poos in some way?
? And that's how
the cycle happens?
? Each and every day?
? Just look at
the green, green grass?
? And the birds
up in the sky?
? It's all here because of poo
now i'll tell you why?
? Grass is eaten
by the cattle?
? Which is eaten
by women and men?
? It fuses with their bodies
and becomes poo again?
? And that poo goes through
the sewer?
? Where it's dumped
into the sea?
? And it's eaten
by the plankton?
? That becomes
the fishes' meal?
? Then that bigger fish
with the poo still inside?
? Swims up near the shore
and gets eaten alive?
? By a grizzly bear that poos
on a dead piece of sand?
? So it can spring to life
and become food for the land?
? It's the poo
of the antelope?
? The poo of the giraffe?
? That falls
onto the earth?
? And becomes
the blades of grass?
? The grass is eaten
by the cattle?
? Which comes out
the other end?
? To make poo for the humans
and start all over again?
You see, son, you're not an
insignificant part of life,
You are life.
But how can i be that giraffe
and blade of grass and a human?
I don't control
what they do.
Just like your heart beats
without you thinking about it,
So, too, your giraffes and
your humans do what they do
Without you even
thinking about it.
But it is all one life form,
it is all... you.
I think i see now.
? I'm the poo
of the antelope?
? That flows
onto the ground?
? Becomes the grass of tomorrow? ? Yeah?
? Which the grazers
turn around?
? So i'm the leg of a leopard
and the wings of the hen?
? Which becomes
dinner for the humans?
? And turns back
to poo again?
? Mm-Hmm?
? That's the cycle
the cycle of poo?
Okay,
here's the script.
But it doesn't have
an ending. No ending?
Well, we can't animate until
we have our voices recorded,
So we better just record what we
have and figure out the ending later.
Okay, talk directly
into the mike
And don't hit any
hard "p"s.
What's a hard "p"?
You know, first thing
in the morning
When it just
won't come out?
Oh yeah.
Umm... okay,
sound is speeding and...
? We wish you
a merry christmas-?
Hold on.
Ahh! Ahh!
Ahh, hmm, okay, and...
? We wish you
a merry christmas?
? We wish
you a merry christmas-?
Hey,
wait a minute!
What?
Aren't you
jewish, kyle?
Well, yes,
i think so.
Dude, jewish people don't
celebrate christmas,
You're supposed to sing
chanukah songs.
? Dreidel dreidel dreidel
i made you out of clay?
? Dreidel dreidel dreidel-?
Heh-Heh-Heh,
chanukah sucks.
Don't you
oppress me, fat boy!
Don't call me fat,
butt!
Then don't belittle my people,
you fat-Ass!
Guys, knock it off,
we have to record this.
Dude, that was awesome.
What's awesome?
The script,
it's sweet.
That's not in the script,
they do this all the time.
Well, it should be
in the script.
All that, you're fat and
you're a jew and stuff.
It's great.
Check it out, dude.
The camera shoots
one frame at a time.
So, all we gotta do is
put the right mouth on,
According to what syllable
they're pronouncing at that frame.
Easy.
Yeah, so what's
the first syllable?
Ah, "w",wewish you
a merry christmas.
Okay, so we put little "woo"
mouths on all our heads.
And then we shoot that
for one frame.
Okay.
One.
That's 1/24th of a second
of our movie already shot.
Kick-Ass!
Now the next mouth.
Ah, "e",wewish you
a merry christmas.
Okay, where are
the "e" mouths?
"E" mouths...
Okay,
"woo" mouths again.
One, two.
So how much done
is that?
"We wish you a merry."
Ah, jesus christ.
These kids better make a good
christmas movie, johnson.
If people in this town
don't start shopping again
We're all gonna be
out of jobs next year!
This place is
pretty rundown.
It's all right, we've got
a cleanup crew coming.
Howww-Dy ho!
Down here!
Ahh!
Oh, mr. Hankey, it's you,
how wonderful.
My family and i are here to get the
drive-In ready for the big movie!
Perfect.
Hi, there, mr. Important
political person.
You want to bet me i won't
take off my clothes
And run naked through
this parking lot?
Honey, please
don't start.
I didn't start it!
He was looking
at my breasts.
They're not real,
you know.
Don't you say that!
Oh, big secret, everyone can
tell they're made of "silicorn".
Ah, we'll just leave you
to your cleanup.
Okay!
Boy oh boy, this place
sure needs a lot of work.
We can
fix it up, dad.
Oh look,
a homeless person.
Oh, he looks sad, papa.
There, that's better.
Good job, amber.
Now this place is starting
to look christmas-Y.
Okay, okay, this shot
is finally set up.
Now shoot the "oh" mouth
for two frames.
A- Choo!
Ahh!
Cartman!
Well, i'm sorry,
i have a cold.
That took us half an hour
to set up, fat-Ass!
All right,
you know what?!
I have been here
too long!
I'm sick of making
this stupid cartoon
And we're never gonna
finish it anyways!
Screw you, guys...
i'm going home!
Fine, we'll do it
without you.
We can't do it
without him, kyle,
We've already
animated him in it.
We'll dub his voiceover.
Kyle, it's hopeless.
We've only got 20 seconds
of animation done.
We still have jesus' and
santa's voices to record.
We don't even have
a third act.
Dude, it would take a miracle
to finish this thing.
Now, don't go
saying that.
There's always hope.
Miracles happen
most everyday...
? To people
like you and me?
? But don't expect
a miracle?
? Unless you help
make it to be?
? You hope
and i'll hurry?
? You pray and i'll plan?
? We'll do what's
necessary?
? 'Cause even a miracle
needs a hand?
? You love?
? We love?
? And i'll labor?
? Tra la la?
? You sit?
? We sit?
? And i'll stand?
? Get help from our
next door neighbor?
? 'Cause even a miracle
needs a hand?
You can do cartman's
voice, can't you?
Uh, i'm so fat.
You gotta sound fatter.
Hey, you guys, seriously.
I'm so fat,
help me out over here.
Cool, now let's try the script. Rolling.
I don't know what to do, dude,
who should we help?
I say we help santa claus.
Oh, you're just saying that
because he brings you candy.
Hey, i don't need to take that
kind of from a jew!
? You wish?
? We wish?
? And i'll whittle?
? Tra la la?
? You sit?
? We sit?
? And i'll stand?
? Let's all try to
help a little?
? 'Cause even a miracle-?
It's okay, we'll just have
his character die in the film.
? Even a miracle
needs a hand...?
Citizens of south park,
The colorado film commission
is pleased to present to you
A work by some of our
very own south park children.
Thank you, thank you.
Cartman, what the hell are you
doing here, you quit?
What are you
talking about "quit"?
Puh-
I don't remember that.
We know that after you see this
darling short film
You will all feel
the mighty glow
Of the christmas spirit
once again.
Boys?
Okay, mr. Hankey.
Okay!
? We wish you
a merry christmas?
? We wish you a merry
christmas?
? We wish you
a merry christmas-?
Hey, wait a minute.
What?
Aren't you jewish, kyle?
Yeah, i think so.
Dude, jewish people don't
celebrate christmas. What?
You're supposed to sing
chanukah songs.
? Dreidel dreidel dreidel-?
Nnn, pretty!
Well, that's christmas
for ya.
Just hang on, folks,
We seem to be having some
technical difficulties.
Stupid.
It's completely destroyed,
there's nothing i can do!
All that hard work.
Well, thanks a lot, kids,
great idea you had there.
Now everyone is more disenfranchised
with christmas than ever.
We want our
300 bucks back.
But we spent it.
Fine,
then we'll sue you.
Johnson.
I... used to
believe in miracles.
All that work.
For nothing.
Boys, i-I'm...
i'm sorry.
Sure, sure,
mr. Hankey.
I guess we might as well
go home now.
It's my fault,
all my fault.
I got everyone's
hopes up.
But, dad, we can
fix the projector.
Oh, it's too late
for that, son.
Everyone's gone home.
And i don't know nothin'
about projectors.
I'm just a stupid
piece of crap.
Dad, you taught me
an important lesson,
That crap is the cycle
of everything.
Oh, that was just a
stupid song, cornwallis!
I was just trying to get you
to stop your bitching.
No, it wasn't
a stupid song,
Because you showed me
that i have the power
And the strength
to do anything i want.
You made me
believe in myself, dad.
Now i'm asking you
to do the same.
Son...
You're the smartest piece of
crap since albert poo-Dinger!
Come on!
Isn't this a nice
christmas, stanley?
No commercialism
and shopping,
Just a nice fire
and family.
I wanna die!
They did it!
They've got it
working!
You have blemished
the meaning of christmas
For the last time, kringle.
I bring happiness and love
To children
all over the world.
Christmas is for
celebrating my birth.
Christmas is for giving.
Oh... wow.
Mom, they got it
working!
What, son, they got your
father's penis working again?
We actually spoke tothe
brian boitano.
Yeah, and you know,
I think i learned
something today.
It doesn't matter
if you're christian,
Or jewish
or atheist or hindu-
Christmas is still about
one very important thing.
Yeah, ham.
No, not ham!
Hey, why the hell did you
have me say that?
We can make you say
whatever we wanted.
Christmas is about something
much more important.
What?
Presents.
Don't you see, kyle?
Presents?
Presents.
My god, they're right!
Christmasis
about presents.
If we all buy presents,
everyone benefits, m'kay.
That is the spirit of
christmas- Commercialism.
Because it's what makes
our country work.
They're starting to
understand, johnson,
understand.
We got so caught up in the
little things of christmas,
Like love and family,
that we almost forgot
It's buying things that
makes our economy thrive.
Hey, the shops
are still open.
We still have
time to shop!
Cool, let's go!
Yeah, let's go!
Woo!
You did it,
mr. Hankey,
You brought back
the spirit of christmas.
No, you did it, boys.
Ah hell,
we all did it.
Kids, that cartoon
was fabulous.
How would you like to
have your own show
And make 100 more of them?
Are you kidding?
I think we'd rather
stab ourselves in the head.
Yeah, let's just go home
and open our presents.
Hey, man, if you're jewish,
you get presents for eight days.
Wow, count me in!
Yeah, i'll be
a jew, too.
? Dreidel dreidel dreidel
i made you out of clay?
with dreidel i will play?
? I'm the poo of the antelope
that flows onto the ground?
? Becomes the grass of tomorrow? ? Yeah?
? Which the grazers
turn around?
? So i'm the leg
of a leopard?
? And the wings
of the hen?
? Which becomes
dinner for the humans?
? And turns back
to poo again?
Captioning made possible by
comedy central
Captioned by
soundwriters™
www.tvsubtitles.net