Captioning made possible by
comedy central
? I'm going down
to south park?
? Gonna have
myself a time?
? Friendly faces
everywhere?
? Humble folks
without temptation?
? Going down
to south park?
? Gonna leave my
woes behind?
? Ample parking
day or night?
? People spouting
"howdy neighbor"?
? Headed on up
to south park?
? Gonna see if
i can't unwind?
? So come on down
to south park?
? And meet some
friends of mine?
Mom! Mom!
Mom, seriously!
Something wonderful
has happened!
What is it, snookums?
Mom, look-
The tooth fairy!
I put a tooth
under my pillow
And she gave me $2.00!
She's only given me
a lousy quarter before!
Oh my, she must
think that
You are a very
special little muffin.
Yeah, this
isso tits!
Don't say
"tits", eric.
Oh, i mean,
this is so cool!
Well, perhaps now
you should take that money
And open up
a savings account
That has compounded
daily interest.
Heh, you can compound
daily my ass with interest, mom
I'm goin' to the toy store,
and buy me a skateboard.
But eric, i think maybe
The tooth fairy wants you
to use that money
To learn about saving.
Mom, you don't know
what the tooth fairy
Wants me to do
with this money, okay?
You're not
the tooth fairy!
I'll see you later.
Oh man,
this is so tits!
You guys, you're not
gonna believe this!
Oh my god, you guys! Just wait
'til you hear this, you guys!
I'm rich! I'm totally rich!
Aren't you stoked?
What the hell's
wrong with cartman?
He's fat
and he's stupid?
Look at what the tooth fairy
left me last night!
$2.Oo!
No way!
For one tooth?
For one tooth!
Dude, every time i lost a
tooth, i only got a quarter.
I only got a
jar of gefilte fish.
Well, that
doesn't matter,
Because i have an idea
that is totally tits!
Totallywhat?
Look, i don't know
why the tooth fairy
Is being
so cool to me,
Maybe she's hot
for me, i don't know.
But if we all
chip in with teeth,
Then i can hide them
undermy pillow
And we can get enough money
to buy asega dreamcast!
Sega dreamcast?
All we need is teeth.
I already lost
all my baby teeth.
Me too!
Uh-Uh!
You still have
baby teeth, kenny?
Mph-Mmp!
Kenny, think about it!
Don't you want
asega dreamcast?
No, i don't!
Thank you
Alright,
kenny's in, you guys!
Tits!
Okay, the string
is tied to kenny's tooth,
You ready over there?
Almost,
you ready, timmy?
Timmy!
When i say go,
You slam your electric wheelchair
into high gear, okay, timmy?
Timmy!
Right, you're timmy.
Gimme a-Yah!
Mphh-Mphh...
I'll tell you why
it has to be you, kenny.
Because your
family is poor,
And therefore
has bad oral hygene
So your teeth are gonna
fall out someday, anyway.
If you think about it,
You should actually
be thanking us.
Oh, thank you, guys!
You're welcome, kenny!
F- Phk-Ymph!
Alright,
get ready, timmy.
Timmy!
Hey, guys,
what are you doin'?
What does it
look like, butters?
We need a tooth,
So we're using
timmy's wheelchair
To pull out
one of kenny's.
Oh, hey, i got
a loose tooth right here.
You what?
You what!
Timmy!
Yep, one of mine came out
not two hours ago.
Uh, butters,
could we have it?
Well, heck no,
you can't have it!
Why i'm gonna
stick it under my pillow
And get money
from the tooth fairy,
She always gives
me 50¢ a tooth!
Well, i'll
see you, fellas!
Dude, maybe
we don't have to
Rip a tooth
out of kenny's mouth.
Yeah, we just have
to get butters' tooth.
Whoo-Hoo!
How we gonna
get it from 'im?
I guess we'll have to
sneak into his house
After he goes
to sleep tonight.
Yeah, let's go!
Go, timmy, go!
No, timmy, wait!
Thing won't gimme!
Oh!
Hey, you guys, i can see
kenny's little ping-A-Ling!
Wa-Aaa!
Higher, you guys!
Christ, why did we pick
the fat guy to lift up?
Ow! Careful,
you assholes!
To the left,
you guys, left!
No, camera left!
Camera left!
That's it, now down!
What the- Who's there?
Who is that?
I am the tooth fairy, my child.
Oh, sorry, miss fairy,
i didn't mean to gaze at you,
I'm back
asleep now, see?
Yes! Now i will leave you
tidings under your pillow!
Oh, gosh, i didn't
think you'd be so fat.
Hey!
Come on, fat ass!
Do not open your eyes
until morning
Or else i will
kick you in the nuts...
Ahh, in the nuts.
Yes, ma'am!
Well?
Bullseye!
? Tucky-Tucky time?
? It's the best time
of the night?
I love that song, mom.
Sing it again!
No, honey, mommy's
got to save her throat.
I have to
work tonight!
Okay.
Goodnight!
What do you
have there, eric?
Another tooth
fell out today.
I'm leavin' it
for the tooth fairy.
Oh my, the tooth fairy
will have to give you
A big surprise for losing
two teeth in two days!
I know, huh?
You guys!
Oh my god, you guys
You're not
gonna believe it!
It's beyond
rational thought!
Holy crap, you guys!
Did the
tooth fairy come?
$4.Oo!
Oh my god!
Do you guys know
what this means?
Yeah, we just gotta
keep finding teeth
And putting them
under your pillow.
Dentist office.
Oh hello, dr. Roberts?
It's miss cartman.
Oh, yes, miss cartman,
what can i do for you?
Well, it's my son,
He's lost a lot
of his baby teeth
And i was starting
to get worried.
Well, losing baby teeth is a
natural thing, miss cartman.
How many has he lost?
About 112.
112?
Yes, 15 of them
in one night.
Perhaps he should
switch toothpaste?
Your son wouldn't happen to be
an alligator, would he, no?
Hmmm, i see.
Well, i'm afraid i can't
help you right now.
The american dental association
convention is this week,
But as soon as i get back,
i'll look into it.
Oh, thank you.
Freebie next week!
What?
Daa-
Tooth?
What the hell?
Mom!
Yes, eric.
The stuipid tooth fairy forgot
to bring me money last night.
Call the police!
Oh, eric-Poopy,
sit down,
Mommy has something
to tell you.
It's just
that... well
There is no
tooth fairy, eric.
I've been putting all that
money under your pillow
And because you've had
so many teeth fall out,
I've actually
run out of money
And can't go to the grocery
store for at least a month.
You almost had me
for a second there, mom.
"There's no tooth fairy"
I suppose next
you're gonna tell me
There's no santa claus,
easter bunny, or jesus either.
Mom?
I'm sorry, eric, all children
find out sooner or later.
You're serious?
There really is
no tooth fairy?
No honey,
it's just-
How could you lie
to me, mother?
Lie right to my face?
Oh eric, it's just
part of being a child.
How can i trust you?
How can i ever trust
anyone ever again, mother?
I guess... to
make it in this life,
I can only trust myself.
Myself, and willikins bear, of course.
Eric, eric, wait!
No, mother!
No more lies!
Dude, where's
the money?
There is no money.
No more money?
What are you
talking about, cartman?
We're only $167 away
from getting a sega.
I know!
Cartman,
what's going on?
You guys...
Oh, god,i don't even
know how to tell you this...
Tell us what?
You guys, there's no
tooth fairy, you guys.
There, i said it.
What do you mean,
there's no tooth fairy?
My mom's been giving us
the money all this time,
Your parents are the
ones that left you money.
Dude!
That can't be!
My parents
wouldn't lie to me.
But now my mom has
given me so much money
That she's bankrupt and
we're poor, like kenny.
Don't touch me, kenny.
You're wrong!
If my dad says that
something is real,
Then it's real!
Kyle, open your
eyes, man!
It's not true!
Oh, hello, son.
Dad, there is so
a tooth fairy, huh?
What? Oh!
Kyle, let's
have a little talk.
Oh my god,
youdidlie to me!
No, kyle, she's
just make-Believe.
Like peter pan.
Peter pan too!?
Kyle!
What about moses,
and abraham?
Well, they were
probably real.
Probably?
Is atlantis real?
Probably not.
Aahhh!
But kyle, adults
make up those things
Because they're
fun for children!
Fun for children?
Look at me, dad!
I don't even know
what's real anymore!
Aaahh!
Man, i can't believe
all our parents
Lied to us about
the tooth fairy.
What about dan rather,
do you think he's real?
Naw man, that's
just a tv show.
You guys, you guys!
I've figured it out!
What? That your
parents lied to you too?
Yeah, but it's okay,
We can still get
oursega dreamcast.
How?
Look, the tooth fairy
is all made up, right?
All made up, not
real, nothing's real.
So all we have to do,
Is go to a really
rich kid's house
Put our tooth
under his pillow
Wait for his parents to leave
him a whole butt-Load of money
Then sneak back in
and take it!
Woo-Hoo!
The kid'll
never even know.
Oh dude, that istits!
That is big fat
oprah tits, right there!
Oh my god,
what if i'm not real?
We can take the
bus to the city
There's super-Rich
people down there.
Yeah!
I mean, what if i'm just
part of my parent's reality?
C'mon, kyle!
What if this is all
just somebody's dream?
Wow! Look at the
size of these houses!
Told you, dude,
Cherry creek is the
richest part of denver.
I'll bet these kids
get 10 bucks a tooth
From the "tooth fairy".
Hey, that house
looks perfect!
There's obviously
kids living there.
Here, you can tell
this is the kids's window
'Cuz it's gotmegaman
stickers on it.
Cartman,once you're
in the kid's room,
Leave the tooth under the
pillow, then come back out.
We'll wait for the parents
to see it and leave money,
Then swing you
back in to grab it.
Got it.
This is the smartest
business venture, ever!
What the-?
Hey, what the hell
are you guys doing?
We're gonna sneak a tooth under
this rich kid's pillow
Then come back and
take the tooth fairy money
That his parents leave him.
Hey, you can't
do that!
Why not?
Because that's what
we're going to do!
Yeah, you ripped off
our idea.
What the hell are
you talking about?
We've been doing this
for over 2 years.
2 years?
Nice tooth fairy costume!
You think anybody'd
believe you in that?
It's better than
your dress!
You look like a bad
jennifer lopez nightmare.
How dare you!
Look, this is our turf,
You better scram before
the boss breaks your legs.
You scram,
we were here first!
What's going on?
Oh, it's the
tooth fairies!
Oh, nice going!
Now you woke him up.
Youwoke him up!
I don't have any
loose teeth, miss fairies.
But i have been
a very good boy.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Alright,
that does it!
C'mon we're going
to see the boss!
Who's the boss?
Loogie.
My associates here tell me you
were working cherry creek tonight.
Is that true?
Uh, yeah.
Right on
our turf, boss,
I ain't never seen
that kinda disre-
We were there first!
Kids been doing the tooth fairy
racket in this town for years
I do it just like
my big brother before me,
And my oldest brother
before that.
Damn it! And we thought
we were so original!
Let me ask you something,
You were gonna sneak a tooth
under this rich kid's pillow?
Then what?
What do you mean?
How were the kid's parents
going to know
There was a tooth
under their child's pillow?
Ha! You guys
don't even know
How the
tooth trade works!
What's the
tooth trade?
Look, any shmuck can
sneak through a window
Wearing a pretty dress.
The tooth racket
is much more involved.
We keep careful track
of what houses we've hit
So we don't hit the same ones
twice in less than 2 months.
We not only have to
sneak a tooth under the pillow
But leave a note for
mom and dad to see.
This is how we let
the parents know
To leave money
under the pillow.
Once the notes have been
placed in the last house,
We start all over,
going back to the first house.
But this time, all we
have to do is collect money.
And the kids never
know what hit 'em.
Wow!
Wow! Wow!
The hardest part
is getting teeth.
We've tried
various places...
Cemetaries...
Hockey games...
Anywhere we can
find them.
No!
The teeth we do
manage to acquire
Are then sorted according to
size, color and quality.
But there's
never enough teeth...
Never enough.
Amazing!
Man, that is tits!
And now my
only problem is:
What do i
do with you?
Raarr!
Tell you what,
how would you like to
Run the south park
tooth racket for me?
Oh, i don't know.
It's that or i can
cut off you penises.
Hmmm, work for you,
or have my penis cut off.
Work for you,
or have my...?
Cartman!
How much do we get
if we work for you?
I'll cut you
in at 2%
2% or have my
penis cut off...?
We're in!
Fellow dentists,
as you all know
We are still
having numerous reports
Of missing teeth
from all over the country
There are also reports of
missing tooth fairy money.
We believe that there can be only
one logical reason for all of this.
A giant half-Chicken,
half-Squirrel
That steals either teeth or
money from children as they sleep
In order to build
some kind of a giant nest
For its genetically superior and
potentially dangerous offspring.
We believe also,
That this creature would have
at least a mild understanding
Of algebra.
Uh, excuse me, i think
i have a more logical theory.
Well, by all means,
mr. Foley, enlighten us.
I think what we've got here
is a black market tooth racket.
Something where one group
is stealing the money and teeth
From another group
for a profit.
Ha ha! Ha ha! Ha ha!
Ha ha!
Ha ha! Ha ha!
Oh, mr. Foley, you realize
how ridiculous that sounds.
It's not ridiculous,
it's very possible!
I've seen it
happen before.
Where?
In montreal.
Ha ha! Ha ha! Ha ha!
Ha ha!
Ha ha! Ha ha!
And where, pray,
is this mon-Tree-Al?
Look, i know
how to handle this.
All we have to do is
bring down the kingpin
And the rest will fall.
You'll see, i'll have it taken
care of in a matter of weeks.
Very well, mr. Foley, you go
on your wild goose chase!
And meanwhile, we'll deal with
therealproblems at hand.
I will!
Anyway, the half-Chicken
half-Squirrel
Would most likely be
3 to 4½ feet tall
His large beak
is probably detachable
And works as
a flotation device.
Hello there,
children!
Hey, chef!
Hey, chefhey, chef!
We all want double
desserts today!
Oh, well, i'm afraid that the
school charges extra for that.
Oh yeah well, that
ain't nothin' but athang.
Oh my god!
There's got to be
at least $15 here.
That's right, keep
the change, my man.
Well, look at you
cute little crackers
With your money, and your fancy
clothes and your cellphones
It's almost
like you were-
Oh my god!
Children!
What have i
old you about drugs?
That there's a time
and a place for everything
And it's calledcollege.
That's right!
And the only thing worse than
doin' drugs, is dealin' drugs.
I'm gonna tell you about
when i was your age
And got offered drugs.
Oh, c'mon now.
Hey kid, you wanna
try some dope?
What?
C'mon,kid, don't you
wanna get high?
Hey man, i don't
need dope.
Let me sing you
a little song.
? I can't wait
until i grow up?
? And my wienie gets
big and strong?
? 'Cuz when it does,
i'm gonna find you?
? And make love to ya'
amanda, all night long?
? I'm gonna make love to
ya' amanda in about 10 years?
What?
What the hell is
he talkin' about?
And this toothpick
is gonna turn into an oak tree.
I'm gonna knock down
Uh, chef!
Knock you over
Chef! Knock you all around.
Chef!
Huh?
We're not
dealing drugs.
You're not?
No.
Oh, uh...
well, children,
Whatever you're doing,
just remember this:
Having money
may seem fun but...
Oh, never mind.
Thanks, chef.
Thanks, thanks, chef.
Damn,that little
amanda was fine.
I gotta look her up.
Dude, having this
much money is great!
Working for loogierules.
Yeah, but you know...
why do we need loogie?
We know how the trade works
Why don't we do it ourselves
and keep all the profits?
We can't do that, dude,
loogie will kick our asses.
Oh, what the hell is that
little pollock gonna do?
C'mon you guys, i say we
create our own mob crime family.
Dude, this book says
there could be
Infinite alternate realities
to every reality.
Sure, kyle.
They're what?
They're not gonna pay me?
Who the hell do they
think they are?
I want those
south park kids dead.
I want their
families dead.
I want their houses
burnt to the ground.
Oh, hi there mister.
My mommy and daddy
are out front if you need 'em.
Let's cut the crap, kid.
My name is tom foley, i'm with
the american dental association.
Sit down, mr. Foley,
you want some spaghetti?
No, thanks,
i just brushed.
I just wanted to let you
know that i'm on to you.
I told the a.D.A.
A thousand times,
I know nothing
about teeth.
I'm just an 8 year old boy who likes
climbing trees and playing in puddles.
I am going to find out
who the boss is,
And when i do
i'm gonna bust his ass
And everyone's ass
who helped hide his ass.
So, you brought me 400 ibs.
Of teeth from china?
That's right, yeah,
it's all top grade stuff, too.
These chinese kids are selling
their teeth for peanuts, see?
How much?
Well, tang lee wants 30,
But i can cut you
a deal for 28, yeah?
What do you say, huh?
Can i ask you
a question, weasel?
Well, why, sure, sure!
Do you think
i'm an idiot?
These are cat teeth,
you son-Of-A-Bitch!
You're trying to sell me
400 ibs. Of cat teeth!
Get outta my sight!
You lousy little scum!
What!
This is your
last chance, kid.
Either you give
the boss his cut,
Or else we're gonna throw
your pal into the river
Wearing concrete galoshes.
I ain't givin' you crap,
kenny's not afraid of you!
Oh, my god!
This book says that negative and
positive are the same thing.
That "real" and
"not real" are one!
He's not gonna do it?
Mprh mprmm mprh!
He's not gonna
do it, boss.
Well, then,
throw him in.
Alright, kid,
time to die.
No! No! No!
Aw, man, how deep
is the platt river?
...to which ms. Clinton replied,
"i don't even like vagina."
Finally, tonight
a human interest story.
Dan akawa is live.
Thanks, tom, i'm at the house
of little billy circlovich
Billy is in desperate need
of a bone marrow transplant,
Or he will
most certainly die.
Billy, how much more money do
you need for the transplant?
600-
Louder, billy,
we can't hear ya!
Just $600.
Well, that's
a lot of money.
How the hell are you
gonna get all that
In the short amount
of time you have left?
Well, i don't know.
Well, billy, i also understand
that you lost a tooth today.
Billy we want you to put that
tooth under your pillow tonight.
Because we have a feeling
that the tooth fairy
Is going to leave you
$600 for it.
Really? Really?
Yes, really, $600!
I might also mention that billy
lives in crestview apartments
Just of arapaho road, on
emporia street, back to you, tom.
How was that?
Perfect!
The trap is set.
Now, c'mon, you
really think anyone
Would fall for
something that stupid?
$600, you guys!
C'mon, get your stuff together,
this is gonna be tits!
Dude,this book says i don't
exist unless i think i do.
But what if i don't?
Will somebody take
those books away from him?
Be sure to put your loose tooth
under your pillow, billy.
Okay, mom.
Thank you for
helping, gentlemen.
If this sting
operation works,
Some bogus tooth fairy
should be showing up
To take the
sick kid's money.
When they touch the kid's pillow
an alarm will sound
And that's when you
hit the button, murphy,
And activate the lights.
Everybody got it?
Got it!
Duh, which button
do i hit again, boss?
Just kidding, you know how
there's always the dumb guy
In sting operations
in the movies,
You know, i was
just acting... oh.
Hurry up you guys,
We gotta get that
sick kid's money
Before luggie does.
I can't deal
with it stan,
All the stuff
i've been reading,
I really don't
think i exist.
Dude, just stop
thinking about it.
But i can't!
What if thinking about it
is the only thing
Keeping my
space-Time together?
Sometimes i can
see time slowing down,
My own existence fading.
Goodnight mom,
goodnight dad.
Alright, everyone
keep your eyes peeled.
I'm going
to bed now, mommy.
I put my tooth
under the pillow.
Do you really think
the tooth fairy
Will give me the money
for the transplant?
I think so, billy,
i think so.
I can't wait to feel
healthy and strong again.
Well, you're gonna have to wait
a little bit longer, billy
'Cuz that 600 bucks ismine.
"Light is a wave,
unless it is observed."
That means all matter
is just a wave.
Nothing's real!
Reality-
Oh god!
It's happening!
Kyle?
Something strange is
happening with the computers!
Well, well well,
what do we have here?
Aw, sh-T!
Did you bastards
really think
That you could
hide from me forever?
Klauski, put this butt-Wipe
out of his misery!
I got it!
The tooth fairy!
Let's move out!
Holy crap!
Give it up, kids, you're
surrounded by dentists.
It was a trap!
That's right!
And now it's all exposed,
you're through!
The only thing left to do is
haul you kids down to prison.
This is reality.
I am everywhere
and nowhere.
What the hell?
Kyle?
I am nothing,
and everything.
Grrrrrr!
Ah-Ha, i told you!
Let's get out of here!
Huh, that was
pretty wierd.
Jesus, the little sick kid
was a set-Up all along.
How could i
be so stupid?
I can't believe i fell
for such an obvious trap,
What the hell's
wrong with me?
Well, don't take it
too hard, dude,
That's what
grown-Ups do, they lie.
Lie right to your face.
Oh well, maybe it's good
my empire has fallen.
Really?
Yeah, i kinda wanted to play on the
flag football team this year, anyway.
So,you're not gonna
hurt us or nothin'?
Naw, in a way i'm just glad
the whole thing's over with.
Yeah, but you know,
i've learned something today.
The basis of all reasoning is
the mind's awareness of itself.
What we think, the external
objects we perceive,
Are all like actors
that come on and off stage.
But our consciousness, the stage
itself, is always present to us.
Tits!
Timmy!
Captions made possible by
comedy central
Captioned by
soundwriters™
www.tvsubtitles.net