1
00:00:07,550 --> 00:00:08,450
瑞克
Rick?

2
00:00:10,490 --> 00:00:12,610
我知道這聽起來很瘋狂
I know this sounds insane,

3
00:00:13,410 --> 00:00:15,400
但這就是個瘋狂的世界
but this is an insane world.

4
00:00:15,610 --> 00:00:18,970
我們必須先下手為強
We have to come for them before they come for us.

5
00:00:18,970 --> 00:00:20,120
就這么簡單
It's that simple.

6
00:00:22,460 --> 00:00:24,630
明天一切從這里開始
This is where it all starts tomorrow.

7
00:00:25,320 --> 00:00:27,100
托賓上卡車
Tobin gets in the truck,

8
00:00:27,420 --> 00:00:29,690
打開出口  我們就出發
opens the exit and we're off.

9
00:00:30,010 --> 00:00:33,630
他下車  在紅氣球處追上他的小隊
He hops out, catches up with his team at red

10
00:00:33,630 --> 00:00:35,940
待在路的西側
staying on the west side of the road.

11
00:00:36,090 --> 00:00:37,790
達里爾騎車
Daryl gets on his bike--

12
00:00:38,760 --> 00:00:39,710
你看見了嗎
You see that?

13
00:00:59,580 --> 00:01:02,630
缺口開了  現在就得行動
It's open! We got to do this now!

14
00:01:03,160 --> 00:01:04,630
現在就行動
We're doing this now!

15
00:01:04,760 --> 00:01:06,370
托賓的小隊  快出發
Tobin's group, get moving, go!

16
00:01:06,370 --> 00:01:08,080
不  瑞克  我們沒準備好  
No, Rick, we're not ready.

17
00:01:08,080 --> 00:01:09,200
薩沙  亞伯拉罕
Sasha! Abraham!

18
00:01:09,200 --> 00:01:10,620
說得對  我們直接開干
Damn straight, we'll do it live.

19
00:01:10,630 --> 00:01:11,780
你們在紅氣球處跟達里爾會合  
You meet Daryl at red.

20
00:01:11,780 --> 00:01:13,180
讓他帶它們通過障礙
Let him take them through the gauntlet.

21
00:01:13,180 --> 00:01:14,770
-好  我們在紅氣球處會合  -快
- Yeah, we meet at red. - Go!

22
00:01:23,590 --> 00:01:26,270
-瑞克  我去拖拉機店  -好  還有誰
- Rick, I'll hit the tractor place. - Okay, who else?

23
00:01:26,270 --> 00:01:27,800
我們得干掉它們  不然它們會讓尸群轉向
We got to take them out or they'll distract the horde.

24
00:01:27,800 --> 00:01:28,920
-我在  讓我幫忙  -不行
- I'm here, let me help. - No.

25
00:01:28,920 --> 00:01:30,840
-我在  -你必須全聽我的
- I'm here! - Do everything I say.

26
00:01:30,840 --> 00:01:33,350
-我會的  -瑞克  這本該是演習
- I will. - Rick, this was supposed to be a dry run.

27
00:01:33,350 --> 00:01:35,350
-達里爾  準備好  -它們來了
- Daryl, get ready. - They're coming.

28
00:01:39,250 --> 00:01:40,860
瑞克  我們還沒說完整個計劃
Rick, we haven't even gone through the whole plan.

29
00:01:40,860 --> 00:01:43,280
你想回去就回去  我們要結束這一切
You want to go back, go back. We're finishing this.

30
00:01:43,500 --> 00:01:46,370
托賓  聽我號令開車
Tobin, you hit it on my signal.

31
00:01:46,540 --> 00:01:49,740
它們要往家那邊去  我們別無選擇
They're heading for home. We don't have a choice.

32
00:01:49,860 --> 00:01:51,970
準備放照明彈
Get ready to hit the flares.

33
00:01:54,230 --> 00:01:55,350
放
Now!

34
00:02:13,700 --> 00:02:15,620
托賓  開車
Tobin, hit the truck!

35
00:03:17,770 --> 00:03:21,980
本藍光版外掛字幕由  風吹來的那片云  用WEB版調軸

36
00:03:17,770 --> 00:03:21,980
行尸走肉
『第六季  第一集』

37
00:03:23,120 --> 00:03:53,120
m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10m -13 -14 l 13 -14 l 13 12 l -13 12 l -13 -14

38
00:03:23,120 --> 00:03:53,120
m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10

39
00:03:23,120 --> 00:03:53,120
m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10

40
00:03:23,120 --> 00:04:03,120
■

41
00:03:23,120 --> 00:03:28,120
本字幕首發于字幕組網站
www.ZiMuZu.tv 歡迎交流

42
00:03:28,120 --> 00:03:33,120
翻譯  冰藍 Reginamoon 33來了 CS小明漫畫家

43
00:03:33,120 --> 00:03:38,120
翻譯  小十三 小酸奶 自然卷 艾瑞卡 送小孩

44
00:03:38,120 --> 00:03:43,120
校對 君君 送小孩 冰藍

45
00:03:41,260 --> 00:03:42,630
你錯了
You were wrong.

46
00:03:43,120 --> 00:03:48,120
時間軸  雪貴人 加森 濤濤 想念Gallifrey

47
00:03:48,120 --> 00:03:53,120
后期 送小哥 拉圖  總監 送小孩吃肉夾饃

48
00:03:53,120 --> 00:03:58,120
打開微信   掃描左側二維碼
或搜索公眾號:    ustvboom
了解最新影視字幕發布信息

49
00:03:53,120 --> 00:04:03,120
m 350 100 l 350 110 l 360 110 l 360 100 m 360 100 m 200 130 l 200 140 l 210 140 l 210 130 m 210 130 m 100 320 l 100 330 l 110 330 l 110 320 m 110 320 m 230 80 l 230 90 l 240 90 l 240 80 m 240 80 m 240 110 l 240 120 l 250 120 l 250 110 m 250 110 m 220 230 l 220 240 l 230 240 l 230 230 m 230 230 m 120 90 l 120 100 l 130 100 l 130 90 m 130 90 m 360 60 l 360 70 l 370 70 l 370 60 m 370 60 m 140 110 l 140 120 l 150 120 l 150 110 m 150 110 m 190 340 l 190 350 l 200 350 l 200 340 m 200 340 m 180 50 l 180 60 l 190 60 l 190 50 m 190 50 m 290 190 l 290 200 l 300 200 l 300 190 m 300 190 m 170 240 l 170 250 l 180 250 l 180 240 m 180 240 m 300 160 l 300 170 l 310 170 l 310 160 m 310 160 m 330 210 l 330 220 l 340 220 l 340 210 m 340 210 m 70 60 l 70 70 l 80 70 l 80 60 m 80 60 m 240 360 l 240 370 l 250 370 l 250 360 m 250 360 m 230 170 l 230 180 l 240 180 l 240 170 m 240 170 m 210 170 l 210 180 l 220 180 l 220 170 m 220 170 m 350 250 l 350 260 l 360 260 l 360 250 m 360 250 m 240 180 l 240 190 l 250 190 l 250 180 m 250 180 m 220 140 l 220 150 l 230 150 l 230 140 m 230 140 m 270 230 l 270 240 l 280 240 l 280 230 m 280 230 m 250 190 l 250 200 l 260 200 l 260 190 m 260 190 m 120 160 l 120 170 l 130 170 l 130 160 m 130 160 m 360 290 l 360 300 l 370 300 l 370 290 m 370 290 m 260 160 l 260 170 l 270 170 l 270 160 m 270 160 m 270 130 l 270 140 l 280 140 l 280 130 m 280 130 m 120 220 l 120 230 l 130 230 l 130 220 m 130 220 m 150 190 l 150 200 l 160 200 l 160 190 m 160 190 m 160 120 l 160 130 l 170 130 l 170 120 m 170 120 m 170 170 l 170 180 l 180 180 l 180 170 m 180 170 m 40 180 l 40 190 l 50 190 l 50 180 m 50 180 m 310 100 l 310 110 l 320 110 l 320 100 m 320 100 m 60 160 l 60 170 l 70 170 l 70 160 m 70 160 m 330 80 l 330 90 l 340 90 l 340 80 m 340 80 m 70 210 l 70 220 l 80 220 l 80 210 m 80 210 m 100 180 l 100 190 l 110 190 l 110 180 m 110 180 m 110 190 l 110 200 l 120 200 l 120 190 m 120 190 m 350 220 l 350 230 l 360 230 l 360 220 m 360 220 m 220 90 l 220 100 l 230 100 l 230 90 m 230 90 m 100 360 l 100 370 l 110 370 l 110 360 m 110 360 m 250 120 l 250 130 l 260 130 l 260 120 m 260 120 m 210 280 l 210 290 l 220 290 l 220 280 m 220 280 m 260 110 l 260 120 l 270 120 l 270 110 m 270 110 m 140 130 l 140 140 l 150 140 l 150 130 m 150 130 m 120 290 l 120 300 l 130 300 l 130 290 m 130 290 m 280 320 l 280 330 l 290 330 l 290 320 m 290 320 m 180 230 l 180 240 l 190 240 l 190 230 m 190 230 m 140 230 l 140 240 l 150 240 l 150 230 m 150 230 m 190 140 l 190 150 l 200 150 l 200 140 m 200 140 m 150 300 l 150 310 l 160 310 l 160 300 m 160 300 m 300 340 l 300 350 l 310 350 l 310 340 m 310 340 m 40 90 l 40 100 l 50 100 l 50 90 m 50 90 m 280 60 l 280 70 l 290 70 l 290 60 m 290 60 m 310 350 l 310 360 l 320 360 l 320 350 m 320 350 m 50 40 l 50 50 l 60 50 l 60 40 m 60 40 m 80 150 l 80 160 l 90 160 l 90 150 m 90 150 m 320 280 l 320 290 l 330 290 l 330 280 m 330 280 m 90 140 l 90 150 l 100 150 l 100 140 m 100 140 m 100 50 l 100 60 l 110 60 l 110 50 m 110 50 m 340 60 l 340 70 l 350 70 l 350 60 m 350 60 m 230 310 l 230 320 l 240 320 l 240 310 m 240 310 m 350 310 l 350 320 l 360 320 l 360 310 m 360 310 m 100 310 l 100 320 l 110 320 l 110 310 m 110 310 m 230 50 l 230 60 l 240 60 l 240 50 m 240 50 m 360 270 l 360 280 l 370 280 l 370 270 m 370 270 m 220 260 l 220 270 l 230 270 l 230 260 m 230 260 m 160 360 l 160 370 l 170 370 l 170 360 m 170 360 m 120 40 l 120 50 l 130 50 l 130 40 m 130 40 m 140 300 l 140 310 l 150 310 l 150 300 m 150 300 m 40 320 l 40 330 l 50 330 l 50 320 m 50 320 m 160 240 l 160 250 l 170 250 l 170 240 m 170 240 m 310 240 l 310 250 l 320 250 l 320 240 m 320 240 m 170 290 l 170 300 l 180 300 l 180 290 m 180 290 m 320 270 l 320 280 l 330 280 l 330 270 m 330 270 m 60 340 l 60 350 l 70 350 l 70 340 m 70 340 m 300 70 l 300 80 l 310 80 l 310 70 m 310 70 m 330 260 l 330 270 l 340 270 l 340 260 m 340 260 m 80 280 l 80 290 l 90 290 l 90 280 m 90 280 m 230 360 l 230 370 l 240 370 l 240 360 m 240 360 m 350 40 l 350 50 l 360 50 l 360 40 m 360 40 m 100 220 l 100 230 l 110 230 l 110 220 m 110 220 m 260 210 l 260 220 l 270 220 l 270 210 m 270 210 m 270 240 l 270 250 l 280 250 l 280 240 m 280 240 m 250 80 l 250 90 l 260 90 l 260 80 m 260 80 m 120 110 l 120 120 l 130 120 l 130 110 m 130 110 m 360 80 l 360 90 l 370 90 l 370 80 m 370 80 m 260 150 l 260 160 l 270 160 l 270 150 m 270 150 m 190 280 l 190 290 l 200 290 l 200 280 m 200 280 m 280 200 l 280 210 l 290 210 l 290 200 m 290 200 m 180 110 l 180 120 l 190 120 l 190 110 m 190 110 m 160 230 l 160 240 l 170 240 l 170 230 m 170 230 m 50 220 l 50 230 l 60 230 l 60 220 m 60 220 m 170 220 l 170 230 l 180 230 l 180 220 m 180 220 m 300 140 l 300 150 l 310 150 l 310 140 m 310 140 m 70 80 l 70 90 l 80 90 l 80 80 m 80 80 m 320 80 l 320 90 l 330 90 l 330 80 m 330 80 m 350 130 l 350 140 l 360 140 l 360 130 m 360 130 m 90 100 l 90 110 l 100 110 l 100 100 m 100 100 m 330 130 l 330 140 l 340 140 l 340 130 m 340 130 m 210 70 l 210 80 l 220 80 l 220 70 m 220 70 m 350 270 l 350 280 l 360 280 l 360 270 m 360 270 m 90 360 l 90 370 l 100 370 l 100 360 m 100 360 m 240 120 l 240 130 l 250 130 l 250 120 m 250 120 m 220 120 l 220 130 l 230 130 l 230 120 m 230 120 m 270 150 l 270 160 l 280 160 l 280 150 m 280 150 m 130 210 l 130 220 l 140 220 l 140 210 m 140 210 m 180 180 l 180 190 l 190 190 l 190 180 m 190 180 m 290 260 l 290 270 l 300 270 l 300 260 m 300 260 m 190 190 l 190 200 l 200 200 l 200 190 m 200 190 m 170 150 l 170 160 l 180 160 l 180 150 m 180 150 m 40 40 l 40 50 l 50 50 l 50 40 m 50 40 m 310 280 l 310 290 l 320 290 l 320 280 m 320 280 m 50 170 l 50 180 l 60 180 l 60 170 m 60 170 m 80 180 l 80 190 l 90 190 l 90 180 m 90 180 m 320 70 l 320 80 l 330 80 l 330 70 m 330 70 m 60 140 l 60 150 l 70 150 l 70 140 m 70 140 m 330 60 l 330 70 l 340 70 l 340 60 m 340 60 m 70 230 l 70 240 l 80 240 l 80 230 m 80 230 m 100 160 l 100 170 l 110 170 l 110 160 m 110 160 m 340 290 l 340 300 l 350 300 l 350 290 m 350 290 m 110 130 l 110 140 l 120 140 l 120 130 m 120 130 m 240 270 l 240 280 l 250 280 l 250 270 m 250 270 m 200 350 l 200 360 l 210 360 l 210 350 m 210 350 m 250 260 l 250 270 l 260 270 l 260 260 m 260 260 m 210 340 l 210 350 l 220 350 l 220 340 m 220 340 m 260 90 l 260 100 l 270 100 l 270 90 m 270 90 m 220 330 l 220 340 l 230 340 l 230 330 m 230 330 m 270 40 l 270 50 l 280 50 l 280 40 m 280 40 m 360 120 l 360 130 l 370 130 l 370 120 m 370 120 m 130 300 l 130 310 l 140 310 l 140 300 m 140 300 m 280 340 l 280 350 l 290 350 l 290 340 m 290 340 m 180 210 l 180 220 l 190 220 l 190 210 m 190 210 m 190 240 l 190 250 l 200 250 l 200 240 m 200 240 m 320 360 l 320 370 l 330 370 l 330 360 m 330 360 m 300 320 l 300 330 l 310 330 l 310 320 m 310 320 m 160 350 l 160 360 l 170 360 l 170 350 m 170 350 m 50 100 l 50 110 l 60 110 l 60 100 m 60 100 m 320 300 l 320 310 l 330 310 l 330 300 m 330 300 m 300 100 l 300 110 l 310 110 l 310 100 m 310 100 m 330 310 l 330 320 l 340 320 l 340 310 m 340 310 m 340 40 l 340 50 l 350 50 l 350 40 m 350 40 m 230 330 l 230 340 l 240 340 l 240 330 m 240 330 m 300 360 l 300 370 l 310 370 l 310 360 m 310 360 m 240 340 l 240 350 l 250 350 l 250 340 m 250 340 m 200 260 l 200 270 l 210 270 l 210 260 m 210 260 m 250 350 l 250 360 l 260 360 l 260 350 m 260 350 m 230 70 l 230 80 l 240 80 l 240 70 m 240 70 m 210 270 l 210 280 l 220 280 l 220 270 m 220 270 m 260 320 l 260 330 l 270 330 l 270 320 m 270 320 m 220 240 l 220 250 l 230 250 l 230 240 m 230 240 m 270 290 l 270 300 l 280 300 l 280 290 m 280 290 m 130 70 l 130 80 l 140 80 l 140 70 m 140 70 m 180 280 l 180 290 l 190 290 l 190 280 m 190 280 m 140 280 l 140 290 l 150 290 l 150 280 m 150 280 m 150 250 l 150 260 l 160 260 l 160 250 m 160 250 m 40 340 l 40 350 l 50 350 l 50 340 m 50 340 m 180 60 l 180 70 l 190 70 l 190 60 m 190 60 m 160 260 l 160 270 l 170 270 l 170 260 m 170 260 m 170 270 l 170 280 l 180 280 l 180 270 m 180 270 m 60 320 l 60 330 l 70 330 l 70 320 m 70 320 m 300 50 l 300 60 l 310 60 l 310 50 m 310 50 m 330 240 l 330 250 l 340 250 l 340 240 m 340 240 m 310 160 l 310 170 l 320 170 l 320 160 m 320 160 m 80 300 l 80 310 l 90 310 l 90 300 m 90 300 m 320 190 l 320 200 l 330 200 l 330 190 m 330 190 m 100 200 l 100 210 l 110 210 l 110 200 m 110 200 m 250 280 l 250 290 l 260 290 l 260 280 m 260 280 m 80 360 l 80 370 l 90 370 l 90 360 m 90 360 m 210 120 l 210 130 l 220 130 l 220 120 m 220 120 m 110 250 l 110 260 l 120 260 l 120 250 m 120 250 m 220 190 l 220 200 l 230 200 l 230 190 m 230 190 m 270 260 l 270 270 l 280 270 l 280 260 m 280 260 m 250 60 l 250 70 l 260 70 l 260 60 m 260 60 m 360 100 l 360 110 l 370 110 l 370 100 m 370 100 m 260 130 l 260 140 l 270 140 l 270 130 m 270 130 m 130 80 l 130 90 l 140 90 l 140 80 m 140 80 m 270 160 l 270 170 l 280 170 l 280 160 m 280 160 m 140 70 l 140 80 l 150 80 l 150 70 m 150 70 m 190 300 l 190 310 l 200 310 l 200 300 m 200 300 m 40 250 l 40 260 l 50 260 l 50 250 m 50 250 m 50 200 l 50 210 l 60 210 l 60 200 m 60 200 m 290 230 l 290 240 l 300 240 l 300 230 m 300 230 m 190 40 l 190 50 l 200 50 l 200 40 m 200 40 m 170 200 l 170 210 l 180 210 l 180 200 m 180 200 m 60 270 l 60 280 l 70 280 l 70 270 m 70 270 m 300 120 l 300 130 l 310 130 l 310 120 m 310 120 m 40 150 l 40 160 l 50 160 l 50 150 m 50 150 m 70 100 l 70 110 l 80 110 l 80 100 m 80 100 m 320 100 l 320 110 l 330 110 l 330 100 m 330 100 m 200 80 l 200 90 l 210 90 l 210 80 m 210 80 m 240 140 l 240 150 l 250 150 l 250 140 m 250 140 m 220 100 l 220 110 l 230 110 l 230 100 m 230 100 m 140 360 l 140 370 l 150 370 l 150 360 m 150 360 m 130 170 l 130 180 l 140 180 l 140 170 m 140 170 m 270 90 l 270 100 l 280 100 l 280 90 m 280 90 m 140 140 l 140 150 l 150 150 l 150 140 m 150 140 m 120 260 l 120 270 l 130 270 l 130 260 m 130 260 m 280 290 l 280 300 l 290 300 l 290 290 m 290 290 m 150 290 l 150 300 l 160 300 l 160 290 m 160 290 m 40 60 l 40 70 l 50 70 l 50 60 m 50 60 m 70 190 l 70 200 l 80 200 l 80 190 m 80 190 m 80 120 l 80 130 l 90 130 l 90 120 m 90 120 m 320 330 l 320 340 l 330 340 l 330 330 m 330 330 m 90 170 l 90 180 l 100 180 l 100 170 m 100 170 m 330 40 l 330 50 l 340 50 l 340 40 m 340 40 m 70 250 l 70 260 l 80 260 l 80 250 m 80 250 m 290 360 l 290 370 l 300 370 l 300 360 m 300 360 m 100 60 l 100 70 l 110 70 l 110 60 m 110 60 m 230 260 l 230 270 l 240 270 l 240 260 m 240 260 m 220 50 l 220 60 l 230 60 l 230 50 m 230 50 m 200 210 l 200 220 l 210 220 l 210 210 m 210 210 m 360 240 l 360 250 l 370 250 l 370 240 m 370 240 m 260 310 l 260 320 l 270 320 l 270 310 m 270 310 m 180 270 l 180 280 l 190 280 l 190 270 m 190 270 m 140 350 l 140 360 l 150 360 l 150 350 m 150 350 m 300 300 l 300 310 l 310 310 l 310 300 m 310 300 m 280 100 l 280 110 l 290 110 l 290 100 m 290 100 m 170 320 l 170 330 l 180 330 l 180 320 m 180 320 m 320 240 l 320 250 l 330 250 l 330 240 m 330 240 m 60 70 l 60 80 l 70 80 l 70 70 m 70 70 m 300 80 l 300 90 l 310 90 l 310 80 m 310 80 m 70 300 l 70 310 l 80 310 l 80 300 m 80 300 m 310 130 l 310 140 l 320 140 l 320 130 m 320 130 m 100 90 l 100 100 l 110 100 l 110 90 m 110 90 m 340 100 l 340 110 l 350 110 l 350 100 m 350 100 m 80 330 l 80 340 l 90 340 l 90 330 m 90 330 m 90 200 l 90 210 l 100 210 l 100 200 m 100 200 m 240 280 l 240 290 l 250 290 l 250 280 m 250 280 m 70 360 l 70 370 l 80 370 l 80 360 m 80 360 m 200 120 l 200 130 l 210 130 l 210 120 m 210 120 m 100 350 l 100 360 l 110 360 l 110 350 m 110 350 m 250 330 l 250 340 l 260 340 l 260 330 m 260 330 m 260 220 l 260 230 l 270 230 l 270 220 m 270 220 m 240 100 l 240 110 l 250 110 l 250 100 m 250 100 m 250 110 l 250 120 l 260 120 l 260 110 m 260 110 m 120 80 l 120 90 l 130 90 l 130 80 m 130 80 m 360 50 l 360 60 l 370 60 l 370 50 m 370 50 m 180 340 l 180 350 l 190 350 l 190 340 m 190 340 m 140 100 l 140 110 l 150 110 l 150 100 m 150 100 m 190 350 l 190 360 l 200 360 l 200 350 m 200 350 m 40 200 l 40 210 l 50 210 l 50 200 m 50 200 m 280 170 l 280 180 l 290 180 l 290 170 m 290 170 m 180 40 l 180 50 l 190 50 l 190 40 m 190 40 m 290 120 l 290 130 l 300 130 l 300 120 m 300 120 m 190 90 l 190 100 l 200 100 l 200 90 m 200 90 m 60 300 l 60 310 l 70 310 l 70 300 m 70 300 m 300 190 l 300 200 l 310 200 l 310 190 m 310 190 m 330 220 l 330 230 l 340 230 l 340 220 m 340 220 m 70 70 l 70 80 l 80 80 l 80 70 m 80 70 m 310 180 l 310 190 l 320 190 l 320 180 m 320 180 m 340 130 l 340 140 l 350 140 l 350 130 m 350 130 m 80 80 l 80 90 l 90 90 l 90 80 m 90 80 m 350 160 l 350 170 l 360 170 l 360 160 m 360 160 m 330 160 l 330 170 l 340 170 l 340 160 m 340 160 m 200 190 l 200 200 l 210 200 l 210 190 m 210 190 m 100 260 l 100 270 l 110 270 l 110 260 m 110 260 m 260 250 l 260 260 l 270 260 l 270 250 m 270 250 m 240 170 l 240 180 l 250 180 l 250 170 m 250 170 m 220 170 l 220 180 l 230 180 l 230 170 m 230 170 m 120 150 l 120 160 l 130 160 l 130 150 m 130 150 m 130 140 l 130 150 l 140 150 l 140 140 m 140 140 m 270 180 l 270 190 l 280 190 l 280 180 m 280 180 m 290 210 l 290 220 l 300 220 l 300 210 m 300 210 m 60 250 l 60 260 l 70 260 l 70 250 m 70 250 m 80 70 l 80 80 l 90 80 l 90 70 m 90 70 m 320 40 l 320 50 l 330 50 l 330 40 m 330 40 m 280 360 l 280 370 l 290 370 l 290 360 m 290 360 m 200 100 l 200 110 l 210 110 l 210 100 m 210 100 m 230 230 l 230 240 l 240 240 l 240 230 m 240 230 m 210 110 l 210 120 l 220 120 l 220 110 m 220 110 m 240 240 l 240 250 l 250 250 l 250 240 m 250 240 m 200 320 l 200 330 l 210 330 l 210 320 m 210 320 m 250 130 l 250 140 l 260 140 l 260 130 m 260 130 m 210 290 l 210 300 l 220 300 l 220 290 m 220 290 m 260 100 l 260 110 l 270 110 l 270 100 m 270 100 m 140 120 l 140 130 l 150 130 l 150 120 m 150 120 m 280 310 l 280 320 l 290 320 l 290 310 m 290 310 m 180 220 l 180 230 l 190 230 l 190 220 m 190 220 m 160 100 l 160 110 l 170 110 l 170 100 m 170 100 m 140 220 l 140 230 l 150 230 l 150 220 m 150 220 m 190 150 l 190 160 l 200 160 l 200 150 m 200 150 m 150 310 l 150 320 l 160 320 l 160 310 m 160 310 m 40 80 l 40 90 l 50 90 l 50 80 m 50 80 m 280 50 l 280 60 l 290 60 l 290 50 m 290 50 m 310 320 l 310 330 l 320 330 l 320 320 m 320 320 m 60 100 l 60 110 l 70 110 l 70 100 m 70 100 m 330 340 l 330 350 l 340 350 l 340 340 m 340 340 m 70 270 l 70 280 l 80 280 l 80 270 m 80 270 m 100 40 l 100 50 l 110 50 l 110 40 m 110 40 m 340 330 l 340 340 l 350 340 l 350 330 m 350 330 m 80 200 l 80 210 l 90 210 l 90 200 m 90 200 m 60 360 l 60 370 l 70 370 l 70 360 m 70 360 m 350 280 l 350 290 l 360 290 l 360 280 m 360 280 m 240 230 l 240 240 l 250 240 l 250 230 m 250 230 m 200 230 l 200 240 l 210 240 l 210 230 m 210 230 m 100 300 l 100 310 l 110 310 l 110 300 m 110 300 m 250 220 l 250 230 l 260 230 l 260 220 m 260 220 m 210 220 l 210 230 l 220 230 l 220 220 m 220 220 m 360 160 l 360 170 l 370 170 l 370 160 m 370 160 m 140 330 l 140 340 l 150 340 l 150 330 m 150 330 m 170 40 l 170 50 l 180 50 l 180 40 m 180 40 m 150 200 l 150 210 l 160 210 l 160 200 m 160 200 m 300 280 l 300 290 l 310 290 l 310 280 m 310 280 m 40 310 l 40 320 l 50 320 l 50 310 m 50 310 m 280 120 l 280 130 l 290 130 l 290 120 m 290 120 m 310 250 l 310 260 l 320 260 l 320 250 m 320 250 m 50 300 l 50 310 l 60 310 l 60 300 m 60 300 m 320 260 l 320 270 l 330 270 l 330 260 m 330 260 m 300 60 l 300 70 l 310 70 l 310 60 m 310 60 m 70 320 l 70 330 l 80 330 l 80 320 m 80 320 m 340 80 l 340 90 l 350 90 l 350 80 m 350 80 m 240 300 l 240 310 l 250 310 l 250 300 m 250 300 m 100 330 l 100 340 l 110 340 l 110 330 m 110 330 m 230 110 l 230 120 l 240 120 l 240 110 m 240 110 m 120 360 l 120 370 l 130 370 l 130 360 m 130 360 m 260 200 l 260 210 l 270 210 l 270 200 m 270 200 m 270 250 l 270 260 l 280 260 l 280 250 m 280 250 m 250 90 l 250 100 l 260 100 l 260 90 m 260 90 m 120 100 l 120 110 l 130 110 l 130 100 m 130 100 m 360 70 l 360 80 l 370 80 l 370 70 m 370 70 m 180 320 l 180 330 l 190 330 l 190 320 m 190 320 m 190 290 l 190 300 l 200 300 l 200 290 m 200 290 m 40 220 l 40 230 l 50 230 l 50 220 m 50 220 m 280 190 l 280 200 l 290 200 l 290 190 m 290 190 m 180 100 l 180 110 l 190 110 l 190 100 m 190 100 m 160 220 l 160 230 l 170 230 l 170 220 m 170 220 m 290 180 l 290 190 l 300 190 l 300 180 m 300 180 m 40 120 l 40 130 l 50 130 l 50 120 m 50 120 m 330 200 l 330 210 l 340 210 l 340 200 m 340 200 m 310 40 l 310 50 l 320 50 l 320 40 m 320 40 m 80 100 l 80 110 l 90 110 l 90 100 m 90 100 m 350 180 l 350 190 l 360 190 l 360 180 m 360 180 m 330 140 l 330 150 l 340 150 l 340 140 m 340 140 m 200 50 l 200 60 l 210 60 l 210 50 m 210 50 m 100 240 l 100 250 l 110 250 l 110 240 m 110 240 m 340 210 l 340 220 l 350 220 l 350 210 m 350 210 m 110 210 l 110 220 l 120 220 l 120 210 m 120 210 m 270 220 l 270 230 l 280 230 l 280 220 m 280 220 m 250 180 l 250 190 l 260 190 l 260 180 m 260 180 m 120 170 l 120 180 l 130 180 l 130 170 m 130 170 m 270 120 l 270 130 l 280 130 l 280 120 m 280 120 m 140 190 l 140 200 l 150 200 l 150 190 m 150 190 m 180 130 l 180 140 l 190 140 l 190 130 m 190 130 m 160 130 l 160 140 l 170 140 l 170 130 m 170 130 m 290 270 l 290 280 l 300 280 l 300 270 m 300 270 m 170 160 l 170 170 l 180 170 l 180 160 m 180 160 m 300 240 l 300 250 l 310 250 l 310 240 m 310 240 m 70 140 l 70 150 l 80 150 l 80 140 m 80 140 m 50 180 l 50 190 l 60 190 l 60 180 m 60 180 m 80 170 l 80 180 l 90 180 l 90 170 m 90 170 m 320 60 l 320 70 l 330 70 l 330 60 m 330 60 m 90 40 l 90 50 l 100 50 l 100 40 m 100 40 m 330 70 l 330 80 l 340 80 l 340 70 m 340 70 m 70 200 l 70 210 l 80 210 l 80 200 m 80 200 m 50 360 l 50 370 l 60 370 l 60 360 m 60 360 m 230 250 l 230 260 l 240 260 l 240 250 m 240 250 m 210 90 l 210 100 l 220 100 l 220 90 m 220 90 m 350 330 l 350 340 l 360 340 l 360 330 m 360 330 m 220 60 l 220 70 l 230 70 l 230 60 m 230 60 m 250 270 l 250 280 l 260 280 l 260 270 m 260 270 m 210 350 l 210 360 l 220 360 l 220 350 m 220 350 m 260 80 l 260 90 l 270 90 l 270 80 m 270 80 m 120 300 l 120 310 l 130 310 l 130 300 m 130 300 m 150 110 l 150 120 l 160 120 l 160 110 m 160 110 m 130 310 l 130 320 l 140 320 l 140 310 m 140 310 m 280 330 l 280 340 l 290 340 l 290 330 m 290 330 m 290 280 l 290 290 l 300 290 l 300 280 m 300 280 m 170 90 l 170 100 l 180 100 l 180 90 m 180 90 m 150 330 l 150 340 l 160 340 l 160 330 m 160 330 m 300 350 l 300 360 l 310 360 l 310 350 m 310 350 m 40 100 l 40 110 l 50 110 l 50 100 m 50 100 m 310 340 l 310 350 l 320 350 l 320 340 m 320 340 m 320 290 l 320 300 l 330 300 l 330 290 m 330 290 m 60 80 l 60 90 l 70 90 l 70 80 m 70 80 m 330 320 l 330 330 l 340 330 l 340 320 m 340 320 m 100 100 l 100 110 l 110 110 l 110 100 m 110 100 m 340 70 l 340 80 l 350 80 l 350 70 m 350 70 m 350 300 l 350 310 l 360 310 l 360 300 m 360 300 m 240 330 l 240 340 l 250 340 l 250 330 m 250 330 m 200 250 l 200 260 l 210 260 l 210 250 m 210 250 m 100 280 l 100 290 l 110 290 l 110 280 m 110 280 m 250 200 l 250 210 l 260 210 l 260 200 m 260 200 m 210 200 l 210 210 l 220 210 l 220 200 m 220 200 m 260 350 l 260 360 l 270 360 l 270 350 m 270 350 m 270 340 l 270 350 l 280 350 l 280 340 m 280 340 m 130 320 l 130 330 l 140 330 l 140 320 m 140 320 m 190 220 l 190 230 l 200 230 l 200 220 m 200 220 m 40 330 l 40 340 l 50 340 l 50 330 m 50 330 m 280 140 l 280 150 l 290 150 l 290 140 m 290 140 m 160 250 l 160 260 l 170 260 l 170 250 m 170 250 m 310 270 l 310 280 l 320 280 l 320 270 m 320 270 m 50 280 l 50 290 l 60 290 l 60 280 m 60 280 m 290 150 l 290 160 l 300 160 l 300 150 m 300 150 m 170 280 l 170 290 l 180 290 l 180 280 m 180 280 m 320 200 l 320 210 l 330 210 l 330 200 m 330 200 m 300 40 l 300 50 l 310 50 l 310 40 m 310 40 m 70 340 l 70 350 l 80 350 l 80 340 m 80 340 m 310 170 l 310 180 l 320 180 l 320 170 m 320 170 m 200 160 l 200 170 l 210 170 l 210 160 m 210 160 m 250 290 l 250 300 l 260 300 l 260 290 m 260 290 m 210 130 l 210 140 l 220 140 l 220 130 m 220 130 m 260 260 l 260 270 l 270 270 l 270 260 m 270 260 m 240 60 l 240 70 l 250 70 l 250 60 m 250 60 m 220 180 l 220 190 l 230 190 l 230 180 m 230 180 m 250 70 l 250 80 l 260 80 l 260 70 m 260 70 m 120 120 l 120 130 l 130 130 l 130 120 m 130 120 m 360 90 l 360 100 l 370 100 l 370 90 m 370 90 m 260 120 l 260 130 l 270 130 l 270 120 m 270 120 m 130 90 l 130 100 l 140 100 l 140 90 m 140 90 m 190 310 l 190 320 l 200 320 l 200 310 m 200 310 m 150 150 l 150 160 l 160 160 l 160 150 m 160 150 m 40 240 l 40 250 l 50 250 l 50 240 m 50 240 m 50 210 l 50 220 l 60 220 l 60 210 m 60 210 m 290 160 l 290 170 l 300 170 l 300 160 m 300 160 m 170 210 l 170 220 l 180 220 l 180 210 m 180 210 m 60 260 l 60 270 l 70 270 l 70 260 m 70 260 m 40 140 l 40 150 l 50 150 l 50 140 m 50 140 m 50 150 l 50 160 l 60 160 l 60 150 m 60 150 m 80 40 l 80 50 l 90 50 l 90 40 m 90 40 m 40 360 l 40 370 l 50 370 l 50 360 m 50 360 m 330 120 l 330 130 l 340 130 l 340 120 m 340 120 m 200 70 l 200 80 l 210 80 l 210 70 m 210 70 m 100 140 l 100 150 l 110 150 l 110 140 m 110 140 m 210 60 l 210 70 l 220 70 l 220 60 m 220 60 m 110 230 l 110 240 l 120 240 l 120 230 m 120 230 m 350 260 l 350 270 l 360 270 l 360 260 m 360 260 m 240 130 l 240 140 l 250 140 l 250 130 m 250 130 m 220 130 l 220 140 l 230 140 l 230 130 m 230 130 m 200 290 l 200 300 l 210 300 l 210 290 m 210 290 m 360 320 l 360 330 l 370 330 l 370 320 m 370 320 m 260 70 l 260 80 l 270 80 l 270 70 m 270 70 m 130 180 l 130 190 l 140 190 l 140 180 m 140 180 m 270 140 l 270 150 l 280 150 l 280 140 m 280 140 m 140 170 l 140 180 l 150 180 l 150 170 m 150 170 m 120 250 l 120 260 l 130 260 l 130 250 m 130 250 m 280 280 l 280 290 l 290 290 l 290 280 m 290 280 m 140 270 l 140 280 l 150 280 l 150 270 m 150 270 m 190 180 l 190 190 l 200 190 l 200 180 m 200 180 m 170 140 l 170 150 l 180 150 l 180 140 m 180 140 m 300 220 l 300 230 l 310 230 l 310 220 m 310 220 m 40 50 l 40 60 l 50 60 l 50 50 m 50 50 m 320 320 l 320 330 l 330 330 l 330 320 m 330 320 m 60 150 l 60 160 l 70 160 l 70 150 m 70 150 m 90 180 l 90 190 l 100 190 l 100 180 m 100 180 m 340 340 l 340 350 l 350 350 l 350 340 m 350 340 m 80 250 l 80 260 l 90 260 l 90 250 m 90 250 m 230 270 l 230 280 l 240 280 l 240 270 m 240 270 m 110 120 l 110 130 l 120 130 l 120 120 m 120 120 m 260 360 l 260 370 l 270 370 l 270 360 m 270 360 m 240 200 l 240 210 l 250 210 l 250 200 m 250 200 m 200 200 l 200 210 l 210 210 l 210 200 m 210 200 m 220 300 l 220 310 l 230 310 l 230 300 m 230 300 m 120 320 l 120 330 l 130 330 l 130 320 m 130 320 m 360 130 l 360 140 l 370 140 l 370 130 m 370 130 m 130 290 l 130 300 l 140 300 l 140 290 m 140 290 m 280 350 l 280 360 l 290 360 l 290 350 m 290 350 m 180 260 l 180 270 l 190 270 l 190 260 m 190 260 m 160 60 l 160 70 l 170 70 l 170 60 m 170 60 m 300 330 l 300 340 l 310 340 l 310 330 m 310 330 m 40 280 l 40 290 l 50 290 l 50 280 m 50 280 m 280 90 l 280 100 l 290 100 l 290 90 m 290 90 m 160 280 l 160 290 l 170 290 l 170 280 m 170 280 m 170 330 l 170 340 l 180 340 l 180 330 m 180 330 m 320 310 l 320 320 l 330 320 l 330 310 m 330 310 m 60 60 l 60 70 l 70 70 l 70 60 m 70 60 m 330 300 l 330 310 l 340 310 l 340 300 m 340 300 m 210 360 l 210 370 l 220 370 l 220 360 m 220 360 m 100 80 l 100 90 l 110 90 l 110 80 m 110 80 m 80 320 l 80 330 l 90 330 l 90 320 m 90 320 m 230 320 l 230 330 l 240 330 l 240 320 m 240 320 m 90 210 l 90 220 l 100 220 l 100 210 m 100 210 m 100 340 l 100 350 l 110 350 l 110 340 m 110 340 m 230 60 l 230 70 l 240 70 l 240 60 m 240 60 m 240 90 l 240 100 l 250 100 l 250 90 m 250 90 m 120 70 l 120 80 l 130 80 l 130 70 m 130 70 m 360 40 l 360 50 l 370 50 l 370 40 m 370 40 m 130 60 l 130 70 l 140 70 l 140 60 m 140 60 m 180 290 l 180 300 l 190 300 l 190 290 m 190 290 m 190 320 l 190 330 l 200 330 l 200 320 m 200 320 m 150 240 l 150 250 l 160 250 l 160 240 m 160 240 m 40 350 l 40 360 l 50 360 l 50 350 m 50 350 m 280 160 l 280 170 l 290 170 l 290 160 m 290 160 m 160 270 l 160 280 l 170 280 l 170 270 m 170 270 m 170 260 l 170 270 l 180 270 l 180 260 m 180 260 m 60 330 l 60 340 l 70 340 l 70 330 m 70 330 m 70 40 l 70 50 l 80 50 l 80 40 m 80 40 m 320 120 l 320 130 l 330 130 l 330 120 m 330 120 m 360 360 l 360 370 l 370 370 l 370 360 m 370 360 m 90 300 l 90 310 l 100 310 l 100 300 m 100 300 m 210 190 l 210 200 l 220 200 l 220 190 m 220 190 m 110 240 l 110 250 l 120 250 l 120 240 m 120 240 m 270 210 l 270 220 l 280 220 l 280 210 m 280 210 m 260 180 l 260 190 l 270 190 l 270 180 m 270 180 m 270 190 l 270 200 l 280 200 l 280 190 m 280 190 m 120 200 l 120 210 l 130 210 l 130 200 m 130 200 m 180 140 l 180 150 l 190 150 l 190 140 m 190 140 m 160 180 l 160 190 l 170 190 l 170 180 m 170 180 m 60 240 l 60 250 l 70 250 l 70 240 m 70 240 m 40 160 l 40 170 l 50 170 l 50 160 m 50 160 m 50 130 l 50 140 l 60 140 l 60 130 m 60 130 m 80 60 l 80 70 l 90 70 l 90 60 m 90 60 m 60 180 l 60 190 l 70 190 l 70 180 m 70 180 m 350 140 l 350 150 l 360 150 l 360 140 m 360 140 m 330 100 l 330 110 l 340 110 l 340 100 m 340 100 m 100 120 l 100 130 l 110 130 l 110 120 m 110 120 m 250 360 l 250 370 l 260 370 l 260 360 m 260 360 m 230 200 l 230 210 l 240 210 l 240 200 m 240 200 m 350 200 l 350 210 l 360 210 l 360 200 m 360 200 m 240 150 l 240 160 l 250 160 l 250 150 m 250 150 m 200 310 l 200 320 l 210 320 l 210 310 m 210 310 m 140 150 l 140 160 l 150 160 l 150 150 m 150 150 m 120 270 l 120 280 l 130 280 l 130 270 m 130 270 m 150 60 l 150 70 l 160 70 l 160 60 m 160 60 m 130 260 l 130 270 l 140 270 l 140 260 m 140 260 m 280 300 l 280 310 l 290 310 l 290 300 m 290 300 m 180 170 l 180 180 l 190 180 l 190 170 m 190 170 m 190 120 l 190 130 l 200 130 l 200 120 m 200 120 m 170 120 l 170 130 l 180 130 l 180 120 m 180 120 m 150 280 l 150 290 l 160 290 l 160 280 m 160 280 m 300 200 l 300 210 l 310 210 l 310 200 m 310 200 m 40 70 l 40 80 l 50 80 l 50 70 m 50 70 m 280 40 l 280 50 l 290 50 l 290 40 m 290 40 m 80 130 l 80 140 l 90 140 l 90 130 m 90 130 m 320 340 l 320 350 l 330 350 l 330 340 m 330 340 m 60 130 l 60 140 l 70 140 l 70 130 m 70 130 m 100 70 l 100 80 l 110 80 l 110 70 m 110 70 m 240 220 l 240 230 l 250 230 l 250 220 m 250 220 m 200 220 l 200 230 l 210 230 l 210 220 m 210 220 m 250 230 l 250 240 l 260 240 l 260 230 m 260 230 m 210 230 l 210 240 l 220 240 l 220 230 m 220 230 m 220 280 l 220 290 l 230 290 l 230 280 m 230 280 m 270 330 l 270 340 l 280 340 l 280 330 m 280 330 m 360 150 l 360 160 l 370 160 l 370 150 m 370 150 m 180 240 l 180 250 l 190 250 l 190 240 m 190 240 m 290 320 l 290 330 l 300 330 l 300 320 m 300 320 m 190 210 l 190 220 l 200 220 l 200 210 m 200 210 m 170 50 l 170 60 l 180 60 l 180 50 m 180 50 m 150 210 l 150 220 l 160 220 l 160 210 m 160 210 m 40 300 l 40 310 l 50 310 l 50 300 m 50 300 m 280 110 l 280 120 l 290 120 l 290 110 m 290 110 m 160 300 l 160 310 l 170 310 l 170 300 m 170 300 m 170 310 l 170 320 l 180 320 l 180 310 m 180 310 m 60 40 l 60 50 l 70 50 l 70 40 m 70 40 m 300 90 l 300 100 l 310 100 l 310 90 m 310 90 m 330 280 l 330 290 l 340 290 l 340 280 m 340 280 m 70 330 l 70 340 l 80 340 l 80 330 m 80 330 m 310 120 l 310 130 l 320 130 l 320 120 m 320 120 m 80 340 l 80 350 l 90 350 l 90 340 m 90 340

50
00:04:46,180 --> 00:04:46,980
羅恩
Ron.

51
00:04:56,970 --> 00:04:57,890
謝謝
Thank you.

52
00:04:58,030 --> 00:04:58,930
別客氣
Of course.

53
00:05:02,380 --> 00:05:03,210
好
Okay.

54
00:05:13,430 --> 00:05:14,280
格倫
Glenn.

55
00:05:15,420 --> 00:05:16,930
格倫  出什么事了  你沒事吧
Glenn, what happened? Are you okay?

56
00:05:16,930 --> 00:05:17,810
我沒事
I'm okay.

57
00:05:18,780 --> 00:05:20,310
你們看起來真糟
You guys look like shit.

58
00:05:23,740 --> 00:05:25,630
她沒事  她沒事
She's fine. She's fine. She's okay.

59
00:05:28,330 --> 00:05:29,230
塔拉
Tara?

60
00:05:30,210 --> 00:05:31,230
我沒事
I'm okay.

61
00:05:31,810 --> 00:05:33,170
你去看看他們
You just check on them.

62
00:05:35,240 --> 00:05:36,720
-我沒事  -出什么事了
- I'm okay. - What happened?

63
00:05:36,720 --> 00:05:37,860
我們出去了
We were out there.

64
00:05:39,330 --> 00:05:42,260
行尸...  我們沒事
The walkers and-- we're all right.

65
00:05:44,230 --> 00:05:45,770
子彈反彈  打傷我了
Got winged by a ricochet.

66
00:05:48,400 --> 00:05:49,450
沒事
It's all right.

67
00:05:53,310 --> 00:05:54,660
天啊
Holy shit.

68
00:05:57,830 --> 00:05:58,910
謝天謝地
Thank god...

69
00:05:59,920 --> 00:06:01,550
你的發型沒事
nothing happened to your hair.

70
00:06:06,110 --> 00:06:08,400
好吧  尤金嚇到我了
Okay, Eugene's freaking me out.

71
00:06:08,640 --> 00:06:10,960
誰去叫諾亞來保護我
Somebody want to send Noah in here to protect me?

72
00:06:40,120 --> 00:06:43,170
抱歉  我是個混蛋
來華盛頓吧
新世界需要瑞克·格蘭姆斯
---亞伯拉罕

73
00:06:57,500 --> 00:06:58,590
你說得對
You were right.

74
00:07:00,680 --> 00:07:01,750
一切還沒結束
It wasn't over.

75
00:07:09,130 --> 00:07:10,760
我們明天多聊聊
We should talk more tomorrow.

76
00:07:14,360 --> 00:07:15,330
聽著
Listen...

77
00:07:19,080 --> 00:07:21,170
我不再冒險了
I don't take chances anymore.

78
00:07:23,670 --> 00:07:24,790
你的確不該
And you shouldn't.

79
00:08:06,750 --> 00:08:09,000
奎恩特  物料公司  5號門

80
00:08:21,220 --> 00:08:23,060
你們都有自己的任務
You all have your assignments.

81
00:08:23,060 --> 00:08:24,970
你們知道在哪里會合
You know where to rendezvous.

82
00:08:28,300 --> 00:08:29,820
達里爾引它們出去
Daryl leads them out.

83
00:08:29,820 --> 00:08:32,800
薩沙和亞伯拉罕在山腳跟他會合
Sasha and Abraham join him at the bottom of the hill.

84
00:08:36,910 --> 00:08:38,300
格倫  你干掉
Glenn, you hit us

85
00:08:38,300 --> 00:08:40,820
拖拉機店的行尸后來找我們
when you take care of the walkers at the tractor place.

86
00:08:40,820 --> 00:08:43,030
那件事必須提前做完
That's the one thing we gotta get ahead of.

87
00:08:44,560 --> 00:08:47,780
奎恩特  物料公司  5號門

88
00:08:45,180 --> 00:08:47,970
大家都要冷靜當心
Everybody keep your heads.

89
00:08:49,070 --> 00:08:50,080
跟上
Just keep up.

90
00:09:17,110 --> 00:09:18,420
他沒意見吧
So, is he okay with it?

91
00:09:18,870 --> 00:09:20,620
基本就是他的主意
It was pretty much his idea.

92
00:09:20,940 --> 00:09:21,850
他懂的
He gets it.

93
00:09:23,030 --> 00:09:24,520
那里有床和浴室
It's got a bed and a bath,

94
00:09:25,330 --> 00:09:26,920
但還是個牢籠
but it's still a cage, you know?

95
00:09:27,100 --> 00:09:28,220
他懂的
He gets it.

96
00:09:29,590 --> 00:09:32,280
他跟我說了之前在卡車那邊的事
He told me what happened out there with the trucks.

97
00:09:33,740 --> 00:09:35,380
他跟你說了他遇到的那些人了嗎
He tell you about those guys he met?

98
00:09:36,200 --> 00:09:37,120
腦門上有W的人
The Ws.

99
00:09:37,200 --> 00:09:39,080
和我們看見的那個行尸一樣  說了
Like that walker we saw, yeah.

100
00:09:40,740 --> 00:09:42,520
我們需要更多的哨點
We need more watch points.

101
00:09:43,420 --> 00:09:44,370
然后我會去和迪安娜說
And I'm gonna tell Deanna

102
00:09:44,370 --> 00:09:46,570
我們不需要再去外面找幸存者了
we don't need to go looking for people anymore.

103
00:09:52,030 --> 00:09:53,470
你有異議嗎
You feel different about it?

104
00:09:55,210 --> 00:09:57,720
我有
Yeah, I do.

105
00:09:59,610 --> 00:10:00,890
外面的那些人
Well, people out there,

106
00:10:02,230 --> 00:10:03,780
他們得照顧自己了
they got to take care of themselves,

107
00:10:03,780 --> 00:10:04,910
就像我們一樣
just like us.

108
00:10:08,780 --> 00:10:10,010
我去放他出來
I'm gonna get him out.

109
00:10:11,410 --> 00:10:13,930
我們不用把他關太久
Shouldn't leave him in there any longer than we have to.

110
00:10:20,460 --> 00:10:21,410
你還好吧
You good?

111
00:10:21,950 --> 00:10:22,790
嗯
Yeah.

112
00:10:24,840 --> 00:10:25,940
我在努力
I'm trying.

113
00:10:29,580 --> 00:10:30,480
聽著  假如你還打算
Listen, if you're still looking

114
00:10:30,480 --> 00:10:32,340
憋著一口氣狂野一把...
to go buck wild with the breath impaired...

115
00:10:32,340 --> 00:10:35,590
你已經問了問題  我也已經回答了
You already asked the question and I already answered it.

116
00:10:38,500 --> 00:10:39,150
假如你這么擔心
If you were so worried,

117
00:10:39,150 --> 00:10:41,320
你他媽為什么還上我的車
why the hell did you get into the car with me?

118
00:10:51,630 --> 00:10:55,060
聽著  做這種大事...
Listen, doing something as big as this...

119
00:10:57,050 --> 00:10:58,010
那才叫活著
That's living.

120
00:11:01,780 --> 00:11:02,710
到了
There it is.

121
00:11:06,470 --> 00:11:08,620
我們到了山腳的紅氣球處了
We're at red at the bottom of the hill.

122
00:11:09,010 --> 00:11:10,720
好了  大隊伍來了
All right, here comes the parade.

123
00:11:41,900 --> 00:11:43,310
你從哪兒學來的
Where'd you learn that?

124
00:11:45,080 --> 00:11:46,060
一個朋友那里
A friend.

125
00:11:47,780 --> 00:11:49,400
之前還是之后
Before or after?

126
00:11:52,020 --> 00:11:53,760
我提問  你回答
I ask, you answer.

127
00:11:54,740 --> 00:11:57,090
這是基本的禮貌  是不是
It's common courtesy, right?

128
00:12:00,930 --> 00:12:02,020
是之后
It was after.

129
00:12:04,740 --> 00:12:06,150
所有事情之后
After everything.

130
00:12:07,300 --> 00:12:09,710
聽著  我對此很抱歉  很抱歉這么做
Look, I'm sorry for this, for having to do this.

131
00:12:09,720 --> 00:12:10,650
沒關系的
It's all right.

132
00:12:11,900 --> 00:12:13,100
在我看來
The way I look at it,

133
00:12:13,780 --> 00:12:16,240
有時沒有出路反而更安全
sometimes you're safer when there's no way out.

134
00:12:20,300 --> 00:12:22,280
可以重新認識對方
Got to get to know each other again.

135
00:12:23,860 --> 00:12:27,000
第一次...重新認識
For the first time... again.

136
00:12:36,750 --> 00:12:39,340
嘿  是我們
Hey, it's us.

137
00:12:39,960 --> 00:12:41,770
我們回來了  快放我們進去
We're back. You gonna let us in or what?

138
00:12:46,600 --> 00:12:48,120
嚴格來說  我未獲得授權
I'm technically not authorized,

139
00:12:48,120 --> 00:12:49,500
所以我不會開門的
so I will not be doing so.

140
00:12:49,500 --> 00:12:51,420
-你他媽是誰  -你先說
- Who the hell are you? - You first.

141
00:12:52,720 --> 00:12:53,850
我是希斯
I'm Heath.

142
00:12:54,650 --> 00:12:57,490
我住在這兒  我的小隊前幾周出外勤了
I live here. My team's been on a run the last couple weeks.

143
00:13:04,570 --> 00:13:05,760
我是尤金
I'm Eugene.

144
00:13:06,100 --> 00:13:07,490
亞倫帶著我和我的隊伍
Aaron brought myself and my group here

145
00:13:07,490 --> 00:13:08,560
在你們出去時入住進來的
directly within that window,

146
00:13:08,570 --> 00:13:09,810
所以我們一直沒機會見面
so we haven't had the chance to meet

147
00:13:09,810 --> 00:13:11,720
因此我無法確認你住在這里
and I can't exactly confirm your residence.

148
00:13:11,720 --> 00:13:12,730
把門打開
Open the gate.

149
00:13:14,240 --> 00:13:16,710
假如我開了  我怎么知道你不會殺了我
If I do, how do I know you won't attempt to kill me?

150
00:13:16,760 --> 00:13:19,120
行了  聽著  我不會殺了你的
Okay, look, I'm not gonna kill you.

151
00:13:20,460 --> 00:13:21,540
但你讓我等的時間越長
But the longer you make me wait,

152
00:13:21,550 --> 00:13:23,960
我就越想揍你一頓  所以...
the more you motivate me to beat your ass, so...

153
00:13:29,250 --> 00:13:30,120
謝謝
Thank you.

154
00:13:50,770 --> 00:13:52,800
是迪安娜讓你來守門的嗎
So Deanna put you on gate duty?

155
00:13:53,450 --> 00:13:55,260
不  我不是值班的人
Oh, no, I'm not proper duty.

156
00:13:55,260 --> 00:13:56,520
現在該霍莉值班
This is Holly's shift.

157
00:13:57,300 --> 00:13:58,280
我只是路過
I was just walking by.

158
00:13:58,280 --> 00:14:00,470
她問我能不能幫她頂一會兒
She asked if I could relieve her for a few ticks.

159
00:14:00,470 --> 00:14:02,150
我說"不能"  但她無視了我
I said, "No, thank you" and she ignored me,

160
00:14:02,150 --> 00:14:03,680
其實我才應該無視她的
which is obviously what I should have done

161
00:14:03,680 --> 00:14:04,970
因為已經過了很久了
as it's been at least five ticks

162
00:14:04,970 --> 00:14:06,260
依然不見霍莉的蹤影
and still no Holly.

163
00:14:10,620 --> 00:14:13,240
我是斯科特  這位是安妮
I'm Scott. This is Annie.

164
00:14:13,840 --> 00:14:14,980
你好  幸會
Hi. Good to meet you.

165
00:14:15,640 --> 00:14:16,890
你們有幾個人
How many of you are there?

166
00:14:17,530 --> 00:14:18,400
13個
13.

167
00:14:18,630 --> 00:14:21,120
我是說  12個
I mean, 12.

168
00:14:22,370 --> 00:14:23,300
我很遺憾
I'm sorry.

169
00:14:25,880 --> 00:14:26,880
我來關門
I'll close up.

170
00:14:42,350 --> 00:14:44,360
我們不在的時候發生了什么大事嗎
Anything big happen while we were gone?

171
00:14:45,720 --> 00:14:47,030
我們昨晚開了個會
We had a meeting last night.

172
00:14:50,150 --> 00:14:52,180
是嗎  關于什么事的
Oh, yeah? About what?

173
00:14:53,630 --> 00:14:55,080
你最好去和迪安娜談談
You might want to talk to Deanna.

174
00:14:55,080 --> 00:14:56,480
聽聽權威消息
Get it from the horse.

175
00:14:56,860 --> 00:14:58,940
讓她親口給你說  懂嗎
Her mouth. You know?

176
00:15:01,250 --> 00:15:02,110
好吧
Right.

177
00:15:03,880 --> 00:15:05,830
遇到我這種人你該高興
Hey, it's good to see someone like me.

178
00:15:06,240 --> 00:15:07,870
我完全尊重別人的發型
I fully respect the hair game.

179
00:15:15,500 --> 00:15:18,380
-墻是誰建的  -他們
- Who put up the wall? - They did.

180
00:15:18,460 --> 00:15:20,250
有個人  叫雷吉
There was a man, Reg.

181
00:15:20,820 --> 00:15:23,500
他擬定的計劃  在災變早期建起來的
He drew up plans, made it happen early on.

182
00:15:24,070 --> 00:15:25,380
這里生活著很多人
A lot of people in here.

183
00:15:25,390 --> 00:15:27,420
他們一直住在墻內
They've been inside from the start.

184
00:15:28,120 --> 00:15:31,390
有飯吃有電用  沒怎么遭遇過行尸
They had food, energy, not a whole lot of walkers.

185
00:15:32,140 --> 00:15:33,840
他們只是生活著
They just lived.

186
00:15:34,060 --> 00:15:35,990
他們不必去求生
They haven't had to survive.

187
00:15:35,990 --> 00:15:38,350
他們想通了  收留了我們
They figured that out, brought us in.

188
00:15:40,120 --> 00:15:41,800
但可能為時已晚
Still might be too late.

189
00:15:41,800 --> 00:15:42,900
此話怎講
Too late how?

190
00:15:44,020 --> 00:15:45,600
他們恐怕改不過來了
For them to come around.

191
00:15:46,670 --> 00:15:47,610
再看吧
We'll see.

192
00:15:48,790 --> 00:15:50,370
你得去找迪安娜談談
You'll have to talk to Deanna.

193
00:15:50,370 --> 00:15:51,830
她是管事兒的
She's the woman in charge.

194
00:15:52,610 --> 00:15:54,380
她曾是雷吉的妻子
She was married to Reg.

195
00:15:55,060 --> 00:15:56,160
曾是
Was?

196
00:15:58,370 --> 00:15:59,560
沒錯
Yeah.

197
00:16:13,860 --> 00:16:14,920
你們在干什么
What are you doing?

198
00:16:17,050 --> 00:16:18,060
我們在...
We're--

199
00:16:19,450 --> 00:16:20,740
我想幫點忙
I wanted to help.

200
00:16:21,310 --> 00:16:22,530
只用挖一個坑
We only need one.

201
00:16:24,960 --> 00:16:26,980
但有兩位死者
We have two men here.

202
00:16:26,980 --> 00:16:29,550
殺人犯不能葬在墻內
We're not gonna bury killers inside these walls.

203
00:16:32,070 --> 00:16:34,190
我明白你的感受
I understand how you feel.

204
00:16:34,190 --> 00:16:35,060
真的
I do.

205
00:16:35,280 --> 00:16:38,020
但這由不得你
But it's not your decision.

206
00:16:39,140 --> 00:16:40,050
托賓
Tobin.

207
00:16:42,070 --> 00:16:43,060
瑞克說得對
Rick's right.

208
00:16:51,130 --> 00:16:52,120
把尸體抬走
Take it away.

209
00:16:53,720 --> 00:16:54,790
朝西
Go west.

210
00:16:56,340 --> 00:16:58,060
順著布蘭登路走幾英里
Down Branton road a few miles.

211
00:16:58,740 --> 00:17:00,240
過了橋就行
Just past the bridge.

212
00:17:01,290 --> 00:17:02,690
我們平常不去那邊
We don't go out that way.

213
00:17:05,360 --> 00:17:06,980
讓他當樹的肥料吧
Let the trees have him.

214
00:17:35,260 --> 00:17:37,970
我殺他是因為他殺死了雷吉
I shot him because he killed Reg.

215
00:17:37,970 --> 00:17:39,830
沒辦法  我們別無選擇
That was it. We didn't have a choice.

216
00:17:41,780 --> 00:17:43,260
可以關牢房啊
You do have a cell.

217
00:17:45,130 --> 00:17:46,430
不能便宜了殺人犯
Not for killers.

218
00:17:49,860 --> 00:17:51,270
我也殺過人  瑞克
I'm a killer, Rick.

219
00:17:53,570 --> 00:17:55,270
我殺過  你也殺過
I am, and you are, too.

220
00:18:04,670 --> 00:18:06,930
格倫  你到了嗎
Glenn, you there yet?

221
00:18:07,010 --> 00:18:09,570
快到了  我們會在尸群抵達之前搞定
Almost. We'll have it handled before they get here.

222
00:18:09,570 --> 00:18:10,870
我們在黃色氣球處和你會合
And we'll meet you at yellow.

223
00:18:10,870 --> 00:18:11,870
收到
Copy that.

224
00:18:19,090 --> 00:18:20,350
應該擋得住
It'll hold.

225
00:18:20,610 --> 00:18:21,750
那就好
Well, that's good.

226
00:18:22,450 --> 00:18:24,450
我們站這么近  擋不住就要遭殃了
You know, considering where we're standing.

227
00:18:31,680 --> 00:18:32,660
米瓊恩
Michonne.

228
00:18:33,840 --> 00:18:34,950
怎么
Yeah?

229
00:18:35,700 --> 00:18:37,470
之前你在那里的時候...
Back when you were in that place...

230
00:18:39,170 --> 00:18:40,320
在我的住處...
Where I lived...

231
00:18:44,170 --> 00:18:46,290
你是不是拿了我一根蛋白棒
Did you take one of my protein bars?

232
00:18:50,390 --> 00:18:51,500
沒有
No.

233
00:18:54,470 --> 00:18:57,210
我發誓  絕對還剩一根花生醬味的
See, I could have sworn there was one more peanut butter left.

234
00:18:58,890 --> 00:19:00,570
這就是現實  不是嗎
That's how it is, isn't it?

235
00:19:01,830 --> 00:19:04,720
你總覺得還剩一根花生醬蛋白棒
You always think there's one more peanut butter left.

236
00:19:34,420 --> 00:19:35,430
摩根
Morgan.

237
00:19:41,200 --> 00:19:42,840
就把他丟這兒吧
Maybe we just leave him here.

238
00:19:49,870 --> 00:19:51,450
你不是那種人
That's not who you are.

239
00:19:55,420 --> 00:19:56,460
我很清楚
I know.

240
00:20:07,190 --> 00:20:08,290
你不清楚
You don't.

241
00:20:33,990 --> 00:20:35,040
摩根
Morgan.

242
00:20:37,390 --> 00:20:38,480
摩根
Morgan.

243
00:20:41,680 --> 00:20:42,720
住手
Stop.

244
00:20:45,330 --> 00:20:46,520
聽到沒
Did you hear that?

245
00:23:02,280 --> 00:23:04,100
你跑到外面來干什么  羅恩
What are you doing out here, Ron?

246
00:23:06,020 --> 00:23:08,370
我想知道我爸被埋在哪了
I wanted to know where my dad was buried.

247
00:23:32,140 --> 00:23:33,480
原來如此
This is how.

248
00:23:37,830 --> 00:23:38,910
什么意思
How what?

249
00:23:39,660 --> 00:23:41,760
那個社區能幸存至今的原因
How the community's still here.

250
00:23:43,350 --> 00:23:45,530
雖然圍墻邊是有行尸
They've had walkers at their walls,

251
00:23:45,530 --> 00:23:48,620
但很多  或許是絕大部分
But a lot of them, maybe most of them,

252
00:23:49,850 --> 00:23:51,280
都被困在了這里
They wound up here.

253
00:24:28,990 --> 00:24:30,140
羅恩
Ron.

254
00:24:31,510 --> 00:24:33,200
-羅恩  -我回去了
- Ron. - I'm going back.

255
00:24:33,380 --> 00:24:34,800
-嘿  -我能行的
- Hey. - I'm fine.

256
00:24:35,200 --> 00:24:37,140
你不該跑出來的
You shouldn't be out here.

257
00:24:38,780 --> 00:24:40,170
我不在乎你怎么想
I don't care what you think.

258
00:24:40,990 --> 00:24:42,700
不是我怎么想  而是事實本如此
It's not what I think, it's what I know.

259
00:24:43,360 --> 00:24:45,610
你保護不了自己  我可以教你
You can't protect yourself. I'll show you how,

260
00:24:45,610 --> 00:24:47,600
但現在你不知道自己在干什么
but right now you have no idea what you're doing.

261
00:24:47,600 --> 00:24:50,690
如果你出來  你就會死
And if you come out here, you're gonna die.

262
00:24:51,510 --> 00:24:54,180
死得緩慢痛苦  而且永無止境
And it won't be quick and it won't ever be over

263
00:24:54,180 --> 00:24:55,350
因為你會變成它們那樣
'cause you'll be one of them.

264
00:24:55,350 --> 00:24:56,760
這就是即將發生的事
That's what's gonna happen.

265
00:24:58,680 --> 00:25:00,500
你立刻跟我們回去
You're coming back with us now.

266
00:25:03,660 --> 00:25:04,930
別找事
Don't make it hard.

267
00:26:06,780 --> 00:26:08,840
格倫  你得快點
Glenn, you have to hurry.

268
00:26:09,050 --> 00:26:11,610
噪音會把尸群從公路上引下來
The noise could distract the herd right off the road.

269
00:26:11,820 --> 00:26:13,530
-回話  -我們到了
- Talk to me. - We're here.

270
00:26:22,700 --> 00:26:23,630
聽起來有很多只
Sounds like a lot.

271
00:26:26,620 --> 00:26:28,630
-我們得讓它們安靜  -計劃是什么
- We need it quiet. - So what's the plan?

272
00:26:30,600 --> 00:26:32,900
放它們出來  每次放幾只
Take 'em out a few at a time.

273
00:26:44,540 --> 00:26:45,710
尼古拉斯  你守住門
Nicholas, you're at the door.

274
00:26:46,640 --> 00:26:47,840
好
All right.

275
00:26:48,480 --> 00:26:50,750
只放出一兩只  然后關門
You let one or two out and then you close it.

276
00:26:50,750 --> 00:26:52,040
循環往復  這就是竅門  
You keep doing that. That's the trick.

277
00:26:52,040 --> 00:26:53,040
這樣就能控制局面
That's how we control it.

278
00:26:53,040 --> 00:26:54,350
等等  如果他關不上門呢
Wait, what if he can't close it?

279
00:26:54,350 --> 00:26:55,670
-我可以的  -那我們就直接上
- I'll be able to. - Then we take them on.

280
00:26:55,670 --> 00:26:56,820
直接上
We take them on?

281
00:26:57,430 --> 00:26:59,710
如果遇到麻煩  我們就繞到樓后
If we get into trouble, we go behind the building

282
00:26:59,710 --> 00:27:01,280
鉆進樹林  把它們引開
into the woods and we draw them away.

283
00:27:02,160 --> 00:27:04,770
他來這里時  你在出外勤
Hey, you've been out on runs since he got here.

284
00:27:04,890 --> 00:27:06,140
他知道自己在做什么
He knows what he's doing.

285
00:27:07,230 --> 00:27:09,310
我和艾登  我們不知道
Me and Aiden, we didn't.

286
00:27:12,100 --> 00:27:14,040
我們本該來演習的
This was supposed to be a dress rehearsal.

287
00:27:14,040 --> 00:27:16,110
我還本該送披薩呢  伙計
I'm supposed to be delivering pizzas, man.

288
00:27:17,020 --> 00:27:18,560
達里爾正在引它們過來
Daryl's leading them this way.

289
00:27:19,070 --> 00:27:20,270
已經不遠了
And they're closing in.

290
00:27:20,600 --> 00:27:22,670
這噪音會把尸群從公路上引下來的
That noise is gonna pull the herd right off the road.

291
00:27:22,670 --> 00:27:24,020
那我們就真有麻煩了
And then we have serious trouble.

292
00:27:24,190 --> 00:27:25,610
我們必須這么做
We have to do this.

293
00:27:25,950 --> 00:27:27,260
是啊  好吧
Yeah, okay.

294
00:27:27,260 --> 00:27:28,450
-好嗎  -好
- Okay? - Okay.

295
00:27:28,450 --> 00:27:29,600
-好  -好
- Okay. - Okay.

296
00:27:30,750 --> 00:27:31,610
來吧
All right.

297
00:27:32,990 --> 00:27:35,750
數三下  準備好了嗎
On three. Ready?

298
00:27:38,110 --> 00:27:39,070
一
One...

299
00:27:40,940 --> 00:27:41,900
二
Two...

300
00:27:43,270 --> 00:27:44,170
三
Three!

301
00:27:48,970 --> 00:27:50,180
該死
Shit!

302
00:28:03,590 --> 00:28:04,810
我的小隊
My team...

303
00:28:05,310 --> 00:28:06,850
之前就看到了
We saw it early on,

304
00:28:07,260 --> 00:28:10,060
早先為了摸清周圍的情況
back when we were on one of those first scouts,

305
00:28:10,070 --> 00:28:11,640
出去偵查時發現的
finding out what was around here.

306
00:28:12,520 --> 00:28:14,470
底下有個營地
There was a camp at the bottom.

307
00:28:15,450 --> 00:28:18,520
災變開始時  那里的人肯定是
The people, they must have blocked the exits with one of those trucks

308
00:28:18,520 --> 00:28:20,520
用其中一輛卡車堵住了出口
back when everything started to go bad.

309
00:28:21,470 --> 00:28:23,040
可他們沒成功  都變成行尸了
They didn't make it. They were all roamers.

310
00:28:23,040 --> 00:28:24,430
可能有十幾個人
Maybe a dozen of them.

311
00:28:24,750 --> 00:28:26,140
之后再沒人去看過嗎
No one's been back since?

312
00:28:28,030 --> 00:28:29,280
在華盛頓
D.C.,

313
00:28:30,550 --> 00:28:33,200
所有值得搜索的城市都在別的方向
every town worth scavenging are all in the other direction.

314
00:28:33,350 --> 00:28:36,800
我可不想去一個自相蠶食的營地周圍吃野餐
And I never really felt like having a picnic next to the camp that ate itself.

315
00:28:36,800 --> 00:28:39,480
所以這么久以來  行尸都被聲音吸引了過去
So all the while the walkers have been drawn by the sound.

316
00:28:39,910 --> 00:28:42,400
它們又發出大的聲音  吸引更多的行尸
And they're making more sound and they're drawing more in.

317
00:28:42,400 --> 00:28:44,090
而我們不巧就在這里
And here we are.

318
00:28:46,000 --> 00:28:47,570
我所提議的計劃
Now what I'm proposing,

319
00:28:48,680 --> 00:28:50,450
雖然聽起來很危險
I know it sounds risky,

320
00:28:50,450 --> 00:28:53,310
但已經有行尸溜出了出口
but walkers are already slipping through the exits.

321
00:28:53,490 --> 00:28:56,080
阻擋行尸進去的一輛卡車
One of the trucks keeping the walkers in.

322
00:28:56,380 --> 00:28:58,040
隨時都有可能掉下來
Could go off the edge any day now.

323
00:28:58,040 --> 00:29:00,280
可能就在下場暴雨之后
Maybe after one more hard rain.

324
00:29:00,500 --> 00:29:03,240
那個出口面向東邊
That exit sends them east.

325
00:29:03,240 --> 00:29:06,210
所有行尸  都會沖我們來
All of them. Right at us.

326
00:29:10,040 --> 00:29:13,790
這不是猜測  只是時間問題
This isn't about if it gives, it's when.

327
00:29:13,790 --> 00:29:14,990
就在眼前了
It's gonna happen.

328
00:29:15,760 --> 00:29:17,530
所以我們必須盡快動手
That's why we have to do this soon.

329
00:29:17,530 --> 00:29:20,590
我都不知道該說什么了
This is-- I don't even have another word for it.

330
00:29:20,590 --> 00:29:21,980
這太恐怖了
This is terrifying.

331
00:29:23,540 --> 00:29:24,670
這一切
All of it.

332
00:29:26,140 --> 00:29:28,250
但似乎沒有別的選擇了
But it doesn't sound like there's any other way.

333
00:29:30,130 --> 00:29:31,660
也許有
Maybe there is.

334
00:29:33,450 --> 00:29:36,880
我是說  難道不能加固薄弱的地方嗎
I mean, couldn't we just build up the weak spots?

335
00:29:37,920 --> 00:29:39,430
我可以擬定計劃
I could draw up plans.

336
00:29:39,430 --> 00:29:41,840
我曾經跟雷吉一起修建圍墻
I worked on the wall with Reg.

337
00:29:42,360 --> 00:29:43,690
施工隊...
Construction crew--

338
00:29:44,190 --> 00:29:45,850
我們可以試著讓它更安全
We can try and make it safe.

339
00:29:45,850 --> 00:29:48,080
就算我們成功  行尸的聲音
Even if we could, the sound of those walkers

340
00:29:48,080 --> 00:29:50,410
也會吸引越來越多的行尸
is drawing more and more every day.

341
00:29:50,410 --> 00:29:52,270
加固出口也無濟于事
Building up the exits won't change that.

342
00:29:53,410 --> 00:29:54,930
我們聽瑞克的
We're gonna do what Rick says,

343
00:29:55,800 --> 00:29:57,320
按他的計劃來
the plan he's laid out.

344
00:30:00,670 --> 00:30:04,700
我說過  讓達里爾把它們引開
I told you all, we're gonna have Daryl leading them away.

345
00:30:05,390 --> 00:30:06,510
我也去
Me, too.

346
00:30:08,250 --> 00:30:10,060
我可以開車  和他并排開
I'll take a car, ride next to him.

347
00:30:10,800 --> 00:30:12,030
不能只有他一個人
Can't just be him.

348
00:30:13,030 --> 00:30:16,010
我引它們往前走  達里爾防止它們跑偏
I'll keep 'em coming, Daryl keeps 'em from getting sloppy.

349
00:30:16,010 --> 00:30:16,930
我和她一起去
I'll go with her.

350
00:30:18,800 --> 00:30:21,020
這么遠一個人不安全
It's a long way to white-knuckle it solo.

351
00:30:23,390 --> 00:30:25,100
我們分成兩隊
We'll have two teams.

352
00:30:25,490 --> 00:30:28,580
樹林兩邊各派一隊控制局面
One on each side of the forest helping manage this thing.

353
00:30:29,620 --> 00:30:31,980
從今往后要安排幾個人站崗
We're gonna have a few people on watch from now on.

354
00:30:32,190 --> 00:30:34,130
羅西塔  斯賓塞  霍莉
Rosita, Spencer, and Holly.

355
00:30:34,130 --> 00:30:35,570
所以他們不參加行動
So they're out.

356
00:30:37,600 --> 00:30:38,660
那誰來參加
So who's in?

357
00:30:40,830 --> 00:30:41,820
我
Me.

358
00:30:43,140 --> 00:30:44,550
你應該留下看著她
You should keep an eye on her.

359
00:30:45,690 --> 00:30:47,580
繼續執行你之前說的那些計劃
Keep going with the plans you talked about.

360
00:30:47,580 --> 00:30:49,270
我知道  但這很重要
I know, but this is important.

361
00:30:49,610 --> 00:30:50,830
她也很重要
She's important.

362
00:30:51,790 --> 00:30:53,220
大家很害怕
People are scared.

363
00:30:53,590 --> 00:30:55,410
他們需要看到她振作
They need to see her come back.

364
00:30:59,180 --> 00:31:00,770
這不是唯一的原因吧
That's not the only reason.

365
00:31:02,200 --> 00:31:04,720
對啊  不是
Yeah, it isn't.

366
00:31:06,080 --> 00:31:06,990
好
Okay.

367
00:31:09,160 --> 00:31:10,160
算我一個
I'm in.

368
00:31:12,270 --> 00:31:13,440
我也想幫忙
I'd like to help as well.

369
00:31:13,440 --> 00:31:14,960
不行  還有誰
No. Who else?

370
00:31:15,480 --> 00:31:16,710
人不夠
We need more.

371
00:31:17,300 --> 00:31:19,140
一定還有別的辦法
There's got to be another play.

372
00:31:20,460 --> 00:31:23,000
我們控制不了那么多行尸
We can't just control that many.

373
00:31:23,000 --> 00:31:25,820
我都說過了  行尸喜歡扎堆
I said it before, walkers herd up.

374
00:31:25,820 --> 00:31:27,660
如果有東西吸引  它們會沿著一條路走
They'll follow a path if something's drawing them.

375
00:31:27,660 --> 00:31:29,610
這樣就可以一網打盡
That's how we can get 'em all at once.

376
00:31:29,610 --> 00:31:32,140
所以呢  我們就該相信你的空口白牙嗎
So, what? We're supposed to just take your word for it?

377
00:31:33,300 --> 00:31:36,780
經歷了那事之后  大家就應該跟隨你嗎
We're all supposed to just fall in line behind you after...

378
00:31:41,440 --> 00:31:42,640
經歷了什么
After what?

379
00:31:42,640 --> 00:31:44,870
你舉著槍
After you wave a gun around

380
00:31:45,410 --> 00:31:48,000
大喊大叫  拿槍對著別人
screaming, pointing it at people.

381
00:31:48,020 --> 00:31:50,380
一槍爆了別人的頭
After you shoot a man in the face.

382
00:31:50,380 --> 00:31:51,790
-你還...  -夠了
- After you... - Enough!

383
00:32:00,200 --> 00:32:01,160
我加入
I'll do it.

384
00:32:03,620 --> 00:32:04,570
我也是
Me, too.

385
00:32:04,770 --> 00:32:05,790
都聽你的
Whatever you need,

386
00:32:06,310 --> 00:32:07,250
我加入
I'm in.

387
00:32:07,570 --> 00:32:08,810
還有誰
Now who else?

388
00:32:17,560 --> 00:32:18,570
我去
I'll go.

389
00:32:20,420 --> 00:32:23,650
我們必須這么做  我得幫忙
We have to do this. I need to help.

390
00:32:30,320 --> 00:32:31,900
你確定你能行嗎
You sure you can handle it?

391
00:32:33,870 --> 00:32:35,150
你們缺人
You need people.

392
00:32:41,460 --> 00:32:43,150
我們會成功的
We'll make this work.

393
00:32:43,150 --> 00:32:44,530
我們會保衛這個地方
We'll keep this place safe.

394
00:32:44,530 --> 00:32:47,030
保護自己的家人  一定會的
Keep our families safe. We will.

395
00:32:47,250 --> 00:32:48,210
你的計劃
The plan.

396
00:32:49,020 --> 00:32:50,240
再說一遍
Go through it again.

397
00:32:50,240 --> 00:32:51,710
老兄  他剛說過啊
Man, he just said it.

398
00:32:51,720 --> 00:32:55,110
再說一遍每個步驟
Every part again.

399
00:32:55,840 --> 00:32:57,450
要具體
The exact plan.

400
00:33:31,420 --> 00:33:37,420
馬歇爾路  雷丁路  熊溪

401
00:33:32,480 --> 00:33:34,330
馬歇爾路和雷丁路
Marshall and Redding.

402
00:33:34,470 --> 00:33:36,130
從這里把它們往西趕
We force them west here.

403
00:33:36,230 --> 00:33:37,000
怎么趕
How?

404
00:33:37,420 --> 00:33:39,910
把其他路擋住  讓它們只有一條路可走
We block it off so they can only go one way,

405
00:33:39,910 --> 00:33:42,290
向西邊  遠離社區
West, away from the community.

406
00:33:42,290 --> 00:33:43,830
用什么擋路
Block it off with what?

407
00:33:44,370 --> 00:33:45,430
車
Cars.

408
00:33:45,520 --> 00:33:47,840
用房車  幾輛大卡車
We'll use the rvs, some of the bigger trucks.

409
00:33:47,840 --> 00:33:48,890
首尾相接
Park them end to end.

410
00:33:48,890 --> 00:33:50,390
我們會把它們引走
We'll be drawing them away.

411
00:33:51,220 --> 00:33:53,650
-它們會一直走  -這么多行尸能行嗎
- They're gonna keep moving. - Yeah, but that many?

412
00:33:53,650 --> 00:33:56,300
幾輛轎車就攔得住嗎
Just bouncing off some sedans?

413
00:33:57,800 --> 00:34:00,750
如果有行尸從縫里擠過去
And then when they start slipping through

414
00:34:00,950 --> 00:34:03,380
偏離路線的行尸開始吸引其他行尸
And the ones that walk away start distracting the rest

415
00:34:03,380 --> 00:34:05,800
你們就不能把它們引走了
and you stop drawing them away?

416
00:34:08,720 --> 00:34:09,540
他說得有道理
Man's got a point.

417
00:34:09,540 --> 00:34:11,030
我們有板材
We got plates.

418
00:34:12,180 --> 00:34:14,750
建筑工地用的那種大金屬板
The big-ass metal ones from the construction site.

419
00:34:14,850 --> 00:34:16,420
可以用來加固擋板
We can use them to fortify the whip wall.

420
00:34:16,420 --> 00:34:17,960
這能分散沖擊力度
It'd help disperse the force of impact

421
00:34:17,960 --> 00:34:19,640
完全疏散那些行尸
and direct the walkers clean.

422
00:34:19,850 --> 00:34:21,930
就像臺球桌  黑八  擊入底袋
Like a pool table. Eight ball, corner pocket.

423
00:34:21,930 --> 00:34:23,910
外面可是有一支軍隊
That's an army out there.

424
00:34:25,890 --> 00:34:28,320
如果這里支撐不住怎么辦
And what happens when this doesn't hold?

425
00:34:28,660 --> 00:34:30,800
它們會繼續前進  順著山坡
And they push on through. The curve in this hillside

426
00:34:30,800 --> 00:34:33,010
直接往東走
is gonna send them right back east.

427
00:34:33,010 --> 00:34:34,800
回到這里
Right back here.

428
00:34:35,750 --> 00:34:37,930
你真的想冒這個險嗎
You seriously want to risk that?

429
00:34:38,630 --> 00:34:39,550
不想
No.

430
00:34:41,270 --> 00:34:43,750
所以你要幫我們確保能支撐住
So you need to help us to make it hold.

431
00:34:45,850 --> 00:34:47,430
這些墻是你造的
These walls, you built them.

432
00:34:47,830 --> 00:34:50,530
你已經做到了不可能完成之事
So you've already done the impossible.

433
00:34:53,010 --> 00:34:53,980
卡特
Carter.

434
00:34:55,050 --> 00:34:56,090
拜托了
Please.

435
00:34:58,970 --> 00:35:03,760
雷丁路
馬歇爾路

436
00:36:42,070 --> 00:36:48,730
雷丁路
馬歇爾路

437
00:37:12,760 --> 00:37:14,010
你之前說
Hey, what you said before

438
00:37:14,010 --> 00:37:16,220
我們要照顧好自己
about us needing to take care of ourselves?

439
00:37:17,610 --> 00:37:19,360
去找更多幸存的人
Going out finding more people,

440
00:37:19,800 --> 00:37:21,820
就是照顧好我們自己的表現
that is taking care of ourselves.

441
00:37:26,430 --> 00:37:27,650
但決定權在你
Your call, though.

442
00:37:36,160 --> 00:37:37,110
謝謝
Thanks.

443
00:37:38,590 --> 00:37:40,420
我可以跟你們一起去的
You know, I can come with all of you.

444
00:37:42,750 --> 00:37:44,920
你和達里爾一直在教我怎么用槍
You and Daryl have been teaching me how to shoot.

445
00:37:46,000 --> 00:37:48,000
我覺得你掌握得很好
I think you got the hang of it.

446
00:37:52,820 --> 00:37:54,180
你應該待在后方
You should stay back,

447
00:37:55,790 --> 00:37:58,140
了解一下這些人是怎么想的
get a feel for how people feel now.

448
00:37:58,950 --> 00:38:01,000
我們跟他們還有好長一段路要走
We still got a long way to go with them.

449
00:38:03,240 --> 00:38:04,310
我們能成功的
We'll get there.

450
00:38:05,320 --> 00:38:06,730
以前她管事兒
She's in charge.

451
00:38:08,130 --> 00:38:09,540
但現在你管事兒
But you're in charge now.

452
00:38:23,060 --> 00:38:25,650
-這主意糟透了  -只能這么辦了
- This is a bad idea. - This is the only idea.

453
00:38:25,650 --> 00:38:27,930
我覺得這里面起碼有十來只
I think there's something like a dozen in there.

454
00:38:27,930 --> 00:38:29,800
我們退后  站在不同的方向
We stay back, we get on opposite ends,

455
00:38:29,800 --> 00:38:30,970
將它們分別引開
we draw them to each of us.

456
00:38:30,970 --> 00:38:32,750
-每人干掉四個嗎  -不
- Try and take down four each? - No.

457
00:38:32,860 --> 00:38:34,350
只有我和希斯
This is just me and Heath.

458
00:38:34,350 --> 00:38:36,360
你回去  不要過來
You get back and you stay back.

459
00:38:36,360 --> 00:38:38,940
一旦出事  你就告訴瑞克  然后引走它們
Things go south, you tell Rick and you draw them away.

460
00:38:40,040 --> 00:38:41,870
回去吧
Just move back.

461
00:38:52,540 --> 00:38:54,000
他害死了諾亞嗎
He got Noah killed?

462
00:38:54,230 --> 00:38:55,170
沒錯
He did.

463
00:38:57,350 --> 00:38:58,710
不止如此
He did more than that.

464
00:39:01,140 --> 00:39:03,720
他引格倫到樹林里  試圖殺了他
He lured Glenn into the woods and tried to kill him.

465
00:39:05,130 --> 00:39:06,280
真的嗎
What the hell?

466
00:39:06,280 --> 00:39:08,050
-沒錯  -搞什么
- Yeah. - What?

467
00:39:08,160 --> 00:39:09,510
格倫告訴我如果我想的話
Glenn told me I could tell everyone

468
00:39:09,510 --> 00:39:10,790
可以告訴所有人
if that's what I wanted to do.

469
00:39:11,270 --> 00:39:13,090
那樣尼古拉斯會被流放
Could get Nicholas exiled.

470
00:39:14,270 --> 00:39:15,740
死在外面
He'd die out there.

471
00:39:16,930 --> 00:39:18,170
我本可以那樣做
Could have done that.

472
00:39:20,020 --> 00:39:21,220
你現在依然可以那樣做
You could do that now.

473
00:39:21,240 --> 00:39:24,200
他害死諾亞  還試圖殺格倫
He got Noah killed and he tried to kill Glenn?

474
00:39:25,450 --> 00:39:26,910
格倫有救人之心
Glenn saves people.

475
00:39:28,390 --> 00:39:29,910
甚至是對這種人
Even people like that.

476
00:39:35,950 --> 00:39:37,510
我之前也沒法接受
I couldn't accept it either.

477
00:39:39,270 --> 00:39:40,870
但后來我想到了你
But then I thought about you.

478
00:39:41,580 --> 00:39:42,830
在我最痛苦的那段時光
How we were on different sides of that fence

479
00:39:42,830 --> 00:39:44,520
我們站在柵欄的兩邊
on the worst day of my life.

480
00:39:47,310 --> 00:39:48,770
但現在你是這個世界上對我來說
And now you're one of the most important people

481
00:39:48,770 --> 00:39:50,070
最重要的人之一
in the world to me.

482
00:39:52,080 --> 00:39:53,420
一切都會好起來的
Things can get better.

483
00:39:55,270 --> 00:39:56,580
我們可以讓一切好起來
We can make them better.

484
00:39:58,680 --> 00:40:00,340
你告訴我你想怎么辦
You tell me what you want to do.

485
00:40:04,260 --> 00:40:07,380
我都聽你的  好嗎
I'm just gonna follow your lead, okay?

486
00:40:08,830 --> 00:40:09,620
好的
Okay.

487
00:40:11,530 --> 00:40:12,410
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.

488
00:40:21,420 --> 00:40:22,260
你準備好了嗎
You ready?

489
00:40:22,520 --> 00:40:25,480
沒有  不過反正你也鐵了心要這么干
No. But since you're doing this thing anyway...

490
00:40:26,530 --> 00:40:27,390
好吧
All right.

491
00:40:47,110 --> 00:40:48,130
還在出來
They're still coming.

492
00:41:23,850 --> 00:41:24,650
干掉它
Get it.

493
00:41:30,380 --> 00:41:31,130
很好
Good.

494
00:41:32,250 --> 00:41:33,170
我們走
Let's go.

495
00:41:54,800 --> 00:41:55,680
拿著
Here you go.

496
00:41:55,830 --> 00:41:56,980
謝謝
Oh, thank you.

497
00:41:57,760 --> 00:41:59,040
你叫卡蘿爾吧
It's Carol, right?

498
00:41:59,720 --> 00:42:00,430
是的
Yeah.

499
00:42:01,260 --> 00:42:02,720
你跟著瑞克很久了嗎
You been with Rick long?

500
00:42:04,460 --> 00:42:05,640
從亞特蘭大那時起
Since Atlanta.

501
00:42:05,990 --> 00:42:07,470
你以前也是個警察嗎
And were you a cop, too?

502
00:42:09,320 --> 00:42:10,960
你為什么這樣想
Why would you think that?

503
00:42:11,240 --> 00:42:12,790
你總是在保持警惕
You're always watching.

504
00:42:14,320 --> 00:42:16,010
你總是...
You always...

505
00:42:16,890 --> 00:42:18,030
時刻準備著
seem ready.

506
00:42:19,640 --> 00:42:20,540
準備什么
For what?

507
00:42:22,450 --> 00:42:24,150
處理一些事情
You know, to handle things.

508
00:42:27,470 --> 00:42:28,770
您過獎了
Aren't you sweet?

509
00:42:36,320 --> 00:42:37,220
怎么了
What is it?

510
00:42:38,570 --> 00:42:40,190
有幾只行尸
Got some looky-loos taking

511
00:42:40,200 --> 00:42:42,500
不隨大流了
a little constitutional off the shoulder.

512
00:42:44,040 --> 00:42:46,220
它們開始跑偏了
They starting a damn walkout.

513
00:42:46,220 --> 00:42:47,950
你要達里爾繞回去嗎
You want to have Daryl circle back?

514
00:42:48,930 --> 00:42:49,860
不用
No.

515
00:42:50,550 --> 00:42:52,780
繼續開  我會追上的
Keep moving. I'll catch up.

516
00:42:53,000 --> 00:42:54,150
亞伯拉罕
Abraham.

517
00:43:01,290 --> 00:43:02,370
笨蛋
Idiot.

518
00:43:13,570 --> 00:43:14,410
來啊
Come on!

519
00:43:17,060 --> 00:43:18,960
那是我的車  混蛋
This is my ride, asshole.

520
00:43:31,960 --> 00:43:34,370
你看我
Well, look at me.

521
00:43:39,650 --> 00:43:41,060
你是沒看到雷吉
You didn't see Reg

522
00:43:42,210 --> 00:43:43,480
他死的那一晚
the night he got it.

523
00:43:46,420 --> 00:43:47,740
簡直一團糟
That was a mess.

524
00:43:50,530 --> 00:43:51,610
還有皮特
And Pete.

525
00:43:52,930 --> 00:43:54,400
他的臉...
His face just...

526
00:43:55,400 --> 00:43:57,580
像是龐貝古城一樣炸了
blowing up like Pompeii

527
00:43:58,320 --> 00:43:59,980
當時我就跟他面對面
right when we were cheek to cheek.

528
00:44:02,810 --> 00:44:05,430
我還是覺得耳朵里進了點他的腦漿
I still think I got some of his brains in my ear.

529
00:44:14,930 --> 00:44:15,970
你看那
Well, look at that.

530
00:44:18,450 --> 00:44:19,390
好吧
All right.

531
00:44:20,620 --> 00:44:23,840
一切又完美了
Everything is aces again.

532
00:44:28,760 --> 00:44:30,180
你到底在干什么
What the hell are you doing?

533
00:44:32,510 --> 00:44:35,080
不過是當機立斷而已
I'm just grabbing the bull by the nutsack.

534
00:44:35,990 --> 00:44:37,290
我還活著  親愛的
I'm living, darling,

535
00:44:38,810 --> 00:44:40,070
像你一樣
just like you.

536
00:44:53,580 --> 00:44:56,060
我還沒機會跟你說  但...
I haven't had a chance to say it yet, but...

537
00:44:56,970 --> 00:44:58,810
雷吉的事我很遺憾
I'm sorry about Reg.

538
00:45:00,450 --> 00:45:04,300
他聰明又善良
He was smart and kind.

539
00:45:05,090 --> 00:45:06,450
他是個好人
He was a good man.

540
00:45:11,210 --> 00:45:12,720
這個決定是正確的
It was the right call.

541
00:45:13,520 --> 00:45:14,800
是我們所需要的
We need this.

542
00:45:18,880 --> 00:45:19,870
還有什么話
What else?

543
00:45:22,440 --> 00:45:23,610
要跟我說的
You need to tell me.

544
00:45:25,300 --> 00:45:27,670
墻里的人需要武裝起來
People need to be armed inside the walls.

545
00:45:27,970 --> 00:45:30,550
每個人  都要接受訓練
They need to be trained, everyone.

546
00:45:35,130 --> 00:45:36,140
別去
Stop.

547
00:45:36,830 --> 00:45:38,150
它們來了
Here they come.

548
00:45:39,970 --> 00:45:42,060
卡特  小心
Carter, heads up.

549
00:45:42,900 --> 00:45:44,230
伙計們  等等
Wait, folks.

550
00:45:52,300 --> 00:45:55,170
用鏟子  槍聲會引來更多行尸
Use your shovels. The guns will draw more.

551
00:45:55,320 --> 00:45:56,310
幫幫我們
Help us.

552
00:45:57,470 --> 00:45:59,940
你能行的  你們所有人都必須做到
You can do this. You need to, all of you.

553
00:46:09,560 --> 00:46:10,780
摩根  別去
Morgan, don't!

554
00:46:33,400 --> 00:46:35,800
你說過你不再冒險的
You said you don't take chances anymore.

555
00:46:49,640 --> 00:46:51,050
快沒有時間了
Time is running out.

556
00:46:51,610 --> 00:46:54,020
他說明天要去演習  該動手了
He's talking about a dry run tomorrow. That's it.

557
00:46:54,030 --> 00:46:56,020
瑞克阻止了皮特
Rick stopped Pete. He stopped him.

558
00:46:56,020 --> 00:46:58,210
這與除掉家暴者無關
This is not taking out a wife-beater.

559
00:46:58,210 --> 00:47:00,600
他是個殺人犯  卡特
He was a murderer, Carter.

560
00:47:00,680 --> 00:47:03,540
瑞克的計劃等于自殺
What Rick wants to do is suicide.

561
00:47:03,540 --> 00:47:05,100
抱歉  斯賓塞
I'm sorry, Spencer,

562
00:47:05,900 --> 00:47:08,500
但迪安娜已經心不在焉了
but Deanna is asleep at the wheel.

563
00:47:09,420 --> 00:47:13,170
只能靠我們了  我們得阻止他
So it's on us. We have got to stop him.

564
00:47:13,900 --> 00:47:16,830
神父是怎么說他還有那些人的
What the priest said about him, about these people,

565
00:47:16,890 --> 00:47:18,130
他說得沒錯
He was right.

566
00:47:19,060 --> 00:47:22,370
還得死多少人
How many more of us have to die

567
00:47:22,370 --> 00:47:24,180
我們才會采取行動啊
before we do something?

568
00:47:24,190 --> 00:47:26,480
因為很快就會太遲了
'cause pretty soon it's gonna be too late.

569
00:47:26,600 --> 00:47:29,880
卡特  你說話要想清楚了
Carter, you need to be really careful here.

570
00:47:29,910 --> 00:47:31,910
你是說要我們去找迪安娜談嗎
You're talking about us going to Deanna and telling her--

571
00:47:31,910 --> 00:47:35,160
我沒說要找她談
No, I'm not talking about talking some more.

572
00:47:35,160 --> 00:47:37,710
我沒有說要開會
About meetings. I'm not talking about that.

573
00:47:37,970 --> 00:47:40,080
說白了  在他殺我們之前
Plain and simple, we kill him

574
00:47:40,600 --> 00:47:42,370
把他干掉
before he kills us.

575
00:47:56,640 --> 00:47:57,830
你好啊
Hello.

576
00:47:59,310 --> 00:48:00,260
卡特
Carter.

577
00:48:01,470 --> 00:48:03,250
-他聽到了  -我沒有
- He heard. - I didn't.

578
00:48:04,130 --> 00:48:06,430
-我是說我沒...  -卡特
- I mean, I didn't-- - Carter.

579
00:48:10,110 --> 00:48:11,250
他聽到了
He heard.

580
00:48:13,450 --> 00:48:15,740
卡特  不要  不可以
Carter, don't. You can't.

581
00:48:22,850 --> 00:48:24,240
發生了什么
What the hell is going on?

582
00:48:26,780 --> 00:48:27,980
你在做什么
What are you doing?

583
00:48:29,020 --> 00:48:30,940
我要從你手中奪回這里的掌控權
I'm taking this place back from you.

584
00:48:34,460 --> 00:48:36,620
你們在這里就是在說這個嗎
That's what you were talking about in here?

585
00:48:36,850 --> 00:48:38,490
是他一個人說的
That's what he was talking about.

586
00:48:42,610 --> 00:48:45,600
換做我  會派人警戒的
See, I would have-- I would have set up some lookouts.

587
00:48:46,810 --> 00:48:49,480
那樣做才明智
That would have been the smart thing.

588
00:48:49,560 --> 00:48:51,140
要是我碰巧
You know, if I happened to--

589
00:48:55,030 --> 00:48:57,870
你真覺得你能從我們手上奪走社區嗎
You really think you're gonna take this community from us?

590
00:48:58,920 --> 00:49:00,660
從格倫手上  從米瓊恩手上
From Glenn? From Michonne?

591
00:49:00,660 --> 00:49:02,350
從達里爾手上  從我手上奪走嗎
From Daryl? From me?

592
00:49:04,120 --> 00:49:08,270
你知道你在跟誰說話嗎
Do you have any idea who you're talking to?

593
00:49:11,100 --> 00:49:12,920
-只是我而已  -什么
- It was just me. - What?

594
00:49:13,150 --> 00:49:14,450
只是我一個人
It was-- it was just me.

595
00:49:14,450 --> 00:49:17,970
殺了我吧
Just-- just kill me.

596
00:49:29,330 --> 00:49:30,230
瑞克
Rick.

597
00:49:34,340 --> 00:49:35,430
我沒事
I'm good.

598
00:49:36,380 --> 00:49:37,380
我沒事
I'm good.

599
00:49:44,750 --> 00:49:46,840
你可以試著跟我們合作
You can try to work with us.

600
00:49:47,700 --> 00:49:49,290
試著生存下去
You can try to survive.

601
00:49:50,870 --> 00:49:52,070
你會這么做嗎
Would you do that?

602
00:50:22,370 --> 00:50:23,270
起作用了
It's working.

603
00:50:25,720 --> 00:50:26,800
你說得沒錯
You were right.

604
00:50:32,670 --> 00:50:36,130
各位  我們要結束這一切
Everyone, we need to finish this.

605
00:50:36,760 --> 00:50:40,200
保持移動  在樹林里沿著尸群站好位
We have to keep moving and fan out down that thing front to back.

606
00:50:40,200 --> 00:50:42,110
就跟游行時的警察一樣
Like we said, cops at a parade.

607
00:50:42,110 --> 00:50:43,960
格倫  你殿后
Glenn, you take the back.

608
00:50:43,960 --> 00:50:45,630
-你拿著另一個對講機  -知道了
- You got the other walkie. - Got it.

609
00:50:45,630 --> 00:50:47,630
要是尸群散了  我們就開槍
If it gets sloppy, we fire our weapons,

610
00:50:47,630 --> 00:50:49,280
把它們引回路上
pull them back on track.

611
00:50:49,890 --> 00:50:50,950
我去前面
I'll hit the front.

612
00:50:50,950 --> 00:50:52,860
好  一個接一個
Okay, one after the other.

613
00:51:40,670 --> 00:51:42,540
托賓  它們偏離了
Tobin, they're breaking off.

614
00:51:42,550 --> 00:51:43,850
你想讓我們怎么做
What do you want us to do?

615
00:51:44,000 --> 00:51:45,780
開槍引它們回來
Fire your guns and draw them back.

616
00:51:53,970 --> 00:51:55,170
出來真舒服
It's nice out.

617
00:51:57,460 --> 00:51:58,450
是啊
Yeah.

618
00:51:59,300 --> 00:52:00,470
希望你不介意
Hope you don't mind.

619
00:52:01,210 --> 00:52:03,440
我想晚上放松一下
I wanted to enjoy the evening a little

620
00:52:03,440 --> 00:52:05,860
我那邊沒門廊
and I don't have a porch over there, so...

621
00:52:13,110 --> 00:52:14,290
拿上你的東西
Get your stuff.

622
00:52:18,170 --> 00:52:20,940
你跟我們一起住這邊
You should stay with us over here.

623
00:52:23,120 --> 00:52:24,240
有房間嗎
You got room?

624
00:52:25,880 --> 00:52:26,990
能擠擠
We'll make it.

625
00:52:28,130 --> 00:52:30,110
我們不需要再那樣做了
We don't need to do that anymore.

626
00:52:32,760 --> 00:52:34,340
我了解你  摩根
I know you, Morgan.

627
00:52:36,720 --> 00:52:38,660
即便是第一次重新相識
Even if this is the first time.

628
00:52:45,510 --> 00:52:46,770
你想抱她嗎
You want to hold her?

629
00:52:54,890 --> 00:52:55,800
好啊
Okay.

630
00:53:02,870 --> 00:53:04,200
這是摩根
This is Morgan.

631
00:53:07,000 --> 00:53:08,180
他是我的朋友
He's a friend of mine.

632
00:53:12,410 --> 00:53:13,300
你好
Hi.

633
00:53:18,230 --> 00:53:19,170
好了
Okay.

634
00:53:24,180 --> 00:53:25,580
讓我好好看看你
Let me have a look at you.

635
00:53:34,370 --> 00:53:36,880
和卡特在武器庫里的那個你
You with that man Carter, in the armory--

636
00:53:37,980 --> 00:53:38,970
那才是你
That's you.

637
00:53:40,590 --> 00:53:42,290
你還是當年那個我在金恩郡認識的人
You're still the same man I met in King county.

638
00:53:42,290 --> 00:53:44,790
那個回來告訴我一切還未結束的人
The one that came back and told me it wasn't over.

639
00:53:46,710 --> 00:53:47,920
那才是你
That was you.

640
00:53:49,880 --> 00:53:52,290
跟我眼前這個人完全一樣
Same you that's right in front of me right now.

641
00:53:57,020 --> 00:53:58,600
我想殺了他
I wanted to kill him.

642
00:54:01,680 --> 00:54:03,730
那樣更簡單
So it would be easier.

643
00:54:06,260 --> 00:54:09,270
那樣我就不用擔心
So I wouldn't have to worry

644
00:54:09,270 --> 00:54:11,610
他捅出什么簍子
about how he could screw up

645
00:54:11,620 --> 00:54:15,550
或再干出什么蠢事  因為他就是那種人
or what stupid thing he'd do next because that's who he is.

646
00:54:15,550 --> 00:54:19,010
他是那種不該在如今存活的人
Just somebody who shouldn't be alive now.

647
00:54:22,270 --> 00:54:23,920
我想殺了他
I wanted to kill him.

648
00:54:27,710 --> 00:54:29,970
但我突然意識到...
But all that hit me and...

649
00:54:31,290 --> 00:54:33,780
我意識到我沒必要殺了他
I realized I didn't have to do it.

650
00:54:41,720 --> 00:54:42,910
他不懂
He doesn't get it.

651
00:54:45,650 --> 00:54:47,090
像他那種人
Somebody like that...

652
00:54:51,470 --> 00:54:53,290
遲早都會死
They're gonna die no matter what.

653
00:55:09,010 --> 00:55:09,960
我死定了
I'm dead.

654
00:55:10,560 --> 00:55:12,440
卡特  深呼吸
Carter, take a breath.

655
00:55:13,010 --> 00:55:13,900
卡特
Carter.

656
00:55:16,850 --> 00:55:18,550
-老天  -安靜
- Oh, god! - be quiet.

657
00:55:20,830 --> 00:55:22,610
-老天  -卡特  卡特
- Oh, god. - Carter. Carter,

658
00:55:23,070 --> 00:55:24,400
你必須安靜
you got to be quiet.

659
00:55:36,110 --> 00:55:36,960
起作用了
It's working.

660
00:55:36,960 --> 00:55:39,370
槍聲又把它們引回路上了
The gunfire is bringing them back on the road.

661
00:55:54,380 --> 00:55:55,490
你做到了  托賓
You got them, Tobin.

662
00:55:56,240 --> 00:55:57,200
收到
Copy that.

663
00:55:58,500 --> 00:55:59,720
剛誰在尖叫
What was that screaming?

664
00:56:01,180 --> 00:56:02,270
是卡特
That was Carter.

665
00:56:02,580 --> 00:56:04,620
他臉被咬了
He got bit right in the face.

666
00:56:04,810 --> 00:56:05,900
我阻止了他
I stopped him.

667
00:56:15,910 --> 00:56:17,940
一小時后  我們把它們送到綠氣球處
We have a good hour until we have 'em to green

668
00:56:17,940 --> 00:56:21,560
轉交給達里爾  薩沙和亞伯拉罕
when we hand them off to Daryl, Sasha, and Abraham.

669
00:56:21,710 --> 00:56:23,900
你回去  告訴所有人發生了什么
Why don't you head back, tell everyone what's happening?

670
00:56:23,900 --> 00:56:25,620
-他們有權知道  -好吧  瑞克  我只是...
- They should know. - Okay, Rick, I just--

671
00:56:25,620 --> 00:56:27,100
你能為我那樣做嗎
Will you do that for me?

672
00:56:33,100 --> 00:56:34,650
我收拾那只
I'll take care of that one.

673
00:56:35,220 --> 00:56:38,470
米瓊恩  你放哨
Michonne, you take point.

674
00:56:41,460 --> 00:56:43,090
我知道這就是現實
I know it's how it is.

675
00:56:44,090 --> 00:56:45,170
我知道
I do.

676
00:56:48,160 --> 00:56:49,170
是啊
Yeah.

677
00:56:50,630 --> 00:56:51,840
我也知道
I do, too.

678
00:57:34,640 --> 00:57:37,930
我只是來拿明天的照明彈的
I was just getting more flares for tomorrow.

679
00:57:50,180 --> 00:57:51,480
我知道我沒有...
I know I haven't--

680
00:57:53,990 --> 00:57:55,700
我只是覺得讓事情
I just-- I just thought it might be best

681
00:57:55,700 --> 00:57:59,280
平息一下  這樣比較好
if I let things be for a while.

682
00:58:00,940 --> 00:58:02,510
羅恩告訴我發生了什么
Ron told me what happened.

683
00:58:03,510 --> 00:58:05,280
是啊  我想和你談談那事
Yeah, I wanted to talk to you about that.

684
00:58:05,280 --> 00:58:06,350
他不該出去
He shouldn't have been out there.

685
00:58:06,360 --> 00:58:07,710
對  他不該出去
No, he shouldn't have.

686
00:58:08,130 --> 00:58:09,060
你說得對
You're right.

687
00:58:11,240 --> 00:58:14,400
但是你不能那樣和他說話  瑞克
But you can't talk to him like that, Rick.

688
00:58:15,410 --> 00:58:16,790
你不能碰他
You can't touch him.

689
00:58:18,690 --> 00:58:19,690
不能是你
Not you.

690
00:58:20,420 --> 00:58:22,860
羅恩必須聽進去我說的每句話
Ron needed to hear every word I said.

691
00:58:22,860 --> 00:58:24,970
所以我才抓住了他  我沒生氣
That's why I grabbed him. I wasn't angry.

692
00:58:24,970 --> 00:58:26,870
我只是在告訴他事實
I was just telling him the truth.

693
00:58:28,390 --> 00:58:32,210
如果由你來說  他是聽不進去的
If it's coming from you, he can't hear it.

694
00:58:33,960 --> 00:58:35,300
你必須明白這點
You got to understand that.

695
00:58:36,730 --> 00:58:38,580
他必須知道如何照顧自己
He needs to know how to handle himself.

696
00:58:38,580 --> 00:58:40,660
-我可以教他  我可以教你  -瑞克
- I can teach him. I can teach you. - Rick.

697
00:58:40,660 --> 00:58:43,300
-你必須知道該怎么做  -瑞克
- You need to know how. - Rick.

698
00:58:46,190 --> 00:58:47,830
當我知道我們可以拿槍時
When I found out we could have them,

699
00:58:47,830 --> 00:58:49,930
我已經讓羅西塔教我了
I asked Rosita to start showing me how.

700
00:58:50,460 --> 00:58:54,810
好嗎  她會教我  然后我教羅恩和山姆
Okay? She's gonna teach me and I'm gonna teach Ron and I'm gonna teach Sam.

701
00:58:58,610 --> 00:59:01,010
你在會上說的話我都聽進去了
I heard what you were saying to us at the meeting.

702
00:59:02,240 --> 00:59:05,650
之前在我屋子里的話也是
And at my house before, you know.

703
00:59:09,110 --> 00:59:11,070
我會抗爭的  瑞克
I am gonna fight, Rick.

704
00:59:39,420 --> 00:59:40,880
好了  這是終點線
All right, this is the finish line.

705
00:59:40,880 --> 00:59:43,390
到綠氣球處后  我們撤退
When we make it to green, we fall back.

706
00:59:43,400 --> 00:59:45,760
溝壟會把它們擋在正路上
The ditches and ridges will keep them on the road.

707
00:59:45,760 --> 00:59:48,660
我們回家  讓達里爾  薩沙和亞伯拉罕
We head home, but Daryl, Sasha, and Abraham

708
00:59:48,660 --> 00:59:51,170
帶它們再走二十英里
take them the rest of the way, 20 miles more.

709
00:59:51,390 --> 00:59:52,500
好了  出發
All right, let's go.

710
00:59:58,710 --> 01:00:00,090
問你個問題
Got a question for you.

711
01:00:02,490 --> 01:00:06,970
在我們明天自駕游之前  收集點信息
Just some intel before our little road trip tomorrow.

712
01:00:07,990 --> 01:00:09,090
問吧
Ask me.

713
01:00:12,110 --> 01:00:13,900
你這樣做是因為想死嗎
You doing this 'cause you want to die?

714
01:00:18,610 --> 01:00:19,580
不是
No.

715
01:00:43,980 --> 01:00:46,080
我們要帶它們走過這里
We're gonna take 'em right past here.

716
01:00:47,090 --> 01:00:49,380
噪音可能會把它們引來
All that noise could distract them.

717
01:00:50,470 --> 01:00:52,430
我們今晚回來干掉它們
We'll clear it on our way back tonight.

718
01:00:53,560 --> 01:00:55,600
明天不能出現任何意外
We don't want any surprises tomorrow.

719
01:01:00,480 --> 01:01:01,490
你做的事
What you've done,

720
01:01:01,690 --> 01:01:03,160
我暫時不會說出去
you're gonna sit with it a while,

721
01:01:03,680 --> 01:01:05,370
因為我明天不想讓你出來
'cause I don't want you out here tomorrow.

722
01:01:05,530 --> 01:01:06,550
你還沒準備好
You're not ready.

723
01:01:07,270 --> 01:01:08,360
你會準備好的
You will be.

724
01:01:10,590 --> 01:01:12,480
不久之后  我會親自確保這點
Some time soon, I'll make sure of it.

725
01:01:12,820 --> 01:01:14,540
然后你再開始贖罪
And then you start to make it right.

726
01:01:16,220 --> 01:01:17,170
謝謝你
Thank you.

727
01:01:46,120 --> 01:01:48,150
我知道這聽起來很瘋狂
I know this sounds insane,

728
01:01:49,790 --> 01:01:52,060
但這就是個瘋狂的世界
but this is an insane world.

729
01:01:52,800 --> 01:01:55,940
我們必須先下手為強
We have to come for them before they come for us.

730
01:01:55,940 --> 01:01:57,200
就這么簡單
It's that simple.

731
01:02:34,850 --> 01:02:36,180
發生了什么
What the hell is happening?

732
01:02:36,250 --> 01:02:37,740
好像是喇叭聲  
It's a horn or something.

733
01:02:39,090 --> 01:02:41,220
隊伍后半部分離開了公路
It's pulling the back half off the road.

734
01:02:42,240 --> 01:02:43,600
天啊
Oh, god.

735
01:02:56,990 --> 01:02:58,800
不管那是什么  都離得很遠
Whatever that is, it's far.

736
01:02:59,360 --> 01:03:01,120
聽起來好像是來自...
It sounds like it's coming from...

737
01:03:01,540 --> 01:03:02,550
家那邊
Home.

738
01:03:15,290 --> 01:03:24,830
您快到家了  
亞歷山大  下個路口右拐
新家園  起價80萬美元

