1
00:00:07,550 --> 00:00:08,450
Rick?

2
00:00:10,490 --> 00:00:12,610
I know this sounds insane,

3
00:00:13,410 --> 00:00:15,400
but this is an insane world.

4
00:00:15,610 --> 00:00:18,970
We have to come for them before they come for us.

5
00:00:18,970 --> 00:00:20,120
It's that simple.

6
00:00:22,460 --> 00:00:24,630
This is where it all starts tomorrow.

7
00:00:25,320 --> 00:00:27,100
Tobin gets in the truck,

8
00:00:27,420 --> 00:00:29,690
opens the exit and we're off.

9
00:00:30,010 --> 00:00:33,630
He hops out, catches up with his team at red

10
00:00:33,630 --> 00:00:35,940
staying on the west side of the road.

11
00:00:36,090 --> 00:00:37,790
Daryl gets on his bike--

12
00:00:38,760 --> 00:00:39,710
You see that?

13
00:00:59,580 --> 00:01:02,630
It's open! We got to do this now!

14
00:01:03,160 --> 00:01:04,630
We're doing this now!

15
00:01:04,760 --> 00:01:06,370
Tobin's group, get moving, go!

16
00:01:06,370 --> 00:01:08,080
No, Rick, we're not ready.

17
00:01:08,080 --> 00:01:09,200
Sasha! Abraham!

18
00:01:09,200 --> 00:01:10,620
Damn straight, we'll do it live.

19
00:01:10,630 --> 00:01:11,780
You meet Daryl at red.

20
00:01:11,780 --> 00:01:13,180
Let him take them through the gauntlet.

21
00:01:13,180 --> 00:01:14,770
- Yeah, we meet at red. - Go!

22
00:01:23,590 --> 00:01:26,270
- Rick, I'll hit the tractor place. - Okay, who else?

23
00:01:26,270 --> 00:01:27,800
We got to take them out or they'll distract the horde.

24
00:01:27,800 --> 00:01:28,920
- I'm here, let me help. - No.

25
00:01:28,920 --> 00:01:30,840
- I'm here! - Do everything I say.

26
00:01:30,840 --> 00:01:33,350
- I will. - Rick, this was supposed to be a dry run.

27
00:01:33,350 --> 00:01:35,350
- Daryl, get ready. - They're coming.

28
00:01:39,250 --> 00:01:40,860
Rick, we haven't even gone through the whole plan.

29
00:01:40,860 --> 00:01:43,280
You want to go back, go back. We're finishing this.

30
00:01:43,500 --> 00:01:46,370
Tobin, you hit it on my signal.

31
00:01:46,540 --> 00:01:49,740
They're heading for home. We don't have a choice.

32
00:01:49,860 --> 00:01:51,970
Get ready to hit the flares.

33
00:01:54,230 --> 00:01:55,350
Now!

34
00:02:13,700 --> 00:02:15,620
Tobin, hit the truck!

35
00:03:23,120 --> 00:03:53,120
m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10m -13 -14 l 13 -14 l 13 12 l -13 12 l -13 -14

36
00:03:23,120 --> 00:03:53,120
m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10

37
00:03:23,120 --> 00:03:53,120
m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10

38
00:03:41,260 --> 00:03:42,630
You were wrong.

39
00:03:53,120 --> 00:04:03,120
m 350 100 l 350 110 l 360 110 l 360 100 m 360 100 m 200 130 l 200 140 l 210 140 l 210 130 m 210 130 m 100 320 l 100 330 l 110 330 l 110 320 m 110 320 m 230 80 l 230 90 l 240 90 l 240 80 m 240 80 m 240 110 l 240 120 l 250 120 l 250 110 m 250 110 m 220 230 l 220 240 l 230 240 l 230 230 m 230 230 m 120 90 l 120 100 l 130 100 l 130 90 m 130 90 m 360 60 l 360 70 l 370 70 l 370 60 m 370 60 m 140 110 l 140 120 l 150 120 l 150 110 m 150 110 m 190 340 l 190 350 l 200 350 l 200 340 m 200 340 m 180 50 l 180 60 l 190 60 l 190 50 m 190 50 m 290 190 l 290 200 l 300 200 l 300 190 m 300 190 m 170 240 l 170 250 l 180 250 l 180 240 m 180 240 m 300 160 l 300 170 l 310 170 l 310 160 m 310 160 m 330 210 l 330 220 l 340 220 l 340 210 m 340 210 m 70 60 l 70 70 l 80 70 l 80 60 m 80 60 m 240 360 l 240 370 l 250 370 l 250 360 m 250 360 m 230 170 l 230 180 l 240 180 l 240 170 m 240 170 m 210 170 l 210 180 l 220 180 l 220 170 m 220 170 m 350 250 l 350 260 l 360 260 l 360 250 m 360 250 m 240 180 l 240 190 l 250 190 l 250 180 m 250 180 m 220 140 l 220 150 l 230 150 l 230 140 m 230 140 m 270 230 l 270 240 l 280 240 l 280 230 m 280 230 m 250 190 l 250 200 l 260 200 l 260 190 m 260 190 m 120 160 l 120 170 l 130 170 l 130 160 m 130 160 m 360 290 l 360 300 l 370 300 l 370 290 m 370 290 m 260 160 l 260 170 l 270 170 l 270 160 m 270 160 m 270 130 l 270 140 l 280 140 l 280 130 m 280 130 m 120 220 l 120 230 l 130 230 l 130 220 m 130 220 m 150 190 l 150 200 l 160 200 l 160 190 m 160 190 m 160 120 l 160 130 l 170 130 l 170 120 m 170 120 m 170 170 l 170 180 l 180 180 l 180 170 m 180 170 m 40 180 l 40 190 l 50 190 l 50 180 m 50 180 m 310 100 l 310 110 l 320 110 l 320 100 m 320 100 m 60 160 l 60 170 l 70 170 l 70 160 m 70 160 m 330 80 l 330 90 l 340 90 l 340 80 m 340 80 m 70 210 l 70 220 l 80 220 l 80 210 m 80 210 m 100 180 l 100 190 l 110 190 l 110 180 m 110 180 m 110 190 l 110 200 l 120 200 l 120 190 m 120 190 m 350 220 l 350 230 l 360 230 l 360 220 m 360 220 m 220 90 l 220 100 l 230 100 l 230 90 m 230 90 m 100 360 l 100 370 l 110 370 l 110 360 m 110 360 m 250 120 l 250 130 l 260 130 l 260 120 m 260 120 m 210 280 l 210 290 l 220 290 l 220 280 m 220 280 m 260 110 l 260 120 l 270 120 l 270 110 m 270 110 m 140 130 l 140 140 l 150 140 l 150 130 m 150 130 m 120 290 l 120 300 l 130 300 l 130 290 m 130 290 m 280 320 l 280 330 l 290 330 l 290 320 m 290 320 m 180 230 l 180 240 l 190 240 l 190 230 m 190 230 m 140 230 l 140 240 l 150 240 l 150 230 m 150 230 m 190 140 l 190 150 l 200 150 l 200 140 m 200 140 m 150 300 l 150 310 l 160 310 l 160 300 m 160 300 m 300 340 l 300 350 l 310 350 l 310 340 m 310 340 m 40 90 l 40 100 l 50 100 l 50 90 m 50 90 m 280 60 l 280 70 l 290 70 l 290 60 m 290 60 m 310 350 l 310 360 l 320 360 l 320 350 m 320 350 m 50 40 l 50 50 l 60 50 l 60 40 m 60 40 m 80 150 l 80 160 l 90 160 l 90 150 m 90 150 m 320 280 l 320 290 l 330 290 l 330 280 m 330 280 m 90 140 l 90 150 l 100 150 l 100 140 m 100 140 m 100 50 l 100 60 l 110 60 l 110 50 m 110 50 m 340 60 l 340 70 l 350 70 l 350 60 m 350 60 m 230 310 l 230 320 l 240 320 l 240 310 m 240 310 m 350 310 l 350 320 l 360 320 l 360 310 m 360 310 m 100 310 l 100 320 l 110 320 l 110 310 m 110 310 m 230 50 l 230 60 l 240 60 l 240 50 m 240 50 m 360 270 l 360 280 l 370 280 l 370 270 m 370 270 m 220 260 l 220 270 l 230 270 l 230 260 m 230 260 m 160 360 l 160 370 l 170 370 l 170 360 m 170 360 m 120 40 l 120 50 l 130 50 l 130 40 m 130 40 m 140 300 l 140 310 l 150 310 l 150 300 m 150 300 m 40 320 l 40 330 l 50 330 l 50 320 m 50 320 m 160 240 l 160 250 l 170 250 l 170 240 m 170 240 m 310 240 l 310 250 l 320 250 l 320 240 m 320 240 m 170 290 l 170 300 l 180 300 l 180 290 m 180 290 m 320 270 l 320 280 l 330 280 l 330 270 m 330 270 m 60 340 l 60 350 l 70 350 l 70 340 m 70 340 m 300 70 l 300 80 l 310 80 l 310 70 m 310 70 m 330 260 l 330 270 l 340 270 l 340 260 m 340 260 m 80 280 l 80 290 l 90 290 l 90 280 m 90 280 m 230 360 l 230 370 l 240 370 l 240 360 m 240 360 m 350 40 l 350 50 l 360 50 l 360 40 m 360 40 m 100 220 l 100 230 l 110 230 l 110 220 m 110 220 m 260 210 l 260 220 l 270 220 l 270 210 m 270 210 m 270 240 l 270 250 l 280 250 l 280 240 m 280 240 m 250 80 l 250 90 l 260 90 l 260 80 m 260 80 m 120 110 l 120 120 l 130 120 l 130 110 m 130 110 m 360 80 l 360 90 l 370 90 l 370 80 m 370 80 m 260 150 l 260 160 l 270 160 l 270 150 m 270 150 m 190 280 l 190 290 l 200 290 l 200 280 m 200 280 m 280 200 l 280 210 l 290 210 l 290 200 m 290 200 m 180 110 l 180 120 l 190 120 l 190 110 m 190 110 m 160 230 l 160 240 l 170 240 l 170 230 m 170 230 m 50 220 l 50 230 l 60 230 l 60 220 m 60 220 m 170 220 l 170 230 l 180 230 l 180 220 m 180 220 m 300 140 l 300 150 l 310 150 l 310 140 m 310 140 m 70 80 l 70 90 l 80 90 l 80 80 m 80 80 m 320 80 l 320 90 l 330 90 l 330 80 m 330 80 m 350 130 l 350 140 l 360 140 l 360 130 m 360 130 m 90 100 l 90 110 l 100 110 l 100 100 m 100 100 m 330 130 l 330 140 l 340 140 l 340 130 m 340 130 m 210 70 l 210 80 l 220 80 l 220 70 m 220 70 m 350 270 l 350 280 l 360 280 l 360 270 m 360 270 m 90 360 l 90 370 l 100 370 l 100 360 m 100 360 m 240 120 l 240 130 l 250 130 l 250 120 m 250 120 m 220 120 l 220 130 l 230 130 l 230 120 m 230 120 m 270 150 l 270 160 l 280 160 l 280 150 m 280 150 m 130 210 l 130 220 l 140 220 l 140 210 m 140 210 m 180 180 l 180 190 l 190 190 l 190 180 m 190 180 m 290 260 l 290 270 l 300 270 l 300 260 m 300 260 m 190 190 l 190 200 l 200 200 l 200 190 m 200 190 m 170 150 l 170 160 l 180 160 l 180 150 m 180 150 m 40 40 l 40 50 l 50 50 l 50 40 m 50 40 m 310 280 l 310 290 l 320 290 l 320 280 m 320 280 m 50 170 l 50 180 l 60 180 l 60 170 m 60 170 m 80 180 l 80 190 l 90 190 l 90 180 m 90 180 m 320 70 l 320 80 l 330 80 l 330 70 m 330 70 m 60 140 l 60 150 l 70 150 l 70 140 m 70 140 m 330 60 l 330 70 l 340 70 l 340 60 m 340 60 m 70 230 l 70 240 l 80 240 l 80 230 m 80 230 m 100 160 l 100 170 l 110 170 l 110 160 m 110 160 m 340 290 l 340 300 l 350 300 l 350 290 m 350 290 m 110 130 l 110 140 l 120 140 l 120 130 m 120 130 m 240 270 l 240 280 l 250 280 l 250 270 m 250 270 m 200 350 l 200 360 l 210 360 l 210 350 m 210 350 m 250 260 l 250 270 l 260 270 l 260 260 m 260 260 m 210 340 l 210 350 l 220 350 l 220 340 m 220 340 m 260 90 l 260 100 l 270 100 l 270 90 m 270 90 m 220 330 l 220 340 l 230 340 l 230 330 m 230 330 m 270 40 l 270 50 l 280 50 l 280 40 m 280 40 m 360 120 l 360 130 l 370 130 l 370 120 m 370 120 m 130 300 l 130 310 l 140 310 l 140 300 m 140 300 m 280 340 l 280 350 l 290 350 l 290 340 m 290 340 m 180 210 l 180 220 l 190 220 l 190 210 m 190 210 m 190 240 l 190 250 l 200 250 l 200 240 m 200 240 m 320 360 l 320 370 l 330 370 l 330 360 m 330 360 m 300 320 l 300 330 l 310 330 l 310 320 m 310 320 m 160 350 l 160 360 l 170 360 l 170 350 m 170 350 m 50 100 l 50 110 l 60 110 l 60 100 m 60 100 m 320 300 l 320 310 l 330 310 l 330 300 m 330 300 m 300 100 l 300 110 l 310 110 l 310 100 m 310 100 m 330 310 l 330 320 l 340 320 l 340 310 m 340 310 m 340 40 l 340 50 l 350 50 l 350 40 m 350 40 m 230 330 l 230 340 l 240 340 l 240 330 m 240 330 m 300 360 l 300 370 l 310 370 l 310 360 m 310 360 m 240 340 l 240 350 l 250 350 l 250 340 m 250 340 m 200 260 l 200 270 l 210 270 l 210 260 m 210 260 m 250 350 l 250 360 l 260 360 l 260 350 m 260 350 m 230 70 l 230 80 l 240 80 l 240 70 m 240 70 m 210 270 l 210 280 l 220 280 l 220 270 m 220 270 m 260 320 l 260 330 l 270 330 l 270 320 m 270 320 m 220 240 l 220 250 l 230 250 l 230 240 m 230 240 m 270 290 l 270 300 l 280 300 l 280 290 m 280 290 m 130 70 l 130 80 l 140 80 l 140 70 m 140 70 m 180 280 l 180 290 l 190 290 l 190 280 m 190 280 m 140 280 l 140 290 l 150 290 l 150 280 m 150 280 m 150 250 l 150 260 l 160 260 l 160 250 m 160 250 m 40 340 l 40 350 l 50 350 l 50 340 m 50 340 m 180 60 l 180 70 l 190 70 l 190 60 m 190 60 m 160 260 l 160 270 l 170 270 l 170 260 m 170 260 m 170 270 l 170 280 l 180 280 l 180 270 m 180 270 m 60 320 l 60 330 l 70 330 l 70 320 m 70 320 m 300 50 l 300 60 l 310 60 l 310 50 m 310 50 m 330 240 l 330 250 l 340 250 l 340 240 m 340 240 m 310 160 l 310 170 l 320 170 l 320 160 m 320 160 m 80 300 l 80 310 l 90 310 l 90 300 m 90 300 m 320 190 l 320 200 l 330 200 l 330 190 m 330 190 m 100 200 l 100 210 l 110 210 l 110 200 m 110 200 m 250 280 l 250 290 l 260 290 l 260 280 m 260 280 m 80 360 l 80 370 l 90 370 l 90 360 m 90 360 m 210 120 l 210 130 l 220 130 l 220 120 m 220 120 m 110 250 l 110 260 l 120 260 l 120 250 m 120 250 m 220 190 l 220 200 l 230 200 l 230 190 m 230 190 m 270 260 l 270 270 l 280 270 l 280 260 m 280 260 m 250 60 l 250 70 l 260 70 l 260 60 m 260 60 m 360 100 l 360 110 l 370 110 l 370 100 m 370 100 m 260 130 l 260 140 l 270 140 l 270 130 m 270 130 m 130 80 l 130 90 l 140 90 l 140 80 m 140 80 m 270 160 l 270 170 l 280 170 l 280 160 m 280 160 m 140 70 l 140 80 l 150 80 l 150 70 m 150 70 m 190 300 l 190 310 l 200 310 l 200 300 m 200 300 m 40 250 l 40 260 l 50 260 l 50 250 m 50 250 m 50 200 l 50 210 l 60 210 l 60 200 m 60 200 m 290 230 l 290 240 l 300 240 l 300 230 m 300 230 m 190 40 l 190 50 l 200 50 l 200 40 m 200 40 m 170 200 l 170 210 l 180 210 l 180 200 m 180 200 m 60 270 l 60 280 l 70 280 l 70 270 m 70 270 m 300 120 l 300 130 l 310 130 l 310 120 m 310 120 m 40 150 l 40 160 l 50 160 l 50 150 m 50 150 m 70 100 l 70 110 l 80 110 l 80 100 m 80 100 m 320 100 l 320 110 l 330 110 l 330 100 m 330 100 m 200 80 l 200 90 l 210 90 l 210 80 m 210 80 m 240 140 l 240 150 l 250 150 l 250 140 m 250 140 m 220 100 l 220 110 l 230 110 l 230 100 m 230 100 m 140 360 l 140 370 l 150 370 l 150 360 m 150 360 m 130 170 l 130 180 l 140 180 l 140 170 m 140 170 m 270 90 l 270 100 l 280 100 l 280 90 m 280 90 m 140 140 l 140 150 l 150 150 l 150 140 m 150 140 m 120 260 l 120 270 l 130 270 l 130 260 m 130 260 m 280 290 l 280 300 l 290 300 l 290 290 m 290 290 m 150 290 l 150 300 l 160 300 l 160 290 m 160 290 m 40 60 l 40 70 l 50 70 l 50 60 m 50 60 m 70 190 l 70 200 l 80 200 l 80 190 m 80 190 m 80 120 l 80 130 l 90 130 l 90 120 m 90 120 m 320 330 l 320 340 l 330 340 l 330 330 m 330 330 m 90 170 l 90 180 l 100 180 l 100 170 m 100 170 m 330 40 l 330 50 l 340 50 l 340 40 m 340 40 m 70 250 l 70 260 l 80 260 l 80 250 m 80 250 m 290 360 l 290 370 l 300 370 l 300 360 m 300 360 m 100 60 l 100 70 l 110 70 l 110 60 m 110 60 m 230 260 l 230 270 l 240 270 l 240 260 m 240 260 m 220 50 l 220 60 l 230 60 l 230 50 m 230 50 m 200 210 l 200 220 l 210 220 l 210 210 m 210 210 m 360 240 l 360 250 l 370 250 l 370 240 m 370 240 m 260 310 l 260 320 l 270 320 l 270 310 m 270 310 m 180 270 l 180 280 l 190 280 l 190 270 m 190 270 m 140 350 l 140 360 l 150 360 l 150 350 m 150 350 m 300 300 l 300 310 l 310 310 l 310 300 m 310 300 m 280 100 l 280 110 l 290 110 l 290 100 m 290 100 m 170 320 l 170 330 l 180 330 l 180 320 m 180 320 m 320 240 l 320 250 l 330 250 l 330 240 m 330 240 m 60 70 l 60 80 l 70 80 l 70 70 m 70 70 m 300 80 l 300 90 l 310 90 l 310 80 m 310 80 m 70 300 l 70 310 l 80 310 l 80 300 m 80 300 m 310 130 l 310 140 l 320 140 l 320 130 m 320 130 m 100 90 l 100 100 l 110 100 l 110 90 m 110 90 m 340 100 l 340 110 l 350 110 l 350 100 m 350 100 m 80 330 l 80 340 l 90 340 l 90 330 m 90 330 m 90 200 l 90 210 l 100 210 l 100 200 m 100 200 m 240 280 l 240 290 l 250 290 l 250 280 m 250 280 m 70 360 l 70 370 l 80 370 l 80 360 m 80 360 m 200 120 l 200 130 l 210 130 l 210 120 m 210 120 m 100 350 l 100 360 l 110 360 l 110 350 m 110 350 m 250 330 l 250 340 l 260 340 l 260 330 m 260 330 m 260 220 l 260 230 l 270 230 l 270 220 m 270 220 m 240 100 l 240 110 l 250 110 l 250 100 m 250 100 m 250 110 l 250 120 l 260 120 l 260 110 m 260 110 m 120 80 l 120 90 l 130 90 l 130 80 m 130 80 m 360 50 l 360 60 l 370 60 l 370 50 m 370 50 m 180 340 l 180 350 l 190 350 l 190 340 m 190 340 m 140 100 l 140 110 l 150 110 l 150 100 m 150 100 m 190 350 l 190 360 l 200 360 l 200 350 m 200 350 m 40 200 l 40 210 l 50 210 l 50 200 m 50 200 m 280 170 l 280 180 l 290 180 l 290 170 m 290 170 m 180 40 l 180 50 l 190 50 l 190 40 m 190 40 m 290 120 l 290 130 l 300 130 l 300 120 m 300 120 m 190 90 l 190 100 l 200 100 l 200 90 m 200 90 m 60 300 l 60 310 l 70 310 l 70 300 m 70 300 m 300 190 l 300 200 l 310 200 l 310 190 m 310 190 m 330 220 l 330 230 l 340 230 l 340 220 m 340 220 m 70 70 l 70 80 l 80 80 l 80 70 m 80 70 m 310 180 l 310 190 l 320 190 l 320 180 m 320 180 m 340 130 l 340 140 l 350 140 l 350 130 m 350 130 m 80 80 l 80 90 l 90 90 l 90 80 m 90 80 m 350 160 l 350 170 l 360 170 l 360 160 m 360 160 m 330 160 l 330 170 l 340 170 l 340 160 m 340 160 m 200 190 l 200 200 l 210 200 l 210 190 m 210 190 m 100 260 l 100 270 l 110 270 l 110 260 m 110 260 m 260 250 l 260 260 l 270 260 l 270 250 m 270 250 m 240 170 l 240 180 l 250 180 l 250 170 m 250 170 m 220 170 l 220 180 l 230 180 l 230 170 m 230 170 m 120 150 l 120 160 l 130 160 l 130 150 m 130 150 m 130 140 l 130 150 l 140 150 l 140 140 m 140 140 m 270 180 l 270 190 l 280 190 l 280 180 m 280 180 m 290 210 l 290 220 l 300 220 l 300 210 m 300 210 m 60 250 l 60 260 l 70 260 l 70 250 m 70 250 m 80 70 l 80 80 l 90 80 l 90 70 m 90 70 m 320 40 l 320 50 l 330 50 l 330 40 m 330 40 m 280 360 l 280 370 l 290 370 l 290 360 m 290 360 m 200 100 l 200 110 l 210 110 l 210 100 m 210 100 m 230 230 l 230 240 l 240 240 l 240 230 m 240 230 m 210 110 l 210 120 l 220 120 l 220 110 m 220 110 m 240 240 l 240 250 l 250 250 l 250 240 m 250 240 m 200 320 l 200 330 l 210 330 l 210 320 m 210 320 m 250 130 l 250 140 l 260 140 l 260 130 m 260 130 m 210 290 l 210 300 l 220 300 l 220 290 m 220 290 m 260 100 l 260 110 l 270 110 l 270 100 m 270 100 m 140 120 l 140 130 l 150 130 l 150 120 m 150 120 m 280 310 l 280 320 l 290 320 l 290 310 m 290 310 m 180 220 l 180 230 l 190 230 l 190 220 m 190 220 m 160 100 l 160 110 l 170 110 l 170 100 m 170 100 m 140 220 l 140 230 l 150 230 l 150 220 m 150 220 m 190 150 l 190 160 l 200 160 l 200 150 m 200 150 m 150 310 l 150 320 l 160 320 l 160 310 m 160 310 m 40 80 l 40 90 l 50 90 l 50 80 m 50 80 m 280 50 l 280 60 l 290 60 l 290 50 m 290 50 m 310 320 l 310 330 l 320 330 l 320 320 m 320 320 m 60 100 l 60 110 l 70 110 l 70 100 m 70 100 m 330 340 l 330 350 l 340 350 l 340 340 m 340 340 m 70 270 l 70 280 l 80 280 l 80 270 m 80 270 m 100 40 l 100 50 l 110 50 l 110 40 m 110 40 m 340 330 l 340 340 l 350 340 l 350 330 m 350 330 m 80 200 l 80 210 l 90 210 l 90 200 m 90 200 m 60 360 l 60 370 l 70 370 l 70 360 m 70 360 m 350 280 l 350 290 l 360 290 l 360 280 m 360 280 m 240 230 l 240 240 l 250 240 l 250 230 m 250 230 m 200 230 l 200 240 l 210 240 l 210 230 m 210 230 m 100 300 l 100 310 l 110 310 l 110 300 m 110 300 m 250 220 l 250 230 l 260 230 l 260 220 m 260 220 m 210 220 l 210 230 l 220 230 l 220 220 m 220 220 m 360 160 l 360 170 l 370 170 l 370 160 m 370 160 m 140 330 l 140 340 l 150 340 l 150 330 m 150 330 m 170 40 l 170 50 l 180 50 l 180 40 m 180 40 m 150 200 l 150 210 l 160 210 l 160 200 m 160 200 m 300 280 l 300 290 l 310 290 l 310 280 m 310 280 m 40 310 l 40 320 l 50 320 l 50 310 m 50 310 m 280 120 l 280 130 l 290 130 l 290 120 m 290 120 m 310 250 l 310 260 l 320 260 l 320 250 m 320 250 m 50 300 l 50 310 l 60 310 l 60 300 m 60 300 m 320 260 l 320 270 l 330 270 l 330 260 m 330 260 m 300 60 l 300 70 l 310 70 l 310 60 m 310 60 m 70 320 l 70 330 l 80 330 l 80 320 m 80 320 m 340 80 l 340 90 l 350 90 l 350 80 m 350 80 m 240 300 l 240 310 l 250 310 l 250 300 m 250 300 m 100 330 l 100 340 l 110 340 l 110 330 m 110 330 m 230 110 l 230 120 l 240 120 l 240 110 m 240 110 m 120 360 l 120 370 l 130 370 l 130 360 m 130 360 m 260 200 l 260 210 l 270 210 l 270 200 m 270 200 m 270 250 l 270 260 l 280 260 l 280 250 m 280 250 m 250 90 l 250 100 l 260 100 l 260 90 m 260 90 m 120 100 l 120 110 l 130 110 l 130 100 m 130 100 m 360 70 l 360 80 l 370 80 l 370 70 m 370 70 m 180 320 l 180 330 l 190 330 l 190 320 m 190 320 m 190 290 l 190 300 l 200 300 l 200 290 m 200 290 m 40 220 l 40 230 l 50 230 l 50 220 m 50 220 m 280 190 l 280 200 l 290 200 l 290 190 m 290 190 m 180 100 l 180 110 l 190 110 l 190 100 m 190 100 m 160 220 l 160 230 l 170 230 l 170 220 m 170 220 m 290 180 l 290 190 l 300 190 l 300 180 m 300 180 m 40 120 l 40 130 l 50 130 l 50 120 m 50 120 m 330 200 l 330 210 l 340 210 l 340 200 m 340 200 m 310 40 l 310 50 l 320 50 l 320 40 m 320 40 m 80 100 l 80 110 l 90 110 l 90 100 m 90 100 m 350 180 l 350 190 l 360 190 l 360 180 m 360 180 m 330 140 l 330 150 l 340 150 l 340 140 m 340 140 m 200 50 l 200 60 l 210 60 l 210 50 m 210 50 m 100 240 l 100 250 l 110 250 l 110 240 m 110 240 m 340 210 l 340 220 l 350 220 l 350 210 m 350 210 m 110 210 l 110 220 l 120 220 l 120 210 m 120 210 m 270 220 l 270 230 l 280 230 l 280 220 m 280 220 m 250 180 l 250 190 l 260 190 l 260 180 m 260 180 m 120 170 l 120 180 l 130 180 l 130 170 m 130 170 m 270 120 l 270 130 l 280 130 l 280 120 m 280 120 m 140 190 l 140 200 l 150 200 l 150 190 m 150 190 m 180 130 l 180 140 l 190 140 l 190 130 m 190 130 m 160 130 l 160 140 l 170 140 l 170 130 m 170 130 m 290 270 l 290 280 l 300 280 l 300 270 m 300 270 m 170 160 l 170 170 l 180 170 l 180 160 m 180 160 m 300 240 l 300 250 l 310 250 l 310 240 m 310 240 m 70 140 l 70 150 l 80 150 l 80 140 m 80 140 m 50 180 l 50 190 l 60 190 l 60 180 m 60 180 m 80 170 l 80 180 l 90 180 l 90 170 m 90 170 m 320 60 l 320 70 l 330 70 l 330 60 m 330 60 m 90 40 l 90 50 l 100 50 l 100 40 m 100 40 m 330 70 l 330 80 l 340 80 l 340 70 m 340 70 m 70 200 l 70 210 l 80 210 l 80 200 m 80 200 m 50 360 l 50 370 l 60 370 l 60 360 m 60 360 m 230 250 l 230 260 l 240 260 l 240 250 m 240 250 m 210 90 l 210 100 l 220 100 l 220 90 m 220 90 m 350 330 l 350 340 l 360 340 l 360 330 m 360 330 m 220 60 l 220 70 l 230 70 l 230 60 m 230 60 m 250 270 l 250 280 l 260 280 l 260 270 m 260 270 m 210 350 l 210 360 l 220 360 l 220 350 m 220 350 m 260 80 l 260 90 l 270 90 l 270 80 m 270 80 m 120 300 l 120 310 l 130 310 l 130 300 m 130 300 m 150 110 l 150 120 l 160 120 l 160 110 m 160 110 m 130 310 l 130 320 l 140 320 l 140 310 m 140 310 m 280 330 l 280 340 l 290 340 l 290 330 m 290 330 m 290 280 l 290 290 l 300 290 l 300 280 m 300 280 m 170 90 l 170 100 l 180 100 l 180 90 m 180 90 m 150 330 l 150 340 l 160 340 l 160 330 m 160 330 m 300 350 l 300 360 l 310 360 l 310 350 m 310 350 m 40 100 l 40 110 l 50 110 l 50 100 m 50 100 m 310 340 l 310 350 l 320 350 l 320 340 m 320 340 m 320 290 l 320 300 l 330 300 l 330 290 m 330 290 m 60 80 l 60 90 l 70 90 l 70 80 m 70 80 m 330 320 l 330 330 l 340 330 l 340 320 m 340 320 m 100 100 l 100 110 l 110 110 l 110 100 m 110 100 m 340 70 l 340 80 l 350 80 l 350 70 m 350 70 m 350 300 l 350 310 l 360 310 l 360 300 m 360 300 m 240 330 l 240 340 l 250 340 l 250 330 m 250 330 m 200 250 l 200 260 l 210 260 l 210 250 m 210 250 m 100 280 l 100 290 l 110 290 l 110 280 m 110 280 m 250 200 l 250 210 l 260 210 l 260 200 m 260 200 m 210 200 l 210 210 l 220 210 l 220 200 m 220 200 m 260 350 l 260 360 l 270 360 l 270 350 m 270 350 m 270 340 l 270 350 l 280 350 l 280 340 m 280 340 m 130 320 l 130 330 l 140 330 l 140 320 m 140 320 m 190 220 l 190 230 l 200 230 l 200 220 m 200 220 m 40 330 l 40 340 l 50 340 l 50 330 m 50 330 m 280 140 l 280 150 l 290 150 l 290 140 m 290 140 m 160 250 l 160 260 l 170 260 l 170 250 m 170 250 m 310 270 l 310 280 l 320 280 l 320 270 m 320 270 m 50 280 l 50 290 l 60 290 l 60 280 m 60 280 m 290 150 l 290 160 l 300 160 l 300 150 m 300 150 m 170 280 l 170 290 l 180 290 l 180 280 m 180 280 m 320 200 l 320 210 l 330 210 l 330 200 m 330 200 m 300 40 l 300 50 l 310 50 l 310 40 m 310 40 m 70 340 l 70 350 l 80 350 l 80 340 m 80 340 m 310 170 l 310 180 l 320 180 l 320 170 m 320 170 m 200 160 l 200 170 l 210 170 l 210 160 m 210 160 m 250 290 l 250 300 l 260 300 l 260 290 m 260 290 m 210 130 l 210 140 l 220 140 l 220 130 m 220 130 m 260 260 l 260 270 l 270 270 l 270 260 m 270 260 m 240 60 l 240 70 l 250 70 l 250 60 m 250 60 m 220 180 l 220 190 l 230 190 l 230 180 m 230 180 m 250 70 l 250 80 l 260 80 l 260 70 m 260 70 m 120 120 l 120 130 l 130 130 l 130 120 m 130 120 m 360 90 l 360 100 l 370 100 l 370 90 m 370 90 m 260 120 l 260 130 l 270 130 l 270 120 m 270 120 m 130 90 l 130 100 l 140 100 l 140 90 m 140 90 m 190 310 l 190 320 l 200 320 l 200 310 m 200 310 m 150 150 l 150 160 l 160 160 l 160 150 m 160 150 m 40 240 l 40 250 l 50 250 l 50 240 m 50 240 m 50 210 l 50 220 l 60 220 l 60 210 m 60 210 m 290 160 l 290 170 l 300 170 l 300 160 m 300 160 m 170 210 l 170 220 l 180 220 l 180 210 m 180 210 m 60 260 l 60 270 l 70 270 l 70 260 m 70 260 m 40 140 l 40 150 l 50 150 l 50 140 m 50 140 m 50 150 l 50 160 l 60 160 l 60 150 m 60 150 m 80 40 l 80 50 l 90 50 l 90 40 m 90 40 m 40 360 l 40 370 l 50 370 l 50 360 m 50 360 m 330 120 l 330 130 l 340 130 l 340 120 m 340 120 m 200 70 l 200 80 l 210 80 l 210 70 m 210 70 m 100 140 l 100 150 l 110 150 l 110 140 m 110 140 m 210 60 l 210 70 l 220 70 l 220 60 m 220 60 m 110 230 l 110 240 l 120 240 l 120 230 m 120 230 m 350 260 l 350 270 l 360 270 l 360 260 m 360 260 m 240 130 l 240 140 l 250 140 l 250 130 m 250 130 m 220 130 l 220 140 l 230 140 l 230 130 m 230 130 m 200 290 l 200 300 l 210 300 l 210 290 m 210 290 m 360 320 l 360 330 l 370 330 l 370 320 m 370 320 m 260 70 l 260 80 l 270 80 l 270 70 m 270 70 m 130 180 l 130 190 l 140 190 l 140 180 m 140 180 m 270 140 l 270 150 l 280 150 l 280 140 m 280 140 m 140 170 l 140 180 l 150 180 l 150 170 m 150 170 m 120 250 l 120 260 l 130 260 l 130 250 m 130 250 m 280 280 l 280 290 l 290 290 l 290 280 m 290 280 m 140 270 l 140 280 l 150 280 l 150 270 m 150 270 m 190 180 l 190 190 l 200 190 l 200 180 m 200 180 m 170 140 l 170 150 l 180 150 l 180 140 m 180 140 m 300 220 l 300 230 l 310 230 l 310 220 m 310 220 m 40 50 l 40 60 l 50 60 l 50 50 m 50 50 m 320 320 l 320 330 l 330 330 l 330 320 m 330 320 m 60 150 l 60 160 l 70 160 l 70 150 m 70 150 m 90 180 l 90 190 l 100 190 l 100 180 m 100 180 m 340 340 l 340 350 l 350 350 l 350 340 m 350 340 m 80 250 l 80 260 l 90 260 l 90 250 m 90 250 m 230 270 l 230 280 l 240 280 l 240 270 m 240 270 m 110 120 l 110 130 l 120 130 l 120 120 m 120 120 m 260 360 l 260 370 l 270 370 l 270 360 m 270 360 m 240 200 l 240 210 l 250 210 l 250 200 m 250 200 m 200 200 l 200 210 l 210 210 l 210 200 m 210 200 m 220 300 l 220 310 l 230 310 l 230 300 m 230 300 m 120 320 l 120 330 l 130 330 l 130 320 m 130 320 m 360 130 l 360 140 l 370 140 l 370 130 m 370 130 m 130 290 l 130 300 l 140 300 l 140 290 m 140 290 m 280 350 l 280 360 l 290 360 l 290 350 m 290 350 m 180 260 l 180 270 l 190 270 l 190 260 m 190 260 m 160 60 l 160 70 l 170 70 l 170 60 m 170 60 m 300 330 l 300 340 l 310 340 l 310 330 m 310 330 m 40 280 l 40 290 l 50 290 l 50 280 m 50 280 m 280 90 l 280 100 l 290 100 l 290 90 m 290 90 m 160 280 l 160 290 l 170 290 l 170 280 m 170 280 m 170 330 l 170 340 l 180 340 l 180 330 m 180 330 m 320 310 l 320 320 l 330 320 l 330 310 m 330 310 m 60 60 l 60 70 l 70 70 l 70 60 m 70 60 m 330 300 l 330 310 l 340 310 l 340 300 m 340 300 m 210 360 l 210 370 l 220 370 l 220 360 m 220 360 m 100 80 l 100 90 l 110 90 l 110 80 m 110 80 m 80 320 l 80 330 l 90 330 l 90 320 m 90 320 m 230 320 l 230 330 l 240 330 l 240 320 m 240 320 m 90 210 l 90 220 l 100 220 l 100 210 m 100 210 m 100 340 l 100 350 l 110 350 l 110 340 m 110 340 m 230 60 l 230 70 l 240 70 l 240 60 m 240 60 m 240 90 l 240 100 l 250 100 l 250 90 m 250 90 m 120 70 l 120 80 l 130 80 l 130 70 m 130 70 m 360 40 l 360 50 l 370 50 l 370 40 m 370 40 m 130 60 l 130 70 l 140 70 l 140 60 m 140 60 m 180 290 l 180 300 l 190 300 l 190 290 m 190 290 m 190 320 l 190 330 l 200 330 l 200 320 m 200 320 m 150 240 l 150 250 l 160 250 l 160 240 m 160 240 m 40 350 l 40 360 l 50 360 l 50 350 m 50 350 m 280 160 l 280 170 l 290 170 l 290 160 m 290 160 m 160 270 l 160 280 l 170 280 l 170 270 m 170 270 m 170 260 l 170 270 l 180 270 l 180 260 m 180 260 m 60 330 l 60 340 l 70 340 l 70 330 m 70 330 m 70 40 l 70 50 l 80 50 l 80 40 m 80 40 m 320 120 l 320 130 l 330 130 l 330 120 m 330 120 m 360 360 l 360 370 l 370 370 l 370 360 m 370 360 m 90 300 l 90 310 l 100 310 l 100 300 m 100 300 m 210 190 l 210 200 l 220 200 l 220 190 m 220 190 m 110 240 l 110 250 l 120 250 l 120 240 m 120 240 m 270 210 l 270 220 l 280 220 l 280 210 m 280 210 m 260 180 l 260 190 l 270 190 l 270 180 m 270 180 m 270 190 l 270 200 l 280 200 l 280 190 m 280 190 m 120 200 l 120 210 l 130 210 l 130 200 m 130 200 m 180 140 l 180 150 l 190 150 l 190 140 m 190 140 m 160 180 l 160 190 l 170 190 l 170 180 m 170 180 m 60 240 l 60 250 l 70 250 l 70 240 m 70 240 m 40 160 l 40 170 l 50 170 l 50 160 m 50 160 m 50 130 l 50 140 l 60 140 l 60 130 m 60 130 m 80 60 l 80 70 l 90 70 l 90 60 m 90 60 m 60 180 l 60 190 l 70 190 l 70 180 m 70 180 m 350 140 l 350 150 l 360 150 l 360 140 m 360 140 m 330 100 l 330 110 l 340 110 l 340 100 m 340 100 m 100 120 l 100 130 l 110 130 l 110 120 m 110 120 m 250 360 l 250 370 l 260 370 l 260 360 m 260 360 m 230 200 l 230 210 l 240 210 l 240 200 m 240 200 m 350 200 l 350 210 l 360 210 l 360 200 m 360 200 m 240 150 l 240 160 l 250 160 l 250 150 m 250 150 m 200 310 l 200 320 l 210 320 l 210 310 m 210 310 m 140 150 l 140 160 l 150 160 l 150 150 m 150 150 m 120 270 l 120 280 l 130 280 l 130 270 m 130 270 m 150 60 l 150 70 l 160 70 l 160 60 m 160 60 m 130 260 l 130 270 l 140 270 l 140 260 m 140 260 m 280 300 l 280 310 l 290 310 l 290 300 m 290 300 m 180 170 l 180 180 l 190 180 l 190 170 m 190 170 m 190 120 l 190 130 l 200 130 l 200 120 m 200 120 m 170 120 l 170 130 l 180 130 l 180 120 m 180 120 m 150 280 l 150 290 l 160 290 l 160 280 m 160 280 m 300 200 l 300 210 l 310 210 l 310 200 m 310 200 m 40 70 l 40 80 l 50 80 l 50 70 m 50 70 m 280 40 l 280 50 l 290 50 l 290 40 m 290 40 m 80 130 l 80 140 l 90 140 l 90 130 m 90 130 m 320 340 l 320 350 l 330 350 l 330 340 m 330 340 m 60 130 l 60 140 l 70 140 l 70 130 m 70 130 m 100 70 l 100 80 l 110 80 l 110 70 m 110 70 m 240 220 l 240 230 l 250 230 l 250 220 m 250 220 m 200 220 l 200 230 l 210 230 l 210 220 m 210 220 m 250 230 l 250 240 l 260 240 l 260 230 m 260 230 m 210 230 l 210 240 l 220 240 l 220 230 m 220 230 m 220 280 l 220 290 l 230 290 l 230 280 m 230 280 m 270 330 l 270 340 l 280 340 l 280 330 m 280 330 m 360 150 l 360 160 l 370 160 l 370 150 m 370 150 m 180 240 l 180 250 l 190 250 l 190 240 m 190 240 m 290 320 l 290 330 l 300 330 l 300 320 m 300 320 m 190 210 l 190 220 l 200 220 l 200 210 m 200 210 m 170 50 l 170 60 l 180 60 l 180 50 m 180 50 m 150 210 l 150 220 l 160 220 l 160 210 m 160 210 m 40 300 l 40 310 l 50 310 l 50 300 m 50 300 m 280 110 l 280 120 l 290 120 l 290 110 m 290 110 m 160 300 l 160 310 l 170 310 l 170 300 m 170 300 m 170 310 l 170 320 l 180 320 l 180 310 m 180 310 m 60 40 l 60 50 l 70 50 l 70 40 m 70 40 m 300 90 l 300 100 l 310 100 l 310 90 m 310 90 m 330 280 l 330 290 l 340 290 l 340 280 m 340 280 m 70 330 l 70 340 l 80 340 l 80 330 m 80 330 m 310 120 l 310 130 l 320 130 l 320 120 m 320 120 m 80 340 l 80 350 l 90 350 l 90 340 m 90 340

40
00:04:46,180 --> 00:04:46,980
Ron.

41
00:04:56,970 --> 00:04:57,890
Thank you.

42
00:04:58,030 --> 00:04:58,930
Of course.

43
00:05:02,380 --> 00:05:03,210
Okay.

44
00:05:13,430 --> 00:05:14,280
Glenn.

45
00:05:15,420 --> 00:05:16,930
Glenn, what happened? Are you okay?

46
00:05:16,930 --> 00:05:17,810
I'm okay.

47
00:05:18,780 --> 00:05:20,310
You guys look like shit.

48
00:05:23,740 --> 00:05:25,630
She's fine. She's fine. She's okay.

49
00:05:28,330 --> 00:05:29,230
Tara?

50
00:05:30,210 --> 00:05:31,230
I'm okay.

51
00:05:31,810 --> 00:05:33,170
You just check on them.

52
00:05:35,240 --> 00:05:36,720
- I'm okay. - What happened?

53
00:05:36,720 --> 00:05:37,860
We were out there.

54
00:05:39,330 --> 00:05:42,260
The walkers and-- we're all right.

55
00:05:44,230 --> 00:05:45,770
Got winged by a ricochet.

56
00:05:48,400 --> 00:05:49,450
It's all right.

57
00:05:53,310 --> 00:05:54,660
Holy shit.

58
00:05:57,830 --> 00:05:58,910
Thank god...

59
00:05:59,920 --> 00:06:01,550
nothing happened to your hair.

60
00:06:06,110 --> 00:06:08,400
Okay, Eugene's freaking me out.

61
00:06:08,640 --> 00:06:10,960
Somebody want to send Noah in here to protect me?

62
00:06:57,500 --> 00:06:58,590
You were right.

63
00:07:00,680 --> 00:07:01,750
It wasn't over.

64
00:07:09,130 --> 00:07:10,760
We should talk more tomorrow.

65
00:07:14,360 --> 00:07:15,330
Listen...

66
00:07:19,080 --> 00:07:21,170
I don't take chances anymore.

67
00:07:23,670 --> 00:07:24,790
And you shouldn't.

68
00:08:21,220 --> 00:08:23,060
You all have your assignments.

69
00:08:23,060 --> 00:08:24,970
You know where to rendezvous.

70
00:08:28,300 --> 00:08:29,820
Daryl leads them out.

71
00:08:29,820 --> 00:08:32,800
Sasha and Abraham join him at the bottom of the hill.

72
00:08:36,910 --> 00:08:38,300
Glenn, you hit us

73
00:08:38,300 --> 00:08:40,820
when you take care of the walkers at the tractor place.

74
00:08:40,820 --> 00:08:43,030
That's the one thing we gotta get ahead of.

75
00:08:45,180 --> 00:08:47,970
Everybody keep your heads.

76
00:08:49,070 --> 00:08:50,080
Just keep up.

77
00:09:17,110 --> 00:09:18,420
So, is he okay with it?

78
00:09:18,870 --> 00:09:20,620
It was pretty much his idea.

79
00:09:20,940 --> 00:09:21,850
He gets it.

80
00:09:23,030 --> 00:09:24,520
It's got a bed and a bath,

81
00:09:25,330 --> 00:09:26,920
but it's still a cage, you know?

82
00:09:27,100 --> 00:09:28,220
He gets it.

83
00:09:29,590 --> 00:09:32,280
He told me what happened out there with the trucks.

84
00:09:33,740 --> 00:09:35,380
He tell you about those guys he met?

85
00:09:36,200 --> 00:09:37,120
The Ws.

86
00:09:37,200 --> 00:09:39,080
Like that walker we saw, yeah.

87
00:09:40,740 --> 00:09:42,520
We need more watch points.

88
00:09:43,420 --> 00:09:44,370
And I'm gonna tell Deanna

89
00:09:44,370 --> 00:09:46,570
we don't need to go looking for people anymore.

90
00:09:52,030 --> 00:09:53,470
You feel different about it?

91
00:09:55,210 --> 00:09:57,720
Yeah, I do.

92
00:09:59,610 --> 00:10:00,890
Well, people out there,

93
00:10:02,230 --> 00:10:03,780
they got to take care of themselves,

94
00:10:03,780 --> 00:10:04,910
just like us.

95
00:10:08,780 --> 00:10:10,010
I'm gonna get him out.

96
00:10:11,410 --> 00:10:13,930
Shouldn't leave him in there any longer than we have to.

97
00:10:20,460 --> 00:10:21,410
You good?

98
00:10:21,950 --> 00:10:22,790
Yeah.

99
00:10:24,840 --> 00:10:25,940
I'm trying.

100
00:10:29,580 --> 00:10:30,480
Listen, if you're still looking

101
00:10:30,480 --> 00:10:32,340
to go buck wild with the breath impaired...

102
00:10:32,340 --> 00:10:35,590
You already asked the question and I already answered it.

103
00:10:38,500 --> 00:10:39,150
If you were so worried,

104
00:10:39,150 --> 00:10:41,320
why the hell did you get into the car with me?

105
00:10:51,630 --> 00:10:55,060
Listen, doing something as big as this...

106
00:10:57,050 --> 00:10:58,010
That's living.

107
00:11:01,780 --> 00:11:02,710
There it is.

108
00:11:06,470 --> 00:11:08,620
We're at red at the bottom of the hill.

109
00:11:09,010 --> 00:11:10,720
All right, here comes the parade.

110
00:11:41,900 --> 00:11:43,310
Where'd you learn that?

111
00:11:45,080 --> 00:11:46,060
A friend.

112
00:11:47,780 --> 00:11:49,400
Before or after?

113
00:11:52,020 --> 00:11:53,760
I ask, you answer.

114
00:11:54,740 --> 00:11:57,090
It's common courtesy, right?

115
00:12:00,930 --> 00:12:02,020
It was after.

116
00:12:04,740 --> 00:12:06,150
After everything.

117
00:12:07,300 --> 00:12:09,710
Look, I'm sorry for this, for having to do this.

118
00:12:09,720 --> 00:12:10,650
It's all right.

119
00:12:11,900 --> 00:12:13,100
The way I look at it,

120
00:12:13,780 --> 00:12:16,240
sometimes you're safer when there's no way out.

121
00:12:20,300 --> 00:12:22,280
Got to get to know each other again.

122
00:12:23,860 --> 00:12:27,000
For the first time... again.

123
00:12:36,750 --> 00:12:39,340
Hey, it's us.

124
00:12:39,960 --> 00:12:41,770
We're back. You gonna let us in or what?

125
00:12:46,600 --> 00:12:48,120
I'm technically not authorized,

126
00:12:48,120 --> 00:12:49,500
so I will not be doing so.

127
00:12:49,500 --> 00:12:51,420
- Who the hell are you? - You first.

128
00:12:52,720 --> 00:12:53,850
I'm Heath.

129
00:12:54,650 --> 00:12:57,490
I live here. My team's been on a run the last couple weeks.

130
00:13:04,570 --> 00:13:05,760
I'm Eugene.

131
00:13:06,100 --> 00:13:07,490
Aaron brought myself and my group here

132
00:13:07,490 --> 00:13:08,560
directly within that window,

133
00:13:08,570 --> 00:13:09,810
so we haven't had the chance to meet

134
00:13:09,810 --> 00:13:11,720
and I can't exactly confirm your residence.

135
00:13:11,720 --> 00:13:12,730
Open the gate.

136
00:13:14,240 --> 00:13:16,710
If I do, how do I know you won't attempt to kill me?

137
00:13:16,760 --> 00:13:19,120
Okay, look, I'm not gonna kill you.

138
00:13:20,460 --> 00:13:21,540
But the longer you make me wait,

139
00:13:21,550 --> 00:13:23,960
the more you motivate me to beat your ass, so...

140
00:13:29,250 --> 00:13:30,120
Thank you.

141
00:13:50,770 --> 00:13:52,800
So Deanna put you on gate duty?

142
00:13:53,450 --> 00:13:55,260
Oh, no, I'm not proper duty.

143
00:13:55,260 --> 00:13:56,520
This is Holly's shift.

144
00:13:57,300 --> 00:13:58,280
I was just walking by.

145
00:13:58,280 --> 00:14:00,470
She asked if I could relieve her for a few ticks.

146
00:14:00,470 --> 00:14:02,150
I said, "No, thank you" and she ignored me,

147
00:14:02,150 --> 00:14:03,680
which is obviously what I should have done

148
00:14:03,680 --> 00:14:04,970
as it's been at least five ticks

149
00:14:04,970 --> 00:14:06,260
and still no Holly.

150
00:14:10,620 --> 00:14:13,240
I'm Scott. This is Annie.

151
00:14:13,840 --> 00:14:14,980
Hi. Good to meet you.

152
00:14:15,640 --> 00:14:16,890
How many of you are there?

153
00:14:17,530 --> 00:14:18,400
13.

154
00:14:18,630 --> 00:14:21,120
I mean, 12.

155
00:14:22,370 --> 00:14:23,300
I'm sorry.

156
00:14:25,880 --> 00:14:26,880
I'll close up.

157
00:14:42,350 --> 00:14:44,360
Anything big happen while we were gone?

158
00:14:45,720 --> 00:14:47,030
We had a meeting last night.

159
00:14:50,150 --> 00:14:52,180
Oh, yeah? About what?

160
00:14:53,630 --> 00:14:55,080
You might want to talk to Deanna.

161
00:14:55,080 --> 00:14:56,480
Get it from the horse.

162
00:14:56,860 --> 00:14:58,940
Her mouth. You know?

163
00:15:01,250 --> 00:15:02,110
Right.

164
00:15:03,880 --> 00:15:05,830
Hey, it's good to see someone like me.

165
00:15:06,240 --> 00:15:07,870
I fully respect the hair game.

166
00:15:15,500 --> 00:15:18,380
- Who put up the wall? - They did.

167
00:15:18,460 --> 00:15:20,250
There was a man, Reg.

168
00:15:20,820 --> 00:15:23,500
He drew up plans, made it happen early on.

169
00:15:24,070 --> 00:15:25,380
A lot of people in here.

170
00:15:25,390 --> 00:15:27,420
They've been inside from the start.

171
00:15:28,120 --> 00:15:31,390
They had food, energy, not a whole lot of walkers.

172
00:15:32,140 --> 00:15:33,840
They just lived.

173
00:15:34,060 --> 00:15:35,990
They haven't had to survive.

174
00:15:35,990 --> 00:15:38,350
They figured that out, brought us in.

175
00:15:40,120 --> 00:15:41,800
Still might be too late.

176
00:15:41,800 --> 00:15:42,900
Too late how?

177
00:15:44,020 --> 00:15:45,600
For them to come around.

178
00:15:46,670 --> 00:15:47,610
We'll see.

179
00:15:48,790 --> 00:15:50,370
You'll have to talk to Deanna.

180
00:15:50,370 --> 00:15:51,830
She's the woman in charge.

181
00:15:52,610 --> 00:15:54,380
She was married to Reg.

182
00:15:55,060 --> 00:15:56,160
Was?

183
00:15:58,370 --> 00:15:59,560
Yeah.

184
00:16:13,860 --> 00:16:14,920
What are you doing?

185
00:16:17,050 --> 00:16:18,060
We're--

186
00:16:19,450 --> 00:16:20,740
I wanted to help.

187
00:16:21,310 --> 00:16:22,530
We only need one.

188
00:16:24,960 --> 00:16:26,980
We have two men here.

189
00:16:26,980 --> 00:16:29,550
We're not gonna bury killers inside these walls.

190
00:16:32,070 --> 00:16:34,190
I understand how you feel.

191
00:16:34,190 --> 00:16:35,060
I do.

192
00:16:35,280 --> 00:16:38,020
But it's not your decision.

193
00:16:39,140 --> 00:16:40,050
Tobin.

194
00:16:42,070 --> 00:16:43,060
Rick's right.

195
00:16:51,130 --> 00:16:52,120
Take it away.

196
00:16:53,720 --> 00:16:54,790
Go west.

197
00:16:56,340 --> 00:16:58,060
Down Branton road a few miles.

198
00:16:58,740 --> 00:17:00,240
Just past the bridge.

199
00:17:01,290 --> 00:17:02,690
We don't go out that way.

200
00:17:05,360 --> 00:17:06,980
Let the trees have him.

201
00:17:35,260 --> 00:17:37,970
I shot him because he killed Reg.

202
00:17:37,970 --> 00:17:39,830
That was it. We didn't have a choice.

203
00:17:41,780 --> 00:17:43,260
You do have a cell.

204
00:17:45,130 --> 00:17:46,430
Not for killers.

205
00:17:49,860 --> 00:17:51,270
I'm a killer, Rick.

206
00:17:53,570 --> 00:17:55,270
I am, and you are, too.

207
00:18:04,670 --> 00:18:06,930
Glenn, you there yet?

208
00:18:07,010 --> 00:18:09,570
Almost. We'll have it handled before they get here.

209
00:18:09,570 --> 00:18:10,870
And we'll meet you at yellow.

210
00:18:10,870 --> 00:18:11,870
Copy that.

211
00:18:19,090 --> 00:18:20,350
It'll hold.

212
00:18:20,610 --> 00:18:21,750
Well, that's good.

213
00:18:22,450 --> 00:18:24,450
You know, considering where we're standing.

214
00:18:31,680 --> 00:18:32,660
Michonne.

215
00:18:33,840 --> 00:18:34,950
Yeah?

216
00:18:35,700 --> 00:18:37,470
Back when you were in that place...

217
00:18:39,170 --> 00:18:40,320
Where I lived...

218
00:18:44,170 --> 00:18:46,290
Did you take one of my protein bars?

219
00:18:50,390 --> 00:18:51,500
No.

220
00:18:54,470 --> 00:18:57,210
See, I could have sworn there was one more peanut butter left.

221
00:18:58,890 --> 00:19:00,570
That's how it is, isn't it?

222
00:19:01,830 --> 00:19:04,720
You always think there's one more peanut butter left.

223
00:19:34,420 --> 00:19:35,430
Morgan.

224
00:19:41,200 --> 00:19:42,840
Maybe we just leave him here.

225
00:19:49,870 --> 00:19:51,450
That's not who you are.

226
00:19:55,420 --> 00:19:56,460
I know.

227
00:20:07,190 --> 00:20:08,290
You don't.

228
00:20:33,990 --> 00:20:35,040
Morgan.

229
00:20:37,390 --> 00:20:38,480
Morgan.

230
00:20:41,680 --> 00:20:42,720
Stop.

231
00:20:45,330 --> 00:20:46,520
Did you hear that?

232
00:23:02,280 --> 00:23:04,100
What are you doing out here, Ron?

233
00:23:06,020 --> 00:23:08,370
I wanted to know where my dad was buried.

234
00:23:32,140 --> 00:23:33,480
This is how.

235
00:23:37,830 --> 00:23:38,910
How what?

236
00:23:39,660 --> 00:23:41,760
How the community's still here.

237
00:23:43,350 --> 00:23:45,530
They've had walkers at their walls,

238
00:23:45,530 --> 00:23:48,620
But a lot of them, maybe most of them,

239
00:23:49,850 --> 00:23:51,280
They wound up here.

240
00:24:28,990 --> 00:24:30,140
Ron.

241
00:24:31,510 --> 00:24:33,200
- Ron. - I'm going back.

242
00:24:33,380 --> 00:24:34,800
- Hey. - I'm fine.

243
00:24:35,200 --> 00:24:37,140
You shouldn't be out here.

244
00:24:38,780 --> 00:24:40,170
I don't care what you think.

245
00:24:40,990 --> 00:24:42,700
It's not what I think, it's what I know.

246
00:24:43,360 --> 00:24:45,610
You can't protect yourself. I'll show you how,

247
00:24:45,610 --> 00:24:47,600
but right now you have no idea what you're doing.

248
00:24:47,600 --> 00:24:50,690
And if you come out here, you're gonna die.

249
00:24:51,510 --> 00:24:54,180
And it won't be quick and it won't ever be over

250
00:24:54,180 --> 00:24:55,350
'cause you'll be one of them.

251
00:24:55,350 --> 00:24:56,760
That's what's gonna happen.

252
00:24:58,680 --> 00:25:00,500
You're coming back with us now.

253
00:25:03,660 --> 00:25:04,930
Don't make it hard.

254
00:26:06,780 --> 00:26:08,840
Glenn, you have to hurry.

255
00:26:09,050 --> 00:26:11,610
The noise could distract the herd right off the road.

256
00:26:11,820 --> 00:26:13,530
- Talk to me. - We're here.

257
00:26:22,700 --> 00:26:23,630
Sounds like a lot.

258
00:26:26,620 --> 00:26:28,630
- We need it quiet. - So what's the plan?

259
00:26:30,600 --> 00:26:32,900
Take 'em out a few at a time.

260
00:26:44,540 --> 00:26:45,710
Nicholas, you're at the door.

261
00:26:46,640 --> 00:26:47,840
All right.

262
00:26:48,480 --> 00:26:50,750
You let one or two out and then you close it.

263
00:26:50,750 --> 00:26:52,040
You keep doing that. That's the trick.

264
00:26:52,040 --> 00:26:53,040
That's how we control it.

265
00:26:53,040 --> 00:26:54,350
Wait, what if he can't close it?

266
00:26:54,350 --> 00:26:55,670
- I'll be able to. - Then we take them on.

267
00:26:55,670 --> 00:26:56,820
We take them on?

268
00:26:57,430 --> 00:26:59,710
If we get into trouble, we go behind the building

269
00:26:59,710 --> 00:27:01,280
into the woods and we draw them away.

270
00:27:02,160 --> 00:27:04,770
Hey, you've been out on runs since he got here.

271
00:27:04,890 --> 00:27:06,140
He knows what he's doing.

272
00:27:07,230 --> 00:27:09,310
Me and Aiden, we didn't.

273
00:27:12,100 --> 00:27:14,040
This was supposed to be a dress rehearsal.

274
00:27:14,040 --> 00:27:16,110
I'm supposed to be delivering pizzas, man.

275
00:27:17,020 --> 00:27:18,560
Daryl's leading them this way.

276
00:27:19,070 --> 00:27:20,270
And they're closing in.

277
00:27:20,600 --> 00:27:22,670
That noise is gonna pull the herd right off the road.

278
00:27:22,670 --> 00:27:24,020
And then we have serious trouble.

279
00:27:24,190 --> 00:27:25,610
We have to do this.

280
00:27:25,950 --> 00:27:27,260
Yeah, okay.

281
00:27:27,260 --> 00:27:28,450
- Okay? - Okay.

282
00:27:28,450 --> 00:27:29,600
- Okay. - Okay.

283
00:27:30,750 --> 00:27:31,610
All right.

284
00:27:32,990 --> 00:27:35,750
On three. Ready?

285
00:27:38,110 --> 00:27:39,070
One...

286
00:27:40,940 --> 00:27:41,900
Two...

287
00:27:43,270 --> 00:27:44,170
Three!

288
00:27:48,970 --> 00:27:50,180
Shit!

289
00:28:03,590 --> 00:28:04,810
My team...

290
00:28:05,310 --> 00:28:06,850
We saw it early on,

291
00:28:07,260 --> 00:28:10,060
back when we were on one of those first scouts,

292
00:28:10,070 --> 00:28:11,640
finding out what was around here.

293
00:28:12,520 --> 00:28:14,470
There was a camp at the bottom.

294
00:28:15,450 --> 00:28:18,520
The people, they must have blocked the exits with one of those trucks

295
00:28:18,520 --> 00:28:20,520
back when everything started to go bad.

296
00:28:21,470 --> 00:28:23,040
They didn't make it. They were all roamers.

297
00:28:23,040 --> 00:28:24,430
Maybe a dozen of them.

298
00:28:24,750 --> 00:28:26,140
No one's been back since?

299
00:28:28,030 --> 00:28:29,280
D.C.,

300
00:28:30,550 --> 00:28:33,200
every town worth scavenging are all in the other direction.

301
00:28:33,350 --> 00:28:36,800
And I never really felt like having a picnic next to the camp that ate itself.

302
00:28:36,800 --> 00:28:39,480
So all the while the walkers have been drawn by the sound.

303
00:28:39,910 --> 00:28:42,400
And they're making more sound and they're drawing more in.

304
00:28:42,400 --> 00:28:44,090
And here we are.

305
00:28:46,000 --> 00:28:47,570
Now what I'm proposing,

306
00:28:48,680 --> 00:28:50,450
I know it sounds risky,

307
00:28:50,450 --> 00:28:53,310
but walkers are already slipping through the exits.

308
00:28:53,490 --> 00:28:56,080
One of the trucks keeping the walkers in.

309
00:28:56,380 --> 00:28:58,040
Could go off the edge any day now.

310
00:28:58,040 --> 00:29:00,280
Maybe after one more hard rain.

311
00:29:00,500 --> 00:29:03,240
That exit sends them east.

312
00:29:03,240 --> 00:29:06,210
All of them. Right at us.

313
00:29:10,040 --> 00:29:13,790
This isn't about if it gives, it's when.

314
00:29:13,790 --> 00:29:14,990
It's gonna happen.

315
00:29:15,760 --> 00:29:17,530
That's why we have to do this soon.

316
00:29:17,530 --> 00:29:20,590
This is-- I don't even have another word for it.

317
00:29:20,590 --> 00:29:21,980
This is terrifying.

318
00:29:23,540 --> 00:29:24,670
All of it.

319
00:29:26,140 --> 00:29:28,250
But it doesn't sound like there's any other way.

320
00:29:30,130 --> 00:29:31,660
Maybe there is.

321
00:29:33,450 --> 00:29:36,880
I mean, couldn't we just build up the weak spots?

322
00:29:37,920 --> 00:29:39,430
I could draw up plans.

323
00:29:39,430 --> 00:29:41,840
I worked on the wall with Reg.

324
00:29:42,360 --> 00:29:43,690
Construction crew--

325
00:29:44,190 --> 00:29:45,850
We can try and make it safe.

326
00:29:45,850 --> 00:29:48,080
Even if we could, the sound of those walkers

327
00:29:48,080 --> 00:29:50,410
is drawing more and more every day.

328
00:29:50,410 --> 00:29:52,270
Building up the exits won't change that.

329
00:29:53,410 --> 00:29:54,930
We're gonna do what Rick says,

330
00:29:55,800 --> 00:29:57,320
the plan he's laid out.

331
00:30:00,670 --> 00:30:04,700
I told you all, we're gonna have Daryl leading them away.

332
00:30:05,390 --> 00:30:06,510
Me, too.

333
00:30:08,250 --> 00:30:10,060
I'll take a car, ride next to him.

334
00:30:10,800 --> 00:30:12,030
Can't just be him.

335
00:30:13,030 --> 00:30:16,010
I'll keep 'em coming, Daryl keeps 'em from getting sloppy.

336
00:30:16,010 --> 00:30:16,930
I'll go with her.

337
00:30:18,800 --> 00:30:21,020
It's a long way to white-knuckle it solo.

338
00:30:23,390 --> 00:30:25,100
We'll have two teams.

339
00:30:25,490 --> 00:30:28,580
One on each side of the forest helping manage this thing.

340
00:30:29,620 --> 00:30:31,980
We're gonna have a few people on watch from now on.

341
00:30:32,190 --> 00:30:34,130
Rosita, Spencer, and Holly.

342
00:30:34,130 --> 00:30:35,570
So they're out.

343
00:30:37,600 --> 00:30:38,660
So who's in?

344
00:30:40,830 --> 00:30:41,820
Me.

345
00:30:43,140 --> 00:30:44,550
You should keep an eye on her.

346
00:30:45,690 --> 00:30:47,580
Keep going with the plans you talked about.

347
00:30:47,580 --> 00:30:49,270
I know, but this is important.

348
00:30:49,610 --> 00:30:50,830
She's important.

349
00:30:51,790 --> 00:30:53,220
People are scared.

350
00:30:53,590 --> 00:30:55,410
They need to see her come back.

351
00:30:59,180 --> 00:31:00,770
That's not the only reason.

352
00:31:02,200 --> 00:31:04,720
Yeah, it isn't.

353
00:31:06,080 --> 00:31:06,990
Okay.

354
00:31:09,160 --> 00:31:10,160
I'm in.

355
00:31:12,270 --> 00:31:13,440
I'd like to help as well.

356
00:31:13,440 --> 00:31:14,960
No. Who else?

357
00:31:15,480 --> 00:31:16,710
We need more.

358
00:31:17,300 --> 00:31:19,140
There's got to be another play.

359
00:31:20,460 --> 00:31:23,000
We can't just control that many.

360
00:31:23,000 --> 00:31:25,820
I said it before, walkers herd up.

361
00:31:25,820 --> 00:31:27,660
They'll follow a path if something's drawing them.

362
00:31:27,660 --> 00:31:29,610
That's how we can get 'em all at once.

363
00:31:29,610 --> 00:31:32,140
So, what? We're supposed to just take your word for it?

364
00:31:33,300 --> 00:31:36,780
We're all supposed to just fall in line behind you after...

365
00:31:41,440 --> 00:31:42,640
After what?

366
00:31:42,640 --> 00:31:44,870
After you wave a gun around

367
00:31:45,410 --> 00:31:48,000
screaming, pointing it at people.

368
00:31:48,020 --> 00:31:50,380
After you shoot a man in the face.

369
00:31:50,380 --> 00:31:51,790
- After you... - Enough!

370
00:32:00,200 --> 00:32:01,160
I'll do it.

371
00:32:03,620 --> 00:32:04,570
Me, too.

372
00:32:04,770 --> 00:32:05,790
Whatever you need,

373
00:32:06,310 --> 00:32:07,250
I'm in.

374
00:32:07,570 --> 00:32:08,810
Now who else?

375
00:32:17,560 --> 00:32:18,570
I'll go.

376
00:32:20,420 --> 00:32:23,650
We have to do this. I need to help.

377
00:32:30,320 --> 00:32:31,900
You sure you can handle it?

378
00:32:33,870 --> 00:32:35,150
You need people.

379
00:32:41,460 --> 00:32:43,150
We'll make this work.

380
00:32:43,150 --> 00:32:44,530
We'll keep this place safe.

381
00:32:44,530 --> 00:32:47,030
Keep our families safe. We will.

382
00:32:47,250 --> 00:32:48,210
The plan.

383
00:32:49,020 --> 00:32:50,240
Go through it again.

384
00:32:50,240 --> 00:32:51,710
Man, he just said it.

385
00:32:51,720 --> 00:32:55,110
Every part again.

386
00:32:55,840 --> 00:32:57,450
The exact plan.

387
00:33:32,480 --> 00:33:34,330
Marshall and Redding.

388
00:33:34,470 --> 00:33:36,130
We force them west here.

389
00:33:36,230 --> 00:33:37,000
How?

390
00:33:37,420 --> 00:33:39,910
We block it off so they can only go one way,

391
00:33:39,910 --> 00:33:42,290
West, away from the community.

392
00:33:42,290 --> 00:33:43,830
Block it off with what?

393
00:33:44,370 --> 00:33:45,430
Cars.

394
00:33:45,520 --> 00:33:47,840
We'll use the rvs, some of the bigger trucks.

395
00:33:47,840 --> 00:33:48,890
Park them end to end.

396
00:33:48,890 --> 00:33:50,390
We'll be drawing them away.

397
00:33:51,220 --> 00:33:53,650
- They're gonna keep moving. - Yeah, but that many?

398
00:33:53,650 --> 00:33:56,300
Just bouncing off some sedans?

399
00:33:57,800 --> 00:34:00,750
And then when they start slipping through

400
00:34:00,950 --> 00:34:03,380
And the ones that walk away start distracting the rest

401
00:34:03,380 --> 00:34:05,800
and you stop drawing them away?

402
00:34:08,720 --> 00:34:09,540
Man's got a point.

403
00:34:09,540 --> 00:34:11,030
We got plates.

404
00:34:12,180 --> 00:34:14,750
The big-ass metal ones from the construction site.

405
00:34:14,850 --> 00:34:16,420
We can use them to fortify the whip wall.

406
00:34:16,420 --> 00:34:17,960
It'd help disperse the force of impact

407
00:34:17,960 --> 00:34:19,640
and direct the walkers clean.

408
00:34:19,850 --> 00:34:21,930
Like a pool table. Eight ball, corner pocket.

409
00:34:21,930 --> 00:34:23,910
That's an army out there.

410
00:34:25,890 --> 00:34:28,320
And what happens when this doesn't hold?

411
00:34:28,660 --> 00:34:30,800
And they push on through. The curve in this hillside

412
00:34:30,800 --> 00:34:33,010
is gonna send them right back east.

413
00:34:33,010 --> 00:34:34,800
Right back here.

414
00:34:35,750 --> 00:34:37,930
You seriously want to risk that?

415
00:34:38,630 --> 00:34:39,550
No.

416
00:34:41,270 --> 00:34:43,750
So you need to help us to make it hold.

417
00:34:45,850 --> 00:34:47,430
These walls, you built them.

418
00:34:47,830 --> 00:34:50,530
So you've already done the impossible.

419
00:34:53,010 --> 00:34:53,980
Carter.

420
00:34:55,050 --> 00:34:56,090
Please.

421
00:37:12,760 --> 00:37:14,010
Hey, what you said before

422
00:37:14,010 --> 00:37:16,220
about us needing to take care of ourselves?

423
00:37:17,610 --> 00:37:19,360
Going out finding more people,

424
00:37:19,800 --> 00:37:21,820
that is taking care of ourselves.

425
00:37:26,430 --> 00:37:27,650
Your call, though.

426
00:37:36,160 --> 00:37:37,110
Thanks.

427
00:37:38,590 --> 00:37:40,420
You know, I can come with all of you.

428
00:37:42,750 --> 00:37:44,920
You and Daryl have been teaching me how to shoot.

429
00:37:46,000 --> 00:37:48,000
I think you got the hang of it.

430
00:37:52,820 --> 00:37:54,180
You should stay back,

431
00:37:55,790 --> 00:37:58,140
get a feel for how people feel now.

432
00:37:58,950 --> 00:38:01,000
We still got a long way to go with them.

433
00:38:03,240 --> 00:38:04,310
We'll get there.

434
00:38:05,320 --> 00:38:06,730
She's in charge.

435
00:38:08,130 --> 00:38:09,540
But you're in charge now.

436
00:38:23,060 --> 00:38:25,650
- This is a bad idea. - This is the only idea.

437
00:38:25,650 --> 00:38:27,930
I think there's something like a dozen in there.

438
00:38:27,930 --> 00:38:29,800
We stay back, we get on opposite ends,

439
00:38:29,800 --> 00:38:30,970
we draw them to each of us.

440
00:38:30,970 --> 00:38:32,750
- Try and take down four each? - No.

441
00:38:32,860 --> 00:38:34,350
This is just me and Heath.

442
00:38:34,350 --> 00:38:36,360
You get back and you stay back.

443
00:38:36,360 --> 00:38:38,940
Things go south, you tell Rick and you draw them away.

444
00:38:40,040 --> 00:38:41,870
Just move back.

445
00:38:52,540 --> 00:38:54,000
He got Noah killed?

446
00:38:54,230 --> 00:38:55,170
He did.

447
00:38:57,350 --> 00:38:58,710
He did more than that.

448
00:39:01,140 --> 00:39:03,720
He lured Glenn into the woods and tried to kill him.

449
00:39:05,130 --> 00:39:06,280
What the hell?

450
00:39:06,280 --> 00:39:08,050
- Yeah. - What?

451
00:39:08,160 --> 00:39:09,510
Glenn told me I could tell everyone

452
00:39:09,510 --> 00:39:10,790
if that's what I wanted to do.

453
00:39:11,270 --> 00:39:13,090
Could get Nicholas exiled.

454
00:39:14,270 --> 00:39:15,740
He'd die out there.

455
00:39:16,930 --> 00:39:18,170
Could have done that.

456
00:39:20,020 --> 00:39:21,220
You could do that now.

457
00:39:21,240 --> 00:39:24,200
He got Noah killed and he tried to kill Glenn?

458
00:39:25,450 --> 00:39:26,910
Glenn saves people.

459
00:39:28,390 --> 00:39:29,910
Even people like that.

460
00:39:35,950 --> 00:39:37,510
I couldn't accept it either.

461
00:39:39,270 --> 00:39:40,870
But then I thought about you.

462
00:39:41,580 --> 00:39:42,830
How we were on different sides of that fence

463
00:39:42,830 --> 00:39:44,520
on the worst day of my life.

464
00:39:47,310 --> 00:39:48,770
And now you're one of the most important people

465
00:39:48,770 --> 00:39:50,070
in the world to me.

466
00:39:52,080 --> 00:39:53,420
Things can get better.

467
00:39:55,270 --> 00:39:56,580
We can make them better.

468
00:39:58,680 --> 00:40:00,340
You tell me what you want to do.

469
00:40:04,260 --> 00:40:07,380
I'm just gonna follow your lead, okay?

470
00:40:08,830 --> 00:40:09,620
Okay.

471
00:40:11,530 --> 00:40:12,410
I'm sorry.

472
00:40:21,420 --> 00:40:22,260
You ready?

473
00:40:22,520 --> 00:40:25,480
No. But since you're doing this thing anyway...

474
00:40:26,530 --> 00:40:27,390
All right.

475
00:40:47,110 --> 00:40:48,130
They're still coming.

476
00:41:23,850 --> 00:41:24,650
Get it.

477
00:41:30,380 --> 00:41:31,130
Good.

478
00:41:32,250 --> 00:41:33,170
Let's go.

479
00:41:54,800 --> 00:41:55,680
Here you go.

480
00:41:55,830 --> 00:41:56,980
Oh, thank you.

481
00:41:57,760 --> 00:41:59,040
It's Carol, right?

482
00:41:59,720 --> 00:42:00,430
Yeah.

483
00:42:01,260 --> 00:42:02,720
You been with Rick long?

484
00:42:04,460 --> 00:42:05,640
Since Atlanta.

485
00:42:05,990 --> 00:42:07,470
And were you a cop, too?

486
00:42:09,320 --> 00:42:10,960
Why would you think that?

487
00:42:11,240 --> 00:42:12,790
You're always watching.

488
00:42:14,320 --> 00:42:16,010
You always...

489
00:42:16,890 --> 00:42:18,030
seem ready.

490
00:42:19,640 --> 00:42:20,540
For what?

491
00:42:22,450 --> 00:42:24,150
You know, to handle things.

492
00:42:27,470 --> 00:42:28,770
Aren't you sweet?

493
00:42:36,320 --> 00:42:37,220
What is it?

494
00:42:38,570 --> 00:42:40,190
Got some looky-loos taking

495
00:42:40,200 --> 00:42:42,500
a little constitutional off the shoulder.

496
00:42:44,040 --> 00:42:46,220
They starting a damn walkout.

497
00:42:46,220 --> 00:42:47,950
You want to have Daryl circle back?

498
00:42:48,930 --> 00:42:49,860
No.

499
00:42:50,550 --> 00:42:52,780
Keep moving. I'll catch up.

500
00:42:53,000 --> 00:42:54,150
Abraham.

501
00:43:01,290 --> 00:43:02,370
Idiot.

502
00:43:13,570 --> 00:43:14,410
Come on!

503
00:43:17,060 --> 00:43:18,960
This is my ride, asshole.

504
00:43:31,960 --> 00:43:34,370
Well, look at me.

505
00:43:39,650 --> 00:43:41,060
You didn't see Reg

506
00:43:42,210 --> 00:43:43,480
the night he got it.

507
00:43:46,420 --> 00:43:47,740
That was a mess.

508
00:43:50,530 --> 00:43:51,610
And Pete.

509
00:43:52,930 --> 00:43:54,400
His face just...

510
00:43:55,400 --> 00:43:57,580
blowing up like Pompeii

511
00:43:58,320 --> 00:43:59,980
right when we were cheek to cheek.

512
00:44:02,810 --> 00:44:05,430
I still think I got some of his brains in my ear.

513
00:44:14,930 --> 00:44:15,970
Well, look at that.

514
00:44:18,450 --> 00:44:19,390
All right.

515
00:44:20,620 --> 00:44:23,840
Everything is aces again.

516
00:44:28,760 --> 00:44:30,180
What the hell are you doing?

517
00:44:32,510 --> 00:44:35,080
I'm just grabbing the bull by the nutsack.

518
00:44:35,990 --> 00:44:37,290
I'm living, darling,

519
00:44:38,810 --> 00:44:40,070
just like you.

520
00:44:53,580 --> 00:44:56,060
I haven't had a chance to say it yet, but...

521
00:44:56,970 --> 00:44:58,810
I'm sorry about Reg.

522
00:45:00,450 --> 00:45:04,300
He was smart and kind.

523
00:45:05,090 --> 00:45:06,450
He was a good man.

524
00:45:11,210 --> 00:45:12,720
It was the right call.

525
00:45:13,520 --> 00:45:14,800
We need this.

526
00:45:18,880 --> 00:45:19,870
What else?

527
00:45:22,440 --> 00:45:23,610
You need to tell me.

528
00:45:25,300 --> 00:45:27,670
People need to be armed inside the walls.

529
00:45:27,970 --> 00:45:30,550
They need to be trained, everyone.

530
00:45:35,130 --> 00:45:36,140
Stop.

531
00:45:36,830 --> 00:45:38,150
Here they come.

532
00:45:39,970 --> 00:45:42,060
Carter, heads up.

533
00:45:42,900 --> 00:45:44,230
Wait, folks.

534
00:45:52,300 --> 00:45:55,170
Use your shovels. The guns will draw more.

535
00:45:55,320 --> 00:45:56,310
Help us.

536
00:45:57,470 --> 00:45:59,940
You can do this. You need to, all of you.

537
00:46:09,560 --> 00:46:10,780
Morgan, don't!

538
00:46:33,400 --> 00:46:35,800
You said you don't take chances anymore.

539
00:46:49,640 --> 00:46:51,050
Time is running out.

540
00:46:51,610 --> 00:46:54,020
He's talking about a dry run tomorrow. That's it.

541
00:46:54,030 --> 00:46:56,020
Rick stopped Pete. He stopped him.

542
00:46:56,020 --> 00:46:58,210
This is not taking out a wife-beater.

543
00:46:58,210 --> 00:47:00,600
He was a murderer, Carter.

544
00:47:00,680 --> 00:47:03,540
What Rick wants to do is suicide.

545
00:47:03,540 --> 00:47:05,100
I'm sorry, Spencer,

546
00:47:05,900 --> 00:47:08,500
but Deanna is asleep at the wheel.

547
00:47:09,420 --> 00:47:13,170
So it's on us. We have got to stop him.

548
00:47:13,900 --> 00:47:16,830
What the priest said about him, about these people,

549
00:47:16,890 --> 00:47:18,130
He was right.

550
00:47:19,060 --> 00:47:22,370
How many more of us have to die

551
00:47:22,370 --> 00:47:24,180
before we do something?

552
00:47:24,190 --> 00:47:26,480
'cause pretty soon it's gonna be too late.

553
00:47:26,600 --> 00:47:29,880
Carter, you need to be really careful here.

554
00:47:29,910 --> 00:47:31,910
You're talking about us going to Deanna and telling her--

555
00:47:31,910 --> 00:47:35,160
No, I'm not talking about talking some more.

556
00:47:35,160 --> 00:47:37,710
About meetings. I'm not talking about that.

557
00:47:37,970 --> 00:47:40,080
Plain and simple, we kill him

558
00:47:40,600 --> 00:47:42,370
before he kills us.

559
00:47:56,640 --> 00:47:57,830
Hello.

560
00:47:59,310 --> 00:48:00,260
Carter.

561
00:48:01,470 --> 00:48:03,250
- He heard. - I didn't.

562
00:48:04,130 --> 00:48:06,430
- I mean, I didn't-- - Carter.

563
00:48:10,110 --> 00:48:11,250
He heard.

564
00:48:13,450 --> 00:48:15,740
Carter, don't. You can't.

565
00:48:22,850 --> 00:48:24,240
What the hell is going on?

566
00:48:26,780 --> 00:48:27,980
What are you doing?

567
00:48:29,020 --> 00:48:30,940
I'm taking this place back from you.

568
00:48:34,460 --> 00:48:36,620
That's what you were talking about in here?

569
00:48:36,850 --> 00:48:38,490
That's what he was talking about.

570
00:48:42,610 --> 00:48:45,600
See, I would have-- I would have set up some lookouts.

571
00:48:46,810 --> 00:48:49,480
That would have been the smart thing.

572
00:48:49,560 --> 00:48:51,140
You know, if I happened to--

573
00:48:55,030 --> 00:48:57,870
You really think you're gonna take this community from us?

574
00:48:58,920 --> 00:49:00,660
From Glenn? From Michonne?

575
00:49:00,660 --> 00:49:02,350
From Daryl? From me?

576
00:49:04,120 --> 00:49:08,270
Do you have any idea who you're talking to?

577
00:49:11,100 --> 00:49:12,920
- It was just me. - What?

578
00:49:13,150 --> 00:49:14,450
It was-- it was just me.

579
00:49:14,450 --> 00:49:17,970
Just-- just kill me.

580
00:49:29,330 --> 00:49:30,230
Rick.

581
00:49:34,340 --> 00:49:35,430
I'm good.

582
00:49:36,380 --> 00:49:37,380
I'm good.

583
00:49:44,750 --> 00:49:46,840
You can try to work with us.

584
00:49:47,700 --> 00:49:49,290
You can try to survive.

585
00:49:50,870 --> 00:49:52,070
Would you do that?

586
00:50:22,370 --> 00:50:23,270
It's working.

587
00:50:25,720 --> 00:50:26,800
You were right.

588
00:50:32,670 --> 00:50:36,130
Everyone, we need to finish this.

589
00:50:36,760 --> 00:50:40,200
We have to keep moving and fan out down that thing front to back.

590
00:50:40,200 --> 00:50:42,110
Like we said, cops at a parade.

591
00:50:42,110 --> 00:50:43,960
Glenn, you take the back.

592
00:50:43,960 --> 00:50:45,630
- You got the other walkie. - Got it.

593
00:50:45,630 --> 00:50:47,630
If it gets sloppy, we fire our weapons,

594
00:50:47,630 --> 00:50:49,280
pull them back on track.

595
00:50:49,890 --> 00:50:50,950
I'll hit the front.

596
00:50:50,950 --> 00:50:52,860
Okay, one after the other.

597
00:51:40,670 --> 00:51:42,540
Tobin, they're breaking off.

598
00:51:42,550 --> 00:51:43,850
What do you want us to do?

599
00:51:44,000 --> 00:51:45,780
Fire your guns and draw them back.

600
00:51:53,970 --> 00:51:55,170
It's nice out.

601
00:51:57,460 --> 00:51:58,450
Yeah.

602
00:51:59,300 --> 00:52:00,470
Hope you don't mind.

603
00:52:01,210 --> 00:52:03,440
I wanted to enjoy the evening a little

604
00:52:03,440 --> 00:52:05,860
and I don't have a porch over there, so...

605
00:52:13,110 --> 00:52:14,290
Get your stuff.

606
00:52:18,170 --> 00:52:20,940
You should stay with us over here.

607
00:52:23,120 --> 00:52:24,240
You got room?

608
00:52:25,880 --> 00:52:26,990
We'll make it.

609
00:52:28,130 --> 00:52:30,110
We don't need to do that anymore.

610
00:52:32,760 --> 00:52:34,340
I know you, Morgan.

611
00:52:36,720 --> 00:52:38,660
Even if this is the first time.

612
00:52:45,510 --> 00:52:46,770
You want to hold her?

613
00:52:54,890 --> 00:52:55,800
Okay.

614
00:53:02,870 --> 00:53:04,200
This is Morgan.

615
00:53:07,000 --> 00:53:08,180
He's a friend of mine.

616
00:53:12,410 --> 00:53:13,300
Hi.

617
00:53:18,230 --> 00:53:19,170
Okay.

618
00:53:24,180 --> 00:53:25,580
Let me have a look at you.

619
00:53:34,370 --> 00:53:36,880
You with that man Carter, in the armory--

620
00:53:37,980 --> 00:53:38,970
That's you.

621
00:53:40,590 --> 00:53:42,290
You're still the same man I met in King county.

622
00:53:42,290 --> 00:53:44,790
The one that came back and told me it wasn't over.

623
00:53:46,710 --> 00:53:47,920
That was you.

624
00:53:49,880 --> 00:53:52,290
Same you that's right in front of me right now.

625
00:53:57,020 --> 00:53:58,600
I wanted to kill him.

626
00:54:01,680 --> 00:54:03,730
So it would be easier.

627
00:54:06,260 --> 00:54:09,270
So I wouldn't have to worry

628
00:54:09,270 --> 00:54:11,610
about how he could screw up

629
00:54:11,620 --> 00:54:15,550
or what stupid thing he'd do next because that's who he is.

630
00:54:15,550 --> 00:54:19,010
Just somebody who shouldn't be alive now.

631
00:54:22,270 --> 00:54:23,920
I wanted to kill him.

632
00:54:27,710 --> 00:54:29,970
But all that hit me and...

633
00:54:31,290 --> 00:54:33,780
I realized I didn't have to do it.

634
00:54:41,720 --> 00:54:42,910
He doesn't get it.

635
00:54:45,650 --> 00:54:47,090
Somebody like that...

636
00:54:51,470 --> 00:54:53,290
They're gonna die no matter what.

637
00:55:09,010 --> 00:55:09,960
I'm dead.

638
00:55:10,560 --> 00:55:12,440
Carter, take a breath.

639
00:55:13,010 --> 00:55:13,900
Carter.

640
00:55:16,850 --> 00:55:18,550
- Oh, god! - be quiet.

641
00:55:20,830 --> 00:55:22,610
- Oh, god. - Carter. Carter,

642
00:55:23,070 --> 00:55:24,400
you got to be quiet.

643
00:55:36,110 --> 00:55:36,960
It's working.

644
00:55:36,960 --> 00:55:39,370
The gunfire is bringing them back on the road.

645
00:55:54,380 --> 00:55:55,490
You got them, Tobin.

646
00:55:56,240 --> 00:55:57,200
Copy that.

647
00:55:58,500 --> 00:55:59,720
What was that screaming?

648
00:56:01,180 --> 00:56:02,270
That was Carter.

649
00:56:02,580 --> 00:56:04,620
He got bit right in the face.

650
00:56:04,810 --> 00:56:05,900
I stopped him.

651
00:56:15,910 --> 00:56:17,940
We have a good hour until we have 'em to green

652
00:56:17,940 --> 00:56:21,560
when we hand them off to Daryl, Sasha, and Abraham.

653
00:56:21,710 --> 00:56:23,900
Why don't you head back, tell everyone what's happening?

654
00:56:23,900 --> 00:56:25,620
- They should know. - Okay, Rick, I just--

655
00:56:25,620 --> 00:56:27,100
Will you do that for me?

656
00:56:33,100 --> 00:56:34,650
I'll take care of that one.

657
00:56:35,220 --> 00:56:38,470
Michonne, you take point.

658
00:56:41,460 --> 00:56:43,090
I know it's how it is.

659
00:56:44,090 --> 00:56:45,170
I do.

660
00:56:48,160 --> 00:56:49,170
Yeah.

661
00:56:50,630 --> 00:56:51,840
I do, too.

662
00:57:34,640 --> 00:57:37,930
I was just getting more flares for tomorrow.

663
00:57:50,180 --> 00:57:51,480
I know I haven't--

664
00:57:53,990 --> 00:57:55,700
I just-- I just thought it might be best

665
00:57:55,700 --> 00:57:59,280
if I let things be for a while.

666
00:58:00,940 --> 00:58:02,510
Ron told me what happened.

667
00:58:03,510 --> 00:58:05,280
Yeah, I wanted to talk to you about that.

668
00:58:05,280 --> 00:58:06,350
He shouldn't have been out there.

669
00:58:06,360 --> 00:58:07,710
No, he shouldn't have.

670
00:58:08,130 --> 00:58:09,060
You're right.

671
00:58:11,240 --> 00:58:14,400
But you can't talk to him like that, Rick.

672
00:58:15,410 --> 00:58:16,790
You can't touch him.

673
00:58:18,690 --> 00:58:19,690
Not you.

674
00:58:20,420 --> 00:58:22,860
Ron needed to hear every word I said.

675
00:58:22,860 --> 00:58:24,970
That's why I grabbed him. I wasn't angry.

676
00:58:24,970 --> 00:58:26,870
I was just telling him the truth.

677
00:58:28,390 --> 00:58:32,210
If it's coming from you, he can't hear it.

678
00:58:33,960 --> 00:58:35,300
You got to understand that.

679
00:58:36,730 --> 00:58:38,580
He needs to know how to handle himself.

680
00:58:38,580 --> 00:58:40,660
- I can teach him. I can teach you. - Rick.

681
00:58:40,660 --> 00:58:43,300
- You need to know how. - Rick.

682
00:58:46,190 --> 00:58:47,830
When I found out we could have them,

683
00:58:47,830 --> 00:58:49,930
I asked Rosita to start showing me how.

684
00:58:50,460 --> 00:58:54,810
Okay? She's gonna teach me and I'm gonna teach Ron and I'm gonna teach Sam.

685
00:58:58,610 --> 00:59:01,010
I heard what you were saying to us at the meeting.

686
00:59:02,240 --> 00:59:05,650
And at my house before, you know.

687
00:59:09,110 --> 00:59:11,070
I am gonna fight, Rick.

688
00:59:39,420 --> 00:59:40,880
All right, this is the finish line.

689
00:59:40,880 --> 00:59:43,390
When we make it to green, we fall back.

690
00:59:43,400 --> 00:59:45,760
The ditches and ridges will keep them on the road.

691
00:59:45,760 --> 00:59:48,660
We head home, but Daryl, Sasha, and Abraham

692
00:59:48,660 --> 00:59:51,170
take them the rest of the way, 20 miles more.

693
00:59:51,390 --> 00:59:52,500
All right, let's go.

694
00:59:58,710 --> 01:00:00,090
Got a question for you.

695
01:00:02,490 --> 01:00:06,970
Just some intel before our little road trip tomorrow.

696
01:00:07,990 --> 01:00:09,090
Ask me.

697
01:00:12,110 --> 01:00:13,900
You doing this 'cause you want to die?

698
01:00:18,610 --> 01:00:19,580
No.

699
01:00:43,980 --> 01:00:46,080
We're gonna take 'em right past here.

700
01:00:47,090 --> 01:00:49,380
All that noise could distract them.

701
01:00:50,470 --> 01:00:52,430
We'll clear it on our way back tonight.

702
01:00:53,560 --> 01:00:55,600
We don't want any surprises tomorrow.

703
01:01:00,480 --> 01:01:01,490
What you've done,

704
01:01:01,690 --> 01:01:03,160
you're gonna sit with it a while,

705
01:01:03,680 --> 01:01:05,370
'cause I don't want you out here tomorrow.

706
01:01:05,530 --> 01:01:06,550
You're not ready.

707
01:01:07,270 --> 01:01:08,360
You will be.

708
01:01:10,590 --> 01:01:12,480
Some time soon, I'll make sure of it.

709
01:01:12,820 --> 01:01:14,540
And then you start to make it right.

710
01:01:16,220 --> 01:01:17,170
Thank you.

711
01:01:46,120 --> 01:01:48,150
I know this sounds insane,

712
01:01:49,790 --> 01:01:52,060
but this is an insane world.

713
01:01:52,800 --> 01:01:55,940
We have to come for them before they come for us.

714
01:01:55,940 --> 01:01:57,200
It's that simple.

715
01:02:34,850 --> 01:02:36,180
What the hell is happening?

716
01:02:36,250 --> 01:02:37,740
It's a horn or something.

717
01:02:39,090 --> 01:02:41,220
It's pulling the back half off the road.

718
01:02:42,240 --> 01:02:43,600
Oh, god.

719
01:02:56,990 --> 01:02:58,800
Whatever that is, it's far.

720
01:02:59,360 --> 01:03:01,120
It sounds like it's coming from...

721
01:03:01,540 --> 01:03:02,550
Home.

