-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
South Park
Season12 Episode05
It's like my whole life has just
been one big screw up, you know?
I admit it, I was sexually lost.
And then I see this person on oprah.
She's a woman, but then she got
a sex change and became a man,
but then she got pregnant and is having a baby
which means she was still a woman all along.
That means I'm really still a man!
I still feel like a man.
Butters: Are we gonna
get tested on this?
This sex change was a big mistake. Okay?
I was on a lot of pain killers at the
time, and I thought it was what I wanted.
Stan: Dude, you wanna
do some math problems?
And then I go to the doctor, right?
And I say doctor, I want to go
back to being a man and he says,
well, there's been too much
damage, you can't go back.
Where are you going to find a penis?
What do you mean where
am i gonna find a penis!
I'm a man!
I deserve a god dammed penis!
Uh, mister --
mister garrison!
Could we speak with you, please?
What do you want? I'm trying to teach.
Uh, we think it's best you not teach until
you get your personal life in order, mkay.
Oh, it's so easy for you,
mackey, you have a penis!
Okay, students, uh, obviously we've had
a little emergency with your teacher.
So, uh, while we deal with this we need one of you
to lead the class and review for tomorrow's quiz.
Me, me! Me!Me!
Right here! Right here!
who else would like to
be teacher for the day?
Anybody else?
Principal victoria! Over here!
Any other volunteers perhaps?
Principal victoria!
Alright, alright, fine.
Eric, you lead the class.
Yes!
Now just lead a review over whatever
mr. Garrison's been teaching you
and I'll be back to
check on your shortly.
Well, well, well...
who's teacher now?
Yeah... who's teacher?
You're not the teacher, fat ass.
That's mister cartman now, kyle!
And you will be wise to not interrupt
my class unless you want to be suspended!
Yeah. You like that.
Alright, clyde, you're
first. Get up here.
Yeah, you're gonna take it, clyde.
So it appears that the local farmer's
market could be soon facing complete closure.
In other news tonight, a south park
bio company is coming under fire
for genetically engineering
body parts onto laboratory mice.
This picture of a mouse genetically
altered to grow a human ear
has already sparked waves of protest.
What?
But the scientists say the process
could help thousands of people
who have become disfigured
and need ears or noses.
Holy freakin' jesus.
RESERCH GROUP LABORTORIES
Using common genetics
and cartilage scaffolding,
we can graft almost any body part
onto a mouse and allow it to develop.
Here's the mouse you saw on television.
Once the ear fully forms, it can
be transplanted onto a person.
Doctor, what about a penis?
Well, a penis is something a
man puts into a woman's vagina.
No, no.
If I gave you some of my dna, could
you grow a penis on a mouse for me?
You don't understand, doing this stuff is very
expensive and we've never tried a penis before.
There's no guarantee it would work!
I will give you all the money
I have to just try. Please.
Doctor, I'm a man
trapped in a woman's body.
I need a penis.
Alright, alright, let's
see what we can do.
Eric, we've called you in to commend
you for your role as student teacher.
Don't commend me, it's the
students fault for being so stupid!
Commend means you've done
a great job, eric, mkay.
After leading your class through review,
your schoolmates scored higher
than they ever have on their tests!
Whatever you did really worked on them!
Oh well, thank you.
I believe strict discipline along with compassion
for my students is catamite to their learning.
These gentlemen from the denver county school
board have something they want to ask you.
Young man, word of your success as a student
teacher has started the whole board thinking.
We would like you to try your methods
on one of our inner city school classes.
These kids just won't
listen to any adult teachers,
and since you handled your class so
well, how'd you like to give it a shot?
That sounds like a chance to really make
an impact on some students who need it most.
How much will you pay me?
Three hundred bucks!
Did you hear what I said you guys!
My awesome teaching skills is
gonna earn me three hundred bucks!
You're not an awesome teacher!
Whatever, the whole class
scored super high on the tests.
The only reason we scored high was
because we took the answers out of
garrison's desk, and you know it!
Yes, but whose idea was it to take
the answers out of garrison's desk?
Kenny's!
Yeah, that was my idea.
Oh, yeah.
But whatever, I'm gonna go teach those
underprivileged inner city students
and really turn their lives around.
Do you know what those
kids are going to do to you?
A little middle class white
boy telling them what to do?
They are going to murder you.
Maybe he's right.
I better be careful how I look.
Students, quiet! Quiet, please!
Give me your attention.
I'll give you my attention
all night long, mrs. Miller!
You're on thin ice, rodriguez!
Now listen up.
The denver county school board has
sent over a special guest teacher.
This may be your last shot at
graduating from high school at all!
I want you to welcome
-- eric cartmanez.
Hello, students.
I am eric cartmanez, your new teacher.
What the hell is this?
I am here to teach you calculus.
I think you're going to be very
pleased with the progress, ms. Garrison.
Mister garrison!
Sorry, 'mister' garrison.
Your dna has replicated and grafted
very successfully with the mouse.
And so here's your penis.
Wow, my penis looks great!
Yes, it's a fantastic penis.
Congratulations.
How long before it's ready?
Well, it still has some
forming to do, but fairly soon.
Lemme see if it feels right in my hand.
No! Don't
open the --
Oh, no!
Don't let it get out the lab.
My penis!
Stop penis! Come back here!
Okay, everyone take a silly bus
and pass it to the amigo behind you.
Hey man, what the hell
do you think you're doing?
Yeah!
Mr. Cartmanez is here to make
sure you all get into college.
Get into college?
Man, we aren't getting
into no college? F you!
- Yeah, man!
- That's right!
- What is this, anyway?
- Man, this is crap!
How do I reeech these keeeds?
The reason that you think you can't get into
college is because you haven't been taught --
how to cheat properly.
How do you think white
people always get ahead?
Because we cheat
all the time --
I mean because they cheat all the time.
This is bill beeelichick.
Coach of the new england patriots.
He's won three superbowls. How?
He cheated.
He even got caught
cheating. And nobody cared.
Bill beelicheck proved that
in america it's ok to cheat,
as long as you cheat
your way to the top.
Hey, I don't want to
be called a cheater.
No, no, if you cheat and
fail, you're a cheater.
If you cheat and
succeed, you're savvyyyy.
This is bull!
I don't want to waste my
time learning to cheat!
Go ahead, the door's right there.
Bye, bye, have fun, we will miss you.
How do I reach these kids?
Boys!
Boys, have you seen my penis?
What?
My penis is on the loose!
If you see it, just try to
catch it with some cheese!
Ow, that hurt my brains.
Nice form, compadre.
Hey I walked out of your class, teacher.
Look, I don't want to argue with
you about the merits of cheating.
Who wants to argue on
a nice day like theeees.
How about a little pickup game?
Hey, petano!
Can you keep score for us?
Sure thing, mr. C.
Okay, you start on defense, amigo.
Oho, that's one to nonothing, amigo.
You cheated!
What's the score, effe?
Okay, let's go. Your turn.
That's two to noteeeng, amigo.
F you, man! You can't do that!
Look at the scoreboard, amigo.
No matter how many times you say I cheated, the scoreboard says 2
- 0.
I know what you're trying to say,
but I still don't agree with it.
Two to nothing, essa.
Two to nothing.
Hoh, how do I reach these keedz?
What is that?
Stephen! Stephen, come quick!
What is it, dear?
A penis is loose in our kitchen!
A penis?
Yes, it just ran across the floor!
Now darling, calm down.
Calm down nothing, I don't want
that penis running through my house!
Ah, women, always afraid of penises.
There! There you see it!
Oh, it's just a little penis, darling.
I don't care, it's probably
got all kinds of diseases.
Butters: Hey, wait! I think
that's teacher's penis!
Your teacher's penis?
Butters: Yeah, that must be his!
Butters, how do you know what
your teacher's penis looks like?
Today, we will discuss one of the
most fundamental ways to cheat --
getting test material ahead of time.
When bill belichick cheated for
the patriots, what did he do?
He videotaped the
opposing team's defense.
Think of the defense as your test.
When taking a test you must
also 'videotape the defense.
Learn what's on the test before they
give it to you, and that way you can --
I thought that, well, maybe
I could give cheating a try.
Have a seat, amigo.
Good to have you back.
Alright.
Now, when bill belichick got caught
with his camera, he did not panic.
He simply said what every good
white cheater says when caught:
I misinterpreted the rules.
It's what you must also
say when caught cheating.
"I misinterpreted the rules."
Say it with me "i
misinterpreted the rules."
Good! Again!
I misinterpreted the rules! Again!
I misinterpreted the rules!
Now you sound like white people!
What the hell do you mean
you just put my penis outside?
Why didn't you call me?
Look, garrison, my wife didn't want a
penis in the house, I had to get it out!
Well now how am I supposed to find it?
It could be anywhere!
Holy crap!
Carol, get down from there!
No! Didn't you see that penis just now?
I'm sure that penis is way more
scared of you than you are of it!
You saw a penis?
It's so big and disgusting!
Come back here, penis!
There you are! Got you!
*************
*******
The answer to number 27 is five.
The answer to number 28 is fourteen.
Man, what's the point?
What's the point of any of this?
Alright, everyone review the section on
sportscasters forgiving the patriots for cheating
and saying it was no big
deal, I'll be right back.
Malita! Malita, hold on!
You can't quit now?
Come on, what's wrong with you?
There isn't any point to all this.
I won't be going to college.
I'm pregnant, alright?
I just found out.
And eduardo isn't going
to help me raise iT.
How do I reach these keeeds?
Alright, let's go get you an abortion.
No, I'm catholic.
I think abortion is wrong.
Abortion isn't wrong.
What's the one thing
I've been teaching you?
That cheating is good.
Yes!
And abortion is the
ultimate form of cheating.
You're cheating nature itself!
Why do rich white
girls get ahead in life?
Because they get abortions
when they're young.
They get pregnant, but they still want to
go to college so whatever, they just cheat.
They cheat that little critter in their
belly right out of a chance at life.
I don't know, mr. C.
Mexicans are told not to cheat.
Don't cheat, you got pregnant
you have to raise the child,
so then you have to raise a child while
the white girls get to go to college
and probably have a
bunch more abortions.
It is at our most challenging times
that we must cheat our very hardest.
And the last time you saw
your penis was two days ago?
That's right.
Long whiskers or short?
Short. And little fluffy ears.
Fluffy ears, ok.
Think you got it, mitch?
I think so, sir.
Is this pretty close?
No, no! Not like that!
That's just silly.
Sir, we might want to get a unit down
to the italian restaurant on kentner.
What is it?
Call just came through.
Seems a penis broke in and cheese.
Well, come on!
What's the matter?
A penis!
A penis? Where?
There it is!
Where is it?
Look there!
Come on!
What's that a penis
doing in a my kitchen?
Don't you dare kill my penis!
Crap! We gotta go back around!
* Someone,somewhere *
* is loving me tonight *
* Looking at the same moon *
* and seeing it so bright *
* Someone, somewhere *
* is feeling my despair *
* and this same moon is
making them think,of that *
There it is!
No! No!
Nooo! Nooooo!
There's not a chance now.
No! We can find it!
Sorry,garrison,your penis is gone.
I'm afraid there's
nothing more we can dO.
You'll just have to
live with being a woman.
A very ugly one. Come on,men.
Students,I want to congratulate
you on your amazing test scores.
The school board is so
impressed with your progress,
that they are going to let you take the standardized
advanced placement test for college credit!
- Alright!
- Cool,man.
The test is going to be heavily monitored
in a private room at their location
to assure that there can
be absolutely no cheating.
Uh what?
The test will be tomorrow.
Make us proud.
Monitor us in a private room?
Now they're gonna know we've
been cheating all along!
I knew it,man!
You made us believe in your
way,and now it's all for nothing.
It's not for nothing!
If you're good enough you can
cheat right in front of them!
Shut up man,you royally screwed us all!
How do I reeeeech these keeeeeds!
Just before the last superbowl,bill
belichick gathered his football players
and said "let's win this one for real.
Just this one time,let's not cheat."
You know what happened? They losT.
Even if you feel all eyes are upon
you,you cannot give on cheating
or else you can lose the
biggest game of your lives.
Yeah,come on,we can do this,guys.
You are the true dreamers.
Tomorrow you will prove it.
We will begin by reviewing how to print out
cheat sheets as labels for your bottled water.
You did this to yourself,garrison.
Get your hopes up with a
stupid genetic experiment
and now all your money's
gone along with your penis.
What
the --
why -- it's
my penis.
My penis came bacK. But why?
I guess it's true.
What's that old saying?
If you love your penis,let it go?
The standardized advanced placement test
is considered one of the most difficult
and carefully monitored
tests in the country.
Twenty four of our
students took the test
and all twenty four
scored one hundred percent!
Uh,can we say something?
Sure.
We would like to present this plaque to the person
who taught us the white people method,mr.Cartmanez.
I reeeeched these keeeeeeeds.
Students and faculty,please
put your hands together
and help me in welcoming
back mister garrison.
Thanks,everyone.
It's great to be bacK.
I'm a man again.
Thanks to my very special new friend.
But you know,I've learned that
I've really been a dude all along.
Because the key difference between men
and women,is that women can have babies.
If you can't have
babies,then you're a man.
Woa,uh,wait. Hang on a second.
My wife had ovarian cancer,so
she can't have babies.
Well,then get an aids test,thompson,
cuz your wife's a dude,faggot.
Yeah! I'm back!
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
www.tvsubtitles.net