-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
South Park
Season12 Episode06
Get off the internet,
stanley. It's time for bed.
Mom, I just got to do
a couple more things.
Now, stanley! The internet will
be waiting for you in the morning.
Off!
Aw, man!
Shelley, off the internet. It's bedtime.
Mom, I'm I-chatting with
my boyfriend in montana.
Now, shelley!
Why do you hate me?
Randy, off the internet.
No! No, come on! Leave me alone.
No, mister. It's time for night-night.
But sharon, I got stuff to do!
I got to see my credit rating and
i got to send an e-mail to nelson
and check out foley's
vacation photos --
You don't have to do all that now.
You can do one more thing
and then it's bedtime.
One more thing?
Oooh, yeah.
What the hell?
Stan!
- Stan, i got to use your computer.
- What?
My internet's not working.
I got to use yours.
And give daddy some
private time, will yeah?
- My internet's not working either.
- What?
Dad, the internet's not working!
I know that, okay?
I have to get online with my
darling amir before school starts.
Randy, i can't get my e-mail to open.
Everyone just calm down.
Calm down, all right?
It's going to be okay.
We just can't panic.
Gerald, please help us.
Randy! What's happened?
Our house. It has no internet.
Oh, my god.
We've got nothing.
It's just gone.
Come in. You can use our internet
until you figure out what to do.
Thank you, gerald.
I'm getting on it first.
Oh, no, you're not!
Kyle, can I use your internet?
- It's not working.
- What?
I've even unplugged it
and plugged it back in.
No, no. Our internet can't be broken.
I've got to get an attachment
larry sent me last night!
It's not working, gerald.
But it has to
work. Maybe if I --
Your internet's not
working, gerald. Face it!
I have to get online before school.
What about starbucks?
They have free internet.
Right! Starbucks!
Everyone get your stuff.
We can take my car.
Hey, is your guys' internet working?
No. Nobody's is.
What's happening?
Jesus, everyone's gonna
have to go to starbucks now.
Everyone in the car! We
have to beat them there!
God, the whole neighborhood's affected.
Get out of the way, peterson!
Folks, there's no internet here.
It's not working, I tell you.
It's not working here?
Kids, get back in the car.
We can go to the mac store.
N, don't! You're wasting your time.
How do you know?
Because we just came from there.
There was nothing.
Not one scrap of internet.
How can there be no internet anywhere?
What's going on?
Anybody got a blackberry?
Check drudge report.
Good idea! No, wait!
We can't check drudge
report. There's no internet.
There has to be a way to
find out what's going on.
We can't! Don't you get it?
There's no internet to find
out why there's no internet!
What did we use to get the
news before the internet?
A television!
Reporter: Once again, we apologize
but we cannot bring you the news.
It appears that we have
no internet here at news 4.
We'll be happy to bring
you up on current events.
Just as soon as our internet is back.
Jesus, it's statewide.
It could be nationwide.
Hello? Do you have internet?
It's channel four news.
No, we don't have internet either.
No internet anywhere.
Jesus, we're all alone.
MONDAY
8 DAYS WITHOUT INTERNET
What's the matter?
I don't know.
I need to get on webmd and see
why I have this cough, but I can'T.
What if my sweetheart
is online looking for me?
He could be wondering why
I don't get online with him.
Maybe he thinks I'm dead.
If my darling amir gets another internet
girlfriend, I'm going to kill him.
And you!
Shelley! Shelley, woa, stop! Stop!
Dad, you got to do something!
She's out of control.
You're right. We can't
just sit here any longer.
Randy, where will you go?
We're gonna head west.
There's a rumor going around that
there might be some internet out there.
So we're heading out california way.
You don't know if there's
any internet in california!
Well, there certainly ain't none here!
Look, maybe it's time
you all face reality.
The internet here is dried up.
It could come back.
Yeah, and maybe it won'T.
In the meantime, I got a family
who needs internet right away.
We'll head out california way
and, and see what we can find.
Come on. Let's gO.
Look, if you do find internet,
let us know, will you?
How? You won't have internet.
California NEED******
Sorry, folks. We're full up.
Know anywhere else we can stay?
We're heading out california way.
Looking for some internet.
You and everyone else.
You'll have to stay out at the transient camp
with all the others heading to california.
It's about a mile down the road.
* I'm going down the road feeling bad *
* oh, lordy my internet
done up and went away *
Where are you from, old-timer?
Kansas city.
Had me a store there, a kind
of computer supply store.
When the internet went,
the stores went too.
Things I'll be different
when we get to california.
Soon as we get us some
internet we can all rest easy.
Why sure.
They*********
************
********
Oh, I'm gonna sit down at t that
internet and just start e-mailing.
Just keep on e-mailing 'til my
fingers are sore to the bone!
Sure will be nice.
You folks all heading to silicon valley?
That's right. We need to get online.
Get online, he says.
What's so funny about that?
Think about it.
How many folks heading
out to california?
A million? More?
How much internet you
think they got out there?
Be some internet, sure, but with
everyone trying to use it at once,
it's gonna go real slow like.
I knows because I seen it.
My two children, they
tried to load a webpage.
Took them over three days.
They sat there waiting,
by the time the loading bar was
only half full they was dead.
Starved on the internet.
With their bellies stuck
out like a pig bladder.
Come on, stan. Let's get us some rest.
Amir, I miss you so much.
Don't cry, shelley.
You'll be able to get online
when we get to california.
Everyone, wake up, we're here!
Silicon valley, california!
Name.
Do they have internet here?
MarsH.
Service provider.
Net zero.
All right. Stay in
line once you're inside.
Red cross volunteers will
direct you to your campsite.
So, is there internet here?
Stay in line and get to your campsite.
Excuse me. We're looking
for some internet.
Yeah, they got it here.
All right!
Bud there ain't enough to go around.
All they got is a little internet.
Barely a bar a signal.
So they have to ration it out carefully.
You sign up over there.
And use your time when
they call your name.
Each family gets 40
seconds of internet per day.
40 seconds?
That ain't even long
enough to check wikipedia!
Well, it's all we got
so we got to make do.
Look, honey. I ordered
us some books on amazon!
All right. Time's up.
No, no, wait! I haven't entered
the shipping information.
No! No!
Next! Grady, john H.
Aw, how am I supposed to
see internet porn that way?
What did you say?
Uh, you go on ahead, sharon, divide
some internet amongst the children.
I got to go talk to somebody.
Reporter: And that's about all we know.
There might be some internet still
in california, and parts of florida.
Though, we certainly
still don't have any here.
A fax! A fax is coming through!
- We got a fax!
- Yeah, a fax!
It says the government has sent
their best people to the internet
in order to repair it.
We got to get a reporter
out to the internet.
Where is the internet?
Gentlemen, president is very angry
that his internet still isn't working.
We've tried everything, sir.
But the internet has slowed to a trickle
and we can't get it working correctly.
Take me down below.
I want to see the internet for myself.
Here it is, general. The internet.
So what's wrong with it?
See that flashing
orange light in the mid?
It's supposed to be solid green.
My god.
Thedancingkitty.Com.
I wonder what that is?
Click on the dancing kitty
and you could win a prize.
All right, time's up.
No wait. I just clicked
on the kitty. I got it!
No! It wasn't long enough! No!
Next. Nelson, peter T.
Excuse me.
I need to uh, have some
private internet time.
Look, we're just trying to get by here.
Everyone's got to
take what they can get.
I haven't jacked off in over two weeks.
So jack off.
You don't understand.
I need the internet to jack off.
I got used to being able to see anything
at the click of a button, you know?
Once you jack off to japanese
girls puking in each other's mouth,
you can't exactly go back to "playboy."
What do you want us to do?
Pick up the whole computer and put it
inside for ten minutes just for you?
- Three minutes would be plenty.
- Get lost.
All right. Each of you take a ticket.
When they call your name,
you can use the internet.
What number are you, turd?
You're 923 now.
Hey, mom!
Shelley, give your
brother his ticket back.
Can't you all see I'm in pain?
Nobody understands pure love.
Amir and I are closer than
anybody in this stupid family!
Over here.
You. Happen to be
looking for internet porn?
Yeah. How'd you know?
Lots of us fellas came
here for that reason.
We all got used to seeing lots of
really perverted stuff on the internet,
so now we can't go back to "playboy."
I know! Right?
Anyway, we got us a simulator.
You just call out what you
want to see and then say click.
Internet porn stimulator.
Give it a try.
Anything you wanted to see
with the click of a button!
Uh, japanese girls exchanging
bodily fluids. Click.
Oh, this sucks! I
can't jack off to this!
Dammit.
Uh, let's see. Gang bang. Click.
She-males. Let's
try she-males. Click.
Bestialty. Click on that.
Brazilian fart fetish
porn? Click. Click.
Nope. This isn't gonna work.
It's just not the same.
Well, sorry.
That'll be $49 on your credit card.
Well, at least that
part's like the internet.
We now have a reporter on
the scene. Let's go live!
Tom, I am at the internet
government officials are doing
their best to get it running again.
All right, internet.
What do you want from us?
If we've angered you
somehow, let us know.
Try to communicate
with it digitally again.
I've had it with this thing.
Fire a warning shot at it.
Hey, wait a minute.
Is it possible
that --
What is it, kyle?
I think I know what's wrong.
This is taking too long.
When do I get to use the internet?
It's got to be our turn soon.
All right, folks. It's bedtime.
No more internet for today
Just a little longer.
No, no. We're locking it away
'til tomorrow. Everyone get to bed.
Finally! I'm online again! Yes!
Japanese girls puke
in each other's mouths.
Oh, nice!
Now let's see some bestialty.
Yes!
Let's get some brazilian
fart porn in there.
That's got it!
What is that?
Sounds like somebody's
being attacked by a tiger.
Get the keys. We got to get in there!
What
the --
- Dad?
- Randy!
Oh, uh, there was a, a ghost!
This is ectoplasm!
Did you see the ghost?
It ran through here and slimed me!
You son of a bitch!
No, it wasn't me. It
was the spooky ghost!
This is our last chance.
With nowhere else to turn, the government
is going to allow one brave 8-year-old boy
to attempt his method to get
the internet running again.
It all comes down to this.
Can the little jewish boy reason with
the internet, or will it be gone forever?
All clear for procedure.
All right. Let's do it.
Look! The flashing yellow
light is steady green now!
He did it!
- I've got internet!
- Me too!
Internet activity in all sectors, sir!
- I've got internet.
- Me too.
It's back!
It's back? It's back!
It's working!
I can I-chat with my darling amir now!
Shelley? Shelley marsh?
What?
It's me. Amir.
Your family came here too,
Yeah.
So, uh, I guess I'll e-mail
you as soon as we get back home.
Yeah, okay, sounds good.
Okay, c'ya.
We're back together!
And so what have we
learned through this ordeal?
The internet went away, it came back.
But for how long we do not know.
We cannot take the internet
for granted any longer.
We as a country must
stop overlogging-on.
We must use the internet
only when we need it.
It's easy for us to think we can
just use up all the internet we want,
but if we don't treat the
internet with the respect
that it deserves,
it could one day be gone forever.
And so let us learn to live
with the internet, not for it.
No more browsing for no apparent reason.
No more mindlessly surfing on our
laptops while watching television.
And finally, we must learn only
the internet for porn twice a day.
Max.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
www.tvsubtitles.net