Okay,kids,we have  something very
serious we need  to discuss today,m'kay.
It appears that some kids in  school
are getting high by  choking themselves.
Some kids call it the choking
game,m'kay,but choking  yourself is bad,m'kay.
Don't do that,m'kay.
You can get high from choking yourself?
Hrggggggg!
School children are often  experimenting
with dangerous  ways to get high.
M'kay,like sniffing glue,guzzling
cough medicine,huffing paint,m'kay.
But they're all bad.M'kay?
My cousins in florida said  kids
in their school get off of  cat pee.
Cat pee?
That's not true.You can't get
high off of cat  urine.Can you?
Well,it's not actually cat  urine.
But male cats,when they are
marking their territory,
spray a concentrated urine
to fend off  other male cats.
And that can get you really  high.M'kay?
Really,really high,m'kay.
Probably shouldn't have
told you that just now,m'kay.
That was probably bad.
All right.This should keep my cat
in place while he sprays the urine.
Yes,poor mitew kitty,are
you  just so upset right now?
You guys are wasting your  time.
Yeah,it's not gonna work.
Okay.You ready,kenny?
- All set!
- All right.
Bring out the other male cat.
Do you feel anything?
Well,kenny?Are you buzzed?
Cool!Check it out!
I see that you are enticed by my
daughter's awesome,rocking  tits.
Yeah.
Then bathe with my daughter
in the fountain of varnoth.
Appease the gods by lathering
her boobs with soapy suds.
Okay!
Kenny.Kenny,wake up.
Wake up,kenny.You all right?
Kenny!Wait.
Where'd she go?
Dude,that cat urine really  You up!
You were seriously tripping  balls.
You Asshole!
Agh!Kenny!Knock it
off!What's wrong with you?
Why couldn't you leave me  alone!
Dude!
Dude,kenny,calm down.
Oh,I was so close!
You should have seen her  titties.
What titties?
The titties!
On the girl,they were  incredible!
Kenny,all you did after the  cat peed in your face
was start  running around in circles  cheering.
Yeah,then you ran through  town screaming
and started  tearing off all your clothes.
I almost touched them.
Dude,I don't think we should be
messing around with that crap anymore.
Next on
fox news --
it's the newest drug craze
and  it's killing your kids!
Killing our kids?
All over america kids are
getting high on cat urine.
Huffing cat urine apparently  causes a euphoric
state and is  also referred to as "cheesing.
" Why cheesing?
Because it's "fon to due.
"   This sixth grade girl says  she's
been snorting cat piss for several months.
We sometimes sneak out during recess and
our friend named  Goes and gets her cats.
And we'll just cheese all day  long.
Oh,my god!Sheila!
Come look at this!
So how can you tell if
your  child is cheesing?
One,your child seems
distant,preoccupied.
Two,your child's face
smells  like cat urine.
Three,when you see tigers at  the zoo,your
child starts  grinding his or her teeth.
You might also notice by certain phrases
your child says to  school friends,such as --
"hey,let's go cheese.
" Or "do you feel like cheesing,guys?
" Or "dude,I'm cheesing my
f-ing  brains out right now.
"   Kids are doing this?
Kids do it because it's  legal.
What can you do before it's too  late?
We have to protect our
children from this,sheila.
20% of american students aged 6 to 12 say
they have tried  cheesing at least once.
Kids also refer to it as "the
cheese game," or "vitamin  cheese,"
or "mary jane/piss in
your face fun time.
" Cheesing is spreading fast.
All right.We're all sufficiently
scared,gerald,but what can we do?
I have written up a bill that would make
having a cat illegal  in the city of south park.
Gerald's right.We have to face it.
Cats are deadly animals.
If you stick your nose up their  crotch
and snort their piss,they can kill you.
With my super lawyer powers
we can rid our town of cats
so  that our kids can
never get high again!
Let's hear it for gerald!
No!
Get over it druggie.Jeez!
Goodbye,scrambles.We'll miss you.
Got two here.
Hey,what the Are you doing?
Sorry,these are illegal.
What?
No!
What are you doing?
Hey,[Bleep] You!
Look,I told you.I had a cat.
But I had it put to sleep
because it pissed me off.
Shhh.
Mister kitty,you have to
live  in the attic for now.
Here.
Write a diary.
Guys,have you seen kenny?
No,I think kenny's out sick  today.
Yeah,and he was out sick  yesterday too.
Guys,I think kenny isn't here
because he's at home cheesing.
Aw,come on.
Kenny knows how dangerous  cheesing is.
Yeah,and where's he gonna  find
cats anyway?They've been outlawed.
Yeah,who has cats these  days?Ha,ha.
Pot's illegal too but people
still manage to find it!
Ever since that first time kenny
cheesed he hasn't been the same.
You've all noticed the change in him!
I'll bet kenny is home
cheesing  right now.
Kenny?
Kenny,you home?
Oh,boy.He's cheesed out his mind!
Kenny
There you go.
Try some coffee,ken.
Kenny,we need to have a  serious talk.
No,we don't,guys.
Yes,we do.
We're your friends,dude.And we're
not gonna let you ruin your life.
I'm not ruining my life.
Will you guys just
back the  [Bleep] Off?
Look at yourself!
You've got to lay off the  cheese!
Yeah,that's it,little  buddy.
Just let it out.
Kenny,i know we're super
cool and everything,
but if we  ever catch you cheesing
again,we're gonna tell on you.
Ugh,okay.Okay.
I just want to sleep now.
Yeah,he needs some sleepny
night-night,doesn't the buddy?
We gotta keep this away from  him.
Miter kitty!Shhhh!
Dammit!
Shhhh.Mitew kitty,you have to but  tuiet
or else they're gonna find you!
What?
The neighbor cat.
He hasn't been caught yet.
No,no,mitew kitty.
I know you like rufus,but
he  has to fend for himself.
I can't hide anymore cats,mitew kitty.
I'm in trouble enough as it is.
All right,all right.Fine.
All right,come on,rufus.Quietly.
Oh,jesus,no!No,I can't hide you all!
I'm sorry.You'll just have
to find  somewhere else to --
Well,i suppose I'll get in just as
much trouble for four cats as for two.
Come on.
Huh?
Oh,my god!
Kyle?
Kyle,can we talk to you
for a  minute,please?
Yeah?
Kyle,have you been getting  high?
No.
Then why did your mother find
this in your dressing drawer?
All right.Look,that isn't mine.
I'm just holding it for a  friend.
Don't lie to us,kyle!
How long have you been on the cheese?
I'm not cheesing!
I've never cheesed once in my  life!
Get up to your room right  now.
Until your mother and I figure
out how to deal with this.
Dad,will you just listen
to  me for a second.
Now,kyle!
God!
Gerald,what are we gonna do?
Our son is a cat pee addict!
First thing is we've
got to  dispose of this.
What are you going to do?
I better just take it down
to the basement for now.
Make sure kyle can't find it.
No,no.What am i thinking?
I shouldn't don't this.
I've been clean for ten years.
I haven't even been near a cat.
But then that report said
our  kids were doing it,too.
I knew kyle would have the same
sickness as I used to have.
Now a cat is in our home
and  it's too tempting.
I,I'll just do it one more  time.
One last time.
Then I'll call the police,have
them pick up the cat.
And I'll never do it again.
After this one last time.
I couldn't stay away.
Curse your rockin' tits.
- Who is it?
- Please,open the door.
They say you're hiding cats!
Hiding cats?That would be illegal!
You don't understand.
My little nishka,she
has  nowhere else to go.
Oh,no!No,I cannot
possibly take in  another.
But they will find her.
I've already taken in the
anderson's cats,the wolitsky'S.
There is simply
nothing else I  can --
then again,perhaps I could find
space for just this one more.
Oh,you show such kindness
in such darkest of times.
What the hell?
Kenny,get outta here!
Oh,crap!Kenny!
Bad kitties.
Dad!Somebody's at the front door!
Well,am I grounded or not?
Fine!I'll get it!
Dude,we've got a big  problem!
Cartman says kenny is really  messed up.
He's cheesing his  Balls off,dude!
What?
He apparently got to all the  cats
cartman's been hiding in  his attic.
What are you doing with
cats  in your attic,fat ass?
They're innocent victims in  this,kyle!
They have to hide or
they'll be  put to death.
Something you just can't  understand.
Come on.We gotta find kenny
before he  hurts himself.
I can't!My dad grounded me!
Wait a minute.
Where is my dad?
Hey,everybody!
Good to seeya again!
Hold!
You cannot yet caress my
daughter's awesome boobage.
How come?
There is another suitor.
What?
Get outta here,kid!
Dude,You!That's my girl!
You're too young for this  stuff!
This must be decided in the
breastriary in nipopolis!
Now fight!For the locknar trophy!
Dad?
Dad!What the hell are you doing?
They been going at it
for a  good 30 minutes.
She's mine,you little  asshole!
Get the Off me!
Gerald?
The key proponent of the cat  ban has been
charged with  cheesing in a public park.
Gerald broflovski is prepared
to give a public statement.
I would like to address
a  personal matter.
I have let myself down and I  would first
like to apologize to my lovely wife --
Don't touch me.
And to the people of south  park.
I was wrong.
And I can't let cats
take the  fall anymore.
It's our fault.
The people who use cats
for  their sweet urine.
We have to learn that
cheesing  just isn't worth it.
Sure,you get to fight
in the  breastriary
and swim in the  fountains of varnoth with
the  ittytitty fairies of mamary  mountain.
What the hell is he talking  about?
I have no idea.
And then you fight the
boobgoblin in the gazangas cave.
And then the girl may thank
you  for it,but she isn't real.
And you never really get a  good
look at her naked boobs  anyway.
Problem is the more you go  into
that world,the more you  need to go.
Until you start blowing off all
the real people who care about  you.
Yeah,I guess so.
Cats aren't the problem.
We made cats illegal,and then i cheesed
for the first time in  ten years.
And kids are always going to
find a new way to get high.
Like sniffing glue or licking  toads
or fermenting feces or  huffing paint.
- You can also
- Okay,that's probably good,gerald.
The point is I was wrong.
It's time to legalize cats.Yeah!
Hooray for gerald!
Let's hear it for gerald!
Scrambles!
So good to have you back.
You ain't sore at us,are you?
I'm sure glad that's over  with.
Me too.
But you know,we've all
aneato fed something,you guys.
We can never persecute living  beings and
force them into  hidinvel it's okaonvel
And you don't see any  parallel between
that and  anything else in history?
nope.
I have no idea what
you're  talking about,kyle.
You guys!Check it out!
It's kenny.
Isn't that great?He's
just getting high on life.
Yeah.
He's getting really high on  lifE.
Dude,he's getting super  wasted on life.
Kenny!
What the hell kind of flowers are those?
Kenny?
www.tvsubtitles.net