-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
South Park Season12
Episode09 Breast Cancer Show Ever
Okay. Chilildren, let's
all take our seats.
Before we get started today.
Wendy testaburger has asked to
share something with the clasS.
Wendy?
Thank you,mr. GarrisoN.
Fellow students, october is awareness month for
the one of the leading causes of death for womeN.
A disease that takes the lives
of american women every day.
I'm talking of course
about breast canceR.
An estimated one in six women will
deal with cancer in their lifetime
and breast cancer is
the most common --.
She said it again.
Is there a problem? Because isn't funny.
Breast cancer is killing people.
Mr. Garcia, do we really need all
of this potty talk in the classroom?
Eric, f for the love of jesus.
This is a serious issue eric,
what you're doing is offensivE.
Me, you're the one talking
about killer titties,
watch out wendy,guys, went
day says boobs can kill you.
I don't want to get killed by boobs.
Will somebody do something.
Every week he gets worse
and nobody does anything.
Eric, stop being offensivE.
I'm trying to engage wendy in a constructive
dialog about breast cancer awareness.
No, you aren'T.
Wendy, you better calm down,
you'll get your boobs angry and
they'll start killing everyone.
I'm on fire today!
Look out everyone, there's some
killer titties on the loose.
Could have swore i heard
them coming through the roof.
Officer, we need to get an apb out on
those titties, they're armed and dangerous.
What is your problem?
Testify breast cancer isn't funny.
Not at all.
Wendy, we are going to get you wendy, where
are your boobs we are going to kill you.
You better shut up or
i'll make you shouldn'T.
Really, what are you
going to do about it wendy?
I'm going to kick your ass,
that's what I am going to do.
Your gonna kick my ass?
That's right, i am gonna kick my ass.
You want to throw down,
dawg, I'll throw down.
You think you're tough.
What's up?What's up?
I'm smack the. Out of you.
Throw down, bitch.
After school, we fight
after school, gout there.
You'll fight me after school?
That's right.
You're a chick, dudE.
As soon as that bell rings we do
it outside and you better be there.
It's on bitch.
Your going tO. Die!
Wendy and eric are fighting
after school everybody.
Wendy and eric are
fighting after schooL.
What?
Wendy and cartman are
going to fight after school
Relly
Wendy and cartman are
fighting after school.
Yea!
Hey, emo kids, wendy and cartman
are gonna fight after school.
Did she just call us emos?
Gee, i can't wait, wendy
gonna fight you after school.
She is pissed off.
She's not gonna show
up to a fight, dawG.
I'm sure she's already tried to
figure out a way to get out of it.
Hey, check it out, she's
totally staring you down.
She sure seems confident, you
should go easy on her, dude,
you don't want to put
her in pt hospital.
I'm gonna teach her a lesson, I'm
not gonna totally kick her ass.
Can't go too easy on her, god
forbid she gets a good punch iN.
Yeah, if you get beat by a girl,
everyone would think you're a faggot.
Wendy, could i talk to you for a second?
What?
wendy, i want to apologize
and tell you that --.
What?
I want to apologize and tell you
that I'm sorry for what i said, okay?
It was wrong of me and i promise
you that it won't happen again.
I don't want to fight you
after school, all right?
So, I'm sorry.
If you're really sorry you can
say it in front of everyone!
Actually i was thinking let's
just keep this between us.
I was wrong to make fun of breast
cancer and I'm very remorsefulness.
No, if you're really sorry and
you want to apologize to me,
then do it in front of everyone!
Apologize?
That's not what i said dumb bitch.
Yes, you did, you stood there and said
you apologized and don't want to fight.
Wendy, a desperate
attempt to get out testify.
These students are too smart to see you're
making excuses to get out of fighting mE.
I am i don't want to get out it.
I'm gonna beat the. Out of you.
That's funny, you're going to die lezbo.
Wendy, seriously, i want to apologize,
I'm sorry i don't think we should fight.
Get away from me!
So, everyone is saying there's going to be a
fight between eric cartman and your girlfriend.
I guess sO.
And you're going to just let at
that guy beat up on your woman?
Doesn't that like go against
your jockey man code or something?
Yeah, i don't ever remember ac/dc singing about
letting it dudes beat up on their girlfriends.
What am i supposed to do about it?
Don't worry, stan, I don't
think it's going to happen.
Cartman says that wendy is begging
him to it call the fight off.
******
I hope not, i want to see
wendy kick the crap out of him.
- Wendy.
- What.
Real quick, real quick.
Wendy, you're not gonna believe this, i
just found out my mom has breast cancer.
Man, i sure got what was coming to me.
I was a real jerk and now they're
gonna cut off my mom's boobS.
You really think that's
going to work on me?
Wendy, i have here $27 in cash.
If you just call off
the fight then i --.
You can't bribe your way out of this.
Wendy, i have muscular dystrophy.
No, you don't.
My mom has muscular
dystrophy in her boobs.
You don't get it asshole, there's
nothing you can do to stop this fight.
I am gonna wipe the playground
in front of everyonE.
I am gonna shove your ass down your
throat and make you eat your underwear.
- Eat my underwear?
- That's right.
Okay, wendy, I'll eat my
underwear right here and right now.
Jesus crys do you have
no sense of self-respecT.
No, unless you want me to, if
you want me to have self-respect.
You suck so hard.
I'm eat my underwear and then we'll
put this whole thing behind us.
What are you doing.
I'm committed to peace, wendy I want
you to see just how humbleed i am,
how much
i --.
Wendy, look at me, wendy.
Oh, my god.
So, are we cool?
No!
I ate my underwear, what
the hell do you want me me?
You are so pathetic.
Wendy, i ate my underwear for you, no!
Jo what's up dawg?
- We need to talk.
- What?
You know, wendy and i are suppose
today fight in like three hours.
- Yeah.
- Dude, aren't you worried?
Wendy is a girl shy could end
up getting really hert, stan,
you're my bro and
she's she's your bitch,
i can't heart my bro's bitch,
*******
she told me she doesn't
want to fight.******
She knows i am gonna kick her ass and feels if she
doesn't fight me the girls will call her chicken.
Really?
Now what she did, she apologized
and begged me not to fight heR.
I said if you're sorry, stay it in
front of everyone, but she wouldn'T.
That's how desperate these.
You have to do something, stan, you
have to. Be a man and forbid her --.
Oh, that's where i put those.
Anyway, stan, you've got
to put a stop to the fight.
Wendy needs you.
Dude, there's nothing I can do about it.
God, you are such a pusy,
stan, you're a pussy,
when i hurt wendy it will be on
And so you see at this point your rip
disease knew he could not win the battle.
I'm going to wipe the playground
with you right in front of everyonE.
If you got beat by a girl
everyone would say you're a faggot.
For homework, i want you
all to read chapter seven.
Take this Wendy!
When the bell rings we've got to get out
there and find a good place to watch this.
There's no way out, she's gonna
kick my ass in front of everyone.
Almost there.
And be be ready for a
quiz tomorrow morning.
I totally can't see the fight dude,
i've got detention after school.
Detention, that's it!
I've got to get detention fast!
Eric, did you just
take a crap on my desk?
What's up? What's up?
Crapped on your desk
dawg, what's up with that?
Welcome to detention mkay?
You're here until your
parents pick you up.
Use your time to study.
Oh, sweet.
Eric
what's going on.
Everyone is start to go say you got detention
on purpose to get out of fighting wendy.
RidiculouS.
Some people say you crapped
on the desk to get detention.
********
Why did you crap on the desK.
*******
I'm anti-establishment, that's how
i roll, dawg, i do stuff like that.
I said he's not scared of fighting
wendy, he'd do it if he could.
I got all punk rock and
got detention, a bad dudE.
That's good because we moved the fight
to first thing tomorrow morning tomorrow
before school starts. Everyone
is going to get there early.
That way it doesn't matter
that you have detention.
Eric, get your buns back over here.
Wendy says she will be there an hour before
school starts, see you in the morning, okay?
Tomorrow morning, you
die tomorrow morning.
- Wendy!
- Yeah?
We need to talk to you right now!
Wendy, have you been
bullying kids at school?
What? No!
Well, do you want to explain why this
little boy's mother had to come talk to us?
Did you tell this little boy
you were going to beat him up?
You don't understand
he said horrible thingS.
The thing is, I totally said I was
sorry, but she still wants to beat me up.
Wendy, no matter what a person says,
you don't respond with violence.
Haven't we taught you that?
The thing swendy, i really
think you're awesome,
and i know I'm just a nerdy
little weakling to you,
but i want to be your friend because I
don't have that many friends at school.
Wendy, you tell this little boy
you aren't going to hurt him!
- Mom, you don't --.
- Now, young lady.
I'm not going to hurt you.
If there's any word of you fighting at school,
it's over for you missy, do you understand?
Yes, sir.
We're so sorry about this, miss cartman.
Oh, no, thank you so much for your time.
It really won't happen again.
You're very sweet. Thank
you again. Come on, muffiN.
Okay, mommy, ma ma, ma ma.
Man, it's almost time for school
to start. Wendy still isn't here.
Yeah, I don't know what's
going on. I showed up.
Where is she?
How come wendy is not
showing up for the fight.
Here she comes!
What's up, wendy i thought we
were meeting early to fight.
Now i can't fight you.
Why not? You chicken? It
bwawk bwawk bwawk, bwawk bwawK.
I can't fift you because you came crying
to my house last night with your mom.
Oh, that's a doozie, wendy, did you
come up with that one on your own.
Yeah, you come up with
that one on your owner?
I ain't frontin' dawg, let's do it.
Come on, wendy kick his ass!
I can't!
God dammit,
she chickened out.
Told you guys!
Oh, i'm glad that's over witH.
Yeah, guess who dodged
a bullet, galahad.
I always knew deep down
wendy didn't have any.
And so we must all recycle every day.
Recycling is important and
it will save our planet earth.
The end.
Very nice, clyde.
Okay, we have time for more more report
before recess, who would like to go?
Okay, eric.
Thank you.
My report today is on
breast cancer awareness.
I do not believe enough is being done
and like the victims of breast cancer,
there's something I'd
like to get off my chest.
We all must fight and hopefully kid
titty cancer will be a distant memory.
You unbelieveable bastard.
You beat me, but you won't stop.
What did the breast cancer
say to the polish monkey.
Okay, eric, that's enough you smart ass.
Why, why are you doing this to me?
Why won't you just stop.
Wendy, wendy.
Wendy testaburger to the
principal's office, please?
Wendy testaburger to
the principal's office.
God!
Wendy, i've been hearing rum irs of
a fight between you and eric cartman.
No, man there isn't going to be a fight.
Oh, no? Are you sure.
Yes, ma'am.
I see.
I noticed all the things you've done
for breast cancer awareness month.
Did you know I'm a
breast cancer survivor?
Ma'am?
I was diagnosed seven years ago.
Cancer is it pure evil, it's a fat
little lump that needs to be destroyed.
When there is a cancer,
you have to fight it.
You can't reason with cancer,
you can't wish it away.
Cancer doesn't play by the
rules so neither can you.
My parents said
that if i fight--.
And you can't listen to
what anybody else tells you.
You have to be willing to give up everything
because the cancer will take everything.
Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am!
When you have cancer, you fight because
it doesn't matter if you beat it or not.
Yo u refuse to let that fat little
lump think you feel powerless.
She's gonna fight.
Wendy's gonna fight cartman right now.
What?
********Not that dude, retard.
She's coming.
******
Wendy is coming to fight you.
Oh, boy, here we go.
About freaking time.
All right. Let's do it!
Wendy, what's up? What's up?
Wendy, don't forget
I'll tell my mom on you.
I don't care.
Recess is almost over, i don't
know if there's really time.
Shut up and fight!
All right, wine, wendy, i'll fight you.
Him up, wendy!
Wendy?
I'm finished.
Somebody, somebody call the principal!
You have don't have to say anything.
I know how it iS.
I'm no longer the cool kid.
Now you all think i'm a fag.
My school life is over because now
all the guys don't think i'm cool.
Dude, we never thought you were cooL.
That's not true.
You're just saying that.
No, really, we've
always thought you suck.
Yeah, nothing's changed.
Our opinion of you can't
possibly go any lower.
You're just saying that
to make me feel betteR.
No, it's truE. We've always hated you.
Yeah.
Don't try and make me
feel better, you guys.
Wait, wait a minute, why would you guys
be saying stuff to make me feel better?
Unless, unless you do think I'm cool.
What?
If you're all trying to make me feel
better then you must still like me.
I've been so worried about you guys were
going to think of me getting beat up by a girL.
It turns out you think
I'm cool no matter what!
Oh, oh, oh, god, what a relief!
Yea!
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
www.tvsubtitles.net