Aghghghgh.
Well there's no doubt about it
Those tonsils need to come out.
What?
Oh,what exactly does that entail,doctor?
It's a very simple operation.
We'll just put you to sleep,eric,and
when you wake up you'll be tonsil-free!
No way.
I'm not going to the hospital,mom!
Oh,I thought you were a tough kid.
You're not scared of hospitals,are you?
No,I'm not scared.
I just,I don't want my
tonsils out,that's all.
Well,then I guess you don't want all the
ice cream you get after the surgery either.
Ice cream?
Be a shame to have to give all that free ice cream
to the big boys who aren't scared of the hospitals.
What do you say,champ?Think
you can tough it out?
Well,you did say free ice cream?
Poopsiekins,wake up.
Wake up,honey.
It's,it's over?
That's right!You did it,poopsiekins!
It's over!
I don't feel anything.
You were right,mom!
I'm so proud of you,eric.
All right. So where's my ice cream?
Oh,here's the doctor now.
Hi,doctor.
You were right,doctor.
Everything is okay.
No,it's not.
Eric,i'm afraid that we've accidentally
infected you with the aids virus.
- What?
- What's that supposed to mean?
During the tonsil surgery we had
to supply you with donor blood,
a mistake was made and you were
given blood contaminated with hiv.
It was a one in a billion fluke.
I have aids?
Not yet,but we've confirmed that you
now have the virus that causes aids.
We are very sorry.
Sorry?
You gave me aids and you're sorry?
Oh,my poor little baby!
Mom,you said nothing would go wrong!
Oh,god!
Oh,no!
No,no,this is a joke,right?
This is a joke!I can't have aids!
We are going to do everything in our
power to make this up to you,eric.
For starters,I think I
owe you some ice cream!
Your ice cream!
You said I'd be fine!
You all said I'd be fine!
My baby has hiv!
No!
Thank you for coming,everyone.
Boys,please take a seat.
What's going on?Are we in trouble?
Boys,the reason we called you all in is because
one of your friends has a serious illness.
Eric cartman has been
diagnosed with hiV.
What?
Oh,no.
He's been to several specialists
since a botched blood transfusion.
The disease is in very early
stages and completely manageable,
but he's naturally,a bit scared.
Cartman has hiv?
We need everyone to understand that
you can't get the virus from eric.
You can still give him
hugs and even kisses.
Don't be afraid of him. Just -
Excuse me.
Eric cartman has hiv.
All right,we're going
to bring eric in now.
And let's all be as supportive as we
can and show him lots of love,okay?
Eric?Come on in.
Your friends all want to say hi,m'kay?
- Hi,eric.
- Hey,there,eric.
No way.
How you doing,eric?
You know,I think you're
a real special little guy.
And even though you have aids,i ain't
gonna act any different towards you.
God dammit,this sucks ass!
Excuse me.
I,I have to step out for a minute.
Poor ol' kyle.
He's really taking it hard.
Is kyle laughing out there?
This isn't time for funny
jokes!I'm going to die.
Now,you're not going to die,eric.
Aids isn't as big a
deal as it used to be.
There are advances in treatment.
Not a big deal?
Is that how everyone feels?
People need to understand the
seriousness of this illness
and the bravery of the
people who struggle with it!
We are here tonight to salute the bravery and the courage
of one very special little boy who is living with hiv
Where the hell is everybody?
Excuse me. Shouldn't we wait for
everyone to arrive before we get started?
This is everyone.
We didn't sell that many tickets.
Great benefit,eric.
The italian meatballs are fantastic.
So this is it?
I'm afraid aids benefits aren't
as popular as they used to be.
Aids was more the '80s/'90s disease.
It's all about cancer now.
Well,that's just great!
Of all the times to get aids,I get it
right when everyone stops giving a crap!
With all of your help,we have
raised over $17 for aids tonight,
and that money will certainly go
towards helping little eric martman.
Just bring out elton john already!
Uh,we're sorry.
Elton couldn't make it.
He had to play at a cancer benefit.
It's all right. We got somebody better.
Jimmy buffet!
Jimmy buffet?
Hello,everyone.
I wrote this song for
a very brave little boy.
Aids burger in paradise
aids burger and it ain't nice
Nobody likes jimmy buffet except for frat
boys and alcoholic chicks from the south!
Little boy in south park
dying of aids in the cold dark
how he got aids I haven't
a clue wasting away again
because of aids how're
we all feeling tonight?
You,jimmy buffet!
You Suck!
Oh,poopsiekins,be nice.
You,mom. I have Aids!
Hey,guys,thanks a lot for coming
to my aids benefit yesterday.
Oh,dude,was that yesterday?We forgot.
Yeah,you forgot.
Just like a lot of people lately have
forgot that aids is still killing people.
Seems like all of america has
forgot that hiv is a serious disease.
Well,did elton john sing a song for you?
No,as a matter of fact
jimmy buffet came instead.
Oh,yeah.
It's real Funny,kyle!
I'm sorry.
I'm
- really!
Cartman,I feel really bad for you.
Honestly.
- No,you don'T.
- I do.
If you really felt bad,you'd
wipe that Smirk off your face!
Well,any god dammed second,kyle!
I'm sorry. I gotta get home.
Jesus christ,can you
believe that asshole?
He does feel bad for you,cartman.
He just thinks it'S...
ironic.
Ironic how?
Well,you know you're always
such a dick and stuff and now -
Oh,and what,I deserve it?
Is that what you think?
Not me!
That's kind of what he thinks.
Nobody deserves this illness,stan!
Kenny!
Nobody!
It's awful!
And maybe somebody needs to teach
kyle how to have some compassion.
Ugh,okay.
It's clear.
All right. Get that
rope ready to hoist me.
All right,but what are you going to do?
Kyle thinks that hiv is funny,so
we're going to make him look funny
and then he'll know how
it feels to be laughed at.
I just,I don't know that I should
be helping you make kyle look silly.
Butters,helping people who have aids is
one of the most important things you can do.
I know,but are you sure kyle
has to be taught a lesson?
I'm not just sure,butters.
I'm hiv positive.
Oh,yeah. I guess that's true.
All right. Now get the rope up over
that third rafter above the window.
That's the easiest access.
Wow!You really know what you're doing.
Yeah,I sneak into kyle's
room lots of times.
You think hiv is something
to be laughed at,kyle?
Well,let's just see how
funny it is now,asshole.
Ugh
- what?
Ugh.
There,there,boobie. You'll be okay.
Oh,doctor,did you find
anything?Is it strep?
No,it isn't strep.
Oh,well,that's a relief.
Mrs. Broflovski,has your son
ever had a blood transfusion?
No,why?
Little boy,have you been
having unprotected anal sex?
What?No!
Doctor,what are you saying?
We've run every test imaginable.
Little kyle here is infected with hiv
- What?
- Hiv?
It took us a long time to narrow
it down,but there is no doubt.
No!That's impossible!
Little boy,are you sure you haven't taken
it up the hoo-hoo just once or twice?
No!No,god dammit!No!
I'm telling you you're wrong!
There is no way I can
have hiv,unless maybe...
oh,my god.
That son of a bitch!
Kyle?Kyle!
Pass me the ball.
Pass me the ball,craig,you
stupid asshole!
Ugugh!
Kyle,what the -
I'm gonna kill you,cartman!
Kyle,what?
What'd he do?
What do I have hiv?
Ooooh.
Ooohhhh,you have hiv,huh,kyle?
Guess it isn't so to funny now,is it?
- What did you do?
- Nothinoo
Then why did butters say he helped you
sneak into my room last friday night?
Oh,nice,butters,you big tattle tail!
Tattle tail?
Do you know how serious this is?
Well,kyle,maybe I was just trying to prove a point that you shouldn't be so
- Ahgghghghe b Ahghghghgh!
Kyle!
Hey,hey,that's enough.
Break it up,m'kay?
Break it up!
Mp[ Ay.
All right,boys.
Now what is this fighting all about?
He gave me aids!
What?
He purposely infected
me with his hiv virus!
Is that true,eric?Did
you give kyle aids?
Well,he was being a total dick
and then he's a big tattle tail and
going around talking crap about me -
Did you infect kyle with
the hivbouirus?Yes or no?
Kind oF.
Eric,that is not
appropriate behavior,mp[ Ay?
You cannot purposely infect
other kids with your disease.
That's right.
I think you owe kyle an apology.
I'm sorry.
An apology?
You're sortail for what,eri!
W I'm sorry for giving you aids,kyle.
That's better.
And now,kyle,maybe you shou this also
admit you were wrong for tattling.
What?
Kyle,the thing about tattling
is that tattling's bad.
Because nobody likes
a tattle tail,mp[ Ay.
A tattle taifri he
infected me with aids!
See?He's tattling again.
He hasn't learned a thing,you guys.
Well,kyle,I guess we're even noW.
Should we just call it a truce?
Kyle,should we call
it even-stevens now?
Kyle,where are you going?
I am going to break
everything that you own.
What is that supposed to kyle,no!
I apologized,kyle!
Kyle!
Kyle,hold on,you asshole.
What the Are you doing?
Kyle,stop it!
god dammit don't
no Kyle, not the fred frog
leave fred frog alone
no
ah Fred Frog
nono not the X-box
not that x-box, wait,
just wait a second
I'm sorry I gave you HIV alright?
Just give me a chance
and I can cure you.
There is no cure,you asshole!
No!No,listen,kyle.
I'm onto something.
There really is a hope.
What hope?
Break my xbox and you'll never know.
You're lying.
No!All right,kyle,magic johnson,kyle!
The key is magic johnson!
Magic johnson?
He was a basketball player.
So what?
So he got hiv like 50 years ago.
He's still totally fine.
Magic johnson has some kind of
resistance to the virus,kyle.
I've been researching
it since i got infected.
If we can track him down and
isolate his genetic prototype,
we have a chance of
beating this thing,buddy.
You and me,kyle.
We can overcome our
illness. I swear it to you!
You better.
Because if you don't the cure
for hiv,I will break your xbox.
My god.
We need two tickets to los
angeles,as soon as possible!
Los angeles,okay. Uh,I
have a 2:00 flight.
That would be $400 each.
Uh,sir,you don't understand.
We have to see magic johnson right away.
You see we have aids.
Aids?
Wow!That's really retro.
But i'm sorry.
I can't just give away free seats.
Don't you get it?
We are two pals,afflicted with an illness and
who only have each other in a race against time!
Innocent,playful children who were stricken
with a deadly disease for no reason.
Oh,please!No reason!
I got aids from him!
Oooh,you boys are like that,huh?
No!
Are you sure you don't
just have any cash?
We're not just sure,we're hiv positive.
Uh,we sometimes offer free seats to cancer patients,but aids,I just
- hey,mitch?
Do we have any aids patient policies?
Forget it,all right!
We'll use another
airline! One that cares!
We're so happy to help
accommodate you brave boys.
What kind of cancer did
you say you have again?
Oh,uh,you know,all-over cancer.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah,well,at least it's
not as bad as having aids!
Aids is the worst disease.
Hmm,I don't know,these days I think
I'd rather have aids than cancer.
No,you would -
look,shouldn't you be serving people
drinks or something?Get outta here!
We're on our way,buddy.
Magic johnson,here we come!
Don't touch me.
I know. I'm scared too.
Magic,magic,could you come
to the front for a minute?
There are a couple of
boys here to see you.
Two,brave little buddies who against all odds have
journeyed across america to find the cure for aids.
All they have is each other
in a race against time.
Thank you for seeing us,mr. Johnson.
We were just hoping that maybe you have some
kind of key that could help us with our disease.
You boys both have
the virus?Are you sure?
We're not just sure,we're hiv positive.
Will you stop it with that?
What part of this is funny to you?
Kyle,we need to try to find -
What part of being infected with
a deadly disease do you find funny?
I don't think it's funny,kyle.
Then stop saying you're not
just sure,you're hiv positive!
This isn't funny.
Aids isn't funny.
Dying isn't funny,so shut the Up.
Well,excuse me,kyle,for
trying to keep some optimism.
You know,sometimes when things seem their
darkest,you just need to try and stay... hiv positive.
But if you want to be so
hiv negative all the time -
Knock it off!Right now!
This isn't funny!
At all!
- Are you sure?
- Yes!
Are you hiv positive
- ow!
Oh... Kyle!
Boys,the truth is I don't know why
my body is so resistant to the virus.
I would love to know so I could
help others,but I just don'T.
Well,I've been thinking.
There's something you've come into
contact with that hinders hiv from growing.
Do you mind if we just look around?
Well,not at all.
The pool is over there,where I
try to swim and stay in shape.
My kitchen is full of very healthy food.
I don't know which thing is what keeps
my t-cell count high,so i try it all.
But everyone tries that.
There has to be something you're
exposed to that others aren'T.
Could we see where you sleep?
Sure.
Just a pretty plain
old ordinary bedroom.
Dude.
Oh. Yeah,I don't trust banks.
I sleep with all my money.
You sleep with money every night?
Yeah. I like to keep it close.
You don't think that -
It's incredible.
Mitch,these boys could
be on to something.
Take a look.
That's a sample of hiv infected blood.
You can clearly see the hiv
attacking the white blood cells,right?
All right. Now watch what happens
when we introduce some cash.
My god!
The hiv particles are receding!
The cash does seem to restrain
the hiv cells from stabilizing.
Now hold on.
All the cash is doing is destrablizing
the virus,not destroying it.
Well,look.
If being around lots of cash
negatively affects the hiv,then maybe -
Then maybe enough cash,shot directly into the
bloodstream could kill the virus altogether.
I have enough cash for all three of us.
We should give it a try!
No,no. This is ridiculous.
We need fda approvals,control studies!
I'm sorry,but this is impossible.
These boys have shown us that a
lot of impossible things can happen.
Their friendship has conquered every
obstacle in their illness-ridden lives!
Their incredible friendship has
brought a sparkle of hope to our world.
That's for sure.
I suppose we could try to distill
magic's cash down to its most highly
concentrated level and
try it on one of them.
But it's very risky.
Yeah,well,if there's a chance
of being cured of this illness,
then kyle is willing to take that risk.
Let's hope to christ this works.
Wait a minute.
Yes.
Yes,take a look!
The cash particles have completely
replaced all the hiv in kyle's blood!
Boys,you've just found
the cure for aids!
All right!
They've found the cure for aids!
The cure for aids!
What is it?
Large doses of concentrated cash!
Get the media on the phone!
All right.
Scientists have just
discovered the cure for aids.
About $180,000 shot directly
into the bloodstream.
nigeria africa
Hey!
They just found the cure for aids!
You just have to infect
yourself with all your cash!
I am pleased to announce that there is no trace of the
hiv virus in either kyle broflovski or eric cartman.
Together,these boys beat their
illness,with nothing but each other,
and overcoming all odds other,and
overcoming all odds these two brave friends.
Oh,stop!We're not friends!
He's the one who infected me with aids!
Those two brave lovers found
the cure and helped the world.
And so to honor these
boys,here is jimmy buffet!
What?Oh,no!
Cure burger in paradise cure
burger there,I said it twice
Agh,god dammit!
Well,I tell you this,kyle.
I'm never getting my
tonsils out again!Ha,ha!
I'm still breaking your xbox.
What?No!
Kyle,kyle,no!
www.tvsubtitles.net