-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
South Park
Season12 Episode07
Kids, everyone together.
Welcome to pioneer village.
This is a re-creation
of early colorado days.
I want you all to meet pioneer paul.
Hi, kids, and welcome to my village.
I settled here in 1864
with my maw and paw.
Sure thing, I ain't never seen strange
clothes like you all are wearing.
And what's that fancy yellow
horse carriage you got out there?
This is gonna suck.
When y'all are ready, just
head up to the village.
All the townsfolk are there
to answer your questions.
And welcome to 1864. Sit 'em up!
Thank you, pioneer paul.
All right, kids, this is a big place so I want
everyone to pick a partner to hold hands with.
Let's be partners, kenny.
No, I'm partners with craig.
Oh, okay.
Stan, let's be partners, dude.
No, I'm with wendy.
You wanna hold hands
with a girl? Gaywad.
All right, let's be partners, kyle.
I hate you, remember?
You wanna be partners, jimmy?
Jesus, what have I ever done to you?
Craig? Token?
Who, who else needs a partner?
Who else needs a partner?
Eric, partner with butters.
God dammit!
Hold butters' hand, eric.
That isn't necessary.
Butters, you are not to let go of eric's
hand until you are both back on that bus.
Do you understand?
I understand.
All right, let's head in.
You can let go now, butters.
No.
Butters, come on.
No!
All right, kids. Go ahead and visit
the charming villagers and learn stuff.
Keep trarack of your partner.
Why, howdy, partners.
I'm the town blacksmith.
Are you folks settlers or are
you just trappers passing through?
Uh, look, can we just drop
the role-playing thing?
I would play along, but my girlfriend's here and
I don't wanna look like a dork in front of her.
Thanks, stan.
Those folk sure are strange, smithy.
We ain't never seen them kind of
fancy hats in our time, have we?
That guy's wearing a digital watch.
Oh, jeez.
- Dammit, chad.
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Howdy, partners. I'm the town gunsmith.
You see, in our time,
it's pretty violent.
See them holes in the walls?
That's so we can put a rifle
through to protect us from indians.
I wanna shoot an indian!
Now some of you might want to meet
abigail at the candle making house.
Or you can head over the general store.
You see any indians?
Nah, it's just the city and a --
oh, my jesus christ monkey balls.
Super fun time.
Dude, check it out. We're only
two blocks from a super fun time!
They got video games
and rides and everything!
Oh, that's cool. Come on, eric,
we need to catch up with everyone.
Dude, screw this place. We
gotta go to super fun time!
Oh, no. I'm not sneaking
out. I'll get in trouble.
Fine. Then let go of my hand.
Teacher said I can't let go
until we're back on the bus.
Well, which is it gonna be, butters?
Are you gonna ditch out with me or are you
gonna disobey the teacher's stupid rule?
I'm not letting go.
Fine. Then you're coming with me.
No, eric!
Butters, let go, god dammit!
No! Teacher! Teacher!
This here is our general store.
It's where I buy all
my supplies and sucH.
Howdy, partners. I own
this here general store.
Look, stan, they had
beef jerky back then.
What do you mean back then?
Don't forget it's 1864!
Right. Except for it really isn'T.
Sure it is. Just look around you.
What's that? It sounds
like police sirens.
What's a siren?
We ain't never heard
of no siren in 1864.
We lost 'em! We lost 'em!
Damn pig cops. Close that gate!
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
Everyone down on the ground. Now!
Whoa now! I'm sheriff mclawdog.
I settled here
back in 1850 --
Jesus christ!
We got to call the
police! Where's your phone?
A phone? Why, what's a phone?
We ain't never heard of such a thing.
What? Come on, this is serious!
Store hand, you ever heard
of this fancy smancy phone?
Uh, no. We ain't got
a phone in our time.
Dude, they just shot a guy in the face.
We got to call the cops.
If you mean the law, only law round
here is town sheriff, mclawdog.
You see, 1864 is a time of growth
and development in the old west --
This is not the time for that!
Oh, man, this is gonna be awesome!
Butters, if you don't let go of my hand
everyone here is going to think we're gay.
Well, that's your problem.
All right, butters. I've
seriously had enough!
Jesus christ.
- One, please.
- Make that two.
Aw, aren't you two cute holding hands.
Are you special little buddies?
No!
Dude, this place sleds!
What should we do first?
We should get back to the pioneer
village. That's what we should do!
Butters, we're going to be back before
anybody even notices we were gone.
Let's go hit the bumper cars.
Over here! This looks like an office.
Here! Here's a phone.
Why, what a strange contraption.
I can't get a dial tone.
What's the number to dial out?
Dial out?
Partner, them are some
funny words you're using.
Dude, do you understand
what's going on here?
Maybe they're right, brian. I mean
this is a special circumstance.
NEVER BREAK CHARACTER!
Hah, I mean, this here
room sure is strange.
We have nothing like these
fancy devices in our time!
Well, I'll say.
I got through! Hello, police?
911, what's your emergency?
There's some terrorists or bank robbers or
something that've taken our class hostage.
Taken hostage where?
The old pioneer village off of kipling.
You mean that annoying place where
employees won't break character?
Sister, you don't know the half of it.
Check it out, dude! I'm a spaceman!
Spaceman, yes!
* I'm having a super fun time day *
yeah! Get that guy! Shoot that guy!
Yeah, now over here!
You got it! Nice!
* Super fun time please don't go away *
What are you oogling at?
* No more worries or
cares it's super fun time *
* the answer to my
prayers super fun time *
* super fun time you're all I need *
* I wanna super fun time
till I freakin' bleed *
* I want you morning, noon
and night super fun time *
*********
* you make my life so
right super fun time *
That's it, eric. We
have to be getting back!
Aw, just a few more things.
No! If we don't leave right now, we're gonna
miss the bus and then they'll know we left!
I guess you're right,
butters. All right. Come on.
Set up the satellite relay.
Check for alternate
routes out of the area.
Unfortunately, your police department got
wind of our robbery and chased after us.
That is unfortunate for you.
Because when I think
it is clear to leave,
we will now need to take hostages with us to
ensure our goods get to their final destination.
Please, if you must take
anyone, don't take me.
These kids are worth more to you.
How did they find us?
Get the loot out of the car
and stash it in that building.
All right, men, listen up.
Looks like our thieves
tried to hide out here.
They've got the employees and
some school kids held hostage.
Tucker, dylan, set up a perimeter.
Everyone stay on your toes.
These are professionals
we're dealing with here.
What did they rob, sir?
A burger king.
All right. Good. Is that all of it?
No, don't forget we got these too.
Excellent. Now listen, everyone.
We're going to be all right.
This is only a small hitch in our plan.
I'd like to speak with
the chief of police.
Who is this?
This is the man who is going to kill
an entire class of fourth graders
if he doesn't get exactly what he wants.
Why aren't the cops coming in?
They must be negotiating.
Them there bandits sure
look mighty strange.
And them pistols is way
bigger than what we gots.
Will you shut up?
Wait, you have guns here?
Sure. Sheriff got lots
of rifles in his office.
Well, why don't you go get
them and bring them back here.
All righty. Come on, store hand.
Yepper!
Oh, man, I can't wait to
see the look on kyle's face
when we tell him we had super fun time while
he was at the dumb, stupid pioneer village.
We're not telling anybody!
I don't want to get in trouble.
And i didn't have a
super fun time anyways.
Butters, you got to learn to chill.
Life goes by pretty fast.
If you don't stop and look
around once in a while,
and do whatever you want all
the time, you could miss it.
Yeah, well, I guess that's kinda true.
Crap, they called the cops on us.
What? They called the caps?
They must have realized we left. Damn!
Oh, my god, the police
are looking for us?
- Butters!
- We're gonna get it now.
Butters, butters, calm down.
I know a way out of this.
You just got me busted forever!
Butters, listen to me. Listen.
No.
All we have to do is sneak back
inside without the cops seeing us.
Then we can say we
were inside all along.
You said they wouldn't notice
we were gone. You promised.
If we sneak back inside we can
say we never left. All right?
All right. Now let go of my hand.
- No. -
Butters --
You made me break one rule.
I'm not breaking the other!
It's all I have now.
All right, come on.
Keep the hostages from talking
and search for holdouts.
Everyone check in at
two-minute intervals.
I hope you have good news, orlich.
The police have us completely
surrounded on all sides.
There's no way we're getting out
above ground without being spotted.
Above ground?
Look. I found this at
the rear of the park.
It's an old mine shaft.
But pioneer village was
sued when a kid died in it,
so they closed it down and protected it
with a huge metal door with a coded lock.
So, if we can get into the shaft, we can
tunnel our way around the police. Excellent.
One more thing, franz.
I want my share of the take now.
What's the matter, arlich?
Lose your sense of trust?
I was just thinking maybe
we get through that tunnel,
then you take the loot to
berlin and I never see you again.
************
******
********
***************
You are an employee here.
That means you are required to know
the door code for fire code reasons.
Mr. David palmer of colorado springs.
My name ain't palmer. It's ol' smithy.
And we ain't never
heard of no fire code.
Why, we got to put fires out ourselves.
That's it. Tell me the code or you die.
One,
two --
- I -
- Yes?
I don't know nothing
about no fancy door code.
I'm just a simple blacksmith.
These pioneer village workers
are really committed to their job.
No! Please! Don't hurt me!
Give us the code to that
door and we can leave!
I never heard of something
called a door code.
Please, can't you ask some other way?
I don't have time for your stupid game!
Tell me or you die right now!
All right, all right.
Look, it's just one of those
new jinkins home security locks.
You press the top button
and then enter 5, 2 --
What he meant to say, kids, is that we
ain't never heard of no fancy door code
'cuz in our time we got to
rely on wood locks and such.
God dammit, you people are Insane!
I don't believe it.
Domino! Volski!
Find out if there are any other
employees or students wandering about.
Bring them here or shoot them.
Oh, crap, we got to hide! Come on.
Yeah, we gotta, got, get
the hell outta here fast!
Sector bravo, no activity.
Jeez, the cops are
looking for us everywhere.
Don't worry. They're not gonna find
us until we're safely back inside.
Look, see that traffic
signal down there?
If we can climb across that, we can jump
to the tree branch and then we're home free.
That looks dangerous.
Not getting busted always
is, butters. Come on.
Good! That's got it. Good!
All right, now head across.
Go easy. Good.
Oh, gosh in heaven.
It's all right. We got it.
- Save me!
- I'm gonna fall!
Oh, dude. Lame.
Frolich, check in. Have you
found any other employees?
We found somebody.
We found this guy in the
jail of the sheriff's office.
You let out murdering murphy!
Y'all are gonna get it for
putting me in that there jail.
Stop it! Stop your bad
historical acting right now.
Tarnation, why'd you
let murdering murphy go?
He's a bad man.
I'm the Bad man!
Do you get that?
Knock it off and give me
the mine shaft access code.
You're just gonna have
to kill us, mister.
'Cuz you ain't making no sense at all.
I won't kill you if you don't tell me.
I'll kill one of them!
Not me! Not me! Not me! Not me! Not me!
You want to see a child die?
No! They don't want to see a child
I am so disappointed in myself.
Teacher gave me a responsibility.
I was just supposed to look
after my partner and I blew it.
Don't be too hard on yourself, butters.
You can't help being a douche bag.
Wait, butters! Look!
This is it. This is our
chance! Swing over, butters. Go!
Quick, are you ready? We got to jump!
- Let's do it.
- Ready? Go!
What about you?
Will you tell us the access code,
or do you want to see this kid die?
I'm sorry. I'm a woman.
And women in our timime ain't allowed to
know the carryings-on of the town proper.
God dammit!
Dude! They're gonna kill kenny!
I can't let them do it.
I've got to make the ultimate sacrifice.
Stan?
Where are you going, stan?
Wendy, I have to do something.
Please look away.
All right, that does it.
On the count of three this child dies.
- One, two - - Give
them the Door code!
Well, howdy there, strangers!
Sorry to interrupt you.
But i done come from pagosa springs
to buy me some wares and such.
- Oh, welcome, partner!
- Howdy!
- Welcome!
- Howdy there!
What, what are you doing?
Say, i heard y'all had some difficulty
with a criminal getting out of your jail.
That's right! Murdering murphy!
He's crazy 'cuz somebody killed his paw.
They killed my paw!
I reckon that maybe you could make a jail
door that opened with numbers instead of keys.
You know like a big safe.
Yeah! I understand that!
Finally, a feller that talks some sensE.
If y'all was to have such a giant safe,
what would you villagers want the number to
be to unlock that there jail door shuck 'em up?
Well, i reckon the
easiest number to remember
for any big safe door
lock would be 1864.
Up! 1864, 'cuz that's what year it is!
We'll take the hostages with us.
No! You got your door code. Let us go!
Copy that. What's the code, over?
Sweet. There's still cops
looking for us in here.
All right. Follow my lead, butters.
Oh, man, hasn't this place
been fascinating, butters?
Yeah, it sure has.
Oh, I just don't know
what I've liked better --
the historical buildings
and artifacts or the, the --
Or the witty anecdotes
of the towns people.
Witty anecdotes, yes.
That's been awesome.
Been a hoot. All right!
Get your hands behind your head.
What'd we do? We've
been here the whole time.
Shut up! Put your hands
behind your head. Do it now!
Let go of each other!
Do what I tell you!
Our teacher said we have to hold
hands the whole time we're here!
Let go or else I'll put a bullet
through your hands and make you let go!
ButterS.
- Now!
- No!
Jesus christ!
Go! Go take care of it.
I'll stay with the hostages.
Hey, murdering murphy.
You see that there feller?
Yeah.
He done killed your paw.
What? I'll rip his head off!
We got a chance! Hostages are clear!
They're coming in!
Hostages are secure
at the park entrance.
I got you now, pioneer paul.
They should have never let you
out of jail, murdering murphy.
Freeze, scumbag! It's all over!
murdering murphy's
gonna kill pioneer paul.
Stop right now! It's over!
Howdy, partners. It's 5 o'clock.
Pioneer village is
now closed for the day.
Head back to your wagons
and have a safe trip home!
We made it! We maid it!
Oh, god. It can't wait
to get out of this dress!
- That was great!
- Oh, what a day!
Listen, if anyone still wants to know, the
phone is in the administration building.
You dial 9 to get out and there's actually
a back exit behind the horse troughs.
Good night, everybody. Thanks
for coming. We did it, guys!
Let's go to tgi fridays and
get some jalapeno poppers!
Yeah! That'd be great!
All right Let's go!
Stan, you were really brave in there.
But you did kinda sound like a big dork.
I know.
Come on, you!
You're hurting my arm! Too bad.
You'll be going away a long time.
Was it worth it?
In a way, it was.
I might not have gotten away, but at least I
learned a lot about pioneer life in the old west.
Those early settlers didn't have all the
modern conveniences we all take for granted.
To think how difficult it was back those times
to do something as simple as washing your clothes.
Pioneer village has
a lot to teach us all.
That's true.
Hey, look!
Teacher, my partner is back on the bus.
www.tvsubtitles.net