[Script Info]
; // The sub is created by AssToolkit
; // AssToolkit is an ASS Converter designed by David C.
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.23,0:00:03.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《行尸走肉》前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.92,0:00:05.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.24,0:00:06.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会后悔的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.09,0:00:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有话对我说吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.70,0:00:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时应该杀死你的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.19,0:00:11.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  你大概是该这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.30,0:00:16.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,撤退
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.31,0:00:21.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.00,0:00:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那种行为
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.84,0:00:24.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绝对不可取
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.16,0:00:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要我动手吗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.05,0:00:29.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,欢迎来到全新的开始  你们这些可怜虫
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.29,0:00:31.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}《谁是老大》[1984年电视剧]
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.87,0:07:46.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡森
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.98,0:07:51.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们刚检查完
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.37,0:07:53.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.42,0:07:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  小德
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.24,0:08:04.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.74,0:08:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别跟他说话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.41,0:08:20.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是阴性的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.50,0:08:23.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许下次吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.51,0:08:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.27,0:08:27.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还在习惯做我自己的助手
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.83,0:08:38.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管他们说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.62,0:08:41.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-照做就行  -我说了别跟他说话
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.28,0:08:46.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  来看看
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.79,0:08:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会好转的  如果你配合
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.10,0:08:56.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根会照顾你
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.89,0:08:58.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.28,0:09:12.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小德怀特
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.55,0:09:16.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得跟我的朋友聊会儿
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.40,0:09:18.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去做你的事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.45,0:09:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除了你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.37,0:09:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你站在那儿
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.64,0:09:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.76,0:10:04.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.21,0:10:06.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.41,0:10:26.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我渐渐知道怎么用这玩意儿了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.64,0:10:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是你的下场  混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.69,0:10:41.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非你放聪明点
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.86,0:10:43.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己选
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.44,0:10:45.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以跟他们一样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.54,0:10:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者跟我一样
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.89,0:10:52.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者跟它们一样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.75,0:11:06.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少受点罪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.02,0:11:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会下跪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.72,0:11:12.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也这样说过
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.11,0:11:15.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.56,0:11:17.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.72,0:11:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是问题所在
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.36,0:11:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不理解
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.82,0:11:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你会的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.00,0:12:04.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他要疯了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.25,0:12:07.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.58,0:12:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你呢  你在火上浇油
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.86,0:12:11.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起作用了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.94,0:12:14.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,虽然见效很慢  但是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.83,0:12:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些人就是更难击溃
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.08,0:12:19.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  他快了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.10,0:12:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.68,0:12:24.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然你做得这么好
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.85,0:12:26.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想跟之前的老熟人
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.68,0:12:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玩一玩吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.28,0:12:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我开玩笑的  放松点
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.67,0:12:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想选谁都行  只要她愿意
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.55,0:12:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,糟了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.18,0:12:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你下面还好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.84,0:12:49.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的老二
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.50,0:12:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那家伙  他...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.05,0:12:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狠狠咬了一口
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.08,0:12:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它会不会...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.80,0:12:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,已经萎了
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.91,0:13:00.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.67,0:13:03.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.58,0:13:04.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挺好的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.73,0:13:10.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你真的"好"吗  德怀特
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.23,0:13:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我刚刚可是说了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.19,0:13:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小妞任选  供君消遣
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.78,0:13:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德怀特可以免费享用
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.31,0:13:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你却告诉我说"不用了"
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.63,0:13:21.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这叫"好"吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.14,0:13:24.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的工作还没完成
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.12,0:13:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还不配得到奖赏
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.38,0:13:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.89,0:13:29.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说什么屁话呢
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.28,0:13:31.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,付出就有收获
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.54,0:13:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出现橙色事件
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.48,0:13:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.67,0:13:40.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿拉特  什么情况  有人偷东西吗
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.86,0:13:42.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  他只能从三条路逃跑
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.32,0:13:44.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蛾子那条 天使那条  或者难走的那条
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.63,0:13:45.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.20,0:13:51.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是小德  我在门口和你汇合
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.85,0:13:54.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想拿回我的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.16,0:13:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那是件苦差事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.73,0:13:59.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不如让肥乔去吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.60,0:14:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他绝对需要多运动运动
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.77,0:14:02.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.13,0:14:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不用去的  德怀特
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.66,0:14:09.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很乐意去
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.32,0:14:16.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,乖孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.02,0:18:30.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁着还能回去  赶紧回去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.80,0:18:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我就回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.05,0:18:37.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论他对你做了什么  都还能更糟
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.40,0:18:39.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有更糟的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.49,0:18:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你逃不掉的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.45,0:18:47.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你被抓回来了  惩罚会更糟
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.79,0:19:51.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吓尿了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.27,0:20:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.00,0:20:07.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.97,0:20:12.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.84,0:20:13.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.68,0:20:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.68,0:20:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.27,0:20:22.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.44,0:20:25.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我无处不在
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.39,0:20:29.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你用这次逃跑
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.26,0:20:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,证明了这个简单的事实
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.16,0:20:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你输了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.19,0:20:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这真是糟透了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.08,0:20:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你的生活本可以变得好很多
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.60,0:20:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说的对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.89,0:20:45.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对极了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.42,0:20:59.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德怀特给了你一些选择
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.72,0:21:02.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你没搞明白
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.58,0:21:04.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我就细说给你听
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.90,0:21:06.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有三个选择
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.72,0:21:09.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一  你被插在柱子上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.54,0:21:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,作为死人替我工作
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.70,0:21:16.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二  你从牢里出来  靠工作赚工分
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.15,0:21:18.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你会生不如死
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.80,0:21:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者第三  你为我效力
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.06,0:21:25.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给自己弄一双新鞋
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.06,0:21:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,活得像国王一样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.10,0:21:31.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这选择似乎很明显嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.52,0:21:35.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该知道  没有第四种选择了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.51,0:21:37.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这些了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.91,0:21:41.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是唯一的办法了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.30,0:21:51.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去他妈的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:00.09,0:22:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很难吓到你嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.43,0:22:05.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.62,0:22:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是露西尔
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.07,0:22:13.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很生气哦
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.93,0:22:17.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她觉得你这样很不敬
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.68,0:22:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算你走运
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.79,0:22:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她今天不是很口渴
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.06,0:22:27.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我很口渴
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.59,0:22:32.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.08,0:22:35.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去喝一杯了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.32,0:23:54.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.12,0:24:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有很多事  我真希望我永远都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.02,0:24:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望我没有试图...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.89,0:24:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前在森林里时
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.94,0:24:23.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我失去蒂娜之后
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.30,0:24:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们拿了你的东西  然后决定回去
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.65,0:24:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我跟你说了抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.74,0:24:38.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当时说  "你会后悔的"
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.49,0:24:43.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我后悔了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.99,0:24:57.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我受伤了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.43,0:24:58.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的摩托废了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.23,0:24:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须回去  因为你欠着债
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.98,0:25:02.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你欠的债更多了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.66,0:25:03.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这值得吗
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.24,0:25:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.27,0:25:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:25:13.58,0:25:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.49,0:25:17.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.94,0:25:23.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们以前关系很好
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.28,0:25:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.16,0:25:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在他做了那些事之后
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.59,0:25:35.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你  对你的妻子所做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.21,0:25:36.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别提到她
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.61,0:25:38.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不是我妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.83,0:25:40.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不再是了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.36,0:25:44.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看  你无处可去
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.58,0:25:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都是他的  早晚都是
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.82,0:25:50.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.78,0:25:56.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续走
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.26,0:26:01.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说继续走
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.13,0:26:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.47,0:26:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.88,0:26:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开枪也不要紧的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.58,0:26:09.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我理解
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.57,0:26:12.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死  我希望你打死我  拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.39,0:26:13.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.61,0:26:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,继续走
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.34,0:26:17.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能回去
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.62,0:26:18.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得回去
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.82,0:26:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为没别的选择
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.80,0:26:22.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这只是他的一面之词
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.02,0:26:25.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他说没别的选择  只能按他说的做
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.29,0:26:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个拿着球棒邪笑的恶棍来了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.39,0:26:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我们那么恐惧  放弃了一切
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.57,0:26:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他只是一个人  我们有这么多人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.37,0:26:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么我们要这样活着
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.66,0:26:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为看看我们现在的情况
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.89,0:26:41.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们以前一直在输
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.04,0:26:43.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不会了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.94,0:26:45.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.19,0:26:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我和玛利亚死里逃生的最初几个月...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.89,0:26:55.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我们到了那里
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.67,0:26:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们以为一切会好的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.86,0:27:04.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们以为自己知道该怎么和怪物抗争
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.26,0:27:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起来
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.02,0:27:21.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要紧的  小德
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.34,0:27:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起来
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.98,0:27:25.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那里没有任何值得我留恋的东西了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.02,0:27:30.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是我今生最后一次下跪
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.57,0:27:31.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起来
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.34,0:27:33.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你懂的  -起来
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.73,0:27:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记得  小德
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.54,0:27:38.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然我就把你认识的所有人都丢进栅栏
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.14,0:27:41.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会蒙住他们的眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.26,0:27:43.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后逼他们在短暂又可悲的余生中
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.13,0:27:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃大便三明治
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.44,0:27:51.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会把你妻子的尸体挖出来喂乌鸦
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.87,0:27:52.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懂吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.87,0:27:55.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你懂吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.73,0:27:56.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  小德
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.22,0:28:02.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你赢了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.20,0:28:14.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你知道  我生无可恋
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.32,0:29:27.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能给我一支吗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.48,0:29:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他对你好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.63,0:29:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.62,0:30:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.53,0:30:05.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.60,0:30:07.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你开心吗
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.75,0:30:11.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.38,0:30:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好
Dialogue: 0,0:30:19.49,0:30:21.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做了正确的事
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.63,0:30:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总比死强多了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.59,0:30:33.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.55,0:31:26.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.04,0:31:33.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你害死了你朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.46,0:31:36.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我害死了蒂娜
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.67,0:31:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别装作你不了解真相
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.87,0:31:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你早该死了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.50,0:31:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是尼根看中了你
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.97,0:31:57.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很走运
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.80,0:31:59.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别忘记这点
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.17,0:32:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祝你胃口好
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.38,0:34:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,进
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.39,0:34:55.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.98,0:34:58.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.72,0:35:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起来糟透了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.99,0:35:03.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别担心
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.86,0:35:06.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会让卡森治好你
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.08,0:35:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你渴吗  给
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.40,0:35:11.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,见鬼  我忘了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.95,0:35:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.72,0:35:16.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肿得像狒狒的屁股
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.50,0:35:18.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要吸管吗
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.55,0:35:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小德  给他根吸管
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.09,0:35:23.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么待客的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.41,0:35:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到那家伙了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.82,0:35:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他负责煽风点火
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.94,0:35:31.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢煽风点火
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.15,0:35:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是信不信由你
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.75,0:35:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们之前并不和睦
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.04,0:35:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小德  他要靠工作赚工分
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.75,0:35:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他和他性感的妻子  还有她性感的妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.13,0:35:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是妹妹  她需要药物
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.66,0:35:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那玩意儿很难搜集
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.91,0:35:59.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以价值更高
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.20,0:36:02.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妹妹没赚够工分
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.19,0:36:04.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我让她嫁给我
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.20,0:36:07.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说我会照顾她
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.35,0:36:09.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论生老病死  等等
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.49,0:36:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我是个顶天立地的男子汉
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.46,0:36:18.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她告诉我她会想想
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.12,0:36:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下来呢
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.41,0:36:23.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就出了橙色事件
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.30,0:36:27.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小德怀特偷走了所有的药
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.12,0:36:29.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带上了他性感的妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.40,0:36:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我性感的准未婚妻跑了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.11,0:36:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我必须派人去追他
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.23,0:36:44.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我不能容忍这种事
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.16,0:36:49.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里是有规矩的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.04,0:36:54.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,追他让我付出了很大代价
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.32,0:36:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你猜怎么着  小德怀特
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.47,0:37:02.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他还是跑掉了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.20,0:37:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但问题是
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.64,0:37:07.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小德  他觉悟了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.31,0:37:09.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他拿出了男子气概  他回来了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.28,0:37:11.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他求我原谅他
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.40,0:37:13.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢这点
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.23,0:37:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我眼前一亮
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.31,0:37:22.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是露西尔
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.59,0:37:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道她是什么样
Dialogue: 0,0:37:27.56,0:37:30.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她很守规矩
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.29,0:37:34.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以德怀特
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.77,0:37:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他求我别杀雪莉
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.26,0:37:41.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得还挺可爱的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.79,0:37:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我只打算杀他
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.97,0:37:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是然后雪莉说她会嫁给我
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.62,0:37:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我让德怀特活命的话
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.45,0:37:53.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,仔细想想  这提议还挺变态的
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.90,0:37:55.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我本来要娶的是她妹妹
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.55,0:37:58.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果她死了  但是
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.77,0:38:01.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雪莉的确非常性感
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.94,0:38:06.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总之  这是个好开始
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.68,0:38:09.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但还不够
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.91,0:38:12.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以德怀特
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.83,0:38:15.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,受了烙铁之刑
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.96,0:38:18.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我娶了他性感的妻子
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.95,0:38:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前妻
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.99,0:38:27.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,经历了这些事  他依然入伙了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.86,0:38:29.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在看看他
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.53,0:38:33.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我最得力的手下之一
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.87,0:38:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们完全和好了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.75,0:38:39.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重点是
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.23,0:38:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为你也能成为那样的人
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.76,0:38:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认为你准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:38:47.74,0:38:49.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看周围
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.42,0:38:50.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这些
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.67,0:38:56.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都可以归你
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.08,0:39:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你用做的只是
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.21,0:39:03.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回答一个简单问题
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.74,0:39:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.90,0:39:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说不出话了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.13,0:39:17.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被这壮丽的景象惊呆了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:20.02,0:39:22.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我再问你一次
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.63,0:39:35.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.67,0:39:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.44,0:40:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是唯一的...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.74,0:40:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别说话
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.07,0:40:09.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没关系  小德
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.16,0:40:15.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他做出了选择
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.95,0:40:21.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他做出愚蠢的选择不是我的错
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.06,0:40:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要么进那个房间
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.53,0:40:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么挂在栅栏上
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.69,0:40:44.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我理解你为什么那样做了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.98,0:40:48.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么接受
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.43,0:40:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是为别人着想
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.83,0:41:02.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这也是我不能接受的原因
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.21,0:05:17.42,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第七季  第三集』
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.23,0:01:07.08,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx2300\fscy200\alpha&AA\pos(129.2,218.4)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.22,0:00:47.22,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻译:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}冰蓝  Reginamoon  君君
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.19,0:00:52.19,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻译:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}CS小明漫画家 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.15,0:00:57.15,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}校对:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.12,0:01:02.12,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}时间轴:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}雪妞 涛涛 加森
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.08,0:01:07.08,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}后期:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小哥  拉图    {\c&H008AFF&}总监： {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小孩
