1
00:00:00,330 --> 00:00:03,610
《行尸走肉》前情提要
Previously, on AMC's "The Walking Dead"...

2
00:00:03,610 --> 00:00:04,820
我只想要尼根
I only want Negan.

3
00:00:05,640 --> 00:00:06,950
一顆子彈解決不了任何問題
A single bullet ain't gonna do it.

4
00:00:06,950 --> 00:00:08,900
最好的情況下  也許你能打死他
Best case, maybe you take him out.

5
00:00:08,900 --> 00:00:10,760
那就給我做一顆子彈
Then make me a bullet.

6
00:00:10,760 --> 00:00:13,050
我們得到的一切  都是抗爭得來的
Everything we have, we got from fighting.

7
00:00:13,050 --> 00:00:16,530
我們遵守他們的規則  就能活下去
We play by their rules, we get some kinda life.

8
00:00:16,530 --> 00:00:19,510
你帶我們來到了樂土  對不對  瑞克
You led us all to the promise land, isn't that right, Rick?

9
00:00:19,630 --> 00:00:20,800
我們成了這樣
He we are!

10
00:00:21,380 --> 00:00:23,190
我喜歡這里
Oh, I like it here.

11
00:00:23,750 --> 00:00:25,810
救世軍其實很講道理的
Saviors can actually be quite reasonable.

12
00:01:32,200 --> 00:01:33,090
瑪姬
Maggie.

13
00:01:37,020 --> 00:01:39,490
我知道人們在議論紛紛
I know people are saying things --

14
00:01:40,010 --> 00:01:43,900
說關于你和薩沙的好話
nice things about you and Sasha, hmm?

15
00:01:46,130 --> 00:01:46,970
是嗎
They are?

16
00:01:47,500 --> 00:01:48,370
是的
They are.

17
00:01:48,990 --> 00:01:50,270
關于那晚
About the other night...

18
00:01:51,520 --> 00:01:53,730
他們覺得是你救了這里
about how they're thinking you saved the place.

19
00:01:56,330 --> 00:01:58,220
別被沖昏了頭腦
Don't let it go to your head.

20
00:01:59,760 --> 00:02:01,580
那你也別介意
Well, don't let it bother you.

21
00:02:03,900 --> 00:02:05,650
看起來你挺介意的
It seems like it bothers you.

22
00:02:16,230 --> 00:02:17,740
你在上面干什么呢
What you doing up there?

23
00:02:21,000 --> 00:02:22,180
你到底吃不吃
You gonna eat that?

24
00:02:23,660 --> 00:02:24,640
我吃
Yes.

25
00:02:26,420 --> 00:02:27,260
哥們
Dude.

26
00:02:28,430 --> 00:02:29,770
你知道她懷孕了
You know she's pregnant.

27
00:02:56,090 --> 00:02:57,970
逆著毛刮  孩子
Against the grain, kid.

28
00:02:58,880 --> 00:03:02,100
總是逆著毛刮
Always against the grain.

29
00:03:40,940 --> 00:03:42,510
聞起來真香
Damn, that smells good.

30
00:03:49,000 --> 00:03:50,040
想嘗嘗嗎
Want a taste?

31
00:03:54,860 --> 00:03:55,700
好吧
Okay.

32
00:04:05,720 --> 00:04:07,300
他要的檸檬粉
Here's his damn lemonade.

33
00:04:08,360 --> 00:04:09,880
我廚房里有一些
I had some in my kitchen.

34
00:04:12,700 --> 00:04:13,840
丹妮斯喜歡喝
Denise liked it.

35
00:04:19,210 --> 00:04:20,100
謝謝
Thank you.

36
00:04:25,240 --> 00:04:26,120
回家去
Go home.

37
00:04:26,960 --> 00:04:28,300
交給我吧
Let me take over.

38
00:04:30,960 --> 00:04:31,760
不
No.

39
00:04:32,530 --> 00:04:33,500
我沒事
I'm fine.

40
00:04:35,660 --> 00:04:37,830
我答應瑞克照看朱迪思
I told Rick I would watch Judith.

41
00:04:39,750 --> 00:04:40,930
我會做到的
I'm gonna do that.

42
00:04:46,860 --> 00:04:47,830
你該走了
You should go.

43
00:04:50,110 --> 00:04:51,550
我們要坐下了
We're about to sit.

44
00:05:20,230 --> 00:05:21,990
我們還需要一套餐具
We're gonna need another setting.

45
00:05:47,240 --> 00:05:49,190
只有今天一天了  對吧
Today and only today, right?

46
00:05:51,100 --> 00:05:52,120
是的
Yeah.

47
00:05:56,260 --> 00:05:57,880
這些彈孔
All these bullet holes --

48
00:05:58,850 --> 00:06:00,970
這船很快會進水
this'll take on water quick.

49
00:06:06,450 --> 00:06:08,310
我們也許能到獨木舟那
We can probably make it to the canoe.

50
00:06:09,930 --> 00:06:11,010
也許吧
Probably.

51
00:06:13,620 --> 00:06:14,840
如果你想留下來...
If you want to stay back...

52
00:06:16,980 --> 00:06:18,810
我要裝作你沒說那話
I'm going to pretend you didn't just say that.

53
00:06:34,650 --> 00:06:35,890
我決心做完這事
I'm seeing this through.

54
00:06:36,600 --> 00:06:37,590
我們都是
We both are.

55
00:07:03,670 --> 00:07:05,390
我不再等你爸爸了
I'm not waiting for your dad anymore.

56
00:07:05,420 --> 00:07:07,420
我不知道他在哪里
I don't know where the hell he is,

57
00:07:09,300 --> 00:07:10,710
但露西爾
but Lucille...

58
00:07:15,610 --> 00:07:16,870
餓了
...is hungry.

59
00:07:22,410 --> 00:07:25,420
卡爾  把面包卷遞給我
Carl, pass the rolls...

60
00:07:30,210 --> 00:07:31,370
麻煩你了
...Please.

61
00:07:36,550 --> 00:07:41,550
{\an4}{\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻譯:  冰藍 Reginamoon CS小明漫畫家 自然卷 蘑菇 送小孩

63
00:07:41,520 --> 00:07:46,520
{\an4}{\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻譯:  最后一次為Gallavich開車的根總迷弟

64
00:07:46,480 --> 00:07:51,480
{\an4}{\pos(12.12,219.36)}校對:  送小孩

65
00:07:51,450 --> 00:07:56,450
{\an4}{\pos(12.12,219.36)}時間軸:  某雪 加森 濤濤

66
00:07:56,410 --> 00:08:01,410
{\an4}{\pos(12.12,219.36)}后期:  送小哥 拉圖    總監： 送小孩

67
00:08:08,590 --> 00:08:12,800
{\an9}{\pos(308.4,176.8)}行尸走肉
『第七季  第八集』

68
00:08:26,580 --> 00:08:29,090
瞧瞧
Ohh. Look at that, huh?

69
00:08:29,640 --> 00:08:30,820
就這么容易
Easy as that.

70
00:08:31,780 --> 00:08:34,500
只是個交易
It's just a transaction.

71
00:08:35,630 --> 00:08:36,850
你看起來很糟糕
You look like shit,

72
00:08:36,850 --> 00:08:38,050
說明你為之奮斗了
which means you fought for this.

73
00:08:38,050 --> 00:08:39,120
盡到了職責
You did your jobs.

74
00:08:41,400 --> 00:08:42,900
你懂道理  我喜歡
You get it, and I like that.

75
00:08:43,330 --> 00:08:45,110
尼根喜歡
Negan likes that.

76
00:08:48,890 --> 00:08:50,700
聽到這話很高興
That's...good to hear.

77
00:08:52,740 --> 00:08:53,700
你好好干
You play your cards right,

78
00:08:53,700 --> 00:08:55,470
也許我會帶你去我們住的地方
maybe I'll show you where we live.

79
00:08:57,020 --> 00:08:58,830
也許我會給你買個三明治
Maybe I'll buy you a sandwich.

80
00:09:05,700 --> 00:09:06,880
告訴我什么時候就好
Just tell me when.

81
00:09:09,310 --> 00:09:10,600
你喜歡看嗎  長毛
You like watching, haircut?

82
00:09:11,300 --> 00:09:12,050
是的
Yes.

83
00:09:13,060 --> 00:09:13,830
我是說
I mean...

84
00:09:14,740 --> 00:09:16,910
你該滾遠點
You mean to get the hell out of here.

85
00:09:17,740 --> 00:09:18,870
馬上
Now!

86
00:09:56,340 --> 00:09:57,170
摩根
Morgan.

87
00:10:00,790 --> 00:10:03,060
這是神之國花園里的
It's just some things from the Kingdom garden --

88
00:10:03,060 --> 00:10:05,790
一些油桃和蘋果
some nectarines, some apples.

89
00:10:06,040 --> 00:10:07,940
謝謝  我不需要
Thank you. I am good.

90
00:10:08,010 --> 00:10:09,460
我知道你可以照顧自己
You can fend for yourself, I know,

91
00:10:09,460 --> 00:10:11,900
但新鮮果蔬不是隨隨便便...
but fresh produce isn't something you can just --

92
00:10:11,900 --> 00:10:12,710
真的
Really.

93
00:10:14,900 --> 00:10:15,780
我不需要
I'm good.

94
00:10:20,120 --> 00:10:21,060
以西結嗎
Ezekiel?

95
00:10:21,060 --> 00:10:23,310
顯然  我說我想一個人待著時
Apparently, some people are having a hard time believing me

96
00:10:23,310 --> 00:10:25,960
有人很難相信我
when I say I just want to be left alone.

97
00:10:26,310 --> 00:10:28,710
我的確是想讓你一個人待著  我以后也會的
You know, I was trying to leave you alone, and I will.

98
00:10:29,540 --> 00:10:31,050
但你叫我進來了
But you called me over.

99
00:10:32,810 --> 00:10:33,690
為什么
Why?

100
00:10:34,200 --> 00:10:35,050
你怎么樣
How are you?

101
00:10:35,140 --> 00:10:35,830
挺好
Good.

102
00:10:37,770 --> 00:10:38,530
那就好
Good.

103
00:10:38,960 --> 00:10:40,230
現在你可以走了
Now you can go.

104
00:10:43,640 --> 00:10:45,220
我覺得你變溫柔了
I think you're going soft.

105
00:10:45,670 --> 00:10:46,990
我覺得你要走了
I think you're going.

106
00:10:56,630 --> 00:10:57,740
卡蘿爾
Carol, hi.

107
00:10:58,430 --> 00:10:59,600
抱歉打擾你了
I'm sorry to bother you.

108
00:11:00,560 --> 00:11:03,140
摩根  我沒想到你也在這里
Morgan, I-I didn't expect you to be here, too.

109
00:11:03,140 --> 00:11:04,330
你來了挺好的
It's good you are.

110
00:11:05,670 --> 00:11:07,550
實際上我想跟你倆都聊聊
I wanted to speak to you both, actually.

111
00:11:07,550 --> 00:11:08,990
是關于一件重要的事
It's about something important.

112
00:11:13,500 --> 00:11:15,060
快到獨木舟了
Almost at the canoe.

113
00:11:19,090 --> 00:11:22,320
-進水太快了  -我知道
- We're taking on water quick, man. - I know.

114
00:11:31,810 --> 00:11:33,020
瑞克  左邊
Rick, on the left!

115
00:12:04,210 --> 00:12:05,120
快到了
We're almost there.

116
00:12:22,150 --> 00:12:23,520
不  不
No, no!

117
00:12:30,380 --> 00:12:31,440
挺住
Hold on!

118
00:12:32,360 --> 00:12:33,320
挺住
Hold on!

119
00:12:33,580 --> 00:12:35,470
待在獨木舟里
Stay in the canoe!

120
00:12:35,640 --> 00:12:37,810
我可以...
I can -- Just --

121
00:12:39,180 --> 00:12:39,960
亞倫
Aaron!

122
00:12:41,360 --> 00:12:42,720
亞倫
Aaron!

123
00:12:51,840 --> 00:12:52,730
亞倫
Aaron!

124
00:12:58,750 --> 00:12:59,760
我沒事
I'm okay.

125
00:13:00,380 --> 00:13:01,330
我沒事
I'm all right.

126
00:13:03,680 --> 00:13:04,550
我沒事
I'm okay.

127
00:13:05,470 --> 00:13:06,300
我沒事
I'm okay.

128
00:13:38,140 --> 00:13:39,880
別靠著墻
Stop hugging the wall.

129
00:13:40,740 --> 00:13:41,780
當心
Watch it!

130
00:13:44,520 --> 00:13:45,980
該死的
God damn it!

131
00:13:50,500 --> 00:13:52,210
去把拖把和桶拿來
Go get a mop and another barrel.

132
00:13:52,210 --> 00:13:53,620
這玩意還要留著嗎
We're keeping this crap?

133
00:13:54,130 --> 00:13:55,500
我們不用吃
We don't have to eat it.

134
00:13:56,470 --> 00:13:58,240
老天  他超恨泡菜的
Jesus. He hates pickles.

135
00:14:08,260 --> 00:14:09,190
明明有鉤子
It's got hooks.

136
00:14:09,200 --> 00:14:10,890
我不知道他為啥不把它系上
I don't know why he didn't strap it in.

137
00:14:11,010 --> 00:14:13,680
和他說了兩次了  他個蠢貨就是不聽
Told him twice. His stupid ass didn't listen.

138
00:14:39,060 --> 00:14:40,790
{\an8}恭喜你贏了
但你還是輸了

139
00:14:46,370 --> 00:14:47,600
這家伙輸不起啊
Bit of a sore loser.

140
00:14:51,360 --> 00:14:54,130
看來除了彈藥  其他東西都還有剩
Looks like the only thing he ran out of was ammo.

141
00:14:55,630 --> 00:14:57,260
我們得馬上把這些弄回去
We got to get this back now.

142
00:14:57,260 --> 00:14:58,090
是啊
Yeah.

143
00:15:00,050 --> 00:15:02,960
他有槳
Well...he's got paddles.

144
00:15:03,720 --> 00:15:04,670
再加上是順風
And with the wind picking up,

145
00:15:04,670 --> 00:15:06,590
漂回岸邊應該不用很久
it shouldn't take long to drift back to shore.

146
00:15:08,310 --> 00:15:09,920
冷靜  冷靜
Easy. Easy.

147
00:15:11,300 --> 00:15:13,320
我們來弄就好  把這玩意放回去
We got it. Take this crap back.

148
00:15:13,320 --> 00:15:15,280
你這次看著點路行嗎
How 'bout, this time, you watch where you're going?

149
00:15:15,280 --> 00:15:17,160
行了  別說他了
Oh, come on. Get off his back.

150
00:15:34,490 --> 00:15:35,600
剛剛在那邊
You know, back there,

151
00:15:37,580 --> 00:15:40,000
我不是說你做不到
I didn't mean that you couldn't do it.

152
00:15:41,880 --> 00:15:42,950
只是...
It's just...

153
00:15:45,560 --> 00:15:48,220
走了這么遠  冒了這么大險
going this far, risking this much

154
00:15:48,390 --> 00:15:49,790
就為了給他們找東西
to get things for them --

155
00:15:49,790 --> 00:15:51,410
很多人并不贊同這種做法
people don't agree with it.

156
00:15:51,840 --> 00:15:53,760
假如你也不情愿我不會怪你
I wouldn't blame you if you didn't.

157
00:15:58,970 --> 00:15:59,880
我當時在場
I was there.

158
00:16:01,930 --> 00:16:03,500
我目睹了一切
I saw what happened on the road.

159
00:16:06,240 --> 00:16:08,380
我們這么做是為了讓大家活命
What we're doing is gonna keep people living.

160
00:16:09,870 --> 00:16:11,110
我們必須這么做
We get to do that,

161
00:16:12,210 --> 00:16:13,780
無論我們自身會遭遇什么
it doesn't matter what happens to us.

162
00:16:15,250 --> 00:16:17,250
米恩瓊不認同這種活法
Michonne doesn't think this is living.

163
00:16:19,430 --> 00:16:23,230
選擇這樣的活法
Well, committing to a choice like this,

164
00:16:24,020 --> 00:16:25,640
相比于我們之前的生活...
after living how we did --

165
00:16:26,520 --> 00:16:27,310
自由的...
free --

166
00:16:28,190 --> 00:16:29,110
我理解她
I get it.

167
00:16:30,790 --> 00:16:31,730
是很難
It's hard.

168
00:16:33,280 --> 00:16:35,930
這是放棄了除你生命以外的一切
It's giving up everything, right up until your own life.

169
00:16:39,870 --> 00:16:42,040
但只有這樣你才能活著
But either your heart's beating, or it isn't.

170
00:16:43,510 --> 00:16:45,910
你愛的人才能活著
Your loved ones' hearts are beating, or they aren't.

171
00:16:50,290 --> 00:16:51,770
我們接受他們的條件
We take what they give us

172
00:16:52,330 --> 00:16:53,580
我們才能活下來
so that we can live.

173
00:17:27,890 --> 00:17:29,960
你和尼根在一起多久了
So, how long you been with Negan?

174
00:17:37,070 --> 00:17:38,750
你為什么獨自一人在外
Why were you out there alone?

175
00:17:41,730 --> 00:17:42,800
告訴我
Tell me.

176
00:17:55,010 --> 00:17:58,030
你認為即便你開口了也改變不了自己的結局
You think talking won't change how this ends for you.

177
00:17:58,170 --> 00:17:59,810
但你不了解我
But you don't know me.

178
00:18:04,610 --> 00:18:06,050
走著瞧吧
Let's see what happens.

179
00:18:23,250 --> 00:18:25,100
我今天不會去殺他
I'm not gonna kill him today.

180
00:18:27,270 --> 00:18:29,490
我要找到一個能讓我們取勝的方法
I'm gonna find the way that we win.

181
00:18:33,140 --> 00:18:35,160
我要改變自己的結局
I'm gonna change how this ends for me.

182
00:18:37,520 --> 00:18:39,160
這就是我獨自一人在外的原因
That's why I'm out here alone.

183
00:18:47,760 --> 00:18:49,070
那是蘋果派嗎
Is that an apple pie?

184
00:18:52,170 --> 00:18:53,680
你是怎么做到的
Uh. How did you do that?

185
00:18:53,680 --> 00:18:55,440
它還在門外我就聞到了
I could smell it from outside the door.

186
00:18:56,500 --> 00:18:58,080
是你烤的嗎
Uh, you baked it?

187
00:18:58,080 --> 00:19:01,040
某個人送給我們以表感激
Some guy gave it to us for what we did.

188
00:19:01,630 --> 00:19:04,340
他女兒說你應該去競選山頂寨總統
His little girl said you should run for President of Hilltop.

189
00:19:04,700 --> 00:19:06,440
"支持瑪姬當總統"
"Maggie for President."

190
00:19:12,270 --> 00:19:14,760
要碟子嗎
Uh, do you want a plate?

191
00:19:14,760 --> 00:19:16,170
不用  這樣就行
No, I'm good.

192
00:19:18,680 --> 00:19:20,200
那些是耶穌給你的嗎
Did Jesus give you those?

193
00:19:21,740 --> 00:19:22,980
他還在這嗎
Is he still around?

194
00:19:24,250 --> 00:19:26,840
趁他還沒走  我想在他的單子上加幾樣東西
There's some things I wanna add to his list before he goes out.

195
00:19:28,240 --> 00:19:29,560
孩子們需要一些寫字用的東西
The kids need something to write with --

196
00:19:29,560 --> 00:19:30,910
水筆  鉛筆
pens, pencils.

197
00:19:31,190 --> 00:19:32,530
你已經是總統了嗎
Are you already president?

198
00:19:32,530 --> 00:19:34,820
我只是和大家聊了一聊
Mm. I've just been talking to people.

199
00:19:35,230 --> 00:19:36,860
耶穌今早離開了
Jesus left this morning.

200
00:19:37,020 --> 00:19:39,350
他讓我和你說一聲來著  但我忘了
He told me to tell you, but I-I forgot.

201
00:19:40,400 --> 00:19:42,330
好吧  等下次吧
Okay. Next time.

202
00:19:43,270 --> 00:19:44,400
我去拿點牛奶
I'm gonna get some milk.

203
00:19:44,400 --> 00:19:46,090
-讓我去吧  -不用  我可以
- Let me. - No, I'm good.

204
00:19:54,940 --> 00:19:55,690
怎么了
What?

205
00:19:56,900 --> 00:19:58,860
耶穌的事你沒對瑪姬說實話
You're lying to Maggie about Jesus.

206
00:20:01,760 --> 00:20:03,110
為什么這么說
What makes you say that?

207
00:20:03,520 --> 00:20:05,100
有個住在房子里的女孩
A girl who lives in the house.

208
00:20:05,110 --> 00:20:06,310
她給我介紹了所有人
She was telling me about everyone.

209
00:20:06,310 --> 00:20:08,060
她說耶穌負責搜集物資
She said Jesus is a runner

210
00:20:08,060 --> 00:20:09,620
他昨天就走了
and that he left yesterday,

211
00:20:10,340 --> 00:20:11,550
不是今早
not this morning.

212
00:20:13,580 --> 00:20:15,940
-騙她是為她好  -為什么
- It's for her own good. ‭- Why?

213
00:20:16,570 --> 00:20:18,410
因為我必須做點什么
Because I need to do something,

214
00:20:19,040 --> 00:20:20,810
而她肯定想幫我
and she'll want to help me.

215
00:20:23,190 --> 00:20:24,570
你想殺尼根
You want to kill Negan.

216
00:20:30,480 --> 00:20:31,780
要是你有幫手呢
What if you have help?

217
00:20:31,910 --> 00:20:35,010
要是有幫手  很多人手
If we had help -- a lot of people...

218
00:20:35,010 --> 00:20:36,410
我就不怕告訴她真相
then I wouldn't be afraid to tell her,

219
00:20:36,410 --> 00:20:38,390
因為她知道她不用管
because she'd know it wasn't on her to do it.

220
00:20:39,290 --> 00:20:41,700
-但如果只有我  那么...  -不是只有你
- But if it's just me, then... - ‭It isn't just you.

221
00:20:41,700 --> 00:20:44,370
你和瑪姬不是唯一想干掉尼根的人
You and Maggie aren't the only ones who want to take Negan out.

222
00:20:44,380 --> 00:20:45,540
-還有...  -不  伊妮德
- There's... - ‭No, Enid.

223
00:20:45,540 --> 00:20:46,890
這樣不行
That's not happening.

224
00:20:46,890 --> 00:20:47,970
如果你真關心她
And if you care about her,

225
00:20:47,970 --> 00:20:49,870
就什么都不要說
you don't say anything about this.

226
00:20:51,550 --> 00:20:53,660
我們必須保護她
We have to keep her safe.

227
00:20:54,470 --> 00:20:57,220
你必須保護她
You have to keep her safe.

228
00:21:00,010 --> 00:21:02,020
不是只有你一個人
It isn't just you.

229
00:21:05,650 --> 00:21:07,060
至少看起來只有我
It sure looks like it.

230
00:21:09,330 --> 00:21:12,240
災變后出現了很多聚居點
A lot of places came together after the world fell apart.

231
00:21:13,040 --> 00:21:15,810
也許你們倆都是從某個聚居點來的
Maybe you're both from one of those places.

232
00:21:17,550 --> 00:21:20,110
那些社區和營地大部分已經消失了
Most of those communities and camps are gone now.

233
00:21:23,120 --> 00:21:24,580
我失去了很多人
I lost people.

234
00:21:24,580 --> 00:21:28,040
我幾乎對人們失去希望了
I pretty much lost hope in people.

235
00:21:30,100 --> 00:21:31,620
但后來我找到了神之國
But then I found the Kingdom.

236
00:21:32,860 --> 00:21:34,260
見到了以西結
I met Ezekiel.

237
00:21:36,050 --> 00:21:37,540
看到了他建立的一切
I saw what he built.

238
00:21:37,810 --> 00:21:40,230
但現在我認為他建立的王國受到了威脅
But now I believe what he built is under threat.

239
00:21:40,230 --> 00:21:42,810
-救世軍  -救世軍
- The Saviors. - The Saviors.

240
00:21:45,520 --> 00:21:46,320
幾個月前
A few months back,

241
00:21:46,320 --> 00:21:49,440
以西結和幾個護衛在林子里遇到他們一隊人
Ezekiel and a few guards met a group of them in the woods.

242
00:21:50,460 --> 00:21:53,030
救世軍承認以西結的能力
The Saviors recognized Ezekiel's capabilities,

243
00:21:53,030 --> 00:21:54,800
以西結也不想跟他們打
and Ezekiel didn't want to fight,

244
00:21:55,180 --> 00:21:56,470
所以他們定了個協議
so they cut a deal.

245
00:21:56,710 --> 00:21:58,630
以食物和補給品
In exchange for food and supplies,

246
00:21:58,630 --> 00:22:00,030
換取他們不傷人
no one would get hurt,

247
00:22:00,030 --> 00:22:02,260
不踏入神之國一步
and they'd never set foot inside the Kingdom,

248
00:22:02,650 --> 00:22:04,520
這事知道的人很少
and very few of us even know.

249
00:22:04,520 --> 00:22:06,570
這跟我有什么關系
What does any of this have to do with me?

250
00:22:06,800 --> 00:22:09,030
我知道以西結欣賞你
I know Ezekiel likes you.

251
00:22:09,520 --> 00:22:11,760
也知道以西結信任你
I also know that Ezekiel trusts you,

252
00:22:11,760 --> 00:22:13,150
所以我才來這里
and that's why I'm here.

253
00:22:13,470 --> 00:22:15,860
我需要你們幫我說服他
I need you to help me convince him of something.

254
00:22:15,860 --> 00:22:18,520
現在  我們跟救世軍保持著和平
Right now, we have peace with the Saviors,

255
00:22:18,960 --> 00:22:21,360
但早晚會出事
but sooner or later, sometimes's gonna go wrong.

256
00:22:21,360 --> 00:22:23,420
也許是某次貢品少了
Maybe we'll be light on a drop,

257
00:22:23,600 --> 00:22:26,110
也許是我們的人不小心冒犯了他們
or maybe one of ours will look at one of theirs the wrong way,

258
00:22:26,110 --> 00:22:30,980
或者他們干脆決定不再遵守協定
or maybe they'll just decide to stop honoring the deal.

259
00:22:32,150 --> 00:22:33,650
總會出事的
Things will go bad.

260
00:22:34,540 --> 00:22:35,860
一旦出事
And when they do...

261
00:22:39,560 --> 00:22:40,910
神之國就完了
...the Kingdom will fall.

262
00:22:45,980 --> 00:22:47,150
我有過家人
I had a family.

263
00:22:47,820 --> 00:22:49,890
災變奪走了他們
I lost it to this world.

264
00:22:51,660 --> 00:22:52,950
我目睹了家人死去
I saw them die.

265
00:22:55,230 --> 00:22:57,830
我怕如果我們現在不做些什么
I'm scared that, if we don't do something now,

266
00:22:58,400 --> 00:23:01,570
我們不只會失去更多人  我們還會失去一切
that we won't only lose more people -- we'll lose everything.

267
00:23:01,910 --> 00:23:04,870
我了解救世軍是什么樣  知道他們的所作所為
I know what the Saviors are, and I know what they do.

268
00:23:05,660 --> 00:23:08,200
更知道他們不值得被信任
And I know they cannot be trusted.

269
00:23:11,480 --> 00:23:13,100
我猜你們也知道這點
And I think you know that, too.

270
00:23:15,340 --> 00:23:17,370
你到底想讓我們做什么
What exactly are you asking?

271
00:23:19,590 --> 00:23:21,490
我想讓你們幫我勸以西結
I'm asking you to help convince Ezekiel

272
00:23:21,490 --> 00:23:24,850
對救世軍先下手為強
to attack the Saviors, to strike first...

273
00:23:25,680 --> 00:23:26,920
滅掉他們
and destroy them.

274
00:23:34,720 --> 00:23:35,940
是為你自己準備的嗎
Is that for you...

275
00:23:37,690 --> 00:23:38,740
還是為尼根
or Negan?

276
00:23:42,560 --> 00:23:43,630
尼根
It's for him.

277
00:23:45,980 --> 00:23:47,180
你要怎么做
How will you do it?

278
00:23:48,640 --> 00:23:50,420
我要扣下扳機
I'll pull the trigger.

279
00:23:51,850 --> 00:23:52,990
他們會殺了你
They'll kill you.

280
00:23:53,250 --> 00:23:55,270
只要他先死就行
As long as he goes first.

281
00:23:57,660 --> 00:23:59,150
你為什么非要送死
Why do you have to die?

282
00:23:59,800 --> 00:24:01,640
因為他必須死
Because he has to.

283
00:24:07,210 --> 00:24:08,300
我贊同
I agree.

284
00:24:09,250 --> 00:24:10,370
但是
But...

285
00:24:16,320 --> 00:24:17,390
為什么你要陪他死
Why do you?

286
00:24:21,420 --> 00:24:22,460
你...
There's, uh...

287
00:24:24,280 --> 00:24:26,580
可以完全對我坦白
No need to lie to me if...

288
00:24:28,480 --> 00:24:30,800
如果這是我們最后一次談話
this is our last conversation.

289
00:24:35,840 --> 00:24:38,420
如果亞伯拉罕還活著  我們就能戰斗
If Abraham was alive, we could fight.

290
00:24:41,340 --> 00:24:42,970
如果格倫還活著
If Glenn was,

291
00:24:44,820 --> 00:24:47,490
瑪姬的孩子就有父親
Maggie's kid would have a father.

292
00:24:50,500 --> 00:24:52,790
米瓊恩和卡爾可以戰斗
Michonne and Carl can fight.

293
00:24:54,430 --> 00:24:55,790
他們有瑞克
They have Rick.

294
00:24:57,440 --> 00:24:59,520
亞倫有埃里克
Aaron has Eric.

295
00:25:01,140 --> 00:25:03,600
尤金知識豐富
Eugene knows things.

296
00:25:05,510 --> 00:25:06,930
達里爾很強
Daryl's strong.

297
00:25:09,850 --> 00:25:11,140
薩沙呢
What about Sasha?

298
00:25:25,900 --> 00:25:27,290
看著我  羅西塔
Look at me, Rosita.

299
00:25:33,610 --> 00:25:35,490
不該是你去死
It shouldn't have been you.

300
00:25:37,210 --> 00:25:39,130
誰都不該去死
It shouldn't have been anyone.

301
00:25:42,090 --> 00:25:43,170
我們會勝利的
We'll win,

302
00:25:44,300 --> 00:25:46,800
但我們要等待合適的時機
but we need to wait for the right moment

303
00:25:47,450 --> 00:25:49,020
或是大家一起...
or create it...

304
00:25:50,580 --> 00:25:51,690
創造時機
together.

305
00:25:53,540 --> 00:25:56,060
你是我們以后抗爭的一員
And you're a part of that together.

306
00:25:59,520 --> 00:26:00,950
不要這么做
Don't do this.

307
00:26:03,760 --> 00:26:07,200
我們需要你
We need you.

308
00:27:05,980 --> 00:27:08,170
聽著  我知道他們人很多
Look. I know there's a lot of them.

309
00:27:08,280 --> 00:27:10,840
我猜比神之國的人還多很多
I'm guessing a good deal more than we have at the Kingdom.

310
00:27:10,890 --> 00:27:13,170
出其不意是我們的唯一希望了
The element of surprise is our only hope.

311
00:27:13,170 --> 00:27:14,460
我們得先出擊
We need to attack first,

312
00:27:14,460 --> 00:27:17,470
趁著我們還有優勢  現在就行動
and we need to do it now while we still have the advantage.

313
00:27:19,650 --> 00:27:22,990
卡蘿爾  我估計那種暴力和爭斗
Carol, I imagine that violence and fighting

314
00:27:22,990 --> 00:27:24,800
你并沒有經歷過
is something you haven't been a part of.

315
00:27:26,060 --> 00:27:27,100
你錯了
You're wrong.

316
00:27:27,370 --> 00:27:28,490
你大錯特錯
You're very wrong.

317
00:27:28,880 --> 00:27:31,630
她可能是這屋子里最強的戰士
She's probably the most capable fighter in this room.

318
00:27:32,130 --> 00:27:33,630
那就是時候反抗了
Then it's time to fight.

319
00:27:35,810 --> 00:27:36,760
不
No.

320
00:27:37,410 --> 00:27:40,150
我不想參與這事
This is something I am not a part of.

321
00:27:40,240 --> 00:27:41,460
那你就不用戰斗
Then you don't have to fight.

322
00:27:41,460 --> 00:27:42,840
你只用說服以西結
You just have to convince Ezekiel

323
00:27:42,840 --> 00:27:44,390
帶領神之國反抗
to bring the Kingdom to fight.

324
00:27:44,390 --> 00:27:46,320
你沒懂我意思
You're not understanding me.

325
00:27:47,140 --> 00:27:48,170
我不想要你
I didn't want you.

326
00:27:48,170 --> 00:27:50,820
我不想要以西結或是摩根來這
I didn't want Ezekiel or Morgan coming here.

327
00:27:50,820 --> 00:27:54,870
你們的死活與我沒有任何關系
And I don't want anything to do with your lives or your deaths.

328
00:27:55,370 --> 00:27:57,130
我只是想一個人待著
I just want to be left alone.

329
00:28:03,330 --> 00:28:06,390
人們會死  很多人會死
People will die -- a lot of them.

330
00:28:07,510 --> 00:28:08,320
你殺過一個人
You killed a man.

331
00:28:08,320 --> 00:28:10,340
我殺人是為了救人
I took a life to save a life.

332
00:28:10,340 --> 00:28:12,350
有什么該死的區別
It's the same goddamn thing.

333
00:28:12,720 --> 00:28:14,440
我們殺他們也是為了自救
We'll be taking their lives to save ours!

334
00:28:14,450 --> 00:28:16,010
只是你不知道會不會成功
Only you don't know that it will.

335
00:28:16,010 --> 00:28:18,310
總有一天你會選擇殺人的  摩根
You're gonna choose to kill one day, Morgan,

336
00:28:18,800 --> 00:28:20,820
因為早晚會到那一步的
'cause it will get that bad!

337
00:28:23,660 --> 00:28:25,080
何不現在就做出選擇呢
Why not choose now,

338
00:28:25,580 --> 00:28:27,670
在失去你關心的人之前
before you lose someone you care about?

339
00:28:27,690 --> 00:28:29,260
現在是和平的
There's a peace now.

340
00:28:29,270 --> 00:28:31,620
我不想去改變它
I won't be a part of changing that.

341
00:28:31,920 --> 00:28:33,700
也許我們可以促進和平
And maybe we can build on that.

342
00:28:33,710 --> 00:28:35,260
不能和這些人
Not with these people!

343
00:28:35,470 --> 00:28:37,080
當他們反咬一口的時候  他們一定會的
When they turn on us -- and they will --

344
00:28:37,080 --> 00:28:39,080
你們的雙手將沾滿鮮血
that blood is gonna be on your hands!

345
00:28:45,500 --> 00:28:47,180
但也許你們倆早就習慣了
But maybe you're both used to that.

346
00:28:52,070 --> 00:28:53,460
你也該走了
You should go, too.

347
00:28:54,150 --> 00:28:55,220
是該走了
I should.

348
00:28:57,790 --> 00:29:00,590
我不希望任何人來這了
I don't want anyone else coming around

349
00:29:00,590 --> 00:29:02,530
也不希望別人知道我在這里
or even knowing where I am.

350
00:29:02,530 --> 00:29:04,790
如果你遇到我們認識的人
If you somehow see anyone we know,

351
00:29:04,790 --> 00:29:06,110
告訴他們我不見了
tell them I'm gone.

352
00:29:06,790 --> 00:29:08,390
請你幫我這個忙
Do that for me please.

353
00:29:08,420 --> 00:29:10,390
我從來沒想讓你看到我
Never meant for you to see me.

354
00:29:59,090 --> 00:30:00,090
你好
Hi.

355
00:30:02,490 --> 00:30:03,500
你好
Hi.

356
00:30:07,250 --> 00:30:08,350
你好
Hi.

357
00:30:17,710 --> 00:30:26,190
{\an8}禁止野營

358
00:31:32,300 --> 00:31:33,380
去赴約嗎
Hot date?

359
00:31:37,600 --> 00:31:39,010
他們對我印象不錯
I'm on a good momentum with them.

360
00:31:39,010 --> 00:31:40,180
我要利用這點
Gonna try to use that.

361
00:31:41,030 --> 00:31:42,200
是嗎  怎么做
Yeah? How?

362
00:31:45,860 --> 00:31:47,570
試圖靠近他們
By trying to get closer,

363
00:31:47,750 --> 00:31:49,450
即便只是剛開始
even just to start trying.

364
00:31:49,450 --> 00:31:50,900
如果我能做到  一段時間后
If I can do that, after a while --

365
00:31:50,900 --> 00:31:53,130
也許幾個月  也許幾年
maybe months, maybe years --

366
00:31:53,160 --> 00:31:54,820
也許以后會有轉機
maybe then we try something.

367
00:31:56,680 --> 00:31:58,350
我認為我媽就會這么做
I think it's what my mom would have done,

368
00:31:59,290 --> 00:32:00,780
所以我也要這么做
so it's what I'm gonna do.

369
00:32:03,320 --> 00:32:04,370
好的
Okay.

370
00:32:08,570 --> 00:32:09,930
不管之前那是什么
Whatever it was...

371
00:32:11,290 --> 00:32:12,940
我以為我們曾有過美好的感情
I thought we had something good --

372
00:32:14,010 --> 00:32:15,870
至少是美好感情的開始
at least, the beginning of something good.

373
00:32:16,660 --> 00:32:17,840
你為什么要結束它
Why'd you end it?

374
00:32:20,000 --> 00:32:21,620
那又為什么要開始呢
Why'd you even start it?

375
00:32:25,940 --> 00:32:27,550
我當時想忘記一些事
I was trying not to think about shit.

376
00:32:30,190 --> 00:32:32,700
你很可愛  個子又高
You're cute, tall.

377
00:32:33,950 --> 00:32:35,470
有時候挺溫柔的
You're sweet sometimes.

378
00:32:37,730 --> 00:32:38,910
所以我利用了你
So I used you.

379
00:32:46,960 --> 00:32:48,090
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.

380
00:32:52,230 --> 00:32:54,750
你待會來吃晚餐嗎
Would you be up for dinner later?

381
00:32:56,810 --> 00:32:58,300
只是吃晚餐
I really mean just dinner.

382
00:32:58,700 --> 00:32:59,910
沒別的意思
‭No strings.

383
00:33:04,440 --> 00:33:05,490
好的
All right.

384
00:33:06,210 --> 00:33:07,110
好的
All right.

385
00:33:29,910 --> 00:33:30,820
怎么回事
What the hell?

386
00:33:39,210 --> 00:33:41,160
一切都好  我發誓
It's cool, I swear.

387
00:33:42,090 --> 00:33:44,590
哥們  你可以從后門走
Buddy, you can walk right out that back gate there,

388
00:33:44,900 --> 00:33:46,800
我什么都不會說的
and I won't say anything to anybody.

389
00:33:47,710 --> 00:33:48,640
我本該在那里的
I'm supposed to be there now,

390
00:33:48,640 --> 00:33:53,170
但聽著  我只是想活下去
but, listen, I'm -- I'm just trying to get by,

391
00:33:53,510 --> 00:33:54,600
像你一樣
just like you.

392
00:33:57,280 --> 00:33:58,250
求你了
Please.

393
00:34:00,670 --> 00:34:01,490
達里爾
Daryl.

394
00:34:11,900 --> 00:34:12,730
達里爾
Daryl.

395
00:34:29,650 --> 00:34:31,580
才不是只想活下去
It ain't just about gettin' by here.

396
00:34:33,510 --> 00:34:34,840
而是想得到一切
It's about gettin' it all.

397
00:34:38,270 --> 00:34:39,720
我拿到鑰匙了  走吧
I got the key. Let's go.

398
00:34:41,770 --> 00:34:43,420
不  我只是想跟他說說話
No. ‭I just want to talk to him.

399
00:34:43,420 --> 00:34:44,610
我說了不行
I said "No."

400
00:34:44,650 --> 00:34:47,570
別無禮  阿拉特
Dot be an asshole, Arat.

401
00:34:47,570 --> 00:34:49,320
讓他過來
Let the man pass.

402
00:34:56,010 --> 00:34:59,250
該死  這是給我的嗎
Oh, crap. Is that for me?

403
00:35:00,420 --> 00:35:02,090
我們還沒正式見過面
We haven't officially met.

404
00:35:02,430 --> 00:35:04,030
我叫斯賓塞·門羅
I'm Spencer Monroe.

405
00:35:06,210 --> 00:35:07,190
你好
Hi.

406
00:35:19,470 --> 00:35:20,610
尼根就在那
That's Negan.

407
00:35:33,910 --> 00:35:35,170
他在那下面嗎
Is he down there?

408
00:35:36,390 --> 00:35:37,380
是的
Yeah.

409
00:35:37,760 --> 00:35:40,050
我們都是尼根
We're all Negan.

410
00:35:43,160 --> 00:35:45,070
不管你想做什么  都行不通
Whatever you're trying to do, you can't.

411
00:35:45,890 --> 00:35:48,140
但你還是有選擇的
But you still have some choices.

412
00:35:49,270 --> 00:35:50,320
回家
Go home.

413
00:35:50,790 --> 00:35:54,470
燒了這輛車  沉進湖里
Burn this car, roll it down into a lake,

414
00:35:54,590 --> 00:35:56,050
讓它消失
make it disappear.

415
00:35:57,730 --> 00:35:59,900
貯物箱里有個消聲器
There's a silencer in the glove compartment.

416
00:37:03,000 --> 00:37:04,160
他在哪
Where is he?

417
00:37:04,320 --> 00:37:05,310
尼根嗎
Negan?

418
00:37:06,020 --> 00:37:07,710
在你屋里  混蛋
He's in your house, asshole,

419
00:37:08,290 --> 00:37:09,620
等你呢
waiting for you.

420
00:37:19,670 --> 00:37:20,830
就這樣進去嗎
Just like that?

421
00:37:21,230 --> 00:37:23,390
我們等了你好幾個小時了
See, we've been waiting for hours

422
00:37:23,390 --> 00:37:26,140
就想看看你能交給我們什么
just to see what you gonna bring us, huh?

423
00:37:27,080 --> 00:37:29,640
不如我們先看看吧
Why don't we have a look first?

424
00:37:32,940 --> 00:37:35,650
自來水  空調
Running water, air conditioning,

425
00:37:37,290 --> 00:37:39,260
還有喬遷賀禮
a housewarming gift?

426
00:37:39,710 --> 00:37:40,490
就這么定了
That settles it.

427
00:37:40,490 --> 00:37:43,620
我要在這里搞個度假屋
I am getting myself a vacation home here.

428
00:37:44,450 --> 00:37:45,610
為此干杯
Cheers to that.

429
00:37:52,870 --> 00:37:55,490
這酒不錯
Oh, that is good.

430
00:37:55,920 --> 00:37:59,190
你看  就差一張臺球桌了
You know, the only thing missing is a pool table.

431
00:37:59,190 --> 00:38:02,000
沒有比一場精彩的八球比賽更棒的了
Nothing better than a good game of 8 ball.

432
00:38:03,520 --> 00:38:06,520
街對面那棟房子的車庫里有一張
The house across the street has one in the garage.

433
00:38:07,520 --> 00:38:09,250
斯賓塞
Oh, Spencer,

434
00:38:09,500 --> 00:38:12,700
你是我新的好朋友了
you may just be my new best friend.

435
00:38:13,720 --> 00:38:15,710
今天天氣這么好
Such a nice day, though --

436
00:38:16,240 --> 00:38:19,970
還窩在車庫里可不合適  你不覺得嗎
too nice to be cooped up inside some garage, don't you think?

437
00:38:21,420 --> 00:38:22,410
沒錯
Yeah.

438
00:38:22,660 --> 00:38:24,920
我有一個更好的主意
Oh, I got a better idea.

439
00:38:34,730 --> 00:38:35,670
還不錯
Not bad.

440
00:38:37,280 --> 00:38:38,770
我們走了很遠
We had to go out pretty far.

441
00:38:40,430 --> 00:38:41,880
這他媽是什么
What the hell's this?

442
00:38:42,620 --> 00:38:45,190
恭喜你贏了  但你還是輸了
"Congrats for winning. But you still lose"?

443
00:38:51,400 --> 00:38:53,110
你給我們留了封小情書嗎
You leave us a little love note?

444
00:38:53,760 --> 00:38:55,730
不是  我只是
No, I just --

445
00:38:56,090 --> 00:38:59,850
我是說  我們顯然不會這樣做
I mean -- We wouldn't, obviously --

446
00:38:59,860 --> 00:39:01,030
等等  你說什么
Wait. What?

447
00:39:01,030 --> 00:39:03,270
你剛是說這是顯然的嗎
Did you just say it's obvious?

448
00:39:07,220 --> 00:39:08,280
字條不是我們留的
We didn't do that.

449
00:39:08,280 --> 00:39:10,670
我說的不是那張該死的字條
It's not about the damn note!

450
00:39:10,670 --> 00:39:11,450
別過來
Don't.

451
00:39:12,850 --> 00:39:15,190
去見尼根  瑞克
Run along to Negan, Rick.

452
00:39:22,400 --> 00:39:23,620
但是你這位朋友
But your friend here --

453
00:39:24,320 --> 00:39:25,850
他沒有地方可去
he's got no place to be.

454
00:39:28,140 --> 00:39:29,220
-你  -后退
- You -- - ‭Back up!

455
00:39:31,920 --> 00:39:34,370
我不可能和瑞克玩這個
I could never do this with Rick.

456
00:39:34,370 --> 00:39:37,510
他只會站在那  皺著眉
He would just be standing there, scowling,

457
00:39:37,740 --> 00:39:41,810
用討厭的眼神斜眼看我
giving me that annoying side-eye he gives me.

458
00:39:41,820 --> 00:39:43,850
其實這才是我來找你的原因
That's actually what I came to see you about.

459
00:39:45,680 --> 00:39:47,320
我想和你說說瑞克
I want to talk to you about Rick.

460
00:39:53,470 --> 00:39:54,600
好吧
All right.

461
00:39:54,600 --> 00:39:56,420
說吧  斯賓塞
Talk to me, Spencer.

462
00:39:56,800 --> 00:39:59,420
和我說說瑞克
Talk to me about Rick.

463
00:40:07,570 --> 00:40:09,690
我明白你想要在這做什么
I get what you're trying to do here,

464
00:40:10,510 --> 00:40:12,150
你想建造什么
what you're trying to build.

465
00:40:12,320 --> 00:40:14,260
我并不是說我贊同你的方法
I'm not saying I agree with your methods,

466
00:40:14,670 --> 00:40:15,870
但我懂了
but I get it.

467
00:40:15,870 --> 00:40:17,090
你在搭建網絡
You're building a network.

468
00:40:17,090 --> 00:40:19,500
讓大家為集體做貢獻
You're making people contribute for the greater good.

469
00:40:20,030 --> 00:40:21,550
有道理
It makes sense.

470
00:40:23,140 --> 00:40:25,950
但你應該知道瑞克·格蘭姆斯
But you should know that Rick Grimes

471
00:40:25,950 --> 00:40:28,530
以前就不能很好的和他人共事
has a history of not working well with others.

472
00:40:32,800 --> 00:40:33,990
是嗎
Is that so?

473
00:40:37,850 --> 00:40:39,770
這里原來不是瑞克管事
Rick wasn't the original leader here.

474
00:40:39,770 --> 00:40:41,220
是我媽媽
My mom was.

475
00:40:42,180 --> 00:40:44,000
她當時做得很好
She was doing a really good job of it.

476
00:40:45,370 --> 00:40:48,650
瑞克出現后不久  她就死了
Then she died, not long after Rick showed up --

477
00:40:49,130 --> 00:40:51,170
我兄弟也死了  我爸爸也死了
same with my brother, same with my dad.

478
00:40:51,530 --> 00:40:55,640
這么說  這些年這里一直歡樂美滿
So, everything was peachy here for -- what -- years?

479
00:40:56,060 --> 00:41:00,190
瑞克出現后  突然之間你就成了孤兒
And then Rick shows up, and suddenly, you're an orphan?

480
00:41:01,640 --> 00:41:04,270
這是我聽過的最悲慘的故事
That is the saddest story I've ever heard.

481
00:41:04,880 --> 00:41:09,450
-好在他不再管事了  -這不重要
- Good thing for you ‭he's not in charge anymore. - Doesn't matter.

482
00:41:09,870 --> 00:41:11,720
他自負得無法控制
His ego's out of control.

483
00:41:11,950 --> 00:41:13,980
他總能找到辦法搞砸事情
He'll find a way to screw things up,

484
00:41:14,120 --> 00:41:16,330
按他自己的想法行事  接管一切
to try and do things his way, to take over.

485
00:41:18,380 --> 00:41:19,910
他就是這樣對我媽媽的
That's what he did with my mom.

486
00:41:19,910 --> 00:41:21,330
他還會重蹈覆轍的
That's what he'll do again.

487
00:41:29,750 --> 00:41:33,080
那你到底想怎么做呢
What exactly are you proposing be done about that?

488
00:41:34,320 --> 00:41:36,100
我是我媽媽的兒子
I am my mother's son.

489
00:41:36,900 --> 00:41:39,230
我可以成為像她一樣的領導者
I can be the leader she was.

490
00:41:40,440 --> 00:41:41,760
這正是這個地方需要的
That's what this place needs.

491
00:41:41,760 --> 00:41:43,100
也是你需要的
That's what you need.

492
00:41:45,520 --> 00:41:47,580
所以我應該讓你管事
So I should put you in charge

493
00:41:48,100 --> 00:41:49,720
你是這個意思嗎
that's what you're saying?

494
00:41:50,670 --> 00:41:52,350
那樣對我們都更好
We'd be much better off.

495
00:41:56,270 --> 00:41:58,770
你沒事  你沒事
You're all right. You're all right.

496
00:42:00,140 --> 00:42:01,620
好了  好了
All right, all right, all right.

497
00:42:02,130 --> 00:42:03,340
讓他學會教訓了
Point made.

498
00:42:12,760 --> 00:42:14,630
我的心還在跳  對吧
My heart's still beating, right?

499
00:42:21,300 --> 00:42:24,570
其實  斯賓塞  我在考慮
You know, I'm thinking, Spencer.

500
00:42:25,400 --> 00:42:27,700
我想到瑞克之前威脅要殺了我
I'm thinking how Rick threatened to kill me,

501
00:42:27,700 --> 00:42:30,770
以及他顯然恨我入骨
how he clearly hates my guts.

502
00:42:30,770 --> 00:42:33,800
但他現在在外面
But he is out there right now,

503
00:42:34,450 --> 00:42:37,220
替我搜集物資  以確保
gathering shit for me to make sure

504
00:42:37,220 --> 00:42:40,610
我不會殺了任何住在這里的好人
I don't hurt any of the fine people that live here.

505
00:42:42,120 --> 00:42:45,210
他把仇恨都咽進肚子里了
He is swallowing his hate

506
00:42:45,210 --> 00:42:47,830
真正替我辦了事
and getting shit done.

507
00:42:50,300 --> 00:42:51,780
那是需要勇氣的
That takes guts.

508
00:42:59,500 --> 00:43:01,010
再看看你
And then there's you...

509
00:43:04,110 --> 00:43:06,440
等著瑞克走了
the guy who waited for Rick to be gone

510
00:43:06,440 --> 00:43:08,780
鬼鬼祟祟跑過來找我談
so he could sneak over and talk to me

511
00:43:08,780 --> 00:43:10,490
想要借我的刀殺人  
to get me to do his dirty work,

512
00:43:10,490 --> 00:43:12,630
好取代瑞克的位置
so he could take Rick's place.

513
00:43:13,340 --> 00:43:15,100
所以我不得不問問
So I got to ask --

514
00:43:15,370 --> 00:43:17,300
如果你想取代瑞克
if you wanna take over,

515
00:43:18,530 --> 00:43:23,670
何不自己動手殺了他  然后取而代之呢
why not just kill Rick yourself and just take over?

516
00:43:23,670 --> 00:43:24,290
什么  不  不是
What? No, no.

517
00:43:24,290 --> 00:43:25,760
我沒有  我不是那個...
I didn't -- I don't --

518
00:43:25,760 --> 00:43:27,390
你知道我是怎么想的嗎
You know what I'm thinking?

519
00:43:27,390 --> 00:43:30,030
我大概猜到了
'Cause I have a guess.

520
00:43:32,710 --> 00:43:37,600
因為你沒膽
It's because you got no guts.

521
00:43:59,570 --> 00:44:02,340
真尷尬
How embarrassing.

522
00:44:03,480 --> 00:44:04,700
竟然有呢
There they are.

523
00:44:04,700 --> 00:44:06,630
你的膽子一直在你的身體里
They were inside you the whole time.

524
00:44:06,630 --> 00:44:08,010
你是有膽的
You did have guts.

525
00:44:08,010 --> 00:44:11,340
這是我這輩子錯得最離譜的一次了
I've never been so wrong in my whole life!

526
00:44:31,460 --> 00:44:37,850
快來個人  把血污清理干凈
Now, someone oughta get up here and clean this mess up.

527
00:44:47,620 --> 00:44:49,650
有人想替他打完這一局嗎
Anyone want to finish the game?

528
00:44:51,120 --> 00:44:52,390
來吧
C'mon.

529
00:44:54,880 --> 00:44:56,130
有人嗎
Anybody?

530
00:44:57,770 --> 00:44:59,090
有人嗎
Anybody?

531
00:45:01,390 --> 00:45:02,980
來嘛
C'mon.

532
00:45:03,550 --> 00:45:05,470
我都快贏了
I was winning!

533
00:45:17,360 --> 00:45:18,800
媽的
Shit!

534
00:45:18,980 --> 00:45:20,380
去他媽的
What the shit?!

535
00:45:21,340 --> 00:45:25,050
該死的  你想殺了老子嗎
Shit! You just -- You tried to kill me?!

536
00:45:25,150 --> 00:45:27,890
-你打中了露西爾  -她礙事了
- You shot Lucille! - She got in the way.

537
00:45:40,910 --> 00:45:42,330
這是什么
What is this?

538
00:45:45,730 --> 00:45:47,290
這是什么
What is this?

539
00:45:47,620 --> 00:45:50,470
這玩意是手工做出來的嗎
This little bad boy made from scratch?

540
00:45:50,960 --> 00:45:53,100
瞧瞧這折痕
Look at those crimps.

541
00:45:53,310 --> 00:45:55,340
這是手工做的
This was homemade.

542
00:45:56,020 --> 00:45:58,490
你或許很愚蠢  親愛的
You may be stupid, darlin',

543
00:45:58,760 --> 00:46:02,370
但是你顯示出了非凡的創造力
but you showed some real ingenuity here.

544
00:46:03,270 --> 00:46:04,660
阿拉特
Arat,

545
00:46:05,260 --> 00:46:09,260
把刀移到那姑娘的臉上去
move that knife up out on that girl's face.

546
00:46:11,650 --> 00:46:15,000
露西爾美麗光滑的臉龐
Lucille's beautiful, smooth surface

547
00:46:15,000 --> 00:46:17,110
再也不會想以前那樣了
is never gonna look the same,

548
00:46:17,140 --> 00:46:18,970
憑什么你的臉可以美麗光滑
so why should yours?!

549
00:46:20,910 --> 00:46:22,390
除非
Unless...

550
00:46:24,840 --> 00:46:29,480
除非你告訴我這是誰做的
Unless you tell me who made this.

551
00:46:29,850 --> 00:46:31,170
是我
It was me.

552
00:46:32,140 --> 00:46:33,410
我做的
I made it.

553
00:46:33,980 --> 00:46:37,810
我覺得你在撒謊
You see, now I just think you're lying.

554
00:46:38,340 --> 00:46:41,630
到了現在你還敢對我撒謊
And you lying to me now?!

555
00:46:44,190 --> 00:46:45,820
真遺憾
Such a shame.

556
00:46:45,820 --> 00:46:48,800
阿拉特只能割花你美麗的小臉蛋了
Arat's gonna have to cut up that pretty face.

557
00:46:50,190 --> 00:46:51,560
再答一次
One more try.

558
00:46:51,940 --> 00:46:53,840
是我做的
It was me.

559
00:46:56,780 --> 00:47:00,140
你可真硬氣啊
You are such a badass!

560
00:47:02,490 --> 00:47:03,900
好吧
Fine.

561
00:47:05,500 --> 00:47:07,110
就順了你的意吧
Have it your way.

562
00:47:07,880 --> 00:47:09,250
阿拉特
Arat...

563
00:47:10,210 --> 00:47:11,720
殺個人
Kill somebody.

564
00:47:13,410 --> 00:47:15,080
不要  是我做的
No. It was me!

565
00:47:15,080 --> 00:47:16,110
不要
No!

566
00:47:36,070 --> 00:47:38,740
-我們達成了協議的  -瑞克
- We had an agreement. - Rick!

567
00:47:39,330 --> 00:47:41,450
大家瞧啊  瑞克來了
Look, everybody, it's Rick.

568
00:47:42,510 --> 00:47:46,750
你的人逼我這么吼來吼去的  嗓子都啞了
Ah, your people are making me lose my voice doin' all this yelling.

569
00:47:48,290 --> 00:47:51,060
瑞克  對我說句謝謝怎么樣
Rick... how about a "Thank you"?

570
00:47:53,890 --> 00:47:57,760
雖然我們這段關系的初始
I mean, look, I know we started this relationship

571
00:47:57,760 --> 00:48:01,140
是我敲爛了你朋友們的腦袋
with me beating the holy shit out of your friends,

572
00:48:01,370 --> 00:48:03,110
因此我們永遠不可能友好地坐下來
and because of that, we're never gonna sit around

573
00:48:03,110 --> 00:48:04,190
給對方編辮子
and braid each other's hair

574
00:48:04,190 --> 00:48:06,540
或是傾吐內心最黑暗的秘密
or share our deepest, darkest secrets,

575
00:48:06,540 --> 00:48:09,040
但你能不能有點感恩之心
but how about a little credit?

576
00:48:09,140 --> 00:48:14,200
我苦心孤詣地向你展示  我是個多么講道理的人
I just bent over backwards to show you how reasonable I am.

577
00:48:15,340 --> 00:48:16,710
你的孩子
Your kid --

578
00:48:17,180 --> 00:48:19,300
他藏在我的一輛卡車里
he hid in one of my trucks

579
00:48:19,300 --> 00:48:22,420
用沖鋒槍掃倒了我的一堆手下
and machine-gunned a bunch of my men down,

580
00:48:22,420 --> 00:48:26,320
我還把他安全帶回來了
and I brought him home, safe and sound,

581
00:48:26,790 --> 00:48:29,190
給他做了意面吃
and I fed him spaghetti.

582
00:48:34,990 --> 00:48:36,800
另一個你的人
Another one of your people --

583
00:48:37,310 --> 00:48:41,920
他想要我殺了你  讓他取而代之
well, he wanted me to kill you and put him in charge.

584
00:48:41,920 --> 00:48:45,740
我為你...干掉了他
I took him out...for you.

585
00:48:46,350 --> 00:48:48,570
另一個人  這位
And another one, here --

586
00:48:49,360 --> 00:48:53,680
她擊中了露西爾  剛才想殺我
she shot Lucille, trying to kill me just now,

587
00:48:53,680 --> 00:48:56,120
所以我又幫你減少了一張要養活的嘴
so I gave you one less mouth to feed.

588
00:48:56,460 --> 00:48:57,940
瞧瞧她那身材
And by looking at her --

589
00:48:58,160 --> 00:49:00,980
那張嘴可吃了不少
that mouth did some major damage.

590
00:49:01,100 --> 00:49:02,400
個人來說
Now, personally,

591
00:49:02,570 --> 00:49:04,400
我不會選擇殺她
I wouldn't have picked her to be the one to go,

592
00:49:04,400 --> 00:49:05,730
但是阿拉特
but Arat --

593
00:49:05,910 --> 00:49:08,040
我不知道  不太信任她
I don't know -- didn't trust her.

594
00:49:16,910 --> 00:49:19,330
你的東西在大門那里放著
Your shit's waiting for you at the gate.

595
00:49:19,330 --> 00:49:20,690
快走吧
Just go.

596
00:49:21,950 --> 00:49:23,940
當然可以  瑞克
Sure thing, Rick...

597
00:49:24,430 --> 00:49:28,170
在我找出造這顆子彈的
right after I find the guy or gal

598
00:49:28,170 --> 00:49:31,360
男人或女人之后
that made this bullet.

599
00:49:32,280 --> 00:49:33,750
阿拉特
Arat?

600
00:49:36,450 --> 00:49:37,750
是我
It was me!

601
00:49:38,190 --> 00:49:40,940
不  不是
No, it wasn't.

602
00:49:49,230 --> 00:49:50,940
是我
It was me.

603
00:49:53,380 --> 00:49:54,990
只有我
It was only me.

604
00:49:55,480 --> 00:49:56,750
你
You?

605
00:50:00,350 --> 00:50:03,230
需要空彈殼  四孔轉動裝彈器
It required one spent casing, one four-holed turret reloader,

606
00:50:03,230 --> 00:50:05,280
火藥  火藥漏斗
powder, one funnel for the powder --

607
00:50:05,280 --> 00:50:06,510
閉嘴
Shut up.

608
00:50:08,500 --> 00:50:09,950
我相信你
I believe you.

609
00:50:24,100 --> 00:50:27,910
露西爾  給我力量
Lucille, give me strength.

610
00:50:32,940 --> 00:50:38,540
我要帶走你的子彈制造者  瑞克
I'm gonna be relieving you of your bullet maker, Rick --

611
00:50:38,960 --> 00:50:42,470
以及你在前門給我留下的東西
that and whatever you left for me at the front gate.

612
00:50:43,150 --> 00:50:47,890
不管你搜集到了多少物資  都不夠
And however much you scavenged, it's not good enough,

613
00:50:47,910 --> 00:50:49,640
因為在今天的事后
because you're still in

614
00:50:49,640 --> 00:50:53,110
你仍然處在深深的
a serious, serious hole

615
00:50:53,110 --> 00:50:54,890
無底洞中
after today.

616
00:50:58,820 --> 00:51:00,160
我們出發
Let's move out!

617
00:51:03,030 --> 00:51:04,980
不不不
No! No, no!

618
00:51:04,980 --> 00:51:06,630
求你了  只帶走我吧
Please, just take me!

619
00:51:06,630 --> 00:51:07,820
不
No!

620
00:51:08,110 --> 00:51:10,750
瑞克  我不會撒謊
Rick, I ain't gonna lie --

621
00:51:10,750 --> 00:51:14,290
你的廚房一團糟
your kitchen is a goddamn mess.

622
00:51:16,420 --> 00:51:18,380
下次見
I'll see you next time.

623
00:52:17,320 --> 00:52:19,690
卡爾告訴我你在這里
Carl told me you were in here. I...

624
00:52:46,240 --> 00:52:48,110
我找到了我想找的東西
I found what I was looking for.

625
00:52:54,240 --> 00:52:56,350
我之前想跟你和亞倫一起去
I wanted to go with you and Aaron,

626
00:52:58,410 --> 00:52:59,800
但我做不到
but I couldn't.

627
00:53:01,860 --> 00:53:03,470
我必須找到自己的路
I had to go my way.

628
00:53:04,970 --> 00:53:06,370
當我找到時
But when I found it...

629
00:53:08,840 --> 00:53:10,290
我發現
...I realized that...

630
00:53:12,690 --> 00:53:14,700
我不希望那只是我的路
I didn't want it to be my way.

631
00:53:16,830 --> 00:53:20,980
我希望那是我們的  我和你的路
I wanted it to be ours -- me and you.

632
00:53:28,470 --> 00:53:30,830
他們有更多人  比我們想的還多
There are more of them, even more than we thought.

633
00:53:31,670 --> 00:53:34,380
敵眾我寡  相去甚遠
We are outnumbered. It's not even close.

634
00:53:36,210 --> 00:53:38,820
但這不能改變我的想法
But that doesn't change the way that I feel,

635
00:53:39,320 --> 00:53:41,780
因為這不會改變事實
because it doesn't change the way that things are.

636
00:53:42,340 --> 00:53:44,300
我們依然活著  瑞克
We're still alive, Rick.

637
00:53:45,320 --> 00:53:47,090
發生了那么多事
So much has happened,

638
00:53:47,090 --> 00:53:49,430
那么多我們不可能挺過去的事
so much that we shouldn't have lived through.

639
00:53:49,430 --> 00:53:50,860
而
And...

640
00:53:50,860 --> 00:53:53,340
不管與此無關還是正因為如此
and in spite of it or maybe because of it,

641
00:53:54,210 --> 00:53:55,390
我們都活下來了
we did.

642
00:53:57,630 --> 00:54:00,420
我們還在這里  我們倆
We're still here, the two of us.

643
00:54:02,420 --> 00:54:06,150
我們還活著  而且我們會繼續活下去
We're still standing, and we're gonna keep standing.

644
00:54:06,150 --> 00:54:08,420
所以我們該對此做些什么呢
So, what do we do with that?

645
00:54:10,010 --> 00:54:12,930
我們如何讓活著更有意義呢
How do we make that mean something?

646
00:54:15,930 --> 00:54:18,500
我們是能做成事的人
We're the ones who get things done.

647
00:54:18,500 --> 00:54:19,870
這是你說的
You said that.

648
00:54:21,800 --> 00:54:23,710
我們是能活下去的人
We're the ones who live.

649
00:54:28,870 --> 00:54:30,750
所以我們更需要戰斗
That's why we have to fight --

650
00:54:32,490 --> 00:54:33,930
不是為了我們
not for us,

651
00:54:34,800 --> 00:54:38,170
是為了朱迪思  為了卡爾
but for Judith, for Carl,

652
00:54:39,450 --> 00:54:41,940
為了亞歷山大  為了山頂寨
for Alexandria, for the Hilltop --

653
00:54:42,670 --> 00:54:44,360
為了所有人
for all of us.

654
00:54:47,470 --> 00:54:49,290
我們能抗爭他們  瑞克
We can fight them, Rick.

655
00:54:49,510 --> 00:54:52,200
我們能找到戰勝他們的方法
We can find a way to beat them.

656
00:54:53,090 --> 00:54:54,720
我們能做到
We can do this.

657
00:54:57,540 --> 00:54:58,910
但是
But...

658
00:55:01,930 --> 00:55:03,440
但是
But...

659
00:55:04,650 --> 00:55:06,370
只有
Only if...

660
00:55:08,580 --> 00:55:11,960
我們一起做
we do this.

661
00:55:19,130 --> 00:55:21,150
是的  我現在知道了
Yeah, I know that now.

662
00:55:28,870 --> 00:55:30,600
我現在知道了
I know that now.

663
00:56:38,840 --> 00:56:42,290
薩沙  伊妮德
Sasha! Enid!

664
00:56:56,870 --> 00:56:58,750
-你沒事吧  -我沒事
- You're okay? ‭- I'm okay.

665
00:57:00,060 --> 00:57:01,590
孩子沒事
The baby's okay --

666
00:57:02,350 --> 00:57:03,610
我們都沒事
all of us.

667
00:57:05,410 --> 00:57:06,660
你說得對
You were right...

668
00:57:08,020 --> 00:57:09,710
從一開始就是對的
right from the start.

669
00:57:11,350 --> 00:57:13,500
你告訴我們要準備抗爭
You told us to get ready to fight.

670
00:57:15,680 --> 00:57:17,640
我沒有聽  我聽不進去
I didn't listen, and I couldn't.

671
00:57:21,030 --> 00:57:22,460
現在我能了
I can now.

