[Script Info]
; // The sub is created by AssToolkit
; // AssToolkit is an ASS Converter designed by David C.
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.02,0:00:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《行尸走肉》前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.95,0:00:05.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起來  我們救你出去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.72,0:00:06.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不跟你們走
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.02,0:00:08.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你命不該絕
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.14,0:00:13.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人為他開門了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.49,0:00:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們決定不管怎么樣  都要保護好自己
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.00,0:00:20.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會一直躲在這里  一直活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.57,0:00:23.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔拉  你在外面比我們走得都遠
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.82,0:00:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少你能告訴我們別去哪找
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.68,0:00:29.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然可以
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.29,0:00:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她們有槍
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.47,0:00:48.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,許多槍
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.62,0:00:49.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看見了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.93,0:00:50.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.94,0:00:51.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個團體
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.79,0:00:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我遇見的女人們
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.59,0:00:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她們有武器庫  有槍
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.72,0:01:01.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之前怎么不跟我們說
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.99,0:01:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做過保證  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.60,0:01:11.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會想起你殺掉的人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.39,0:01:18.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.60,0:01:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果計劃失敗  你有心理準備嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.69,0:01:30.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會失敗的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.94,0:01:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果失敗了  你不必內疚
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.09,0:01:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的確內疚
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.39,0:01:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會內疚的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.21,0:01:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔拉
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.12,0:01:39.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不必
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.63,0:02:30.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第七季  第十五集』
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.80,0:02:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得用一塊防水布蓋住
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.79,0:02:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-防水布嗎  -對
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.50,0:02:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.83,0:02:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想想
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.61,0:02:41.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接告訴我吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.46,0:02:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們需要保溫
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.24,0:02:48.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣它們就會在冬天來臨之前發芽
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.47,0:02:49.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那樣的話  我們扯掉防水布 
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.71,0:02:50.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它們就會自然枯亡
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.89,0:02:52.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就不用一直除草了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.21,0:02:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去蓋防水布吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.24,0:02:56.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題  女老大
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.43,0:02:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  你去哪
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.79,0:03:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是農民
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.80,0:03:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要幫助
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.44,0:03:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不需要
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.13,0:03:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看見外面長著野生藍莓灌木叢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.49,0:03:08.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果足夠嫩
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.18,0:03:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就要把它拔出來  種在這里
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.22,0:03:12.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好植株能結40多年的藍莓
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.96,0:03:15.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們得開始規劃活那么久了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.80,0:03:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,挺好的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.57,0:03:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就蓋防水布  別碰
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.79,0:03:23.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后我來看看你做得怎么樣
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.02,0:03:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\fs16\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\b1\c&HECB000&\pos(99,242)}原創翻譯  雙語字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.52,0:03:28.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\fn方正準圓_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs17\pos(235.108,242)\K40}最新連載海外影視劇下載\N{\fs19\K30}請登陸 {\c&H26F4FF&\fn方正綜藝_GBK\K30}www.YYeTs.com\N{\fn方正準圓_GBK\fs15\c&HFFFFFF&\K60}僅供交流學習  禁止商用盈利
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.25,0:03:35.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}翻譯     冰藍 Reginamoon CS小明漫畫家
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.25,0:03:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}翻譯     小僵僵 蘑菇 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.09,0:03:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你上去后  注意信號
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.85,0:03:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幾點開始
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.25,0:03:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}校對     送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.97,0:03:43.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等她一進去就開始
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.25,0:03:50.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(27,235)}時間軸     某雪  加森  濤濤
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.97,0:03:47.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.25,0:03:55.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}后期     送小哥  拉圖
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.27,0:03:51.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.25,0:04:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}總監     送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.30,0:04:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很高興你來了  我知道這很難
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.07,0:04:16.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我知道你不想這樣  -我之前不想
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.67,0:04:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我現在開始明白是怎么回事了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.91,0:04:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以像這些人一樣躲藏
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.03,0:04:21.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以繼續供奉救世軍
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.98,0:04:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以時常看見你被毒打
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.93,0:04:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者我們可以反抗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.07,0:04:26.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我們來了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.28,0:04:30.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且跟你在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.52,0:04:34.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓無助的恐懼可以容忍了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.65,0:04:43.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我該更努力地阻止羅西塔和薩沙的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.25,0:04:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果她們再等一天...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.43,0:04:48.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薩沙槍法很好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.92,0:04:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,羅西塔知道如何照顧自己
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.07,0:04:53.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她們也許現在都回山頂寨了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.16,0:04:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少我希望如此  我們需要她們
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.67,0:04:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還得死很多人的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.81,0:05:16.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好啊
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.22,0:05:19.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.59,0:05:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能給我點水嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.94,0:05:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我該自我介紹一下
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.79,0:05:38.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是大衛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.60,0:05:42.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道你昨晚是否記得我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.96,0:05:45.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你記得嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.82,0:05:48.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不記得
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.94,0:05:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能原諒你
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.15,0:05:56.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚簡直一團亂
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.02,0:06:00.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是我把繩子遞給那些人  把你綁起來的
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.68,0:06:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我總是帶著一些繩子
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.23,0:06:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用繩子能做許多有趣的事情
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.51,0:06:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  你真漂亮
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.12,0:06:22.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我給你水喝
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.50,0:06:26.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是我不該做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.85,0:06:29.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你愿意為我做點事嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.29,0:06:33.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做點你不該做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.87,0:06:35.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你愿意嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.69,0:06:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我你有多渴
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.10,0:06:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.25,0:07:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.70,0:07:13.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反抗只會讓過程更持久
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.36,0:07:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴你  我無所謂
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.92,0:07:21.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大衛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.53,0:07:26.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你他媽在這里干什么呢
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.52,0:07:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根  先生
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.33,0:07:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真覺得我需要你回答嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.69,0:07:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能看出你想強奸這女人
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.21,0:07:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想強奸這女人  對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.71,0:07:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是不可接受的行為
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.46,0:07:51.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,強奸違反了這里的規定
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.37,0:07:54.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不想待在允許強奸的地方
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.52,0:07:59.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,負責的人放過這種事...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.70,0:08:09.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大衛
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.67,0:08:14.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的越線了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.03,0:08:17.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  先生
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.01,0:08:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.81,0:08:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不接受你的道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.06,0:08:42.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.52,0:08:45.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薩沙
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.73,0:08:49.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,名字真好聽
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.38,0:08:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給薩沙拿件新襯衫
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.81,0:09:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉讓你看到了這些
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.56,0:09:05.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繩子的事我也很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.49,0:09:08.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許有些小題大做
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.39,0:09:12.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你昨晚鬧了好大一場事
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.25,0:09:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.73,0:09:24.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我記得你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.19,0:09:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.84,0:09:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你當時在場
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.38,0:09:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死  我現在懂了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.12,0:09:38.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得承認
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.00,0:09:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你這娘們真他媽有種
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.07,0:09:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不顧死活地就沖進來了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.80,0:09:46.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,問題是
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.11,0:09:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你說實話
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.33,0:09:54.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是瑞克派你來的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.69,0:09:56.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.75,0:10:00.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的狗嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.44,0:10:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.17,0:10:06.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎樣  你肯定以為你必死無疑
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.98,0:10:09.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,畢竟你那樣獨自闖進來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.16,0:10:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但事情不會這樣發展
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.76,0:10:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恰恰相反
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.19,0:10:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這
Dialogue: 0,0:10:17.34,0:10:19.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可能只是個開始
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.52,0:10:34.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刀現在歸你了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.35,0:10:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以試著使用  干掉我
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.85,0:10:40.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但考慮到我站在你上方
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.54,0:10:42.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿著一根球棒
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.60,0:10:44.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那可不是明智之舉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.05,0:10:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以用刀來割腕
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.46,0:10:51.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就太可惜了  但我懂
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.59,0:10:54.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考慮到最近發生的事  你顯然
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.27,0:10:56.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是什么陽光女人
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.01,0:10:59.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以坐在那里  什么也不做
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.23,0:11:03.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等著老大衛復活  咬掉你的臉
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.99,0:11:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這也很可惜  有些瘋狂
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.35,0:11:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你有權做出選擇
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.59,0:11:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者你可以用刀來干掉強奸犯老大衛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.48,0:11:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阻止他變成強奸犯行尸大衛
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.91,0:11:25.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己救自己  加入救世軍
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.41,0:11:30.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我要拿你怎么辦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.00,0:11:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么辦
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.64,0:11:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我少了個男丁
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.11,0:11:39.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,媽的  這個人渣算不上男人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.35,0:11:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但依然  我少了人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.64,0:11:43.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你這娘們有種極了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.77,0:11:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要好好利用你的勇氣
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.94,0:11:51.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有朝一日你可以幫我管理這個地方
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.30,0:11:55.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們所有人一起  跟著規矩走
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.95,0:11:58.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站在同一戰線
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.02,0:12:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從來都是這么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.82,0:12:03.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你依然可以選這條路
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.23,0:12:06.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考慮到我的所作所為
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.62,0:12:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道這有點難以想象
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.87,0:12:14.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  薩沙  人人都有必須邁過去的坎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.04,0:12:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,花點時間  好好想想
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.36,0:12:26.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無論你的決定如何  都由你說了算
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.93,0:12:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別有壓力
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.77,0:12:32.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有  再次道歉  很抱歉你不得不目睹那幕
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.36,0:12:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我知道你是見過場面的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.38,0:12:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只希望你能明白...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.37,0:12:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不是怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.86,0:13:26.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們把你怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.36,0:13:31.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們在保護我
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.31,0:13:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我給你帶了些能讓你舒服點的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.45,0:13:44.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實話說  這枕頭不防過敏
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.87,0:13:49.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,關于我該不該過來有過一些爭論
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.81,0:13:52.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們說假如我被你攜刀劫持的話
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.56,0:13:54.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就只能靠自己了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.73,0:13:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就這么一說
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.25,0:14:04.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根向我傳達了他對你的招安之意
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.79,0:14:07.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我看來你應該接受
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.68,0:14:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像我一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.79,0:14:11.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道這是不得已而為之
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.52,0:14:13.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但與這里的頭頭做朋友
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.09,0:14:15.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的是正確的選擇
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.38,0:14:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾經認為自己可以勇敢起來
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.69,0:14:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當一個亞伯拉罕那樣的生存者...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.32,0:14:27.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開著那輛房車駛向夕陽是...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.42,0:14:31.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一生中最棒的37分鐘
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.81,0:14:35.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我如今明白那只是一個完全不切實際的幻想
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.74,0:14:41.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我這輩子最害怕的一次
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.19,0:14:43.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是那晚在那個林子里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.91,0:14:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跪在地上
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.86,0:14:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,覺得自己死定了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.73,0:14:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后看見勇敢的生存者...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.51,0:14:53.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,被殺了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.67,0:14:57.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后那種讓人嚇尿褲子的恐懼
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.16,0:14:59.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看著那個場景一次又一次重現...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.76,0:15:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.66,0:15:04.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.60,0:15:11.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來這邊意味著我再不用恐懼了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.71,0:15:15.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如你答應的話  你也不用了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.91,0:15:18.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求求你答應吧
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.97,0:15:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他希望你能答應
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.95,0:15:32.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不希望
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.31,0:15:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.88,0:15:37.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們依然活著
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.62,0:15:39.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,世道已經變了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.34,0:15:41.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以隨之做出改變  我們必須如此
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.24,0:15:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.56,0:16:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他已經開始...  -拜托了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.51,0:16:07.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.79,0:17:00.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還從沒見過你到墻外來呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.83,0:17:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我建這些圍墻就是為了用的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.63,0:17:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如我想吃綠菜了  我可以吃沙拉
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.50,0:17:10.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你為什么來這里
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.81,0:17:12.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本打算找你談談
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.98,0:17:14.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我看見你一個人跑出來
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.31,0:17:16.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很擔心你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.27,0:17:18.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的朋友們呢
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.82,0:17:21.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們出去了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.09,0:17:26.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們在找需要的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.14,0:17:28.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不去嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.82,0:17:34.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是好奇  你怎么還留在這  瑪姬
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.57,0:17:36.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡森已經不在了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.00,0:17:38.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽說你要救他回來
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.71,0:17:41.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.98,0:17:45.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還是只是說說而已
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.40,0:17:47.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪姬  你得信任我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.92,0:17:50.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人們都很緊張  很擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.41,0:17:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我們表現得像一伙
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.53,0:17:57.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家會安心得多
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.21,0:18:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我們能真正成為一伙  會輕松得多
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.45,0:18:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說得對
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.91,0:18:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得對合作持更開放的態度
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.55,0:18:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.20,0:18:11.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我從不希望我們之間鬧成這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.80,0:18:14.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感謝你這么說
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.36,0:18:19.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亡羊補牢永遠不晚  知道嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.27,0:18:27.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你是認真的  我稍后會找你詳談
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.37,0:18:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.54,0:18:30.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好了
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.25,0:18:40.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還以為很快就能完事
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.26,0:18:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,弄完之前  你能幫我留意一下四周嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.26,0:18:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.72,0:18:45.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,樂意之至
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.19,0:19:35.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來了一只
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.57,0:19:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我來
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.85,0:19:41.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是來保護孕婦的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.11,0:19:43.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用孕婦保護我
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.97,0:19:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以前殺過行尸嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.62,0:19:48.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒殺過我就不可能站在這了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.58,0:19:56.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-沒事  我來吧  -不
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.13,0:20:09.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.31,0:20:12.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  你來
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.55,0:20:28.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪姬
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.82,0:20:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救救我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.29,0:20:46.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.66,0:20:59.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他以前沒殺過行尸
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.95,0:21:01.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正在學習
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.59,0:21:03.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他跟我們可不是這么說的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.53,0:21:10.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝你救我
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.81,0:21:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己抓到的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.20,0:21:30.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那他媽當然  -‭瑞秋
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.66,0:21:32.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是說  那當然
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.80,0:21:35.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我去把它清理干凈  -好
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.67,0:21:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別出聲
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.52,0:21:57.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手放頭上
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.53,0:21:59.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在村里時我們就該殺了你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.73,0:22:04.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會慶幸你們沒殺我的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.61,0:22:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不是一個人來的  對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.89,0:22:06.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.42,0:22:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.48,0:22:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想讓你坐下
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.12,0:22:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  辛蒂
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.93,0:22:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你保證過的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.75,0:22:28.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對  我保證過
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.55,0:22:29.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把手放在頭上
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.12,0:22:40.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我別無選擇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.38,0:22:41.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你來這干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.23,0:22:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說了  我別無選擇
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.29,0:22:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你們有  你倆都有
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.33,0:22:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的同伴現在就在外面
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.35,0:22:51.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們會攻占這里  希望不必開火
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.67,0:22:54.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  你們要"攻占這里"
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.41,0:22:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在說什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.32,0:22:56.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們需要你們的槍
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.83,0:22:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.75,0:22:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們要抵抗救世軍
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.61,0:23:00.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你們應該加入我們  -不
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.98,0:23:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救世軍殺害了你們的父親
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.81,0:23:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兄弟  丈夫  兒子  而你們選擇逃避
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.99,0:23:07.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以為我們鏟除了他們
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.32,0:23:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,碧翠絲說還有更多救世軍  她說得對
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.56,0:23:10.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.71,0:23:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺了我的朋友們
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.97,0:23:15.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺了我的女友
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.08,0:23:18.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接管了我們  奪走了我們的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.51,0:23:21.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們對救世軍千依百順
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.54,0:23:23.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們以為我們依然效忠  但不是
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.16,0:23:24.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們打算反抗
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.92,0:23:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有其他社區加入我們
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.53,0:23:28.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有了海邊旅館  我們就有了一支軍隊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.27,0:23:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.93,0:23:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"謝謝給槍  你們應該加入我們"
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.39,0:23:35.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我們聯手  可以打敗他們
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.27,0:23:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們必須試試
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.26,0:23:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們會贏的  塔拉  我見過  你也見過
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.26,0:23:41.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我們團隊的首領談談  瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.59,0:23:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只用談談  我們不必攻占這里
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.36,0:23:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不想那樣做
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.41,0:23:45.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以示意他們停下
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.93,0:23:48.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你必須現在就告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.45,0:23:53.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著  我們不只是藏在樹林里
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.03,0:23:55.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們在做事  我們沒有放棄
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.63,0:23:58.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想打破我的承諾  辛蒂  
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.56,0:24:01.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是世界可以屬于好人  公正的人
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.77,0:24:03.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我們有足夠的勇氣去嘗試
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.85,0:24:06.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不是好人  也不勇敢
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.43,0:24:08.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你我都不是
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.01,0:24:09.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.20,0:24:10.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我們才有現在這麻煩
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.17,0:24:13.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔拉  如果你們拿走我們的槍
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.61,0:24:15.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還不如把我們全殺了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.19,0:24:16.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是你們做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.73,0:24:18.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們應該和他們談談
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.47,0:24:19.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.60,0:24:21.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以試著阻止這事
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.29,0:24:22.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  辛蒂
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.10,0:24:28.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無所謂了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.78,0:24:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒法阻止了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.96,0:24:37.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.65,0:24:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,武器庫
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.16,0:25:00.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趴下  快
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.67,0:25:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手抱頭
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.26,0:25:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.80,0:25:29.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的人殺我的人
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.86,0:25:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炸彈安置在墻外
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.81,0:25:33.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你本可以阻止的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.60,0:25:35.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望所有人都沒事  真的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.39,0:25:36.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.40,0:25:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起來
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.59,0:25:39.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該走了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.53,0:25:46.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的腿
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.35,0:25:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,站住  后退
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.10,0:25:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛蒂  別動
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.58,0:25:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是空的  什么
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.42,0:25:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒裝彈
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.96,0:26:02.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不是來傷人的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.86,0:26:04.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,辛蒂  給我
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.93,0:26:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.15,0:26:11.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜塔尼亞  就和瑞克談談
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.54,0:26:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,閉嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.03,0:26:17.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人蹲下
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.11,0:26:18.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手放頭上
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.34,0:26:19.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人冷靜
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.58,0:26:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不想傷害任何人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.30,0:26:23.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別動  聽我們說
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.01,0:26:26.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們想讓這件事盡量簡單和平地解決
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.72,0:26:28.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們都可以做到
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.50,0:26:31.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去那邊蹲著  安靜
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.24,0:26:36.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們搞出了很大動靜
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.04,0:26:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我們想盡快了事  這樣你們就可以派人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.54,0:26:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,引開過來的行尸
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.32,0:26:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔拉說你們這片森林比較稀疏
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.62,0:26:45.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我們不會冒險
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.27,0:26:48.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何人都不必受傷
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.82,0:26:53.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的只是你們有什么  我們需要什么
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.03,0:26:55.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒人可以帶走任何東西
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.01,0:26:57.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放了所有人
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.04,0:27:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立刻離開
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.23,0:27:02.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,離開  不然她就得死
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.91,0:27:04.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  我們會離開
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.59,0:27:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我們要帶走你們的武器
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.04,0:27:08.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這點不會改變
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.85,0:27:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是娜塔尼亞  對嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.37,0:27:13.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放下槍
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.87,0:27:16.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們來談談我們可以改變什么
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.68,0:27:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  馬上離開
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.11,0:27:22.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米恩瓊  不要
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.98,0:27:26.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們只是不想被打擾
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.47,0:27:28.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒問題  我們會離開
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.49,0:27:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,立刻放開她
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.56,0:27:34.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然我們就殺了你
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.87,0:27:36.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們都不想那樣
Dialogue: 0,0:27:36.64,0:27:38.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們想讓我們反抗救世軍
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.49,0:27:44.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們試過  輸了  輸得很慘
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.02,0:27:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不會再失去任何東西了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.65,0:27:48.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管是我們的槍  還是我們的安全
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.04,0:27:50.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們做了那么多  好不容易才來這里
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.14,0:27:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會贏的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.29,0:27:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有了你們的槍  無論你們幫不幫我們
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.39,0:28:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,娜塔尼亞  放下槍
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.51,0:28:04.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺了我你也會死
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.68,0:28:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的人一樣會拿走槍  什么都不會變
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.40,0:28:14.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許我們應該試一下
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.92,0:28:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祖母  住手吧
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.85,0:28:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結束了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.13,0:28:22.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和他們談談吧  好嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.35,0:28:24.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒完
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.87,0:28:26.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們都忘了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.70,0:28:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們都忘了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.69,0:28:31.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們中有些人真想反抗他們嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.50,0:28:33.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,經歷了那一切以后
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.31,0:28:35.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以失去槍
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.76,0:28:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我們也要離開這里去戰斗嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.36,0:28:39.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,經歷了那么多事以后
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.84,0:28:41.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必須提醒你們
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.83,0:28:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:42.71,0:28:45.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會這樣做  我會死
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.76,0:28:47.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但就是這么重要
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.60,0:28:49.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是你們的人生  你們所有人的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.40,0:28:51.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想它是什么樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.51,0:28:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想想他們以前是怎么對我們的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.48,0:28:56.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們要看清楚  睜眼好好看著
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.30,0:28:58.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克  有行尸
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.36,0:29:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人起來
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.59,0:29:07.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓孩子們站到后面
Dialogue: 0,0:29:07.20,0:29:08.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它們過來了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.20,0:29:09.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一班  跟他們站一排
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.73,0:29:12.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拔刀  只殺行尸  只殺行尸
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.52,0:29:13.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪也別去
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.10,0:29:17.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有人  10英尺以內再開槍
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.47,0:29:18.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.82,0:29:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開槍
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.17,0:30:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我們不會跟你們一起反抗他們
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.98,0:30:45.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿著你們的槍滾吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.24,0:31:14.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你贏了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.54,0:31:15.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.11,0:31:19.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你贏了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.65,0:31:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫點人來  清理干凈
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.84,0:31:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.85,0:31:40.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不會真的以為
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.71,0:31:43.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會讓你留著這把刀吧
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.91,0:31:47.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我相信你效忠之前
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.43,0:31:50.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還要走很長一段路
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.73,0:31:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一步步來嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.24,0:31:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕不是針對你
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.09,0:31:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果情況調過來
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.90,0:32:01.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定也不會相信我
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.24,0:32:03.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.73,0:32:06.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自救的方式
Dialogue: 0,0:32:08.05,0:32:11.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你剛向我投降的方式
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.48,0:32:13.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是個很好的開始
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.49,0:32:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  我們還得辦點事  薩沙
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.90,0:32:22.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過我保證  我會盡量讓過程充滿樂趣
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.47,0:32:26.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實話說了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.70,0:32:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一只小鳥告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.31,0:32:32.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克和你們其他的人在動歪腦筋
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.07,0:32:36.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這需要改變
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.53,0:32:38.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你要幫我改變
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.57,0:32:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會找到一個雙贏的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.37,0:32:43.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.27,0:32:46.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你打算...  -我會給你找些東西
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.14,0:32:47.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你更舒適
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.49,0:32:50.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓你體驗一下我們能提供什么
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.72,0:32:52.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好享受一晚
Dialogue: 0,0:32:52.17,0:32:54.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為明天
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.49,0:32:58.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是個大日子
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.18,0:34:07.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凱爾
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.83,0:34:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.54,0:34:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你開車帶我去個地方
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.72,0:34:22.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你最好打個包
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.22,0:34:29.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.97,0:34:31.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.76,0:34:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽說你愿意加入這里了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.56,0:34:37.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在也許看起來不像
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.88,0:34:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我向你保證
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.26,0:34:41.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你同樣做了正確的選擇
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.64,0:34:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我錯了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.79,0:34:50.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.32,0:34:54.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會做
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.21,0:34:57.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直坐在這里
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.20,0:35:01.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想著我怎么能做到
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.93,0:35:03.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發生了那么多事
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.11,0:35:06.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的朋友們還在外面
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.74,0:35:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還被他們傷害著
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.76,0:35:11.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道我怎么能那樣說
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.12,0:35:17.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在  我陷入了困境
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.45,0:35:19.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必須幫我
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.44,0:35:20.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會的
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.97,0:35:22.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會幫你習慣現實
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.74,0:35:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闡明利害  演示為什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.31,0:35:27.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是個錯誤
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.66,0:35:29.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本來準備好了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.65,0:35:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道如果我昨晚沒殺死他
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.22,0:35:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就完了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.89,0:35:37.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒殺死他  所以就這樣吧
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.53,0:35:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.82,0:35:43.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必須給我搞些東西來
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.28,0:35:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刀  槍  剃須刀片
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.10,0:35:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為了尼根嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:35:49.26,0:35:50.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.17,0:35:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管怎樣  他都會利用我傷害我的朋友們
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.74,0:35:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們的朋友們
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.82,0:36:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我對此無能為力
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.82,0:36:05.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非我死了  不給他機會
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.43,0:36:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要我活著  他就會傷害他們
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.49,0:36:11.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必須死
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.37,0:36:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是唯一的辦法
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.74,0:36:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不認為...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.10,0:36:16.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你不會做任何事阻止他們
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.96,0:36:18.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.05,0:36:21.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是求你了  尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.32,0:36:24.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別讓他們利用我傷害我們的人
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.92,0:36:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  你必須給我一些東西了斷自己
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.63,0:36:32.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,槍  刀  玻璃
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.19,0:36:34.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不在乎
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.29,0:36:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必須死
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.86,0:36:38.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.57,0:36:43.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.78,0:36:45.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會考慮
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.75,0:36:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.56,0:37:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不需要全拿走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.33,0:37:32.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們需要
Dialogue: 0,0:37:37.71,0:37:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不只是我殺的人
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.62,0:37:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也會想起我沒殺的人
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.70,0:37:55.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,結束后我們會把槍送回來
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.33,0:37:59.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想跟你們走
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.34,0:38:01.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們有些人想反抗  但不是所有人
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.61,0:38:03.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須達成共識她們才加入
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.06,0:38:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我祖母認為你們都會死
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.99,0:38:08.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你祖母很多想法都是錯的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.73,0:38:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.65,0:38:10.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不想看見這個
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.66,0:38:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她躺下了  我把她打得挺重
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.71,0:38:15.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感謝你之前救我命
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.99,0:38:17.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有另一次
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.91,0:38:19.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有另一次
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.84,0:38:21.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許還有今天
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.05,0:38:22.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.18,0:38:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.83,0:38:29.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.73,0:38:37.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不給我們留一把嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.82,0:38:39.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不留  回見  瑞秋
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.50,0:38:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.93,0:38:47.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還好
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.43,0:38:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你說得對
Dialogue: 0,0:38:50.70,0:38:51.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不必內疚
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.38,0:39:14.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薩沙
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.19,0:39:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在
Dialogue: 0,0:39:20.87,0:39:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我仔細考慮權衡了上次談話
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.45,0:39:29.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我決定滿足你的請求
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.84,0:39:35.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用這個就行
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.12,0:39:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是毒藥  本人親手制作
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.50,0:39:52.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,攝入后約20至30分鐘內必死
Dialogue: 0,0:39:53.93,0:39:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信應該是無痛的
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.67,0:39:57.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不太確定
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.53,0:39:59.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我做藥是因為曾有人提過類似請求
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.90,0:40:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后來我發現她們給了我虛假信息
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.25,0:40:03.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,于是我懸崖勒馬
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.91,0:40:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在的不同之處是
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.11,0:40:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們倆是長期旅伴
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.51,0:40:12.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你證明了自己是一個誠實勇敢
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.67,0:40:14.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,具備完全自我意識的人
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.91,0:40:16.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我確信我欠你人情
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.95,0:40:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你讓我幫你找解脫辦法
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.33,0:40:20.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我找到了一個
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.85,0:40:26.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,首先聲明  我完全不希望你死
Dialogue: 0,0:40:29.09,0:40:31.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是聽起來你已經下了必死之心
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.28,0:41:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:41:20.07,0:41:21.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,薩沙在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.64,0:41:26.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人來了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.08,0:41:56.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢點  等等
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.03,0:41:57.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他說他想幫我們
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.75,0:42:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:42:09.47,0:42:10.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想幫忙
Dialogue: 0,0:42:11.42,0:42:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:42:29.02,0:42:30.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:42:36.83,0:42:38.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跪下
