[Script Info]
; // The sub is created by AssToolkit
; // AssToolkit is an ASS Converter designed by David C.
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.22,0:00:03.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《行尸走肉》前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.77,0:00:07.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們該走了
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.93,0:00:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,趁你們還沒領教到我們是多危險的人之前
Dialogue: 0,0:00:09.91,0:00:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你剛是在威脅我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.62,0:00:18.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們要在這生產子彈
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.57,0:00:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,根據供求法則
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.09,0:00:22.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一盒子彈現在就是流通貨幣
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.31,0:00:24.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們得到的一切都是抗爭得來的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.49,0:00:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們遵守他們的規則  就能活下去
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.32,0:00:29.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么個活法
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.88,0:00:40.88,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻譯:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}Reginamoon CS小明漫畫家
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.89,0:01:00.74,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an5\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx2300\fscy200\alpha&AA\pos(129.2,218.4)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.85,0:00:45.85,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}翻譯:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}冰藍 蘑菇 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.81,0:00:50.81,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}校對:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.78,0:00:55.78,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}時間軸:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}某雪 加森 濤濤
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.74,0:01:00.74,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\c&H008AFF&\pos(12.12,219.36)}后期:  {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小哥  拉圖    {\c&H008AFF&}總監： {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.75,0:02:58.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幾點了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.04,0:03:03.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剛過五點半
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.36,0:03:07.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.28,0:03:31.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,昨晚沒看見那個
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.56,0:03:34.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒看見什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.03,0:03:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還在走
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.20,0:03:46.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但看起來像是隊尾了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.40,0:03:49.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走了一夜啊
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.49,0:03:51.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少尼根夠聰明
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.64,0:03:53.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒讓那些東西接近我們
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.61,0:03:56.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肥喬至少還是有點用處的
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.41,0:03:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是說他很能吃蛋糕嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.40,0:04:02.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他負責引尸改道
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.14,0:04:03.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是出去轉轉
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.56,0:04:04.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什么大不了的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.36,0:04:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像游擊隊
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.58,0:04:09.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像什么
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.68,0:04:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戰爭中的游擊隊  白癡
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.12,0:04:15.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上個月搜刮拿到的槍
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.87,0:04:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新人那里拿到的火箭筒
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.89,0:04:21.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許能削減數量
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.45,0:04:23.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除掉它們
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.09,0:04:27.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  很少了
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.18,0:04:29.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我們走  -終于
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.81,0:04:30.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝天謝地
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.08,0:05:35.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做記號
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.28,0:05:38.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得我們接近了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.16,0:05:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們該跳車了  剩下的路跟著走
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.21,0:05:50.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看能看見什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.54,0:05:52.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.04,0:05:52.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么跳
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.67,0:05:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般摔下去不會受傷
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.20,0:05:59.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抗拒才會受傷  順勢滾滾就行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.12,0:06:00.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡車速度夠慢了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.31,0:06:02.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會在盲區
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.14,0:06:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以跟著別的車過去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.23,0:06:04.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我搞砸了  我們被抓了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.66,0:06:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會沒事的  我們得快點跳了
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.96,0:06:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  先給我演示一下
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.19,0:06:29.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"先給我演示一下"
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.61,0:06:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  小伙子們  卸貨搬進去
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.84,0:07:00.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要回去了  自己也瀉點火
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.56,0:07:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根  得跟你談談引尸的事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.81,0:07:05.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,引尸怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.10,0:07:06.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞砸了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.17,0:07:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們現在在處理  但外面一團糟
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.97,0:07:10.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是誰的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.02,0:07:11.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一個背包和一個帳篷
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.78,0:07:13.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.37,0:07:15.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還以為他們裝得滿滿的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.20,0:07:16.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別擔心
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.31,0:07:17.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們還會送更多來的
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.70,0:07:18.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.96,0:07:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.53,0:07:26.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么回事
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.22,0:07:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后退  放下武器
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.76,0:07:36.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想要尼根
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.81,0:07:39.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他殺了我的朋友們
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.14,0:07:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別人沒必要死
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.44,0:07:50.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.12,0:07:57.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真可愛
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.97,0:08:01.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你選了這把槍是因為它看起來很酷嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.53,0:08:04.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,絕對是  對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.72,0:08:07.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子  我不會撒謊
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.69,0:08:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你嚇死老子了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.75,0:08:17.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.48,0:08:19.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德懷特
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.68,0:08:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后退
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.05,0:08:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是招待新客人的方式嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.37,0:08:37.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧  孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.02,0:08:39.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帶你四處轉轉
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.14,0:09:58.35,*Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第七季  第七集』
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.75,0:10:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧  孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.13,0:10:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我帶你四處轉轉
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.16,0:10:09.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟你爸爸一樣  都有令人討厭的眼神
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.58,0:10:12.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不過只有一半討厭  因為
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.46,0:10:14.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道的  你
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.29,0:10:15.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,少了只眼睛
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.23,0:10:20.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.92,0:10:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真的不拉我的手嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.58,0:10:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為你還有手是你走運
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.58,0:10:30.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的伙伴達里爾也是
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.61,0:10:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在我想起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.95,0:10:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,工作怎么樣  達里爾
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.49,0:10:36.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對你來說夠勁嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.65,0:10:40.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  一只手會很難工作
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.52,0:10:50.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聰明的孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.02,0:10:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在跟我來
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.39,0:10:55.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德懷特  你帶上達里爾
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.86,0:10:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去廚房  準備點吃的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.46,0:11:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,新計劃  伙計們
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.29,0:11:02.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死人燒了  晚點再卸貨
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.16,0:11:04.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  我今天都沒時間
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.99,0:11:07.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,干我的老婆們了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.79,0:11:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許有時間干一個吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.29,0:11:17.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.96,0:11:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要對我做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.59,0:11:28.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.50,0:11:32.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別打破我對你的印象
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.06,0:11:34.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是個硬漢  天不怕地不怕
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.61,0:11:37.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別怕我  這令人失望
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.38,0:11:38.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第二
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.57,0:11:42.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真想讓我毀掉驚喜嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.30,0:11:45.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你的  孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.93,0:11:47.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說真的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.98,0:11:50.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去你的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.75,0:11:59.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}關門前一定要進行夜間檢查
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.14,0:12:05.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來看看
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.61,0:12:20.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救世軍去外面
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.83,0:12:22.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與行尸斗爭
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.29,0:12:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶回來了一些很好的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.41,0:12:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你們努力工作  遵守規定
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.06,0:12:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有些東西可以歸你們
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.24,0:12:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天  每個人晚餐都能吃到新鮮蔬菜
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.23,0:12:43.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不需要工分
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.71,0:12:49.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看見了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.92,0:12:52.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尊重
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.94,0:12:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很酷吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.47,0:12:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們還跪著嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.48,0:13:00.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還原
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.49,0:13:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想給你看一些我打了B+
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.41,0:13:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或是更高分數的潛力地點
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.11,0:13:12.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我們要去哪里
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.66,0:13:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然我感到你十分確定
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.70,0:13:16.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但為了不疏忽  我還是要說
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.13,0:13:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在對周邊區域的深入分析后
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.48,0:13:20.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打叉了所有我們搜尋過的地點
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.58,0:13:21.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我相信我準確定位了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.81,0:13:24.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一些值得考慮的地點  來進行手頭的特定任務
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.50,0:13:25.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.11,0:13:28.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為尼根找東西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.87,0:13:31.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我們才不為那混蛋做事
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.38,0:13:36.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你出去不為救世軍找東西嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.38,0:13:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.82,0:13:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒什么好抵抗的  羅西塔
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.19,0:13:47.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許我們該一起去
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.10,0:13:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愿意
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.77,0:13:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,四個人在大海里更容易撈針
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.71,0:13:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們自己可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.96,0:13:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你不喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.35,0:13:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不想聽我說
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.33,0:13:58.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我們得為他們找東西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.44,0:14:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就像是交稅
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.66,0:14:02.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-喂  -過來
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.90,0:14:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.70,0:14:06.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以一直對我生氣
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.84,0:14:08.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但這不是我做的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.65,0:14:09.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.00,0:14:13.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得你可以做得更好
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.37,0:14:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.78,0:14:17.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當然啦
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.83,0:14:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你肯定給自己藏了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.55,0:14:23.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一卡車東西  是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.79,0:14:25.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去拿吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.31,0:14:30.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去交稅  別他媽來煩我
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.25,0:14:33.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.75,0:14:50.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女士們
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.55,0:14:53.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別管這孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.19,0:14:58.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.26,0:15:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你來的地方  每個女人
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.55,0:15:03.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,穿得都像是汽修店里的會計
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.64,0:15:05.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會想看看她們的乳頭的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.16,0:15:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事  我不介意
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.87,0:15:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她們不介意  你自便
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.41,0:15:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能和你談談嗎  愛妻
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.78,0:15:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用拘束  小子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.06,0:15:52.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安珀和馬克怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.47,0:15:54.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不在這里時我們所談論的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.35,0:15:56.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與你無關
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.73,0:16:00.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.86,0:16:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我聽說了什么嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.69,0:16:13.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我聽說馬克翹掉了引尸的班
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.79,0:16:15.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就為了和安珀幽會
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.45,0:16:18.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得知道這是不是真的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.81,0:16:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我立規矩是有原因的
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.95,0:16:30.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人要是死了什么都是一場空
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.52,0:16:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,親愛的  你在這里是因為你懂這點
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.73,0:16:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她只是犯了個錯誤
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.38,0:16:47.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別難為她
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.68,0:16:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,冷靜點
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.58,0:16:57.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我打過你們中的任何一人嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.74,0:16:59.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.13,0:17:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我了解你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.48,0:17:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有更可怕的手段
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.13,0:17:17.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧你啊
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.51,0:17:24.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下次繼續
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.75,0:17:58.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安珀  寶貝
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.86,0:18:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我不希望這里有人是
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.96,0:18:03.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不情不愿地留下的  對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.97,0:18:09.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如你想離開我
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.56,0:18:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回到馬克身邊...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.04,0:18:13.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.84,0:18:16.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你知道什么事是不可以做的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.58,0:18:20.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背著你亂搞
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.31,0:18:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完全正確
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.97,0:18:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.32,0:18:29.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,背著我亂搞
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.59,0:18:37.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有大把妞兒想取代你的位置
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.08,0:18:40.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也能想到幾個適合你做的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.90,0:18:44.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想回到馬克和你媽媽身邊嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.59,0:18:48.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以安排你們三個做同一個工作
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.08,0:18:49.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.20,0:18:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.26,0:18:52.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會留下來的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.42,0:18:54.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...我很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.02,0:18:58.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那意味著什么吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.29,0:19:04.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道那意味著什么吧
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.08,0:19:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知...道
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.87,0:19:12.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愛你  尼根
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.26,0:19:16.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你當然愛我了  親愛的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.52,0:19:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你在哭什么
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.59,0:19:25.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會過得舒舒服服的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.21,0:19:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能去幫我把卡森喊來嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.17,0:19:57.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好的  -你剛剛看見了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.76,0:19:59.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我沒為難她
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.05,0:20:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便我...總體來說很不好說話[硬]
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.06,0:20:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就是個混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.17,0:20:06.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.80,0:20:10.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但詭異的是  你依然喜歡我
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.39,0:20:14.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道真相的  和我一樣
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.24,0:20:58.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡爾  能幫我端著盤子嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.46,0:21:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你為什么把他帶來這里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.56,0:21:11.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不在這里時我們所談論的事
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.03,0:21:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,與你無關
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.52,0:21:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,別逼我把這根牙簽
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.24,0:21:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,插進他僅剩的那只眼睛里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.72,0:21:29.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟德懷特走
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.62,0:21:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他會給你找個拖把
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.54,0:21:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小德懷特...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.42,0:21:35.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把爐子生起來
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.85,0:21:37.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一會兒就下去
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.41,0:21:39.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是時候往日重現了
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.34,0:21:42.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧  孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.48,0:22:20.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們只有今天一天的時間搜尋物資了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.53,0:22:23.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們可能明天就回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.80,0:22:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也可能現在就回來了
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.28,0:22:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}繼續向前走\N等著你的只有麻煩
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.08,0:22:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恨某個人...這算是罪嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.42,0:22:56.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不算
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.62,0:22:59.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不一定算
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.28,0:23:02.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想法只是想法而已
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.58,0:23:04.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重要的是我們的行為
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.30,0:23:16.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我恨瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.65,0:23:21.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他曾經是個警察  那又怎樣
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.44,0:23:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不該他管事的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.80,0:23:27.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我母親  她...是國會的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.99,0:23:29.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她領導人們
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.37,0:23:31.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她能發掘人們的閃光點
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.31,0:23:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克發掘了我的閃光點
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.91,0:23:37.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么發掘的  靠欺負你嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.28,0:23:42.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是有點
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.83,0:23:46.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但主要還是靠啟發我
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.92,0:23:49.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不僅僅是保住了大家的命
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.48,0:23:51.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他還讓我們團結在了一起
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.28,0:23:55.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不完美  但他是個有主見的人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.19,0:23:58.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他可沒有保住所有人的命  加百利
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.44,0:24:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我母親  我父親  我兄弟...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.55,0:24:02.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是他的錯
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.66,0:24:05.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他到了這里  他們就死了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.03,0:24:09.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許別人還活著是因為他到了這里
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.79,0:24:12.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許我們不該襲擊那個哨站
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.00,0:24:13.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那樣格倫...  -我們事先不知情
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.24,0:24:17.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不可能知道
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.02,0:24:20.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒機會知道
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.30,0:24:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,事已至此...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.38,0:24:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以著眼于未來
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.16,0:24:31.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么未來
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.22,0:24:34.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他管事的話我們沒有未來
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.74,0:24:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我現在禁不住想...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.26,0:24:42.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許目前能發生在我們身上的最好的事...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.78,0:24:46.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是他回不來了
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.63,0:24:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停車
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.13,0:25:09.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你所說的話...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.49,0:25:12.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不會讓你成為罪人
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.27,0:25:17.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但會讓你成為一個徹頭徹尾的混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.87,0:25:19.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但這只是一時
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.31,0:25:24.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人是可以改變的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.77,0:25:35.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.51,0:27:07.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有那些女人  真的都是你的...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.65,0:27:10.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妻子  是的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.52,0:27:12.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直夢想著能睡一大群不同的女人
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.40,0:27:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么吊死在一棵樹上呢
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.36,0:27:17.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么要遵守老規矩呢
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.24,0:27:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,何不讓生活變得更美好些
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.18,0:27:21.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說到這個...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.07,0:27:24.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.24,0:27:28.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們開始吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.66,0:27:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,開始干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.46,0:27:36.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想加深一下對你的了解  卡爾
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.46,0:27:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.57,0:27:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,自己想想
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.11,0:27:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很聰明
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.79,0:27:44.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,實際上  我要告訴你你有多聰明
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.93,0:27:46.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以免你自己還沒意識到
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.60,0:27:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以為你這年齡的孩子只會悶悶不樂
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.52,0:27:53.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,無所事事
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.00,0:27:56.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就知道為錯過舞會而哭哭啼啼
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.93,0:28:00.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你  你卻肩負起重任
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.37,0:28:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找到了我  殺了我兩個手下
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.34,0:28:09.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且你足夠聰明  知道我不會放過你
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.91,0:28:18.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...我說不下去了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.32,0:28:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,感覺像是對著生日禮物說話似的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.50,0:28:23.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得把你臉上那個鬼玩意取下來
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.98,0:28:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想看看禮物里包著的是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.12,0:28:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  -兩個手下
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.44,0:28:34.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩個...手下
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.02,0:28:37.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,懲罰
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.64,0:28:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真想激怒我嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.75,0:29:13.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.96,0:29:22.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把頭發從臉上撩開
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.52,0:29:23.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我看看
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.10,0:29:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天爺
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.26,0:29:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真惡心
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.89,0:29:34.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪不得你要遮起來了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.95,0:29:36.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己看過嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.62,0:29:38.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你照過鏡子嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.29,0:29:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是太他媽惡心了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.40,0:29:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都能看到你的眼窩了
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.37,0:29:46.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想摸摸
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.22,0:29:49.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來嘛  能給我摸摸嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.64,0:30:01.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.48,0:30:07.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,老天啊  孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.78,0:30:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.21,0:30:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.63,0:30:17.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你很容易讓人忘了...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.48,0:30:19.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只是個孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.66,0:30:23.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是故意要傷你心的  我...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.03,0:30:28.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我只是在開玩笑  -算了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.31,0:30:36.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,進
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.37,0:30:39.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉打擾  先生  但是
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.48,0:30:42.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,您把露西爾落在貨車那邊了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.32,0:30:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.21,0:30:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我從沒那樣做過
Dialogue: 0,0:30:47.33,0:30:49.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜是小朋友開沖鋒槍
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.61,0:30:51.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,分散了我的注意力
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.25,0:30:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不開玩笑  你看起來酷斃了
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.56,0:31:01.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,換做是我  就不會遮住
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.46,0:31:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,女孩子可能不喜歡
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.12,0:31:05.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我向你保證
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.47,0:31:08.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,長成這樣  沒人敢惹你
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.94,0:31:10.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒人敢  先生
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.72,0:31:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肥喬  是你幫我把她一路拿過來的嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.04,0:31:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  先生
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.80,0:31:29.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿的時候溫柔嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.22,0:31:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,體貼嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.01,0:31:35.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像對待女士一樣對她嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.91,0:31:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  先生
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.59,0:31:42.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你像對待女士一樣愛撫她的私處嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.00,0:31:49.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我開玩笑的  伙計
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.25,0:31:51.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,球棍哪有什么私處
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.01,0:31:56.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滾出去
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.21,0:32:02.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.80,0:32:05.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說的就是這個
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.69,0:32:08.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,男人都互相打趣
Dialogue: 0,0:32:08.71,0:32:11.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這種事該是你爸教你的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.20,0:32:19.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你平時有什么娛樂
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.08,0:32:22.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喜歡音樂嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.44,0:32:30.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要你給我唱首歌
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.66,0:32:33.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.85,0:32:34.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.12,0:32:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你用沖鋒槍打死我兩個手下
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.65,0:32:41.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想要點交換
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.35,0:32:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-給我唱首歌  -我...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.24,0:32:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我想不起來  -放屁
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.08,0:32:53.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你媽媽給你唱過什么歌
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.46,0:32:56.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸開車時聽什么歌
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.71,0:33:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-開始唱  -好  好
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.49,0:33:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.20,0:33:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*你是我的陽光*
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.60,0:33:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,繼續
Dialogue: 0,0:33:27.01,0:33:29.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*我唯一的陽光*
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.46,0:33:33.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*你使我快樂*
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.86,0:33:36.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*即使天空陰霾*
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.51,0:33:43.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要被我打攪了  年輕人
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.93,0:33:48.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*你不知道*
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.54,0:33:52.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*親愛的  我有多愛你*
Dialogue: 0,0:33:53.62,0:34:00.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*所以請不要帶走我的陽光*
Dialogue: 0,0:34:03.41,0:34:04.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,唱得不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.94,0:34:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,露西爾也喜歡聽歌
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.68,0:34:11.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這可能是唯一一件  比砸碎腦殼
Dialogue: 0,0:34:11.88,0:34:14.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更讓她喜歡的事了
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.79,0:34:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奇怪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.15,0:34:28.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這首歌是你媽媽唱給你的吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.06,0:34:30.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她現在在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.90,0:34:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.46,0:34:39.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了  是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.60,0:34:44.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你親眼目睹了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.12,0:34:48.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我開槍打死了她
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.58,0:34:51.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在轉化之前...
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.56,0:34:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠  難怪你是個成長中的小連環殺手
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.02,0:35:05.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,順便說  那也是打趣的一個好例子
Dialogue: 0,0:35:12.28,0:35:14.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,來吧孩子  起來
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.18,0:35:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,應該準備好了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.73,0:35:19.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么準備好了
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.10,0:35:22.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,烙鐵
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.29,0:35:45.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幫我拿著
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.47,0:35:54.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們知道規矩
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.36,0:36:00.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,接下來你們要看到的一幕比較難接受
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.31,0:36:02.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也不想這么做
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.63,0:36:06.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望能無視規矩  讓這事過去算了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.41,0:36:07.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可是不行
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.03,0:36:11.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.68,0:36:13.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有規矩才能活命
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.40,0:36:19.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說  得  對
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.68,0:36:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們活了下來
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.84,0:36:26.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們保護他人
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.53,0:36:30.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們讓世界重回文明
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.42,0:36:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們是救世軍
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.62,0:36:40.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但沒有規矩  我們就做不到
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.14,0:36:44.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,規矩是一切運轉的前提
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.22,0:36:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道這很難
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.29,0:36:49.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但總是有工作要做
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.42,0:36:52.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一切都是有代價的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.47,0:36:57.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在這里  如果你想逃避責任
Dialogue: 0,0:36:57.07,0:37:00.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想著偷工減料
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.15,0:37:09.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你就要受烙鐵之刑
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.76,0:37:20.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起立
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.62,0:37:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小德
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.02,0:37:58.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,馬克  抱歉了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.64,0:38:02.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但規矩就是規矩
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.16,0:38:48.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也不是太糟糕  對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.01,0:38:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  他尿褲了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.09,0:39:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,打掃干凈
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.06,0:39:15.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醫生  我完事了  你來吧
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.34,0:39:24.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個孬種暈過去了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.95,0:39:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但事情解決了  我們兩清了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.27,0:39:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:30.38,0:39:33.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就讓馬克的臉每天提醒他
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.87,0:39:38.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,提醒所有人  規矩很重要
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.94,0:39:45.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望大家今天都學到了東西
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.35,0:39:47.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為我再也不想
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.12,0:39:50.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做這種事了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.86,0:40:01.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很瘋狂是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:40:01.40,0:40:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可能會覺得我是個瘋子
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.73,0:40:05.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.42,0:40:08.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓我們想想怎么處置你
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.72,0:41:34.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}拉丁語
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.02,0:42:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想回到這
Dialogue: 0,0:42:13.47,0:42:14.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:22.42,0:42:23.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:42:26.50,0:42:28.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我請你幫我做一顆子彈
Dialogue: 0,0:42:29.95,0:42:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你答應了我
Dialogue: 0,0:42:32.30,0:42:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就給我做一顆子彈
Dialogue: 0,0:42:33.39,0:42:35.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯  我當時是答應了你
Dialogue: 0,0:42:36.19,0:42:37.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但那只是
Dialogue: 0,0:42:38.80,0:42:39.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一時沖動
Dialogue: 0,0:42:40.15,0:42:42.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在中間時刻  我深入思考了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:42.98,0:42:45.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,其他選擇和意外情況
Dialogue: 0,0:42:45.34,0:42:47.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想要復盤找出
Dialogue: 0,0:42:47.06,0:42:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任何開始這項行動的理由
Dialogue: 0,0:42:52.99,0:42:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是想徹底阻止你
Dialogue: 0,0:42:57.12,0:42:58.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是想放慢你的節奏
Dialogue: 0,0:42:59.53,0:43:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許先讓你平靜  營造某種安全感的錯覺
Dialogue: 0,0:43:02.93,0:43:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我不會等了  尤金  -那只是在犯傻
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.85,0:43:08.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蠢貨  你根本不知道自己在說什么
Dialogue: 0,0:43:08.13,0:43:09.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:43:11.21,0:43:13.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我徹底分析了局勢
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.05,0:43:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不管你是偷襲
Dialogue: 0,0:43:15.50,0:43:17.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狙擊  用槍或者用刀
Dialogue: 0,0:43:17.76,0:43:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞伯拉罕是對的  他們人多
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.89,0:43:22.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他占優勢  想要對付他
Dialogue: 0,0:43:22.32,0:43:24.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,除非我們集中人力  有人領導
Dialogue: 0,0:43:24.01,0:43:25.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,集中力量放大招
Dialogue: 0,0:43:26.00,0:43:27.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一顆子彈解決不了任何問題
Dialogue: 0,0:43:27.30,0:43:29.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好的情況下  也許你能打死他
Dialogue: 0,0:43:29.14,0:43:30.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就給我做一顆子彈
Dialogue: 0,0:43:30.68,0:43:32.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人會付出代價的
Dialogue: 0,0:43:34.88,0:43:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即便你情愿奉獻自己
Dialogue: 0,0:43:37.56,0:43:40.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就我們目前所知  犧牲的也不一定會是你
Dialogue: 0,0:43:40.98,0:43:44.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺了我們救命恩人的人該不該死
Dialogue: 0,0:43:44.71,0:43:47.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-也許吧  -那就給我做顆子彈
Dialogue: 0,0:43:47.58,0:43:50.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你勸服不了我  尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:43:50.66,0:43:53.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你欠我的  你也欠他的
Dialogue: 0,0:43:53.20,0:43:55.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果有代價  我來承擔
Dialogue: 0,0:43:55.74,0:43:58.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你不能告訴我不行
Dialogue: 0,0:44:00.72,0:44:02.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么都不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:44:02.16,0:44:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么都不做
Dialogue: 0,0:44:05.71,0:44:07.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是個懦夫
Dialogue: 0,0:44:07.72,0:44:09.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是個弱者
Dialogue: 0,0:44:10.56,0:44:12.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你之所以還活著
Dialogue: 0,0:44:12.19,0:44:15.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因為你撒謊  大家同情你
Dialogue: 0,0:44:21.58,0:44:23.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  這一次
Dialogue: 0,0:44:24.96,0:44:27.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做點有用的事
Dialogue: 0,0:44:30.01,0:44:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,給我做顆子彈
Dialogue: 0,0:45:25.36,0:45:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不要怪自己
Dialogue: 0,0:45:28.32,0:45:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我為什么要怪自己
Dialogue: 0,0:45:30.16,0:45:31.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他
Dialogue: 0,0:45:32.52,0:45:34.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他問了你馬克和安珀的事
Dialogue: 0,0:45:34.88,0:45:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你出賣了他們  對吧
Dialogue: 0,0:45:38.88,0:45:40.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不得不這樣
Dialogue: 0,0:45:42.15,0:45:43.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,并不是這樣的
Dialogue: 0,0:45:50.12,0:45:52.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你晚上能安睡就好
Dialogue: 0,0:46:01.36,0:46:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么睡得著
Dialogue: 0,0:46:02.53,0:46:03.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不睡
Dialogue: 0,0:46:04.87,0:46:07.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看電視直到天明
Dialogue: 0,0:46:12.33,0:46:14.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當我們跟他定下協議時
Dialogue: 0,0:46:14.62,0:46:16.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我們做出的決定
Dialogue: 0,0:46:16.30,0:46:18.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那本該只影響到我們
Dialogue: 0,0:46:18.02,0:46:19.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:46:19.91,0:46:21.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要你還站著
Dialogue: 0,0:46:21.94,0:46:24.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就是站在別人背上
Dialogue: 0,0:46:30.94,0:46:33.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你該走了  會被人看見的
Dialogue: 0,0:46:33.80,0:46:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們沒做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:46:37.11,0:46:39.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對  我們沒做
Dialogue: 0,0:46:52.95,0:46:55.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能遮住臉了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:46:55.56,0:46:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  絕對不行
Dialogue: 0,0:46:57.85,0:46:59.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么不行
Dialogue: 0,0:47:00.93,0:47:03.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧這硬漢
Dialogue: 0,0:47:04.33,0:47:07.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行是因為我還沒玩夠你
Dialogue: 0,0:47:08.18,0:47:10.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡看著你惡心的
Dialogue: 0,0:47:10.28,0:47:13.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,酷酷的  屌屌的眼睛  所以不準遮
Dialogue: 0,0:47:18.53,0:47:19.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么
Dialogue: 0,0:47:19.86,0:47:21.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有話說嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:47:23.33,0:47:24.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你為什么不殺我
Dialogue: 0,0:47:25.39,0:47:27.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或我爸爸  或達里爾
Dialogue: 0,0:47:29.37,0:47:30.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,達里爾
Dialogue: 0,0:47:31.60,0:47:33.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,會成為我的好戰士
Dialogue: 0,0:47:34.61,0:47:37.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他以為自己扛得住
Dialogue: 0,0:47:38.08,0:47:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你看到了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:40.34,0:47:41.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:47:42.10,0:47:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他已經開始給我好東西了
Dialogue: 0,0:47:44.41,0:47:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至于你嘛
Dialogue: 0,0:47:49.36,0:47:53.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走著瞧吧
Dialogue: 0,0:47:54.92,0:47:57.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,擊潰你更有成效
Dialogue: 0,0:47:58.59,0:48:00.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也更有趣
Dialogue: 0,0:48:02.06,0:48:03.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得這很蠢嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:48:03.97,0:48:05.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得我們不同
Dialogue: 0,0:48:10.78,0:48:12.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是個聰明孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:48:13.88,0:48:15.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你認為我該怎么做
Dialogue: 0,0:48:16.04,0:48:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我不能放走你
Dialogue: 0,0:48:19.61,0:48:21.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么  我該殺了你嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:48:22.20,0:48:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,燙你的臉
Dialogue: 0,0:48:24.13,0:48:25.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,砍掉你的胳膊
Dialogue: 0,0:48:26.58,0:48:27.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我
Dialogue: 0,0:48:28.33,0:48:29.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看該怎么辦
Dialogue: 0,0:48:31.53,0:48:32.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看你該跳窗
Dialogue: 0,0:48:32.92,0:48:34.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,省下我殺你的麻煩
Dialogue: 0,0:48:42.27,0:48:46.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這才是那個讓我印象深刻的小子
Dialogue: 0,0:48:48.20,0:48:49.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我認為你不說你要對我做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:48:49.77,0:48:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因為你什么都不會做
Dialogue: 0,0:48:52.37,0:48:55.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你了解我們  如果你了解那些事
Dialogue: 0,0:48:56.00,0:48:57.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會殺了我們的
Dialogue: 0,0:48:58.54,0:48:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是你不能
Dialogue: 0,0:49:04.56,0:49:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許你說得對
Dialogue: 0,0:49:07.18,0:49:08.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許我不能
Dialogue: 0,0:49:14.12,0:49:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們去兜兜風  孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:49:39.11,0:49:40.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,達里爾
Dialogue: 0,0:49:44.64,0:49:47.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看起來很擔心  所以我要帶這孩子回家
Dialogue: 0,0:49:48.17,0:49:49.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你敢對他做任何事
Dialogue: 0,0:49:49.41,0:49:50.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,德懷特
Dialogue: 0,0:49:52.34,0:49:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,達里爾需要靜靜
Dialogue: 0,0:49:53.69,0:49:55.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,讓他進小屋里待待
Dialogue: 0,0:50:58.51,0:51:02.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}趁現在快走
Dialogue: 0,0:52:01.64,0:52:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放下槍
Dialogue: 0,0:52:08.26,0:52:09.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有你的刀
Dialogue: 0,0:52:15.82,0:52:17.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后呢  你要我的鞋嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:52:20.60,0:52:21.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶我去找尼根
Dialogue: 0,0:52:37.88,0:52:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,發動  我們走
Dialogue: 0,0:53:10.48,0:53:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶我...去找尼根
Dialogue: 0,0:53:28.54,0:53:30.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-卡爾  在哪...  -伊妮德沒事
Dialogue: 0,0:53:30.29,0:53:33.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好  很好  很好
Dialogue: 0,0:53:34.52,0:53:35.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:53:35.96,0:53:37.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我
Dialogue: 0,0:53:37.26,0:53:39.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我只是...  -不在乎
Dialogue: 0,0:53:40.13,0:53:41.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克在哪
Dialogue: 0,0:53:43.23,0:53:45.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出去給你找東西了
Dialogue: 0,0:53:46.42,0:53:47.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不錯
Dialogue: 0,0:53:47.63,0:53:48.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會等
Dialogue: 0,0:53:50.26,0:53:53.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他去的地方很遠
Dialogue: 0,0:53:53.26,0:53:55.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們今天也許回不來
Dialogue: 0,0:53:56.40,0:53:58.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們一切物資都很缺
Dialogue: 0,0:53:58.63,0:54:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們差不多要餓死了
Dialogue: 0,0:54:03.20,0:54:04.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,餓死
Dialogue: 0,0:54:06.69,0:54:07.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就你
Dialogue: 0,0:54:08.39,0:54:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"差不多"指的是"還沒有"吧
Dialogue: 0,0:54:23.15,0:54:24.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:54:25.79,0:54:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們這些人真沒幽默感
Dialogue: 0,0:54:35.94,0:54:37.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不好意思
Dialogue: 0,0:54:40.39,0:54:41.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫什么來著
Dialogue: 0,0:54:42.99,0:54:44.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奧利維亞
Dialogue: 0,0:54:45.72,0:54:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對
Dialogue: 0,0:54:47.20,0:54:48.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奧利維亞
Dialogue: 0,0:54:57.72,0:55:02.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉剛才對你無禮
Dialogue: 0,0:55:03.46,0:55:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起來我要在這里待一會兒
Dialogue: 0,0:55:05.59,0:55:08.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等待你們無畏的領袖歸來
Dialogue: 0,0:55:09.36,0:55:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你愿意
Dialogue: 0,0:55:12.45,0:55:14.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得讓我狠狠干你一炮
Dialogue: 0,0:55:15.38,0:55:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定會很享受
Dialogue: 0,0:55:17.60,0:55:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是說  如果你同意的話
Dialogue: 0,0:55:34.19,0:55:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對你的喜歡又增加了50%
Dialogue: 0,0:55:39.98,0:55:41.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是說說
Dialogue: 0,0:55:48.50,0:55:51.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  我要把腳翹起來
Dialogue: 0,0:55:51.10,0:55:53.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等著我的東西抵達這里了
Dialogue: 0,0:55:54.69,0:55:55.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奧利維亞
Dialogue: 0,0:55:56.09,0:55:59.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能做個乖孩子  給我們沖點檸檬水嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:55:59.81,0:56:02.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我給你們留了一些粉類的好東西
Dialogue: 0,0:56:02.63,0:56:04.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我應該要去...
Dialogue: 0,0:56:04.03,0:56:05.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去沖
Dialogue: 0,0:56:09.41,0:56:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去沖
Dialogue: 0,0:56:11.39,0:56:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢慢來
Dialogue: 0,0:56:13.93,0:56:15.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好好沖
Dialogue: 0,0:56:26.53,0:56:27.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:56:28.08,0:56:29.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,帶我參觀吧
Dialogue: 0,0:56:53.48,0:56:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個房間呢
Dialogue: 0,0:56:54.79,0:56:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一個熱水器
Dialogue: 0,0:56:56.25,0:56:57.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是認真的嗎  孩子  拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:57:01.83,0:57:04.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:57:09.32,0:57:12.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看這個小天使
Dialogue: 0,0:57:46.68,0:57:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs12\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}我叫萊斯利·威廉姆·斯坦頓\N我裝備有魯格10/22步槍(槍法神準  可擊中70碼以外目標)\NARS-157(騙你不是人)  AK-47  手榴彈(有種來試試)\N以及多把老式手槍和步槍(來自收藏者和愛好者)\N不聽從第一個告示是愚蠢的做法  你已被警告\N我會毫不猶豫地保護我的家  食物  補給  彈藥\N如果你看到這里還沒中槍  那只可能是我死了\N隨便拿吧  混蛋
Dialogue: 0,0:57:50.95,0:57:53.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這家伙  他有槍
Dialogue: 0,0:57:53.52,0:57:55.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,食物  補給  彈藥
Dialogue: 0,0:58:05.12,0:58:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"如果你看到這里還沒中槍
Dialogue: 0,0:58:07.66,0:58:10.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那只可能是我死了"
Dialogue: 0,0:58:31.91,0:58:34.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起來他保護了自己的補給
Dialogue: 0,0:58:34.87,0:58:36.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看起來補給依然被保護著
Dialogue: 0,0:58:39.83,0:58:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有今天  對嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:58:44.83,0:58:46.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對
Dialogue: 0,0:59:05.00,0:59:06.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,謝謝
Dialogue: 0,0:59:10.23,0:59:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我對我說過的話道歉
Dialogue: 0,0:59:11.50,0:59:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我拒絕接受
Dialogue: 0,0:59:13.08,0:59:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真的很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:59:14.46,0:59:15.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:59:16.81,0:59:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘴上道歉  但心里沒有
Dialogue: 0,0:59:20.69,0:59:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你語氣很真誠  但只是在耍猴
Dialogue: 0,0:59:23.48,0:59:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得到了想要的東西
Dialogue: 0,0:59:24.97,0:59:25.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不過是你感到內疚
Dialogue: 0,0:59:25.97,0:59:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不代表你說的不是真心話
Dialogue: 0,0:59:28.15,0:59:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是真心的  你是那樣想的
Dialogue: 0,0:59:29.61,0:59:30.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是事實
Dialogue: 0,0:59:31.83,0:59:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:59:33.48,0:59:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我現在想回到尷尬的沉默中
Dialogue: 0,0:59:54.90,0:59:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,找到想要的東西了嗎
Dialogue: 0,0:59:56.23,0:59:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算是吧
Dialogue: 0,1:00:00.06,1:00:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是
Dialogue: 0,1:00:07.51,1:00:09.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是從哪里找到的
Dialogue: 0,1:00:13.35,1:00:14.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拉丁語
Dialogue: 0,1:00:14.84,1:00:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是門痛苦難熬的課
Dialogue: 0,1:00:16.76,1:00:20.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我媽媽說那痛苦總有一天會有回報
Dialogue: 0,1:00:20.37,1:00:23.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是一個有計劃的死人的貯藏清單
Dialogue: 0,1:00:23.54,1:00:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我挖出了醫藥用品  凈水器  照明彈
Dialogue: 0,1:00:27.45,1:00:28.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你會全給他們
Dialogue: 0,1:00:30.04,1:00:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是瑞克要我們做的  對吧
Dialogue: 0,1:00:35.52,1:00:36.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我會這樣做
Dialogue: 0,1:00:37.96,1:00:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還會做更多
Dialogue: 0,1:01:03.26,1:01:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們來了
Dialogue: 0,1:01:05.42,1:01:06.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他來了
Dialogue: 0,1:01:10.51,1:01:13.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這小姑娘真可愛
Dialogue: 0,1:01:16.89,1:01:18.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好  鄰居
Dialogue: 0,1:01:19.35,1:01:20.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,晚點過來做客吧
Dialogue: 0,1:01:20.75,1:01:22.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們也許會燒烤
Dialogue: 0,1:01:25.35,1:01:27.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜歡這里
Dialogue: 0,1:01:30.61,1:01:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,說不定我會住下
Dialogue: 0,1:01:35.47,1:01:38.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在想你之前說的話  卡爾
Dialogue: 0,1:01:41.01,1:01:44.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許讓你和你爸爸活著是很愚蠢
Dialogue: 0,1:01:46.39,1:01:48.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我何必這么努力呢
Dialogue: 0,1:01:49.81,1:01:54.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許我應該把你們倆埋在某個花壇里
Dialogue: 0,1:01:59.30,1:02:01.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后自己住在這近郊住宅區里
Dialogue: 0,1:02:01.79,1:02:03.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得怎么樣
