1
00:00:00,220 --> 00:00:03,650
Previously on AMC's The Walking Dead...

2
00:00:05,770 --> 00:00:07,030
You should go.

3
00:00:07,930 --> 00:00:09,910
Before you find out how dangerous we all are.

4
00:00:09,910 --> 00:00:11,240
did you just threaten me?

5
00:00:16,620 --> 00:00:18,570
We're gonna manufacture bullets here.

6
00:00:18,570 --> 00:00:20,090
Per the law of supply and demand,

7
00:00:20,090 --> 00:00:22,310
a full cartridge is now the coin of the land.

8
00:00:22,310 --> 00:00:24,490
Everything we have, we got from fighting.

9
00:00:24,490 --> 00:00:28,320
We play by their rules, and we get some kind of life.

10
00:00:28,320 --> 00:00:29,900
What kind of a life?

17
00:02:57,750 --> 00:02:58,650
What time is it?

18
00:03:02,040 --> 00:03:03,730
Just past 5:30.

19
00:03:06,360 --> 00:03:07,250
Let's go.

20
00:03:30,280 --> 00:03:31,560
Didn't see that last night.

21
00:03:33,560 --> 00:03:34,800
Didn't see what?

22
00:03:42,030 --> 00:03:43,270
Still going.

23
00:03:45,200 --> 00:03:46,720
Looks like the end of them, though.

24
00:03:47,400 --> 00:03:49,680
All damn night.

25
00:03:50,490 --> 00:03:51,640
At least Negan's smart enough

26
00:03:51,640 --> 00:03:53,730
not to let that mess anywhere near us.

27
00:03:54,610 --> 00:03:56,750
Fat Joey's good for something, at least.

28
00:03:57,410 --> 00:03:58,660
What, eating cake?

29
00:04:00,400 --> 00:04:02,080
He rigged the herdway.

30
00:04:02,140 --> 00:04:03,320
Just trips.

31
00:04:03,560 --> 00:04:04,900
Nothing fancy.

32
00:04:05,360 --> 00:04:06,910
Guerilla kind of stuff.

33
00:04:08,580 --> 00:04:09,660
What kind of stuff?

34
00:04:10,680 --> 00:04:12,660
As in warfare, idiot.

35
00:04:13,120 --> 00:04:15,830
Those demo sticks from that run last month,

36
00:04:15,870 --> 00:04:18,150
the RPGs from the new guys.

37
00:04:19,890 --> 00:04:21,370
Maybe it takes it down.

38
00:04:22,450 --> 00:04:23,520
Takes them out.

39
00:04:26,090 --> 00:04:27,180
All right, it's a trickle.

40
00:04:27,180 --> 00:04:29,440
- Let's go. - Finally.

41
00:04:29,810 --> 00:04:30,940
Thank Christ.

42
00:05:34,080 --> 00:05:35,120
Making a trail.

43
00:05:37,280 --> 00:05:38,430
I think we're close.

44
00:05:46,160 --> 00:05:48,610
We should bail out, follow the rest of the way,

45
00:05:49,210 --> 00:05:50,280
see what we can see.

46
00:05:50,540 --> 00:05:52,020
I, uh...

47
00:05:52,040 --> 00:05:52,760
How?

48
00:05:53,670 --> 00:05:55,590
It isn't usually the fall that gets us.

49
00:05:56,200 --> 00:05:59,120
It's trying to fight it. Run with it or roll with it.

50
00:05:59,120 --> 00:06:00,780
The truck's going slow enough.

51
00:06:01,310 --> 00:06:02,140
We'll be in the blind spot.

52
00:06:02,140 --> 00:06:03,230
We can race behind one of the other cars.

53
00:06:03,230 --> 00:06:04,660
I-I-If -- If I screw up and we get caught --

54
00:06:04,660 --> 00:06:07,380
It'll be fine. We just got to go now.

55
00:06:08,960 --> 00:06:10,360
Okay. Show me first.

56
00:06:28,190 --> 00:06:29,810
"Show me first"...

57
00:06:54,610 --> 00:06:57,840
Okay, boys, let's get this haul unloaded and inside.

58
00:06:57,840 --> 00:07:00,560
I want to get back in there and unload a little myself.

59
00:07:00,560 --> 00:07:02,850
Negan, need to talk to you about redirect.

60
00:07:03,810 --> 00:07:05,100
What about the redirect?

61
00:07:05,100 --> 00:07:06,100
It got screwed up.

62
00:07:06,170 --> 00:07:07,970
We're on it now, but it's a mess out there.

63
00:07:07,970 --> 00:07:10,020
And whose job was that?

64
00:07:10,020 --> 00:07:11,130
...A pack and a tent...

65
00:07:11,780 --> 00:07:13,370
Aw, damn.

66
00:07:13,370 --> 00:07:15,100
I thought they packed this up tight.

67
00:07:15,200 --> 00:07:16,220
Ah, no worries.

68
00:07:16,310 --> 00:07:17,700
Plenty more where this came from.

69
00:07:17,700 --> 00:07:18,290
Right?

70
00:07:22,960 --> 00:07:24,470
Son of a bitch!

71
00:07:25,530 --> 00:07:26,350
What the hell?

72
00:07:30,220 --> 00:07:32,520
Stay back! Drop your weapons.

73
00:07:35,760 --> 00:07:36,830
I only want Negan.

74
00:07:37,810 --> 00:07:39,370
He killed my friends.

75
00:07:40,140 --> 00:07:41,500
No one else needs to die.

76
00:07:49,440 --> 00:07:50,340
Damn.

77
00:07:54,120 --> 00:07:57,150
You are adorable.

78
00:07:58,970 --> 00:08:01,810
Did you pick that gun 'cause it looks cool?

79
00:08:02,530 --> 00:08:04,360
You totally did, right?

80
00:08:05,720 --> 00:08:07,690
Kid, I ain't gonna lie --

81
00:08:07,690 --> 00:08:10,570
you scare the shit outta me.

82
00:08:16,750 --> 00:08:17,490
Kid!

83
00:08:18,480 --> 00:08:19,260
Dwight.

84
00:08:20,680 --> 00:08:21,780
Back off.

85
00:08:31,050 --> 00:08:33,790
Is that any way to treat our new guest?

86
00:08:36,370 --> 00:08:37,390
Come on, kid.

87
00:08:38,020 --> 00:08:39,950
I will show you around.

89
00:10:01,750 --> 00:10:02,820
Come on, kid.

90
00:10:03,130 --> 00:10:04,370
I'll show you around.

91
00:10:06,160 --> 00:10:09,580
You know, you do the same damn stink-eye as your dad,

92
00:10:09,580 --> 00:10:12,120
except it's only half as good 'cause...

93
00:10:12,460 --> 00:10:14,120
well, you know, you're...

94
00:10:14,290 --> 00:10:15,650
missing an eye.

95
00:10:19,230 --> 00:10:20,030
Really?

96
00:10:20,920 --> 00:10:23,410
You're really not gonna take my hand?

97
00:10:23,580 --> 00:10:26,760
'Cause you're lucky you even still have a hand.

98
00:10:28,580 --> 00:10:30,600
Same as your boy Daryl over here,

99
00:10:30,610 --> 00:10:32,230
now that I think about it.

100
00:10:32,950 --> 00:10:34,740
How's the job going, Daryl?

101
00:10:35,490 --> 00:10:36,850
Hot enough for you?

102
00:10:37,650 --> 00:10:40,030
Yeah, it'd be tough with one arm.

103
00:10:48,520 --> 00:10:50,300
Ah, smart kid.

104
00:10:51,020 --> 00:10:52,450
Now come with me.

105
00:10:53,390 --> 00:10:55,860
Dwighty-boy, why don't you grab Daryl,

106
00:10:55,860 --> 00:10:58,500
take him to the kitchen, do a little grub prep.

107
00:10:59,460 --> 00:11:00,290
New plan, boys.

108
00:11:00,290 --> 00:11:02,860
Let's burn the dead, unload the truck later.

109
00:11:03,160 --> 00:11:04,990
Damn, I am not gonna have time

110
00:11:04,990 --> 00:11:07,110
to screw any of my wives today.

111
00:11:09,790 --> 00:11:11,290
I mean, maybe one.

112
00:11:16,290 --> 00:11:17,020
Come on.

113
00:11:17,960 --> 00:11:19,170
What are you gonna do to me?

114
00:11:27,590 --> 00:11:28,610
Number one,

115
00:11:29,500 --> 00:11:32,060
do not shatter my image of you.

116
00:11:32,060 --> 00:11:34,610
You're a badass. You're not scared of shit.

117
00:11:34,610 --> 00:11:37,020
Don't be scared of me. It's a disappointment.

118
00:11:37,380 --> 00:11:38,450
Number two...

119
00:11:39,570 --> 00:11:42,150
you really want me to ruin the surprise?

120
00:11:44,300 --> 00:11:45,850
Screw you, kid.

121
00:11:46,930 --> 00:11:47,850
Seriously.

122
00:11:48,980 --> 00:11:50,870
Screw you.

124
00:12:04,140 --> 00:12:05,310
Check this out.

125
00:12:18,610 --> 00:12:20,830
The Saviors have gone out into the world

126
00:12:20,830 --> 00:12:22,290
and fought the dead

127
00:12:22,290 --> 00:12:26,230
and come back with some really good stuff.

128
00:12:26,410 --> 00:12:30,060
Some of that stuff can be yours

129
00:12:30,060 --> 00:12:35,000
if you work hard and play by the rules.

130
00:12:36,240 --> 00:12:41,230
Today, everybody gets fresh vegetables at dinner.

131
00:12:41,230 --> 00:12:43,630
No points needed.

132
00:12:48,710 --> 00:12:49,680
You see that?

133
00:12:50,920 --> 00:12:52,410
Respect.

134
00:12:53,940 --> 00:12:55,350
Cool, huh?

135
00:12:56,470 --> 00:12:58,280
They still on their knees?

136
00:12:59,480 --> 00:13:00,690
As you were!

137
00:13:07,490 --> 00:13:09,410
Hey, I wanted to show you a few potentials

138
00:13:09,410 --> 00:13:11,110
I've rated B-plus or higher.

139
00:13:11,110 --> 00:13:12,490
I know where we're going.

140
00:13:12,660 --> 00:13:14,700
While I'm picking up a high level of certainty,

141
00:13:14,700 --> 00:13:16,130
I'd be remiss if I didn't mention

142
00:13:16,130 --> 00:13:18,480
that after a thorough analysis of the grid,

143
00:13:18,480 --> 00:13:20,570
X'ing out any places we've already combed,

144
00:13:20,580 --> 00:13:21,810
I do believe I've bull's-eye'd

145
00:13:21,810 --> 00:13:24,500
some worth considering for the specific task at hand.

146
00:13:24,500 --> 00:13:25,280
What?

147
00:13:27,110 --> 00:13:28,570
Finding goods for Negan.

148
00:13:28,870 --> 00:13:31,000
No, we're not doing shit for that cabron.

149
00:13:34,380 --> 00:13:36,560
You're not going out to find stuff for the Saviors?

150
00:13:38,380 --> 00:13:39,210
Why not?

151
00:13:41,820 --> 00:13:43,340
There's no fighting it, Rosita.

152
00:13:45,190 --> 00:13:47,050
Perhaps we should all travel together.

153
00:13:47,100 --> 00:13:48,000
I'm down.

154
00:13:48,770 --> 00:13:51,710
We come across a haystack, four POVs could draw out whatever we're looking for.

155
00:13:51,710 --> 00:13:52,970
We're fine on our own.

156
00:13:53,960 --> 00:13:55,350
I know you don't like it

157
00:13:55,350 --> 00:13:56,330
and you don't want to hear it from me,

158
00:13:56,330 --> 00:13:58,420
but we got to produce for them.

159
00:13:59,440 --> 00:14:00,920
This is like taxes.

160
00:14:01,660 --> 00:14:02,900
- Hey. - Come here.

161
00:14:02,900 --> 00:14:03,620
Hey.

162
00:14:05,700 --> 00:14:06,840
You can keep acting pissed at me,

163
00:14:06,840 --> 00:14:08,250
but I didn't do this.

164
00:14:08,650 --> 00:14:09,520
Rick did.

165
00:14:12,000 --> 00:14:13,480
You think you can do better.

166
00:14:14,370 --> 00:14:15,140
Yes.

167
00:14:16,780 --> 00:14:17,670
Sure.

168
00:14:18,830 --> 00:14:21,550
No, I bet you already have a whole truck-load full of stuff

169
00:14:21,550 --> 00:14:23,200
hidden out there for yourself, huh?

170
00:14:24,790 --> 00:14:25,760
Go get it.

171
00:14:26,310 --> 00:14:30,020
Pay your taxes, and leave me the hell alone.

172
00:14:33,250 --> 00:14:33,950
Let's go.

173
00:14:49,750 --> 00:14:50,790
Ladies.

174
00:14:52,550 --> 00:14:53,740
Don't mind the kid.

175
00:14:57,190 --> 00:14:58,170
I know.

176
00:14:59,260 --> 00:15:00,550
Every woman where you're from

177
00:15:00,550 --> 00:15:03,180
dresses like they do the books at an auto shop.

178
00:15:03,640 --> 00:15:05,960
You're gonna want to look at their titties.

179
00:15:07,160 --> 00:15:08,870
It's cool. I won't mind.

180
00:15:08,870 --> 00:15:11,240
They won't mind. Knock yourself out.

181
00:15:18,410 --> 00:15:21,930
Can I talk to you for a minute, dear wife?

182
00:15:26,780 --> 00:15:28,850
Make yourself comfortable, kid.

183
00:15:50,060 --> 00:15:52,470
What happened with Amber and Mark?

184
00:15:52,470 --> 00:15:54,350
What we talk about when you're not here

185
00:15:54,350 --> 00:15:56,420
is none of your business.

186
00:15:58,730 --> 00:16:00,030
Fair play.

187
00:16:06,860 --> 00:16:08,320
You want to know what I heard?

188
00:16:10,690 --> 00:16:13,790
I heard that Mark skipped out on redirect duty

189
00:16:13,790 --> 00:16:15,250
to be with Amber.

190
00:16:16,450 --> 00:16:18,660
I need to know if it's true.

191
00:16:25,810 --> 00:16:28,040
There are rules for a reason.

192
00:16:28,950 --> 00:16:30,750
Nothing matters if you're dead.

193
00:16:31,520 --> 00:16:36,780
You, my dear, are here because you get that.

194
00:16:43,730 --> 00:16:45,360
She made a mistake.

195
00:16:46,380 --> 00:16:47,680
Go easy on her.

196
00:16:47,680 --> 00:16:49,600
Calm the hell down.

197
00:16:55,580 --> 00:16:57,200
I ever hit one of you?

198
00:16:58,740 --> 00:16:59,560
No.

199
00:17:01,130 --> 00:17:02,510
But I know you.

200
00:17:03,480 --> 00:17:04,920
There's worse.

201
00:17:15,130 --> 00:17:17,980
Well, look at you!

202
00:17:22,510 --> 00:17:24,080
To be continued.

203
00:17:55,750 --> 00:17:58,300
Amber, baby.

204
00:17:59,860 --> 00:18:01,960
You know I don't want anyone here

205
00:18:01,960 --> 00:18:03,970
that doesn't want to be here, right?

206
00:18:07,970 --> 00:18:09,560
So if you want to leave

207
00:18:09,560 --> 00:18:11,170
and go back to Mark...

208
00:18:12,040 --> 00:18:13,140
you can.

209
00:18:14,840 --> 00:18:16,760
But what can't you do?

210
00:18:19,580 --> 00:18:20,310
Cheat on you.

211
00:18:20,310 --> 00:18:23,270
That is exactly right.

212
00:18:23,970 --> 00:18:25,900
You can't...

213
00:18:28,320 --> 00:18:29,580
cheat on me.

214
00:18:34,590 --> 00:18:37,080
There's plenty of other gals who would love to take your place,

215
00:18:37,080 --> 00:18:40,560
and there's a few job openings that I can think of.

216
00:18:41,900 --> 00:18:44,670
You want to go back to Mark and your mom?

217
00:18:45,590 --> 00:18:48,740
Hell, I'll put you all on the same job.

218
00:18:49,080 --> 00:18:49,920
No.

219
00:18:50,200 --> 00:18:51,200
I --

220
00:18:51,260 --> 00:18:52,420
I'll stay.

221
00:18:52,420 --> 00:18:54,880
I'm...I'm sorry.

222
00:18:57,020 --> 00:18:58,990
You know what that means, right?

223
00:19:00,290 --> 00:19:04,000
You know what that means, right?

224
00:19:06,080 --> 00:19:08,700
Ye-- Yes.

225
00:19:10,870 --> 00:19:12,260
I love you, Negan.

226
00:19:12,260 --> 00:19:16,510
Oh, of course you do, darlin'.

227
00:19:19,520 --> 00:19:21,150
I don't know why you're crying.

228
00:19:22,590 --> 00:19:25,110
It's all gonna work out aces for you.

229
00:19:51,210 --> 00:19:53,060
Will you get Carson for me?

230
00:19:55,170 --> 00:19:57,270
- Yeah. - Did you see that?

231
00:19:57,760 --> 00:19:59,050
Wasn't hard on her,

232
00:19:59,050 --> 00:20:03,270
even though I am... very hard in general.

233
00:20:04,060 --> 00:20:05,170
You're an asshole.

234
00:20:05,170 --> 00:20:06,590
I know.

235
00:20:06,800 --> 00:20:10,360
But the messed-up thing is, you like me anyway.

236
00:20:11,390 --> 00:20:14,520
You know the truth, just like me.

237
00:20:56,240 --> 00:20:58,910
Carl, will you grab this tray for me?

238
00:21:04,460 --> 00:21:06,610
Why do you got him here?

239
00:21:08,560 --> 00:21:11,640
What we talk about when you're not here...

240
00:21:13,030 --> 00:21:14,890
is none of your business.

241
00:21:20,520 --> 00:21:23,240
Do not make me put this toothpick

242
00:21:23,240 --> 00:21:26,380
through the only eye he has.

243
00:21:27,720 --> 00:21:29,020
You go with Dwight.

244
00:21:29,620 --> 00:21:31,120
He'll get you a mop.

245
00:21:31,540 --> 00:21:32,640
Dwighty boy...

246
00:21:33,420 --> 00:21:35,510
fire up that furnace.

247
00:21:35,850 --> 00:21:37,410
I'll be down in a few.

248
00:21:37,410 --> 00:21:39,690
Time for a little deja vu.

249
00:21:41,340 --> 00:21:42,660
Come on, kid.

250
00:22:17,480 --> 00:22:20,850
We have today and only today to find somethin'.

251
00:22:21,530 --> 00:22:23,270
They could be back by tomorrow.

252
00:22:24,800 --> 00:22:26,030
Could be back now.

254
00:22:51,080 --> 00:22:53,390
Hating somebody -- is that a sin?

255
00:22:55,420 --> 00:22:56,380
No.

256
00:22:57,620 --> 00:22:59,580
Well, not necessarily.

257
00:23:00,280 --> 00:23:02,040
Thoughts are just thoughts.

258
00:23:02,580 --> 00:23:04,950
It's our actions that matter in the end.

259
00:23:15,300 --> 00:23:16,660
I hate Rick.

260
00:23:18,650 --> 00:23:21,150
He was a cop. Fine.

261
00:23:21,440 --> 00:23:23,060
He shouldn't be in charge.

262
00:23:23,800 --> 00:23:27,990
My mother, she -- she served in Congress.

263
00:23:27,990 --> 00:23:29,370
She led people.

264
00:23:29,370 --> 00:23:31,120
She brought out the good in people.

265
00:23:31,310 --> 00:23:33,280
Rick brought out the good in me.

266
00:23:34,910 --> 00:23:37,100
How? By bullying you?

267
00:23:41,280 --> 00:23:42,220
A little.

268
00:23:43,830 --> 00:23:46,320
But mostly by inspiring me.

269
00:23:47,920 --> 00:23:49,480
He didn't just keep people alive.

270
00:23:49,480 --> 00:23:51,240
He brought us all together.

271
00:23:52,280 --> 00:23:55,190
He's not perfect, but he's a man who finds his way.

272
00:23:55,190 --> 00:23:58,200
He didn't keep everybody alive, Gabriel.

273
00:23:58,440 --> 00:24:00,550
My mother, my father, my brother...

274
00:24:00,550 --> 00:24:02,050
It wasn't his fault.

275
00:24:02,660 --> 00:24:05,210
He got here, they died.

276
00:24:06,030 --> 00:24:09,350
Or maybe other people didn't die because he got here.

277
00:24:09,790 --> 00:24:12,000
Or maybe we shouldn't have attacked that outpost

278
00:24:12,000 --> 00:24:13,420
- and then Glenn... - We don't know! 

279
00:24:16,240 --> 00:24:17,280
We can't.

280
00:24:19,020 --> 00:24:20,240
We don't get to.

281
00:24:23,300 --> 00:24:24,600
We're here now...

282
00:24:25,380 --> 00:24:27,310
and we can look to the future.

283
00:24:30,160 --> 00:24:31,280
What future?

284
00:24:32,220 --> 00:24:34,230
There's no future with him in charge.

285
00:24:36,740 --> 00:24:39,030
The thing I can't stop thinking is that...

286
00:24:40,260 --> 00:24:42,870
maybe the only good thing that could happen for us now...

287
00:24:44,780 --> 00:24:46,570
is he never makes it back.

288
00:24:51,630 --> 00:24:52,810
Stop the car.

289
00:25:08,130 --> 00:25:09,800
What you're saying --

290
00:25:10,490 --> 00:25:12,570
it doesn't make you a sinner.

291
00:25:14,270 --> 00:25:17,000
But it does make you a tremendous shit.

292
00:25:18,870 --> 00:25:19,990
Just for now.

293
00:25:22,310 --> 00:25:24,180
It doesn't have to be terminal.

294
00:25:33,770 --> 00:25:35,160
I'm gonna go back.

295
00:27:05,510 --> 00:27:07,650
Are all of those women actually your --

296
00:27:07,650 --> 00:27:10,130
Wives? Yeah.

297
00:27:10,520 --> 00:27:12,400
Always wanted to screw a whole bunch of different women.

298
00:27:12,400 --> 00:27:14,360
I mean, why settle for just one?

299
00:27:14,360 --> 00:27:17,240
Why follow the same old rules?

300
00:27:17,240 --> 00:27:19,200
Why not make life better?

301
00:27:20,180 --> 00:27:21,790
Speaking of...

302
00:27:23,070 --> 00:27:24,050
sit.

303
00:27:27,240 --> 00:27:28,590
Let's get started.

304
00:27:29,660 --> 00:27:30,910
Started on what?

305
00:27:33,460 --> 00:27:36,660
I want to get to know you a little better, Carl.

306
00:27:37,460 --> 00:27:38,360
Why?

307
00:27:39,570 --> 00:27:40,790
Work it out.

308
00:27:41,110 --> 00:27:42,440
You're smart.

309
00:27:42,790 --> 00:27:44,920
In fact, I'm gonna tell you just how smart you are,

310
00:27:44,930 --> 00:27:46,910
in case you don't already know.

311
00:27:47,600 --> 00:27:51,520
See, I'd expect a kid your age to be moping around,

312
00:27:51,520 --> 00:27:53,000
not doing a damn thing,

313
00:27:53,000 --> 00:27:56,030
except crying about missing the prom.

314
00:27:56,930 --> 00:28:00,880
But you -- you go on a mission.

315
00:28:01,370 --> 00:28:04,340
You find me, you kill two of my men,

316
00:28:04,340 --> 00:28:09,650
and you're smart enough to know that I'm not gonna let this slide.

317
00:28:15,910 --> 00:28:18,970
I can't -- I can't do it.

318
00:28:19,320 --> 00:28:22,160
It's like talking to a birthday present.

319
00:28:22,500 --> 00:28:23,980
You got to take that crap off your face.

320
00:28:23,980 --> 00:28:26,180
I want to see what Grandma got me.

321
00:28:28,120 --> 00:28:29,800
- No. - Two men!

322
00:28:32,440 --> 00:28:34,790
Two...men.

323
00:28:36,020 --> 00:28:37,340
Punishment.

324
00:28:39,640 --> 00:28:42,730
Do you really want to piss me off?

325
00:29:11,750 --> 00:29:13,190
Almost there.

326
00:29:20,960 --> 00:29:22,520
Get that hair out of your face.

327
00:29:22,520 --> 00:29:23,710
Let me see.

328
00:29:29,100 --> 00:29:30,780
Christ!

329
00:29:31,260 --> 00:29:32,890
That is disgusting.

330
00:29:32,890 --> 00:29:34,690
No wonder you cover that up.

331
00:29:34,950 --> 00:29:36,360
Have you seen it?

332
00:29:36,620 --> 00:29:38,290
I mean, have you looked in the mirror?

333
00:29:38,290 --> 00:29:41,030
That is gross as hell.

334
00:29:41,400 --> 00:29:43,610
I can see your socket.

335
00:29:45,370 --> 00:29:46,740
I want to touch it.

336
00:29:47,220 --> 00:29:49,230
Oh, come on. Can I touch it?

337
00:30:00,640 --> 00:30:01,750
Damn.

338
00:30:05,480 --> 00:30:07,550
Holy hell, kid.

339
00:30:08,780 --> 00:30:09,850
Look...

340
00:30:13,210 --> 00:30:14,200
I just --

341
00:30:14,630 --> 00:30:17,080
It's easy to forget that you're...

342
00:30:18,480 --> 00:30:19,710
just a kid.

343
00:30:20,660 --> 00:30:23,920
And I didn't mean to hurt your feelings or anything. I --

344
00:30:26,030 --> 00:30:28,370
- I was just screwing around. - Just forget it.

345
00:30:35,310 --> 00:30:36,330
Come in.

346
00:30:37,370 --> 00:30:39,770
I'm sorry to interrupt, sir, but, uh...

347
00:30:40,480 --> 00:30:42,960
you left Lucille out by the truck.

348
00:30:43,320 --> 00:30:44,440
Seriously?

349
00:30:46,210 --> 00:30:47,330
I never do that.

350
00:30:47,330 --> 00:30:49,610
I guess a kid firing a machine gun

351
00:30:49,610 --> 00:30:51,750
is a little bit of a distraction.

352
00:30:54,250 --> 00:30:59,230
All jokes aside, you look rad as hell.

353
00:30:59,560 --> 00:31:01,460
I wouldn't cover that shit up.

354
00:31:01,460 --> 00:31:03,820
It may not be a hit with the ladies,

355
00:31:04,120 --> 00:31:05,470
but I swear to you,

356
00:31:05,470 --> 00:31:08,940
no one is gonna screw with you looking like that.

357
00:31:08,940 --> 00:31:10,210
No, sir.

358
00:31:14,720 --> 00:31:19,030
Fat Joseph, did you carry her all the way up here for me?

359
00:31:19,040 --> 00:31:20,020
Yes, sir.

360
00:31:27,800 --> 00:31:29,130
Were you gentle?

361
00:31:29,220 --> 00:31:30,480
Were you kind?

362
00:31:33,010 --> 00:31:35,140
Did you treat her like a lady?

363
00:31:35,910 --> 00:31:38,550
Mm, yes. Yes, sir.

364
00:31:40,590 --> 00:31:42,810
Did you pet her little pussy like a lady?

365
00:31:48,000 --> 00:31:49,250
I'm just screwing around, man.

366
00:31:49,250 --> 00:31:51,480
A baseball bat doesn't have a pussy.

367
00:31:55,010 --> 00:31:56,230
Get the hell out.

368
00:32:01,210 --> 00:32:02,690
Now, you see?

369
00:32:03,800 --> 00:32:05,680
That's what I'm talking about.

370
00:32:05,690 --> 00:32:08,340
Men breaking each other's balls.

371
00:32:08,710 --> 00:32:11,720
This is the shit your dad's supposed to be teaching you.

372
00:32:18,200 --> 00:32:19,870
What do you like to do for fun?

373
00:32:21,080 --> 00:32:22,340
You like music?

374
00:32:28,440 --> 00:32:30,660
I want you to sing me a song.

375
00:32:32,660 --> 00:32:33,610
What?

376
00:32:33,850 --> 00:32:34,770
Yeah.

377
00:32:35,120 --> 00:32:37,650
You mowed down two of my men with a machine gun.

378
00:32:37,650 --> 00:32:41,130
I want something in return for that.

379
00:32:42,350 --> 00:32:45,360
- Sing me a song. - I...

380
00:32:47,240 --> 00:32:50,590
- I -- I can't think of any. - Bullshit!

381
00:32:51,080 --> 00:32:53,210
What'd your mom used to sing you?

382
00:32:54,460 --> 00:32:56,660
What'd your dad play in the car?

383
00:33:06,710 --> 00:33:10,040
- Start singing. - Okay, okay.

384
00:33:10,490 --> 00:33:11,500
Okay.

385
00:33:21,200 --> 00:33:25,270
*You are my sunshine*

386
00:33:25,600 --> 00:33:26,200
Go on.

387
00:33:27,010 --> 00:33:29,240
*My only sunshine* 

388
00:33:30,460 --> 00:33:33,280
*You make me happy*

389
00:33:33,860 --> 00:33:36,230
*When skies are gray*

390
00:33:39,510 --> 00:33:43,480
Do not let me distract you, young man.

391
00:33:44,930 --> 00:33:48,290
*You'll...Never know...* 

392
00:33:48,540 --> 00:33:52,690
*Dear, how much I love you*

393
00:33:53,620 --> 00:34:00,290
*So...please don't take my...sunshine away*

394
00:34:03,410 --> 00:34:04,780
That's pretty good.

395
00:34:05,940 --> 00:34:08,540
Lucille loves being sung to.

396
00:34:09,680 --> 00:34:11,880
It's about the only thing she loves more

397
00:34:11,880 --> 00:34:14,460
than bashing in brains.

398
00:34:14,790 --> 00:34:16,090
Weird, huh?

399
00:34:26,150 --> 00:34:28,010
Did your mother sing that to you?

400
00:34:29,060 --> 00:34:30,370
Where is she now?

401
00:34:35,900 --> 00:34:36,920
Damn.

402
00:34:38,460 --> 00:34:39,650
Dead, huh?

403
00:34:43,600 --> 00:34:44,990
You see it happen?

404
00:34:47,120 --> 00:34:48,190
I shot her...

405
00:34:50,580 --> 00:34:51,990
before it could...

406
00:34:55,560 --> 00:34:59,230
Damn, no wonder you're a little serial killer in the making.

407
00:35:02,020 --> 00:35:05,300
That was an example of breaking balls, by the way.

408
00:35:12,280 --> 00:35:14,600
Come on, kid. Get up.

409
00:35:15,180 --> 00:35:16,650
It should be ready.

410
00:35:17,730 --> 00:35:19,090
What should be ready?

411
00:35:21,100 --> 00:35:22,400
The iron.

412
00:35:44,290 --> 00:35:45,970
Hold that for me.

413
00:35:53,470 --> 00:35:54,820
You know the deal.

414
00:35:56,360 --> 00:36:00,260
What's about to happen is gonna be hard to watch.

415
00:36:01,310 --> 00:36:02,740
I don't want to do it.

416
00:36:03,630 --> 00:36:06,410
I wish I could just ignore the rules and let it slide,

417
00:36:06,410 --> 00:36:07,830
but I can't.

418
00:36:10,030 --> 00:36:11,170
Why?

419
00:36:11,680 --> 00:36:13,990
The rules keep us alive.

420
00:36:15,400 --> 00:36:19,210
That...is...right.

421
00:36:21,680 --> 00:36:23,130
We survive.

422
00:36:23,840 --> 00:36:26,530
We provide security to others.

423
00:36:26,530 --> 00:36:30,440
We bring civilization back to this world.

424
00:36:31,420 --> 00:36:34,850
We are the Saviors.

425
00:36:37,620 --> 00:36:40,140
But we can't do that without rules.

426
00:36:40,140 --> 00:36:44,180
Rules are what make it all work.

427
00:36:45,220 --> 00:36:47,330
I know it's not easy.

428
00:36:48,290 --> 00:36:49,420
But there's always work.

429
00:36:49,420 --> 00:36:52,590
There is always a cost.

430
00:36:53,470 --> 00:36:57,070
Here, if you try to skirt it, 

431
00:36:57,070 --> 00:37:00,200
if you try to cut that corner...

432
00:37:07,150 --> 00:37:09,770
...then it is the iron for you.

433
00:37:18,760 --> 00:37:20,150
On your feet.

434
00:37:34,620 --> 00:37:35,700
D...

435
00:37:55,020 --> 00:37:58,490
Mark...I'm sorry.

436
00:37:59,640 --> 00:38:02,540
But it is what it is.

437
00:38:45,160 --> 00:38:48,030
Ah, that wasn't so bad, now, was it?

438
00:38:53,010 --> 00:38:56,170
Jesus. He pissed himself.

439
00:39:05,090 --> 00:39:06,290
Clean that up.

440
00:39:12,060 --> 00:39:15,620
Doc, I'm all done. Do your thing.

441
00:39:21,340 --> 00:39:24,340
Well, the pussy passed out.

442
00:39:25,950 --> 00:39:27,270
But it's settled -- we're square.

443
00:39:27,270 --> 00:39:29,800
Everything is cool.

444
00:39:30,380 --> 00:39:33,870
Let Mark's face be a daily reminder to him

445
00:39:33,870 --> 00:39:38,400
and to everyone else that the rules matter.

446
00:39:41,940 --> 00:39:45,350
I hope that we all learned something today,

447
00:39:45,350 --> 00:39:47,260
because I don't ever... 

448
00:39:48,120 --> 00:39:50,320
want to have to do that again.

449
00:39:58,860 --> 00:40:01,290
Some crazy shit, huh?

450
00:40:01,400 --> 00:40:03,910
You probably think I'm a lunatic.

451
00:40:04,730 --> 00:40:05,420
Come on.

452
00:40:05,420 --> 00:40:08,070
Let's go figure out what to do with you.

454
00:42:12,020 --> 00:42:13,470
I didn't want to come back here.

455
00:42:13,470 --> 00:42:14,530
I don't...

456
00:42:22,420 --> 00:42:23,650
No.

457
00:42:26,500 --> 00:42:28,460
I asked you to make me a bullet.

458
00:42:29,950 --> 00:42:31,510
You said yes.

459
00:42:32,300 --> 00:42:33,390
So make me a bullet.

460
00:42:33,390 --> 00:42:35,010
You're right. I said yes.

461
00:42:36,190 --> 00:42:37,530
But that...

462
00:42:38,800 --> 00:42:39,970
was peak heat of the moment.

463
00:42:40,150 --> 00:42:42,980
Uh, in the intervening hours, I've been taking a deep dive

464
00:42:42,980 --> 00:42:45,160
into other options and contingencies,

465
00:42:45,340 --> 00:42:47,060
trying to game out any iteration

466
00:42:47,060 --> 00:42:50,440
in which charging into this enterprise makes any sense.

467
00:42:52,990 --> 00:42:55,750
I'm not trying to definitively stop ya.

468
00:42:57,120 --> 00:42:58,900
Just maybe slow your roll.

469
00:42:59,530 --> 00:43:02,930
Maybe go on for some lullin', false sense of security-wise.

470
00:43:02,930 --> 00:43:05,850
- I'm not waiting, Eugene. -That's just being stupid.

471
00:43:05,850 --> 00:43:08,130
Pendejo, you don't know what the hell you're talking about.

472
00:43:08,130 --> 00:43:09,410
I think I do.

473
00:43:11,210 --> 00:43:13,160
I've analyzed this top to bottom.

474
00:43:14,050 --> 00:43:15,500
It doesn't matter if you're stealthy,

475
00:43:15,500 --> 00:43:17,160
snipey, gun, or knifey.

476
00:43:17,760 --> 00:43:20,100
Abraham was right -- they have the numbers.

477
00:43:20,890 --> 00:43:22,320
His ballgame, unless we put together

478
00:43:22,320 --> 00:43:24,010
a finishing move for a force of many,

479
00:43:24,010 --> 00:43:25,750
along with the man in charge.

480
00:43:26,000 --> 00:43:27,300
A single bullet ain't gonna do it.

481
00:43:27,300 --> 00:43:29,140
Best case, maybe you take him out.

482
00:43:29,140 --> 00:43:30,680
Then make me a bullet.

483
00:43:30,680 --> 00:43:32,450
Somebody has to pay the price.

484
00:43:34,880 --> 00:43:36,390
Even if you're willing...

485
00:43:37,560 --> 00:43:40,180
from all we've seen, it's not a lock you'll be the one.

486
00:43:40,980 --> 00:43:44,390
Will the man who killed the man who saved our lives die?

487
00:43:44,710 --> 00:43:47,580
- Maybe. - Then make me a bullet.

488
00:43:47,580 --> 00:43:50,310
You're not talking me out of this, Eugene!

489
00:43:50,660 --> 00:43:53,190
You owe me, and you owe him.

490
00:43:53,200 --> 00:43:55,590
And if there's a price, I'll pay it.

491
00:43:55,740 --> 00:43:58,520
But don't you tell me no.

492
00:44:00,720 --> 00:44:02,160
You don't know anything.

493
00:44:02,160 --> 00:44:04,440
You don't do anything.

494
00:44:05,710 --> 00:44:07,010
You're a coward.

495
00:44:07,720 --> 00:44:09,130
And you're weak.

496
00:44:10,560 --> 00:44:12,190
The only reason you're alive

497
00:44:12,190 --> 00:44:15,870
is because you lied and because people feel sorry for you.

498
00:44:21,580 --> 00:44:23,240
So, for once...

499
00:44:24,960 --> 00:44:27,230
do something useful...

500
00:44:30,010 --> 00:44:32,420
...and make me a bullet.

501
00:45:25,360 --> 00:45:27,210
Don't beat yourself up.

502
00:45:28,320 --> 00:45:29,380
Why would I?

503
00:45:30,160 --> 00:45:31,440
He --

504
00:45:32,520 --> 00:45:34,880
He asked you about Mark and Amber,

505
00:45:34,880 --> 00:45:36,310
and you sold 'em out, right?

506
00:45:38,880 --> 00:45:40,480
You had to.

507
00:45:42,150 --> 00:45:43,960
That's not what happened.

508
00:45:50,120 --> 00:45:52,040
Whatever helps you sleep at night.

509
00:46:01,360 --> 00:46:02,530
How do you sleep at night?

510
00:46:02,530 --> 00:46:03,710
I don't.

511
00:46:04,870 --> 00:46:07,240
I watch TV straight to the morning.

512
00:46:12,330 --> 00:46:14,220
When we made that deal with him,

513
00:46:14,620 --> 00:46:16,300
that was us deciding something.

514
00:46:16,300 --> 00:46:18,020
This was only supposed to affect us.

515
00:46:18,020 --> 00:46:19,430
No.

516
00:46:19,910 --> 00:46:21,490
If you're still standing,

517
00:46:21,940 --> 00:46:24,130
then it's always on somebody else's back.

518
00:46:30,940 --> 00:46:33,100
You should go. Someone's going to see us.

519
00:46:33,800 --> 00:46:35,360
We're not doing anything.

520
00:46:37,110 --> 00:46:39,930
No. We're not.

521
00:46:52,950 --> 00:46:55,300
Can I wrap up my face now?

522
00:46:55,560 --> 00:46:57,850
No, you absolutely cannot.

523
00:46:57,850 --> 00:46:59,210
Why the hell not?!

524
00:47:00,930 --> 00:47:03,570
Look at this badass.

525
00:47:04,330 --> 00:47:07,490
You can't because I'm not done with you.

526
00:47:08,180 --> 00:47:10,280
And I like looking at your disgusting,

527
00:47:10,280 --> 00:47:13,940
rad-ass, badass eye, so it's staying out.

528
00:47:18,530 --> 00:47:19,760
What?

529
00:47:19,860 --> 00:47:21,250
You got something to say?

530
00:47:23,330 --> 00:47:24,870
Why haven't you killed me?

531
00:47:25,390 --> 00:47:27,620
Or my dad or Daryl?

532
00:47:29,370 --> 00:47:30,520
Daryl...

533
00:47:31,600 --> 00:47:33,720
is gonna make a good soldier for me.

534
00:47:34,610 --> 00:47:37,210
You see, he thinks he's holding it together...

535
00:47:38,080 --> 00:47:39,400
but you saw it.

536
00:47:40,340 --> 00:47:41,560
Your dad?

537
00:47:42,100 --> 00:47:44,410
He's already getting me great stuff.

538
00:47:44,410 --> 00:47:47,290
You, on the other hand...

539
00:47:49,360 --> 00:47:53,620
Well, we shall see.

540
00:47:54,920 --> 00:47:57,320
It's more productive to break you.

541
00:47:58,590 --> 00:48:00,330
More fun, too.

542
00:48:02,060 --> 00:48:03,820
You thinking that's stupid?

543
00:48:03,970 --> 00:48:05,480
I'm thinking we're different.

544
00:48:10,780 --> 00:48:12,250
You're a smart kid.

545
00:48:13,880 --> 00:48:15,280
What do you think I should do?

546
00:48:16,040 --> 00:48:18,060
You know I can't let you go.

547
00:48:19,610 --> 00:48:21,670
So, do I kill you?

548
00:48:22,200 --> 00:48:23,880
Iron your face?

549
00:48:24,130 --> 00:48:25,660
Chop off your arm?

550
00:48:26,580 --> 00:48:27,580
Tell me.

551
00:48:28,330 --> 00:48:29,680
What do you think?

552
00:48:31,530 --> 00:48:32,920
I think you should jump out the window

553
00:48:32,920 --> 00:48:34,990
to save me the trouble of killing you.

554
00:48:42,270 --> 00:48:46,020
Now, there is the kid that impressed the hell out of me.

555
00:48:48,200 --> 00:48:49,770
I think you're not saying what you're gonna do to me

556
00:48:49,770 --> 00:48:51,700
because you're not going to do anything.

557
00:48:52,370 --> 00:48:55,340
If you knew us, if you knew anything,

558
00:48:56,000 --> 00:48:57,560
you would kill us.

559
00:48:58,540 --> 00:48:59,950
But you can't.

560
00:49:04,560 --> 00:49:06,010
Maybe you're right.

561
00:49:07,180 --> 00:49:08,740
Maybe I can't.

562
00:49:14,120 --> 00:49:16,070
Let's go for a ride, kid.

563
00:49:39,110 --> 00:49:40,460
Daryl!

564
00:49:44,640 --> 00:49:47,550
You seem worried, so I'm taking the kid home.

565
00:49:48,170 --> 00:49:49,410
If you do anything to him --

566
00:49:49,410 --> 00:49:50,510
Dwight!

567
00:49:52,340 --> 00:49:53,690
Daryl needs a time-out.

568
00:49:53,690 --> 00:49:55,760
Put him back in his box for a while.

570
00:52:01,640 --> 00:52:02,940
Drop it.

571
00:52:08,260 --> 00:52:09,850
Your knife, too.

572
00:52:15,820 --> 00:52:17,370
What next? You want my shoes?

573
00:52:20,600 --> 00:52:21,920
Take me to Negan.

574
00:52:37,880 --> 00:52:39,450
Start it up. Let's go.

575
00:53:10,480 --> 00:53:14,200
Take me...to Negan.

576
00:53:28,540 --> 00:53:30,290
- Carl, where's -- - Enid's fine.

577
00:53:30,290 --> 00:53:33,110
Great, great, great, great, great, great!

578
00:53:34,520 --> 00:53:35,730
Where's Rick?

579
00:53:35,960 --> 00:53:37,260
Uh, I --

580
00:53:37,260 --> 00:53:39,760
- I'm just -- - Don't care

581
00:53:40,130 --> 00:53:41,380
Where's Rick?

582
00:53:43,230 --> 00:53:45,730
Um, out scavenging for you.

583
00:53:46,420 --> 00:53:47,450
Cool.

584
00:53:47,630 --> 00:53:48,900
I'll wait.

585
00:53:50,260 --> 00:53:53,260
Um...he went out pretty far.

586
00:53:53,260 --> 00:53:55,150
They might not be back today.

587
00:53:56,400 --> 00:53:58,500
We're running really low on everything.

588
00:53:58,630 --> 00:54:00,660
We're practically starving here.

589
00:54:03,200 --> 00:54:04,610
Starving?

590
00:54:06,690 --> 00:54:07,930
You?

591
00:54:08,390 --> 00:54:12,350
By "Practically," You mean "Not really."

592
00:54:23,150 --> 00:54:24,320
Really?

593
00:54:25,790 --> 00:54:29,070
You people seriously don't have a sense of humor.

594
00:54:35,940 --> 00:54:37,070
Excuse me.

595
00:54:40,390 --> 00:54:41,840
What's your name again?

596
00:54:42,990 --> 00:54:44,440
Olivia.

597
00:54:45,720 --> 00:54:46,990
Right.

598
00:54:47,200 --> 00:54:48,330
Olivia.

599
00:54:57,720 --> 00:55:02,720
I am sorry for having been so rude to you just now.

600
00:55:03,460 --> 00:55:05,590
And it looks like I'm gonna be here for a while,

601
00:55:05,590 --> 00:55:08,450
awaiting your fearless leader's return.

602
00:55:09,360 --> 00:55:10,930
And if you'd like...

603
00:55:12,450 --> 00:55:14,970
I think it would be enjoyable...

604
00:55:15,380 --> 00:55:17,390
to screw your brains out.

605
00:55:17,600 --> 00:55:20,820
I mean, if, you know, you're agreeable to it.

606
00:55:34,190 --> 00:55:37,650
I am about 50% more into you now.

607
00:55:39,980 --> 00:55:41,480
Just sayin'.

608
00:55:48,500 --> 00:55:51,100
All right, well, I'm just gonna put my feet up

609
00:55:51,100 --> 00:55:53,140
and wait for my stuff to get here.

610
00:55:54,690 --> 00:55:55,910
Olivia...

611
00:55:56,090 --> 00:55:59,810
would you be a lamb and make us a little lemonade?

612
00:55:59,810 --> 00:56:02,630
Now, I know I left you all some of that good powdered stuff.

613
00:56:02,630 --> 00:56:04,030
Well, I'm supposed to be with --

614
00:56:04,030 --> 00:56:05,160
Make it.

615
00:56:09,410 --> 00:56:10,610
Make it.

616
00:56:11,390 --> 00:56:12,800
Take your time.

617
00:56:13,930 --> 00:56:15,360
Make it good.

618
00:56:26,530 --> 00:56:27,700
All right, kid!

619
00:56:28,080 --> 00:56:29,910
Take me on the grand tour.

620
00:56:53,480 --> 00:56:54,790
How about this one? 

621
00:56:54,790 --> 00:56:56,250
Oh, I-it's just a water heater --

622
00:56:56,250 --> 00:56:57,730
Are you serious, kid? Come on.

623
00:57:01,830 --> 00:57:04,620
Oh-ho, my.

624
00:57:09,320 --> 00:57:12,600
Look at this little angel.

626
00:57:50,950 --> 00:57:53,370
This guy -- he's armed.

627
00:57:53,520 --> 00:57:55,670
Has food, supplies, ammo.

628
00:58:05,120 --> 00:58:07,660
"The only way that you have possibly read this far

629
00:58:07,660 --> 00:58:10,920
without being shot is that I am dead."

630
00:58:31,910 --> 00:58:34,060
Looks like he protected his supplies.

631
00:58:34,870 --> 00:58:36,860
Looks like they're still protected.

632
00:58:39,830 --> 00:58:41,490
Today and only today, right?

633
00:58:44,830 --> 00:58:46,080
Yeah.

634
00:59:05,000 --> 00:59:06,180
Thank you.

635
00:59:10,230 --> 00:59:11,500
I'm sorry for what I said.

636
00:59:11,500 --> 00:59:12,800
I reject that.

637
00:59:13,080 --> 00:59:14,380
I am sorry.

638
00:59:14,460 --> 00:59:15,420
No.

639
00:59:16,810 --> 00:59:18,780
Maybe the words, but not the intent.

640
00:59:20,690 --> 00:59:23,060
You sound sincere, but it's just a flea circus.

641
00:59:23,480 --> 00:59:24,960
You got what you wanted.

642
00:59:24,970 --> 00:59:25,970
This is just you feeling bad

643
00:59:25,970 --> 00:59:27,930
and not saying that you didn't mean what you said.

644
00:59:28,150 --> 00:59:29,610
You meant it, you felt it.

645
00:59:29,610 --> 00:59:30,780
That's your truth.

646
00:59:31,830 --> 00:59:32,990
Eugene...

647
00:59:33,480 --> 00:59:35,670
I'd like to take it back to awkward silence now.

648
00:59:54,900 --> 00:59:56,090
Find what you wanted?

649
00:59:56,230 --> 00:59:57,210
Did just fine.

650
01:00:00,060 --> 01:00:01,110
Yeah, me too.

651
01:00:07,510 --> 01:00:09,230
Where did you acquire all this?

652
01:00:13,350 --> 01:00:14,430
Latin.

653
01:00:14,840 --> 01:00:16,430
It was a pain-in-the-ass class.

654
01:00:16,760 --> 01:00:20,110
My mom said that pain would be useful someday.

655
01:00:20,370 --> 01:00:23,130
It's a list of caches from a dead guy with a plan.

656
01:00:23,540 --> 01:00:27,450
Dug up medical supplies, water purifiers, flares...

657
01:00:27,450 --> 01:00:28,990
And you're just gonna give it all to them.

658
01:00:30,040 --> 01:00:33,370
That's what Rick wants us to do, right?

659
01:00:35,520 --> 01:00:36,900
So that's what I'm gonna do.

660
01:00:37,960 --> 01:00:39,400
I'm gonna do more than that.

661
01:01:03,260 --> 01:01:04,340
They're here.

662
01:01:05,420 --> 01:01:06,750
He's here.

663
01:01:10,510 --> 01:01:13,270
Oh, this little girl is precious.

664
01:01:16,890 --> 01:01:18,030
Hey, neighbor.

665
01:01:19,350 --> 01:01:20,750
Why don't you come by later?

666
01:01:20,750 --> 01:01:22,260
We might grill out.

667
01:01:25,350 --> 01:01:27,330
Oh, I like it here.

668
01:01:30,610 --> 01:01:33,450
I might just have to stay here.

669
01:01:35,470 --> 01:01:38,390
You know, I was thinking about what you said earlier, Carl.

670
01:01:41,010 --> 01:01:44,570
Maybe it is stupid keeping you and your dad alive.

671
01:01:46,390 --> 01:01:48,830
I mean, why am I trying so hard?

672
01:01:49,810 --> 01:01:54,630
Maybe I should just bury you both down in one of those flower beds.

673
01:01:59,300 --> 01:02:01,560
And then I could just settle into the suburbs.

674
01:02:01,790 --> 01:02:03,810
What do you think about that?

