[Script Info]
; // The sub is created by AssToolkit
; // AssToolkit is an ASS Converter designed by David C.
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.16,0:00:03.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《行尸走肉》前情提要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Previously, on AMC's The Walking Dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.31,0:00:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有人手和武器\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have people, and weapons.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.66,0:00:08.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们联盟  先下手为强  就能打败他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If we strike first, together, we can beat them.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.83,0:00:10.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会死人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}People will die.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:10.34,0:00:12.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会死很多人  不仅是救世军\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A lot of people, and not just the Saviors.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:12.34,0:00:14.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果能找到更好的办法  必须找到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If we can find another way, we have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.33,0:00:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道如何打架  不意味着你应该去找茬\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just because you now know how to fight, doesn't mean you should seek one.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.81,0:00:21.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只用说服以西结带领神之国反抗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You'll just have to convince Ezekiel to bring The Kingdom to fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.82,0:00:24.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不想参与这事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, this is something I am not a part of.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.13,0:00:26.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去少了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ah, it looks light.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.30,0:00:28.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你该再看看  加文\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Perhaps you might look again, Gavin.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.17,0:00:29.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们履行了义务\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've met our obligations.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.73,0:02:53.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}God damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.34,0:03:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,醒醒  孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wake it up, kid.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.25,0:03:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么非得这么早\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why does it have to be so early?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.04,0:03:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天有很多事要做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Got a lot to do today.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.47,0:03:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想继续睡觉吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want to go back to sleep?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.60,0:03:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No way.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.52,0:03:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚来找我的时候  \N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You said you wanted to be able to knock your brother
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.35,0:03:23.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说想打败你哥哥\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}on his butt when you first came to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.47,0:03:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真想这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That really what you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.80,0:03:30.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.28,0:03:32.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.21,0:03:35.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想跟你哥哥一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You want to be like your brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.08,0:03:37.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.22,0:03:39.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah. ‭
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.57,0:03:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.05,0:03:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,检查你的步法\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Check your feet,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.94,0:03:49.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-如果你的步法错  -一切都错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- 'cause if your feet ain't right -- - Nothing's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.23,0:05:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们正打算出去清理...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We were just about to come out to clear the --
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.52,0:05:19.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩根在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where's Morgan?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.04,0:05:22.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你没事吧  -摩根在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You okay? - Where is Morgan?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.71,0:05:36.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为什么耶稣带达里尔和其他人来神之国\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why did Jesus bring Daryl and everyone else to the Kingdom?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.62,0:05:40.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They, um...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.64,0:05:47.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们想看看我们能不能一起合作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They wanted to see if we could all start working together on things.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.96,0:05:52.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救世军还在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The Saviors are still here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.33,0:05:54.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们没跟神之国打仗  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're not fighting with the Kingdom, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.75,0:05:59.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔说他们在亚历山大打败了救世军\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Daryl said they beat them back in Alexandria.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.93,0:06:00.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is that true?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.90,0:06:03.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们达成了协议吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That they made a deal with them?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.74,0:06:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is everyone okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.85,0:06:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我是不是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just tell me if it's true.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.12,0:06:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得去问达里尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You need to talk to Daryl about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.60,0:06:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你让我不告诉所有人你的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wanted me to keep the whole story about you from everybody.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.53,0:06:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我不说你在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Told me not to say where you were,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.04,0:06:27.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我照你的吩咐做了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and I did what you asked.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.03,0:06:31.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔不是靠我找到你的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Daryl didn't find you because of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.76,0:06:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你俩之间说的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And what was said between you and him
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.41,0:06:36.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你俩的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}was said between you and him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.02,0:06:42.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会跟你去亚历山大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I will go with you to Alexandria,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.78,0:06:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if you want to make the trip...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.00,0:06:47.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想跟他谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if you want to talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.16,0:06:55.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不该一个人去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You shouldn't go alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.19,0:07:08.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你找到了想要的  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You found what you wanted, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.55,0:07:12.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你逃开了所有人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You got away from everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.28,0:07:16.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是你想要的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is it what you wanted?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.80,0:07:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还是太迟  已经没法逃离了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Was it just too late to get away?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.94,0:07:33.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在就能去亚历山大\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, we can leave for Alexandria right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.52,0:07:36.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right now, if you want to.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.94,0:07:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能帮你什么忙吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is there anything I can help you with?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.58,0:07:47.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不能  -我能不能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- No. - ‭Well, can I just --
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.33,0:07:50.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你不介意  我可以送你回小屋吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you don't mind, could I walk back to the cottage with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.59,0:07:51.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.97,0:07:54.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们今天要上贡  但我可以不去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have a drop today, but I can miss it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.06,0:07:57.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.21,0:08:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在努力学习\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm trying to learn,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.23,0:08:02.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到了你之前做的事  我...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and seeing what you did here, I...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.59,0:08:05.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有五个行尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There were five of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.51,0:08:08.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你能让我看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I would just really appreciate it
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.87,0:08:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是怎么做到的  我会很感激\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if you would just...let me see how you do what you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.77,0:08:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  去上贡吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. Go do your drop.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.89,0:08:22.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.78,0:09:06.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}凯蒂
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.88,0:09:45.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,准你上前  娜比拉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You may approach, Nabila.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.57,0:09:46.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我待在原地就好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm fine where I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.91,0:09:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希瓦喜欢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Shiva likes you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.61,0:09:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就怕它喜欢我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what I'm afraid of.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.26,0:09:59.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告诉我你发现了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tell me what you found.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.10,0:10:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会喜欢的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're not gonna like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.66,0:10:03.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我更不喜欢被坏消息吊胃口\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I like waiting to hear bad news less.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.54,0:10:06.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们遇到了个小问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We got a little problem
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.34,0:10:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但它一周之内就可能变成大问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that could turn into a big problem inside of a week.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.32,0:10:12.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下面大部分植物都生了象鼻虫\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Most of the plants down there, they got weevils.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.77,0:10:15.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须把它们全部剪了烧掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have to cut and burn everything
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.84,0:10:18.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然会蔓延到院子里的主要农作物上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}before the weevils get to the main crops in the courtyard.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.38,0:10:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道皇家花园对你而言很重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know the Royal Garden is important to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.30,0:10:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.84,0:10:27.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你  娜比拉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you, Nabila.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.35,0:10:29.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该怎么办就怎么办吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do what must be done.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.62,0:10:32.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下  美妙之处就在于...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here's the beautiful thing, Your Majesty --
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.13,0:10:36.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以把它们拔了剪了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you can tear it out and cut it down.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.63,0:10:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以把它们烧了扔掉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can burn it and throw it all away.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.65,0:10:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果你想的话  它们还会再长回来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But if you want, it can all grow back.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.48,0:10:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  我觉得我尿裤子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay. I think I just pissed myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.52,0:10:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm-a gonna go.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.72,0:11:14.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五分钟后出发\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're at "five minutes go."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.35,0:11:16.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.37,0:11:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你给了我这本书\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thank you for this.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.03,0:11:23.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还在思考\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm still thinking about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.99,0:11:26.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"伤害敌人就是伤害自己"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"To injure an opponent is to injure oneself."
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.01,0:11:30.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无论如何都会受伤是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get injured no matter what.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.48,0:11:36.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给你带了件礼物  放在你新家的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got something for you -- for the new place.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.10,0:11:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.59,0:11:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我出去找物资时在一家餐厅里发现的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I found it at a restaurant I was scavenging.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.88,0:11:54.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我认识一个女孩  她帮我把它修好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know a girl, and she, uh, fixed it up for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.74,0:11:59.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.87,0:12:03.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正好看那钉子看烦了呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was getting tired of looking at that nail.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.63,0:12:07.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个女孩是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, who's the girl?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.75,0:12:12.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还有三分钟就要出发了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're at, like, "three minutes go" right now,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.69,0:12:13.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.23,0:12:33.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子小小年纪就得当爹\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Kid's too young to be a father.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.21,0:12:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当过爹吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Were you one?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.84,0:12:39.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当过  谢天谢地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was, thank God.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.59,0:12:41.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我那时可不小\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I wasn't too young --
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.60,0:12:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,完美的年纪  完美的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}perfect age, perfect time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.74,0:12:49.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有完美的家庭和完美的人生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I had myself the perfect family and the perfect life.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.57,0:12:54.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我所求不多  得到的却超过预期\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't ask for much, and I got more than I deserved.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.01,0:12:57.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And you?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.37,0:13:08.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉我俩之间有些不快\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry for how things have been between you and me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.96,0:13:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得你对杀戮的看法是错的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think you're wrong about killing...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.57,0:13:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得我们能和救世军长期共处的想法也是错的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}about how you think things can last like this with the Saviors.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.13,0:13:19.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我还是得道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.21,0:13:22.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道你是个好人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know you're a good man.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.17,0:13:31.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但总有一天  你不能再这样好下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The day's coming where you can't be that good.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.54,0:13:34.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等到那时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}When that happens,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.76,0:13:37.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别为此自责\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}don't beat yourself up about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.39,0:13:46.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本杰明  我们该出发了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Benjamin, it's time for us to take our leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.79,0:13:49.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见  小伙子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See you, little man.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.45,0:13:53.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把馅饼放下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Leave the cobbler.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.32,0:13:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真要这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.84,0:13:56.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杰瑞\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jerry.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.91,0:14:00.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.46,0:14:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那女孩是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Who's the girl?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.30,0:14:27.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都别动  把枪端好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everyone stay down. Get your guns up.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.34,0:14:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人把路堵上了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Somebody blocked the road.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.39,0:14:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一定不是什么好事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Can't be for anything good.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.67,0:14:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,陛下  留在车里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your Majesty, stay inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.39,0:14:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们想的话就下来看看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take a look if you want,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.45,0:14:55.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但把枪都端好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but keep your guns up.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.80,0:15:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,梯队向右\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Echelon right.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.36,0:15:13.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向那栋楼行进\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Force towards the building over there.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.99,0:15:25.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}迪恩家电维修
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.39,0:15:16.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家围着国王\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's close around the king.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.07,0:15:19.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来掩护\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got cover.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.59,0:15:34.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们到那栋楼去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's move towards the building.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.86,0:15:42.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本杰明  把枪端起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Benjamin, get your gun up.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.39,0:15:47.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,端得够高了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Think that's high enough?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.75,0:15:50.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做得挺好的  伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're fine, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.65,0:16:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}葬我于此
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.80,0:16:20.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jesus...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.16,0:16:28.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个世界把人逼疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This world drives one mad.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.11,0:16:34.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,人们经历了各种苦难\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}People have lived through every kind of misery...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.52,0:16:38.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,暴君  种族灭绝  仇恨制度\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}tyrants, genocide, systems of quiet hate...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.93,0:16:42.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而别人却在同一块土地上享受着自由\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}while others enjoy freedom on the same piece of land.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.04,0:16:45.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然而如今  我们唯有这样生存\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yet this, how we must exist now...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.15,0:16:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没全都被逼疯仅仅是走运\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It is mere luck we are not all insane.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.94,0:16:51.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是走运  陛下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It isn't luck, Your Majesty.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.04,0:16:53.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎讲\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.65,0:16:56.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这世界确实把人逼疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The world does drive people crazy now.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.06,0:16:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.19,0:17:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为我们创造了新世界\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you made us another world.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.98,0:17:38.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们迟到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're late.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.88,0:17:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希望你能原谅  我们在路上...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you could indulge us your pardon, our path...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.91,0:17:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想听\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't want to hear about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.68,0:17:44.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别打断国王\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't interrupt the king.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.19,0:17:51.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你个獐头鼠目的混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You rat-faced prick.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.18,0:17:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以西结  这里没有国王\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Ezekiel, there aren't any kings,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.20,0:17:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总统或首相\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}presidents, or prime ministers.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.33,0:18:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些都是童话故事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And all that is a fairy tale, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.13,0:18:05.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别在我们面前玩"陛下"那一套\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't bring that "Your Highness" Shit our way.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.88,0:18:11.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很感谢你们一直上贡  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, I appreciate that you've been delivering, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.19,0:18:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,气氛总是不必要的紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}things have been unnecessarily tense,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.04,0:18:16.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我也不必要的紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and that makes me unnecessarily tense.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.59,0:18:18.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来办这事不是找压力的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I didn't go this route for stress.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.97,0:18:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我是来放松的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No. Just the opposite.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.10,0:18:24.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那么进入正题  今天的贡品带了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So let's get to it. Do you have today's offering?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.80,0:18:39.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的枪我也要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I want your guns, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.79,0:18:44.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,协议可没有这条\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We did not agree to that.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.59,0:18:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们有个选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, you got a choice...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.97,0:18:49.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我猜一开始你们就有这个选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Same one that's been there since the beginning, I guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.11,0:18:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们可以交出枪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can give up your guns, 
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.45,0:18:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者开枪试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}or you can try to use them.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.60,0:18:55.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选哪个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's it gonna be?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.00,0:19:07.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该交枪  陛下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We should give them over, Your Majesty.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.25,0:19:10.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该交枪  陛下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Ehh, we should give 'em over, Your Majesty".
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.49,0:19:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许我应该用棍子捅穿你喉咙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or maybe I'll just shove this down your throat.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.46,0:19:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把棍子还给摩根\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give Morgan his stick back.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.82,0:19:22.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,枪就给你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then you can have the guns.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.71,0:19:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-然后大家各奔东西  -以西结\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- And all of us can go on with our day's journeys. - Ezekiel...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.47,0:19:32.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你明白现在这种局面的严重性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need you to understand the gravity of what's happening here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.63,0:19:35.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我给了你选择\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I gave you a choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.45,0:19:37.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你选哪个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is it going to be?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.81,0:19:40.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,选吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.90,0:19:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道该选哪个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know the answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.41,0:19:44.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,算了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.06,0:19:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,枪给他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give them your guns.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.00,0:20:09.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们拿走你们的枪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We took your guns just now
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.93,0:20:12.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是因为你们马上会动感情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because things are about to get emotional.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.33,0:20:13.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据以往的经验\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You guys have proven
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.38,0:20:16.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们一感情用事  就搞砸事情\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that you don't do so good with emotional.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.34,0:20:17.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,贡品不够\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're short.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.05,0:20:20.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要十二颗  这只有十一颗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We said 12. I count 11.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.73,0:20:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是十二颗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There are 12 there.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.96,0:20:23.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是  -再数一遍\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- There aren't. - Count again.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.69,0:20:25.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来数\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You count them!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.67,0:20:38.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我数过的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I counted them.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.27,0:20:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我数过  这不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I did. T-This is impossible.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.44,0:20:43.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有可能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.83,0:20:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's real.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.19,0:20:48.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就发生在眼前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's happening now.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.11,0:20:53.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而现在  问题必须解决\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And the problems have to end...now.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.78,0:20:56.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们必须明白代价\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have to learn the stakes here,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.56,0:20:58.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得教教你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}so we're gonna teach you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.58,0:21:00.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不用动手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't have to do anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.10,0:21:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一小时之内我们会送来双倍贡品\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll get you twice the tribute in an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.17,0:21:04.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right now...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.69,0:21:08.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是唯一重要的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is the only time that matters.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.73,0:21:10.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而现在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And right now...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.62,0:21:15.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们没有履行义务\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you haven't held up your side of the bargain.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.22,0:21:19.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们谈了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}After we have talked about things,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.13,0:21:23.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一遍又一遍之后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}over and over again and again.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.37,0:21:28.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只能做个了结\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So we're gonna deal with all of this...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.68,0:21:32.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就现在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.71,0:21:36.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  是字面意思的"现在"吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right now as in..."right now"?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.78,0:21:37.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.27,0:21:41.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right...now.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.15,0:22:08.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,动手吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.21,0:22:11.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.82,0:22:12.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.25,0:22:15.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.53,0:22:18.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家都别动\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everybody settle down!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.53,0:22:22.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得把本杰明带回神之国\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need to get Benjamin back to the Kingdom.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.05,0:22:27.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把那人的棍子还他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give the man his damn stick!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.21,0:22:30.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚回车里去  一个字都别说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get in the truck! Don't say a goddamn word!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.44,0:22:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们得回去  -不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- We need to get back. ‭- No.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.52,0:22:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  你们都得听好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right now, you have to listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.33,0:22:40.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这一次  给我听仔细了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}For once, be present and listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.61,0:22:42.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以后  你们必须每一次\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You will make your deliveries on time,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.83,0:22:45.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都按时送货  不能少一分\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}every time, and they will be complete.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.11,0:22:48.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要么优秀要么不及格  没有未完成\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's A's or F's, no I's.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.09,0:22:51.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明天把你们欠的贡品送过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You are gonna show me that you understand
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.02,0:22:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,向我证明你们懂我的意思了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}by bringing the balance of what you owe tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.27,0:22:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得马上走  他会流血身亡的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need to go! He's bleeding out!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.18,0:22:57.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一颗甜瓜  不多不少\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One cantaloupe, not more, not less!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.92,0:23:00.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you understand?!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.18,0:23:02.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yes, I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.61,0:23:04.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-去处理他的伤口吧  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Go patch him up. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.16,0:23:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,戴安  我们得带他去卡萝尔那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Dianne, we need to drive to Carol's!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.29,0:23:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们给了她很多医疗用品\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We loaded her up with medical supplies!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.31,0:23:10.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得赶快止住他的血\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We need to stop the bleeding.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.42,0:23:12.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他撑不到回神之国了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's not gonna make it to the Kingdom.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.72,0:23:13.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.30,0:23:16.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Up!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.61,0:23:20.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上车啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Get in!
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.22,0:24:01.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坚持住  坚持住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stay with me. Stay with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.35,0:24:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就在这  坚持住\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm right here. Stay with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.29,0:24:08.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好了  没事  -没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- All right. Okay. - It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.43,0:24:11.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.30,0:24:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"伤害敌人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"T-To injure an opponent...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.60,0:24:21.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是伤害自己"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}is to injure yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.44,0:24:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉过来打搅你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry for coming to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.82,0:24:56.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们实在没办法了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We had no choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.97,0:25:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩根  等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Morgan, wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.08,0:25:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.65,0:25:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.52,0:25:27.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}葬我于此
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.70,0:25:30.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}清醒
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.31,0:25:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别靠近我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Stay away from me.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.76,0:25:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}听着就好
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.78,0:25:35.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着就好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.96,0:25:39.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}葬我于此
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.40,0:25:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}听着就好
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.28,0:25:43.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No! No! Aah!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.43,0:25:46.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.95,0:25:51.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No! No! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.58,0:25:53.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I know!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.04,0:25:58.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了  不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Enough! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.24,0:26:17.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本杰明  把枪端起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Benjamin, get your gun up.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.44,0:26:41.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本来死的人该是我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was supposed to be me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.12,0:26:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加文说过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what Gavin said --
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.34,0:26:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会是第一个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that I'd be first.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.35,0:26:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本想阻止的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was trying to stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.83,0:26:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本想献出自己的性命来警醒你们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was gonna give my life to show you!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.76,0:26:58.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天本该那样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what should've happened today.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.08,0:27:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是那样试着做的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's what I tried.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.59,0:27:04.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是发生了意料之外的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And something else happened
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.50,0:27:08.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们没有做什么去阻止他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because we have done nothing to stop them.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.42,0:27:09.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们什么都没做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We've done nothing!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.83,0:27:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.44,0:27:35.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,灾变发生时我在一个营地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was in a camp when it started.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.64,0:27:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无边无际的大营\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was huge...endless...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.72,0:27:47.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到处是帐篷  茅厕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}a city of -- of tarps and latrines
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.64,0:27:50.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,炊烟  婴儿的哭声\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and wood smoke and babies crying.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.14,0:27:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总有婴儿的哭声\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There were always babies crying.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.11,0:28:04.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道情况不妙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I knew they had problems,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.72,0:28:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不觉得轮得到我来管\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but I didn't think they were mine to solve.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.26,0:28:11.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为比我有能力比我聪明的人会管\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought there were stronger or smarter people there than me.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.84,0:28:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我算什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}W-Who the hell am I, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.13,0:28:23.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我什么都没做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So I did nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.51,0:28:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后有一场战斗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}A-And there was a fight...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.61,0:28:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,起了火\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and a fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.50,0:28:36.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我失去了妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I lost my wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.42,0:28:41.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,三天没有食物  没有睡觉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And after three days of running, 
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.91,0:28:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恐怖骇人的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}no food, and no sleep...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.63,0:28:49.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,逃命后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}of horror and terror...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.68,0:28:54.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我失去了女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I lost my little girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.98,0:29:00.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在我面前...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right in front of me...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.39,0:29:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我什么都没做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}because I didn't do something.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.59,0:29:17.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我干等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because I waited.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.97,0:29:34.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:35.22,0:29:36.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.12,0:29:39.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着就好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.47,0:29:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以利用这事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can use what's happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.08,0:29:49.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以向救世军表明我们吸取了教训\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We can show the Saviors that we get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.42,0:29:53.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明白要做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We understand what we need to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.15,0:29:55.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道怎么继续下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We know how to go on.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.39,0:30:01.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们要相信我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And they need to believe us.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.27,0:30:06.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须得做点什么使他们相信\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have to do something to make them believe us.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.50,0:30:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我们赢回他们的信任后\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And then, when we gain their trust back...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.64,0:30:14.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再杀了他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we kill them...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.17,0:30:17.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一了百了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}end them.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.58,0:30:20.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们加入亚历山大和山顶寨的同盟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We join with Alexandria and the Hilltop,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.74,0:30:23.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一举歼灭他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and we crush them in one fell swoop.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.16,0:30:30.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你得接受事实  摩根\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But this is it, Morgan.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.40,0:30:39.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必须要杀戮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have...to...kill.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.00,0:30:46.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不然你还不如自杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Or else you might as well just kill yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.42,0:30:54.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总得有人死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Someone had to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.81,0:30:58.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我曾想成为那个人  但没有成功\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I tried to be the one. That didn't happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.89,0:31:07.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我要成为领导我们的军队\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So I'll be the one to lead our army
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.66,0:31:10.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去粉碎救世军的人  摧毁他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to crush the Saviors -- destroy them.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.86,0:31:13.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Me.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.70,0:31:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会和以西结说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll talk to Ezekiel.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.89,0:31:22.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会告诉所有人我做的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll tell everyone what I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.75,0:31:28.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后我会用余生去弥补\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I'll live the rest of my life making up for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.42,0:33:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你告诉他了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you tell him?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.64,0:33:05.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Did you?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.27,0:33:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not now.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.27,0:33:11.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们回去再说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll talk about it when we get back.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.19,0:33:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:12.43,0:33:15.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好我们回去再说  陛下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's better to talk about it when we get back, Your Majesty.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.70,0:33:20.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在就说\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll talk about it now.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.41,0:34:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那孩子怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How's the kid?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.75,0:34:28.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.90,0:34:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我杀了你之前快滚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Start walking back now before I kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.29,0:34:42.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你多说一句  多瞟一眼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You say one word or throw one look,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.31,0:34:44.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就地杀了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'll kill you right here and now.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.58,0:34:47.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,滚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.02,0:35:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,东西拿了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you have it?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.06,0:35:28.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想说  我们明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just want to say we get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.61,0:35:29.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.97,0:35:36.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-住手  -别管\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Cease this! - Leave 'em be!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.11,0:35:39.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩根  住手\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Morgan! Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.64,0:35:40.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩根\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Morgan!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.04,0:36:33.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是他搞的鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He set it all up.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.20,0:36:40.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他昨天挡路  让我们迟到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He blocked the road yesterday, made us late.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.13,0:36:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是他干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was all him.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.81,0:36:51.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们离开时  贡品还在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And we had your offering when we left --
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.59,0:36:53.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都在\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}had it all.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.54,0:37:01.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他从里面拿走了一颗  藏了起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He took one from the cargo, and he hid it --
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.63,0:37:04.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我们停车时\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}when we stopped.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.50,0:37:08.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他想挑起神之国和救世军的争端\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He wanted to get something started between the Kingdom and the Saviors.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.58,0:37:25.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让你看到...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wanted to show you...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.42,0:37:30.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让你看到我们吸取了教训\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wanted to show you that we get it...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.82,0:37:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明白要做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That we understand what it is that we need to do --
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.72,0:37:39.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道怎么继续下去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that we know how to go on.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.00,0:37:47.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.73,0:37:54.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下周  同一时间\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Next week, same time.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.94,0:38:01.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们明白\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We -- We understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.18,0:38:25.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是他干的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He -- He did this?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.27,0:38:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他之前就想为我们死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He wanted to die for us before.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.23,0:38:32.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他希望死的是自己\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He wanted it to be him.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:38.28,0:38:41.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他以为自己有的选  所以德韦恩才死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thought he could choose, and that's why Duane had to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.50,0:38:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"德韦恩"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"Duane"?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.49,0:39:04.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,本杰明  所以本杰明才...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Benjamin -- Benjamin -- That's why Benjamin...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.62,0:39:10.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩根\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Morgan...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.46,0:39:14.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}let us take our leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.31,0:39:16.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来就打算走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was supposed to.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:16.91,0:39:19.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩根  你不能一个人待在外面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Morgan, you should not be alone here.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.16,0:39:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.02,0:39:22.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not now.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.75,0:39:25.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-本杰明不想...  -我说了现在不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Benjamin not -- would not - ‭Man, I said not now!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.23,0:39:30.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说了...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I said...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.52,0:39:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Y'all just go.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.28,0:40:52.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}凯蒂
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.39,0:41:47.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你真想知道亚历山大发生了什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you really want to know what happened in Alexandria?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.88,0:41:52.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What happened to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.08,0:41:55.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我杀了理查德\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Killed Richard.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:58.90,0:42:00.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,掐死了他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I strangled him.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:03.34,0:42:05.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他害死了本杰明  所以...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He's the one got Benjamin killed, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:09.57,0:42:12.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想知道亚历山大发生了什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you want to know what happened in Alexandria?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.99,0:42:20.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:25.96,0:42:28.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根杀了格伦和亚伯拉罕\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Negan killed Glenn and Abraham.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:30.72,0:42:31.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:32.83,0:42:34.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,用棒球棍活活打死了他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Beat them to death with a baseball bat.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:41.07,0:42:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在救世军统治着亚历山大  瑞克和其他人...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now the Saviors have Alexandria, and Rick and everybody else...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:46.74,0:42:49.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都得为救世军做事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}everything they do is for the Saviors now.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:00.80,0:43:02.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们还杀了更多人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And they killed more.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:06.42,0:43:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,杀了斯宾塞  奥利维亚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Killed Spencer, Olivia...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:13.74,0:43:16.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶稣带瑞克一伙人来是因为\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Jesus brought Rick and the rest here because...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:17.69,0:43:19.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克想反抗他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick wants to fight them.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:26.06,0:43:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你想知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wanted to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:30.02,0:43:31.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在你知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:33.92,0:43:35.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你去哪  -我去杀他们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Where are you going? - I'm gonna kill them --
Dialogue: 0,0:43:36.02,0:43:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在外面  一个个杀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}out there, one by one.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:38.07,0:43:39.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-但是去哪  -别的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- But where? ? - Somewhere else.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:40.10,0:43:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}W-Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:41.03,0:43:42.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wait. Just wait. Wait!
Dialogue: 0,0:43:48.62,0:43:52.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以走  同时也不走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can go...and not go.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:58.37,0:43:59.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:04.79,0:44:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:44:18.24,0:44:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}单行道
Dialogue: 0,0:45:06.44,0:45:07.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡萝尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Carol.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:08.29,0:45:09.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很遗憾\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:11.43,0:45:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:18.88,0:45:20.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会住在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna be here now.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:22.65,0:45:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要做准备\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have to get ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:25.63,0:45:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须反抗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We have to fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:30.61,0:45:31.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We do.
Dialogue: 0,0:45:34.27,0:45:35.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不在今天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But not today.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.79,0:01:48.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第七季  第十三集』
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.79,0:01:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(550,500)\p1\bord2\shad0\fscx150\fscy160\alpha&566\c&H000000&\3c&HECB000&\move(145,247,145,227,0,500)\clip(30,188,340,210)\t(0,500,\clip(30,168,340,190))}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.79,0:01:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(550,500)\p1\bord2\shad0\fscx150\fscy160\alpha&566\c&H000000&\3c&HECB000&\move(145,207,145,227,0,500)\clip(30,220,340,235)\t(0,500,\clip(30,240,340,255))}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.79,0:01:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(550,500)\p1\bord3\blur3\shad0\fscx150\fscy0\t(0,400,\fscy160)\alpha&566\c&H000000&\pos(145,227)\clip(30,210,340,220)\t(0,500,\clip(30,190,340,240))}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.29,0:01:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(550,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\fscx11\fscy14.5\p1\c&HCE8F00&\pos(67,223)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.29,0:01:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(550,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\fscx11\fscy14\p1\c&HF6DBA1&\pos(67,223)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.29,0:01:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(550,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx15\fscy18\p1\c&HFFFFFF&\blur9\pos(58,213)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.29,0:01:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(550,500)\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\fscx11\fscy14\p1\c&HECB000&\pos(84,223)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.29,0:01:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(550,500)\fs16\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\b1\c&HECB000&\pos(99,242)}原创翻译  双语字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.79,0:01:53.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(550,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\b1\bord0\2a&HFF&\shad0\fs17\pos(235.108,242)\K40}最新连载海外影视剧下载\N{\fs19\K30}请登陆 {\c&H26F4FF&\fn方正综艺_GBK\K30}www.YYeTs.com\N{\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs15\c&HFFFFFF&\K60}仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.01,0:02:30.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\bord0\shad0\shad0\fscx130\fscy170\frz180\p1\alpha&88\c&H000000&\b1\move(-180,245,70,245,0,500)\clip(49,215,304,257)\fad(550,550)}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.51,0:02:30.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an2\fad(550,550)\bord0\shad0\shad0\fscx150\fscy170\p1\pos(26,248)\c&HECB000&\b1}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.52,0:02:00.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}翻译     {\c&HFFFFFF&}冰蓝 Reginamoon CS小明漫画家
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.52,0:02:05.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}翻译     {\c&HFFFFFF&}凉粉 小僵僵 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.52,0:02:10.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}校对     {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.52,0:02:15.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(27,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}时间轴     {\c&HFFFFFF&}某雪  加森
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.52,0:02:20.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}后期     {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小哥  拉图
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.52,0:02:25.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)\fn方正准圆_GBK\c&H000000&}总监     {\c&HFFFFFF&}送小孩
