1
00:00:03,100 --> 00:00:05,850
-迈克尔  那人不是我杀的  -可证据确凿
-I didn't kill that man Michael.  -The evidence says you did.

2
00:00:05,860 --> 00:00:08,400
我是被陷害的
I was set up.

3
00:00:09,050 --> 00:00:10,370
把枪放下!
Put down your weapon.

4
00:00:10,380 --> 00:00:13,460
本席在此宣判 你入狱服刑
I find it incumbent that you see the inside of a prison cell.

5
00:00:13,470 --> 00:00:15,600
我想找个人  他叫林肯·布伦斯
I'm looking for someone guy named Lincoln Burrows.

6
00:00:15,610 --> 00:00:17,120
杀害副总统哥哥的那个?
Man killed the vice president's brother.

7
00:00:17,130 --> 00:00:18,920
你为什么这样急着见布伦斯?
Why you want to see Burrows so bad anyhow?

8
00:00:18,930 --> 00:00:20,010
他是我哥哥
'Cause he's my brother.

9
00:00:20,020 --> 00:00:22,190
-我要把你弄出去  -不可能
-I'm getting you out of here.  -It's impossible.

10
00:00:22,200 --> 00:00:24,420
除非这个地方是你设计的 你说呢
Not if you designed the place,it isn't

11
00:00:24,430 --> 00:00:25,790
你看过蓝图了?
You've seen the blueprints.

12
00:00:25,800 --> 00:00:27,070
不仅如此
Better than that.

13
00:00:27,080 --> 00:00:28,970
我都纹在身上了
I've got 'em on me.

14
00:00:28,980 --> 00:00:30,480
有个好管闲事的律师
There's a lawyer poking around.

15
00:00:30,490 --> 00:00:31,810
多诺万小姐
Ms Donovan?

16
00:00:31,820 --> 00:00:33,320
我没想吓倒您
 I didn't mean to scare you.

17
00:00:33,330 --> 00:00:34,100
不见了!
It's gone.

18
00:00:34,110 --> 00:00:35,570
都谁还有这里的钥匙?
Does anyone else have a key to this place?

19
00:00:35,580 --> 00:00:36,990
你当时也在的  记得么?
You were here.remember?

20
00:00:37,000 --> 00:00:41,170
我走过橱柜  然后
I walked over to the cabinet and I...

21
00:00:46,780 --> 00:00:49,480
对我们的小朋友有什么意见么?
Got an issue with our little friend over there?

22
00:00:49,490 --> 00:00:54,560
是时候给他点颜色看看了
Yeah. Maybe it's time I lit up that leather once and for all, huh?

23
00:00:54,570 --> 00:00:55,840
发生了什么事?
What happened?

24
00:00:55,850 --> 00:00:57,590
别逼我骗你
Don't make me lie to you.

25
00:00:57,600 --> 00:00:58,680
你听说了么?
You heard the news, didn't you?

26
00:00:58,690 --> 00:00:59,720
听说什么?
No. What?

27
00:00:59,730 --> 00:01:01,660
-他们是兄弟  -谁?
-They're brothers.  -Who?

28
00:01:01,670 --> 00:01:05,140
-布伦斯 和斯科菲尔德  -迈克尔·斯科菲尔德?
-Burrows and Scofield.  -Michael Scofield?

29
00:01:05,150 --> 00:01:07,950
今晚打算再到墙那边 看看能否顺利到达屋顶
I'm going into the walls tonight,see if I can access the roof.

30
00:01:07,960 --> 00:01:10,180
不要给布伦斯留下丝毫希望
Take the only thing Burrows has left.

31
00:01:10,190 --> 00:01:14,510
在监狱里行刑不一定非要通过电椅
The chair isn't the only way to take a man's life in prison.

32
00:01:30,950 --> 00:01:35,260
那就再玩几次吧  回来后就走
Just a few more rides.Then you have to wrap it up.

33
00:01:37,730 --> 00:01:39,770
亚当已经长大了?
Wow. Adam's getting bigger.

34
00:01:39,780 --> 00:01:42,140
-10岁了?  -这里说话不方便
-Ten.  -Not here.

35
00:01:42,150 --> 00:01:45,400
帮我们个忙
We need a favour.

36
00:01:45,410 --> 00:01:47,420
你也知道 我早就洗手不干了
been out of the life for years,you know that.

37
00:01:47,430 --> 00:01:48,200
我知道
I know.

38
00:01:48,210 --> 00:01:49,770
可问题是  帝蒙  谁又会相信你呢
Problem is, Diamond, no one's gonna believe that

39
00:01:49,780 --> 00:01:51,810
尤其是当我把包里的海洛因
if I take the heroin in my pocket

40
00:01:51,820 --> 00:01:56,580
适当的放在你装手套的盒子里的时候
and put it in the glove box of the reasonably priced minivan you got over there.

41
00:01:56,590 --> 00:01:57,520
我将会逮捕你
I will cuff you.

42
00:01:57,530 --> 00:02:02,270
然后当着众人的面把你带走
I will drag you out of here in front of everyone.

43
00:02:04,910 --> 00:02:08,460
你想怎样?
What do you need?

44
00:02:10,800 --> 00:02:12,820
美国需要的
What America needs

45
00:02:12,830 --> 00:02:15,530
是一个环保的
is an environmentally friendly,

46
00:02:15,540 --> 00:02:18,040
可持续发展的
logistically feasible

47
00:02:18,050 --> 00:02:23,700
经济可靠的全新替代型燃料
and economically responsible alternative fuel source.

48
00:02:25,020 --> 00:02:28,630
请留言  我会尽快回电 谢谢
Leave a message and I'll call you back. Thanks.

49
00:02:28,640 --> 00:02:30,000
嗨  是温蒂
It's Wendy.

50
00:02:30,010 --> 00:02:32,950
知道你工作时不想分心 所以不用接了
 I know you wanted to work with no distractions, so don't pick up.

51
00:02:32,960 --> 00:02:36,960
我只想告诉你 尼克·萨维恩给你打了六个电话
I just wanted to let you know that Nick Savrinn left six messages for you...

52
00:02:36,970 --> 00:02:38,860
你都告诉她什么了?
What did you tell him?

53
00:02:38,870 --> 00:02:41,810
照你的吩咐  告诉他你在开会
What you said to say you were in a meeting.

54
00:02:41,820 --> 00:02:44,560
好的  如果明天他还来的话 告诉他我不在这里  好么?
Look,If he comes by tomorrow, tell him I'm not there.OK?

55
00:02:44,570 --> 00:02:46,220
好的  晚安维罗妮卡
OK. Goodnight, Veronica.

56
00:02:46,230 --> 00:02:49,060
多谢  温蒂
Thanks, Wendy.

57
00:04:41,440 --> 00:04:44,630
查宿
Bed check.

58
00:05:23,090 --> 00:05:25,550
能向我解释一下为什么不回我电话么?
Do you want to tell me why haven't you returned any of my calls?

59
00:05:25,560 --> 00:05:29,600
听着  我很感激你一直以来给予我的帮助?
Look, I really appreciate everything you've done,okay?

60
00:05:29,610 --> 00:05:31,500
但我从此不需要了
but I don't want your help anymore.

61
00:05:31,510 --> 00:05:33,470
不再需要我的帮助了
Don't want my help anymore.

62
00:05:33,480 --> 00:05:35,900
你还是以为那盘丢失的录像带和我有关?
Do you really think I had something to do with that missing tape?

63
00:05:35,910 --> 00:05:39,330
不  我只是想冲杯咖啡  然后继续工作好么?
No. I'm just gonna go grab a cup of coffee and get back to work.okay?

64
00:05:39,340 --> 00:05:43,030
我现在没时间来讨论这个
I don't have time for this right now.

65
00:05:45,040 --> 00:05:46,450
维罗妮卡
Veronica,

66
00:05:46,460 --> 00:05:48,110
请等一下
just wait a second.

67
00:05:48,120 --> 00:05:49,860
能不能听我说?
Will you hold on a second?

68
00:05:49,870 --> 00:05:52,580
-你为什么躲着我?  -不要碰我  好么?
-Listen, what are you avoid...  -Don't touch me!all right?

69
00:05:52,590 --> 00:05:55,080
没事吧 多诺万小姐?
Everything OK, Miss Donovan?

70
00:05:55,090 --> 00:05:59,300
卢卡斯  可否麻烦你送我回屋?
Lucasz, do you mind walking me back inside?

71
00:06:01,410 --> 00:06:03,620
走远点  伙计
Take a walk, pal.

72
00:06:03,630 --> 00:06:06,550
别痴心妄想了
You're being paranoid.

73
00:06:07,390 --> 00:06:11,410
-别痴心妄想了  -滚远点
-You're being paranoid.  -Go away, Nick.

74
00:06:23,410 --> 00:06:26,140
露点皮出来 斯科菲尔德
Show some skin, Scofield.

75
00:06:32,740 --> 00:06:35,180
斯科菲尔德
Hey, Scofield!

76
00:06:46,450 --> 00:06:49,570
刚睡着呢  老大
I'm trying to sleep, boss.

77
00:06:58,230 --> 00:07:00,720
到不了围墙
I can't get through the wall.

78
00:07:00,730 --> 00:07:02,810
什么意思  你到不了围墙?
What do you mean you can't get through the wall?

79
00:07:02,820 --> 00:07:04,700
我知道怎么做
I know how to do it.

80
00:07:04,710 --> 00:07:07,170
只是没有足够的时间
I just don't have the time to do it.

81
00:07:07,180 --> 00:07:09,950
咱们被关在这儿 有的是时间
We're locked up. All we got is time.

82
00:07:09,960 --> 00:07:12,290
你不明白
You don't understand.

83
00:07:12,300 --> 00:07:14,530
我本来已计划好了这一切
I planned this break on a schedule.

84
00:07:14,540 --> 00:07:16,140
但这里却总是点名
They constantly coming up here for count

85
00:07:16,150 --> 00:07:18,970
使我无法顺利完成墙那边的工作
won't let me do what I need to do to get through the wall.

86
00:07:18,980 --> 00:07:20,780
如果我不能按时回来
If I'm not back on schedule,

87
00:07:20,790 --> 00:07:24,590
就意味着即使几天后 咱们顺利穿过了那堵墙
which means we're through by the end of the day manana,

88
00:07:24,600 --> 00:07:27,450
也无法离开这里
we're not getting out of here.

89
00:07:27,460 --> 00:07:29,690
生活中有三个东西是无法逃避的
Look, there's three things for certain in life

90
00:07:29,700 --> 00:07:33,200
死亡  税收  还有点名
death, taxes and count.

91
00:07:33,290 --> 00:07:36,930
唯一逃避点名的办法就是
The only way to stop count is...

92
00:07:37,580 --> 00:07:39,170
是什么?
What?

93
00:07:39,180 --> 00:07:41,180
算了  这主意不好
Never mind. It's a bad idea.

94
00:07:41,190 --> 00:07:45,220
比失去玛丽克鲁兹还糟?
Worse than the idea of losing Maricruz?

95
00:07:49,710 --> 00:07:51,400
一级禁闭
A lockdown.

96
00:07:51,410 --> 00:07:54,730
只要能让这里禁闭一天 你就有足够的时间来做你想做的
 We get Gen Pop locked down for a day, you'll have all the time you need.

97
00:07:54,740 --> 00:07:58,200
-不用点名?  -那帮畜生甚至都不会来
-And no count?  -Bulls don't even come by.

98
00:07:58,210 --> 00:08:00,700
只是有一点
Only one problem.

99
00:08:00,710 --> 00:08:04,460
怎样才能让这里被禁闭呢?
How do we get a lockdown?

100
00:08:09,460 --> 00:08:11,630
你到得了空调机房么?
Can you get to the prison AC unit?

101
00:08:11,640 --> 00:08:14,140
或许
Maybe.

102
00:08:14,460 --> 00:08:18,650
想要被封闭 首先要激怒这里的囚犯
You want a lockdown? You got to get the inmates riled up.

103
00:08:18,660 --> 00:08:21,730
想再狠点的话
And if you wanna piss off the meat in concrete,

104
00:08:21,740 --> 00:08:25,570
再加点温
turn up the heat.

105
00:09:24,000 --> 00:09:25,650
还以为你退休了呢
I thought you were retired.

106
00:09:25,660 --> 00:09:27,250
不用管我
Never mind me.

107
00:09:27,260 --> 00:09:30,540
上面希望这事尽早解决 我也是迫不得已
Some heavy hitters want this done, so that means I want it done.

108
00:09:30,550 --> 00:09:32,210
不能有丝毫差错
No screw-ups.

109
00:09:32,220 --> 00:09:34,750
既然你开口  肯定没问题
For you, Diamond, it's not a problem.

110
00:09:34,760 --> 00:09:38,020
布伦斯死定了
Burrows is as good as dead.

111
00:09:47,830 --> 00:09:50,000
这个四月还真是热
Hottest April on record.

112
00:09:50,010 --> 00:09:53,270
-全球气候变暖   -或许吧  现在有时间么?
-Global warming.  -Probably. You got a minute?

113
00:09:53,280 --> 00:09:55,970
有差不多5年呢
About five years' worth.

114
00:09:55,980 --> 00:09:59,340
没错 
Sorry. Right.

115
00:09:59,380 --> 00:10:01,780
你从没和我说过林肯·布伦斯是你哥哥
You never told me Burrows is your brother.

116
00:10:01,790 --> 00:10:04,330
-你也没问过  -没错
-It never came up.  -Right.

117
00:10:04,340 --> 00:10:08,460
我很好奇 这事是否和我的那个州长父亲有关
I'm curious if that isn't because of my father, the governor.

118
00:10:09,630 --> 00:10:10,540
他说话可能不太管用
He may not be the one pulling the switch,

119
00:10:10,550 --> 00:10:13,840
你我都知道  他可以请求缓刑 但他是不会那样做的
but you and I both know he has power to grant clemency and he won't.

120
00:10:13,850 --> 00:10:17,140
永远都不会
and he never does.

121
00:10:17,150 --> 00:10:21,470
我家老头曾因酗酒成性将家人抛弃
My old man was an abusive drunk who abandoned his family.

122
00:10:21,480 --> 00:10:25,150
(所以)我从来不通过家长的举动看人
I don'tjudge anyone by their father's actions,or inactions,

123
00:10:25,160 --> 00:10:30,040
你是担心这个吗?
if that was your concern.

124
00:10:30,050 --> 00:10:35,670
正如你所知道的 我不太赞同他的某些政策
Just so you know,I don't agree with his politics.

125
00:10:36,500 --> 00:10:39,110
你哥哥的事我很抱歉
And I'm sorry about your brother.

126
00:10:39,120 --> 00:10:42,770
多谢了
I appreciate that.

127
00:10:51,230 --> 00:10:54,540
虽说帮不上太大的忙
Hey, this isn't much...

128
00:10:57,440 --> 00:10:59,850
我每周要为林肯做检查
I have to give Lincoln a weekly checkup now.

129
00:10:59,860 --> 00:11:01,750
如果愿意的话 我可以把他的检查时间安排在
If you want, I could schedule those visits

130
00:11:01,760 --> 00:11:04,790
在给你打针之前
to end right before you come in for your shots.

131
00:11:04,800 --> 00:11:07,670
这样或许
That way

132
00:11:07,680 --> 00:11:12,120
你们能互相见一面 虽然时间不长
you could at least see each other,even if it's just in passing.

133
00:11:12,130 --> 00:11:15,000
谢谢你了
Thank you.

134
00:11:17,710 --> 00:11:20,110
不客气
Yeah.

135
00:11:34,290 --> 00:11:38,310
来自厨师的问候  菜鸟 100块钱
Greetings from the kitchen, fish. 100 bucks.

136
00:11:45,240 --> 00:11:49,970
图多尔·伯格威尔 从医务室归来
Theodore Bagwell,transferred back from the infirmary.

137
00:12:02,550 --> 00:12:07,660
为你准备了一个"康复"礼物
We got you a little "get well" gift.

138
00:12:10,620 --> 00:12:14,350
大小正合适
It's just the right size.

139
00:12:14,360 --> 00:12:16,850
谢谢伙计们
Thank you, boys.

140
00:12:16,860 --> 00:12:19,840
回见
I'll catch up with you later.

141
00:12:24,460 --> 00:12:26,990
你叫什么名字?
What's your name?

142
00:12:27,000 --> 00:12:29,540
塞斯
Seth.

143
00:12:29,550 --> 00:12:32,230
新来的  塞斯?
You new, Seth?

144
00:12:32,240 --> 00:12:36,260
害怕么?  看着我 孩子
Scared? Look at me, boy.

145
00:12:41,070 --> 00:12:44,330
你应该听说过我的故事
You probably heard stories about me.

146
00:12:46,950 --> 00:12:50,350
不全是真的
They're not all true.

147
00:12:53,160 --> 00:12:57,270
我们出去走走好么?
What do you say we go for a walk, huh?

148
00:14:19,110 --> 00:14:20,760
您的助理已经到了
Your co-counsel's already here.

149
00:14:20,770 --> 00:14:22,980
你说什么?
Excuse me?

150
00:14:26,570 --> 00:14:28,220
你来这干什么?
What the hell are you doing here?

151
00:14:28,230 --> 00:14:29,980
和客户谈话
I'm talking to my client.

152
00:14:29,990 --> 00:14:31,750
-不要和他讲话  -维罗妮卡
-Don't talk to him.  -Veronica

153
00:14:31,760 --> 00:14:33,490
我们还不了解他
We don't know anything about this guy.

154
00:14:33,500 --> 00:14:36,800
他找到能帮助我们的办法了
He found somebody that could help us out.

155
00:14:36,990 --> 00:14:38,890
只给你1分钟
You have one minute.

156
00:14:38,900 --> 00:14:41,250
我看了谋杀当晚的报告
I've been going over the incident report from the night og the murder,

157
00:14:41,260 --> 00:14:43,950
有位匿名人士打电话给警察
and somebody made an anonymous phone call to the local cops

158
00:14:43,960 --> 00:14:46,620
宣称看见林肯从车库中跑出来
claiming to see Lincoln running away from the garage

159
00:14:46,630 --> 00:14:47,890
身穿血裤
 with bloody pants.

160
00:14:47,900 --> 00:14:48,890
这个我们以前讨论过
We've been through this

161
00:14:48,900 --> 00:14:51,220
听着  我们不能去盘问一个 我们根本不知道是谁的人
look, You can't cross-examine a witness if you don't know who it is.

162
00:14:51,220 --> 00:14:52,200
根本就不用知道他是谁
We don't need to know who it is

163
00:14:52,200 --> 00:14:53,640
我们知道他在哪儿
We know where he is.

164
00:14:53,650 --> 00:14:54,710
你的意思是?
What do you mean?

165
00:14:54,720 --> 00:14:55,790
虽然费了些时间
Well, it took some doing,

166
00:14:55,790 --> 00:14:59,790
一个私家侦探朋友帮我跟踪 到了那个打到警察局的电话
But a PI friend of mine backtracked the phone call back to the police department.

167
00:14:59,790 --> 00:15:00,540
不管是谁打的那个电话
Whoever made that call

168
00:15:00,540 --> 00:15:03,620
那晚他根本不可能看到林肯从车库中跑出来
couldn't have seen Lincoln rom the garage that night.

169
00:15:03,630 --> 00:15:05,730
何以见得?
How do you know?

170
00:15:05,740 --> 00:15:10,200
因为电话是从华盛顿打来的
Because the phone call came from Washington DC.

171
00:15:28,920 --> 00:15:33,560
我只是让你关掉空调 你狗日的把暖气也给打开了
You were supposed to turn off the AC,not turn on the furnace.

172
00:16:00,070 --> 00:16:01,300
这里还真是热啊
It's getting so hot in here.

173
00:16:01,310 --> 00:16:05,270
我没说过让你讲话吧 雏儿?
Did I say you could talk, Cherry?

174
00:16:06,190 --> 00:16:09,920
我让你开口的时候才能说话
You'll know when I want you to open your mouth.

175
00:16:12,750 --> 00:16:15,740
盖里!
Geary!

176
00:16:16,860 --> 00:16:18,440
这么热你总得做点什么吧?
You got to do something about the heat.

177
00:16:18,450 --> 00:16:20,530
-我们已经尽力了  -尽了力也还是废物
-Doing the best we can.  -Your best is garbage.

178
00:16:20,540 --> 00:16:22,140
这里都够100度了
It's 100 degrees in here.

179
00:16:22,150 --> 00:16:25,550
我看起来像很凉快么?
Look like I got frostbite to you?

180
00:16:25,560 --> 00:16:28,410
排好队!
Line up!

181
00:16:44,910 --> 00:16:47,840
为什么不把我们转到其他凉快的地方?
Why don't you transfer us all someplace cooler,

182
00:16:47,850 --> 00:16:50,820
非洲怎么样?
 like Africa?

183
00:16:51,710 --> 00:16:55,880
你给我站好队  臭犯人
Get your ass on the line, convict.

184
00:16:58,450 --> 00:17:00,520
全体人  都站到线上!
All of you, hit that line!

185
00:17:00,530 --> 00:17:06,970
这里的温度恢复正常了我们就回去  可以么?
We'll move when the temperature situation is rectified.all right?

186
00:17:08,760 --> 00:17:10,910
贝利克,我是牢区的马克
 Hey Bellick, this is Mack in cell block.

187
00:17:10,920 --> 00:17:12,360
这里有人要闹事
We got some cons popping off.

188
00:17:12,370 --> 00:17:14,600
先海扁他们一顿 然后仍到线后  再记下他们的名子
Give 'em a smack, throw 'em on the line and write 'em up.

189
00:17:14,610 --> 00:17:19,010
你要是连这个都办不了 这周就别想拿薪水了
If you can't handle it,don't cash your paycheck this week.

190
00:17:20,180 --> 00:17:21,830
恐怕现在不合适  医生
This is not a good time, Doc.

191
00:17:21,840 --> 00:17:24,210
我听说有犯人患了热衰竭
I got a call a prisoner was suffering from heat exhaustion

192
00:17:24,220 --> 00:17:27,110
-他胡说的  -这就是你的诊断么?
-He's faking it.  -Is that your medical opinion?

193
00:17:27,120 --> 00:17:30,750
A区热的让人有些神志不清了
We got a bunch of overheated cons getting loud in A-Wing.

194
00:17:30,760 --> 00:17:32,620
这不能怪他们  那里简直是个烤箱
I don't blame 'em. It's an oven in there

195
00:17:32,630 --> 00:17:33,840
这里一切正常
Everything's under control.

196
00:17:33,850 --> 00:17:36,210
但你必须立刻回到医务室
But you should go back to the infirmary building.

197
00:17:36,220 --> 00:17:37,730
等情况稳定下来
When things calm down,

198
00:17:37,740 --> 00:17:40,430
我会把病人送到你那里去的
 I'll have your patients transferred from Sick Bay.

199
00:17:40,440 --> 00:17:42,280
我这也是为你着想
I'm just looking out for your best interests.

200
00:17:42,290 --> 00:17:44,750
非常感谢
And I appreciate that.

201
00:17:44,760 --> 00:17:46,610
但是贝利克长官  你我都知道
But Officer Bellick, you and I both know that

202
00:17:46,620 --> 00:17:48,880
拒绝对犯人医治是犯法的
it's illegal to deny a prisoner medical care

203
00:17:48,890 --> 00:17:50,400
你也会因此丢掉饭碗的
and you could lose yourjob over it.

204
00:17:50,410 --> 00:17:53,810
我这也是在替你着想
and I'm just looking out for your best interests.

205
00:17:56,570 --> 00:17:59,870
请便吧
Go right on in.

206
00:17:59,880 --> 00:18:03,050
那就多谢了
Thank you, sir.

207
00:18:04,820 --> 00:18:06,890
T-bag 别像个孩子似的
Don't be a baby, T-Bag.

208
00:18:06,900 --> 00:18:09,460
没那么热
It ain't that hot.

209
00:18:09,470 --> 00:18:12,310
还不够热么?!
Not that hot?!

210
00:18:12,320 --> 00:18:17,990
这哥们早上起床时还是白人呢!
When this guy woke up this morning,he was white!

211
00:18:24,280 --> 00:18:27,250
你想凉快下来是么?
You wanna cool off?

212
00:18:28,540 --> 00:18:31,100
退后!
Step back.

213
00:18:34,560 --> 00:18:40,440
有冷风后我们自然会回去的
We'll step back when we get some wind blowing in here.

214
00:18:43,390 --> 00:18:46,180
好吧  你们自找的!一级禁闭!
All right! That's it! Lockdown!

215
00:18:46,190 --> 00:18:48,030
都回到牢房里去!
Everyone back to your cells!

216
00:18:48,040 --> 00:18:53,150
我让你们都回到牢房里  臭犯人!
I said everyone back to your cells.Now, convicts!

217
00:18:53,160 --> 00:18:55,680
一级禁闭!
Lockdown!

218
00:18:56,540 --> 00:18:58,430
你得到了你的禁闭  伙计
You got your lockdown.bro, Do your thing.

219
00:18:58,440 --> 00:19:00,890
-你也得一起来  -什么? 不  不  不
-You're coming with me.  － What? No, no, no, no.

220
00:19:00,900 --> 00:19:02,730
我只负责把风伙计  仅此而已
I'm the lookout, man, that's it.

221
00:19:02,740 --> 00:19:05,950
我需要你帮忙 这是俩人的活
I need you down there. It's a two-man job.

222
00:19:05,960 --> 00:19:07,080
把床单挂上
Let's hang a sheet.

223
00:19:07,090 --> 00:19:07,750
不 这不行  伙计
N-N-No way, man.

224
00:19:07,750 --> 00:19:11,060
难道不知道只有想和狱友亲热的时候才挂那个
You only hang a sheet when you and your cellie wanna get friendly.you know?

225
00:19:11,070 --> 00:19:12,680
你想保持在监狱里的声誉
You wanna protect your prison rep?

226
00:19:12,690 --> 00:19:16,000
还是想离开这儿?
Or you wanna get out of here?

227
00:20:18,000 --> 00:20:20,140
这里到底是怎么回事?
What the hell's going on in here?

228
00:20:20,150 --> 00:20:22,850
犯人异常兴奋  都不肯回去
Well, these inmates became belligerent and they refused to rack in.

229
00:20:22,860 --> 00:20:25,630
有的犯人还没回到牢房你就把门关上了是么?
You locked it down with inmates still out of their cells?

230
00:20:25,640 --> 00:20:30,270
20个总比300个人要好处理的多
We can handle 20 out-of-control inmates easier than 300.

231
00:20:32,280 --> 00:20:36,020
听着  伙计  贝利克  我有话要告诉你
Listen up, bros.Listen up. Bellick.I got one for you.

232
00:20:36,030 --> 00:20:39,100
你知道如何称呼一个无法通过警察考试的白种猪头
What do you call a piece of white trash who couldn't pass the cops exam

233
00:20:39,110 --> 00:20:41,610
而现在混的却连个邮差都不如的人么?
and now makes less than a mailman?

234
00:20:41,620 --> 00:20:44,790
狱警
A CO.

235
00:20:46,280 --> 00:20:47,450
把手从栅栏上拿开
Get your hands off the fence.

236
00:20:47,460 --> 00:20:48,630
去你的  猪!
Suck it, pig!

237
00:20:55,150 --> 00:20:58,190
特迪 你真的很我很失望 我实在不想说你
You know, Teddy, You really let me down.And that's hard to do,

238
00:20:58,200 --> 00:21:00,450
因为我的期望值不是很高
because I don't expect much

239
00:21:00,460 --> 00:21:05,390
尤其是对个天生的智障
from the inbred child of a retard.

240
00:21:06,850 --> 00:21:09,620
没错 特迪
That's right, Teddy.

241
00:21:09,630 --> 00:21:11,810
我看过你的病例
I read your psych records.

242
00:21:11,820 --> 00:21:15,760
某人的爸爸强奸了他的白痴妹妹
About how your daddy raped his mongoloid sister

243
00:21:15,770 --> 00:21:21,610
然而在9个月后小特迪破壳而出了
and then nine months later little Teddy pops out.

244
00:21:24,700 --> 00:21:27,810
老子宰了你
I'm gonna kill you!

245
00:21:35,580 --> 00:21:36,950
简直比地狱还热
Hot as hell.

246
00:21:36,960 --> 00:21:41,400
用不了多久他们就会吃不消的
They'll wear themselves out eventually.

247
00:21:44,690 --> 00:21:46,040
电话里说的是假的
The call was a fake.

248
00:21:46,050 --> 00:21:47,940
那能不能延缓我的死刑?
What about a stay of execution or...?

249
00:21:47,950 --> 00:21:49,450
不行  法律依据还不足
No no It's legally insufficient.

250
00:21:49,460 --> 00:21:52,410
这是什么意思
What the hell does that mean?

251
00:21:52,420 --> 00:21:53,870
这又是为什么?
What the hell does that mean?

252
00:21:53,880 --> 00:21:57,030
因为他们指出了你的罪证
It means the prosecution could point out the evidence from your criminal trial.okay?

253
00:21:57,040 --> 00:22:00,250
血样  录像  还有枪
The blood, the video, the gun.

254
00:22:00,260 --> 00:22:04,680
一个可疑的电话不足以否定那些的
A questionable phone call is not gonna stack up to that.

255
00:22:04,690 --> 00:22:07,620
-但的确能说明些问题  对么?  -是的
-But it's something, right?  -Absolutely.

256
00:22:07,630 --> 00:22:08,700
我们有区号
 We got an area code.

257
00:22:08,710 --> 00:22:11,440
我的人将会继续跟踪那个号码 这样就能确定具体的
and my contact is going to track that number to someplace more specific

258
00:22:11,450 --> 00:22:13,420
大楼  地区  或是街区
a building,a neighbourhood, a block

259
00:22:13,430 --> 00:22:15,350
然后找到打那个电话的人
to the person who made this call.

260
00:22:15,360 --> 00:22:16,640
然后呢?
OK. What happens next?

261
00:22:16,650 --> 00:22:19,470
我们必须马上去赶开往华盛顿的飞机
We need to catch the next flight to DC.

262
00:22:19,480 --> 00:22:23,990
前提是  你现在要相信我
That is, of course, if you trust me now.

263
00:22:25,530 --> 00:22:27,260
是时候了!
It's coming.

264
00:22:27,270 --> 00:22:30,160
时候到了! 时候到了!
It's coming! It's coming!

265
00:22:30,170 --> 00:22:32,900
来呀!
Get on the train! Whoo!

266
00:22:42,780 --> 00:22:45,220
来呀!
Get on the train!

267
00:22:45,230 --> 00:22:47,250
来呀!
Get on the train!

268
00:22:47,260 --> 00:22:49,630
跟我回办公室
Let's get to my office.

269
00:22:49,640 --> 00:22:51,390
正如我所料
Oh, just what I thought.

270
00:22:51,400 --> 00:22:53,680
小猪怕大狼
The piglets are scared of the big bad wolf.

271
00:22:53,690 --> 00:22:56,500
大坏狼!
Big bad wolf!

272
00:22:57,770 --> 00:23:00,440
正如我所料
Oh, just what I thought.

273
00:23:00,450 --> 00:23:04,170
再加把劲儿
Get on the train!

274
00:23:15,750 --> 00:23:18,100
快走
Come on.

275
00:23:54,470 --> 00:23:57,200
玛丽莲 不!
Marilyn, no!

276
00:24:19,330 --> 00:24:21,440
这是谁的钥匙?
Whose keys are those?

277
00:24:21,450 --> 00:24:24,400
可能是暴动的时候
I guess in the commotion...

278
00:24:27,230 --> 00:24:32,120
你的子弹够干掉几个人?
How many rounds you think you're going to get off before they get their hands on you?

279
00:24:34,310 --> 00:24:35,910
我是贝利克
This is Bellick.

280
00:24:35,920 --> 00:24:38,100
我们的地区已经被突破
Our wing has been breached.

281
00:24:38,110 --> 00:24:40,280
请求关闭A区并撤退
I want A-Wing evacuated and shut down.

282
00:24:40,290 --> 00:24:43,650
同时关闭通往B区的入口
All access to B-Wing cut off now.

283
00:24:51,200 --> 00:24:54,100
为你输点液就会没事了  好么?
I'm gonna get some fluids into you,you'll be good as new.

284
00:24:54,110 --> 00:24:57,080
相信我的话就点点头
Nod your head if you believe me.

285
00:24:57,090 --> 00:24:59,850
好样的
Good man.

286
00:25:00,410 --> 00:25:02,040
西奥
Theo.

287
00:25:02,050 --> 00:25:04,850
今天能为你做些什么?
What can we do for you today?

288
00:25:07,650 --> 00:25:09,290
是这儿么?
Hmm. This where it hurts?

289
00:25:09,300 --> 00:25:11,070
左面再往上点
A little higher and to the left

290
00:25:11,080 --> 00:25:13,150
你刚做完手术三个礼拜
You're three weeks post-op.

291
00:25:13,160 --> 00:25:15,440
膝盖现在还是用一根棍和三颗钉子固定在一起
Your knee's held together by a rod and three screws.

292
00:25:15,450 --> 00:25:18,990
所以敏感是正常的 不必再用药了
I'm saying tenderness is normal. No more meds.

293
00:25:19,000 --> 00:25:22,560
酷密 你又怎么了?
OK. Kwame, why are you back?

294
00:25:22,570 --> 00:25:24,130
犯人已经突破了禁闭
Inmates in cell block have compromised

295
00:25:24,140 --> 00:25:26,840
并且突破了A区的警卫站
lockdown and breached A-Wing.

296
00:25:26,850 --> 00:25:28,380
A区将关闭
A-Wing is shutting down.

297
00:25:28,390 --> 00:25:31,960
人多力量大!
It's popping off up in G Pop!

298
00:25:48,690 --> 00:25:50,270
在墙那边的某处
Somewhere on the other side of this wall

299
00:25:50,280 --> 00:25:54,470
是通往旧排水系统的主管道
is the main drainage pipe to the prison's old sewer system.

300
00:25:56,670 --> 00:26:00,620
只要能穿过这面墙 就能进入到管子里
If we can get through this wall,we can get into the pipe.

301
00:26:01,350 --> 00:26:05,120
到了管子里  就能到医务室
we can get into the pipe,we can get into the infirmary.

302
00:26:06,990 --> 00:26:12,350
如果能到达医务室 咱们就可以离开这儿了
If we can get to the infirmary,then we can get out of here.

303
00:26:14,100 --> 00:26:16,110
抱歉  所有来访者都必须马上离开
Sorry, all visitors have to leave the facility

304
00:26:16,120 --> 00:26:18,050
-我是授权律师  -你必须得离开
-This is privileged attorney...  -you have to leave.

305
00:26:18,060 --> 00:26:19,790
牢区内发生了小骚动
There's a minor disturbance in cell block.

306
00:26:19,800 --> 00:26:22,570
为安全起见  A区已经关闭
 A-Wing is being shut down for safety purposes.

307
00:26:22,580 --> 00:26:25,360
A区?维罗妮卡,迈克尔还在那儿
A-Wing? Veronica, Michael's in there.

308
00:26:25,370 --> 00:26:27,740
-他不会有事吧?  -你得走了
-Will he be OK?  -You have to leave now.

309
00:26:27,750 --> 00:26:29,490
去华盛顿  也只能这样了
Go to DC. It's all we've got.

310
00:26:29,500 --> 00:26:30,920
我会照顾迈克尔的  好么?
I'll take care of Michael. All right?

311
00:26:30,930 --> 00:26:34,090
-好的  -麻烦你了
-okay  -Please.

312
00:26:35,590 --> 00:26:36,800
不好意思打断你们
Sorry about cutting you short.

313
00:26:36,810 --> 00:26:39,950
鲍勃,和你说过多少次 道歉会使你看起来软弱
Bob, how many times have I told you not to apologize. It makes you look weak.

314
00:26:39,960 --> 00:26:40,840
现在情况如何?
Now What's going on?

315
00:26:40,850 --> 00:26:42,690
正如我所说  小骚动
Like I said,It's a minor disturbance.

316
00:26:42,700 --> 00:26:47,180
小骚动? 我弟弟也在里面 带我过去
Minor disturbance? My brother is in Gen Pop.Give it to me straight.

317
00:26:47,190 --> 00:26:49,270
一些混蛋弄坏了牢区门
Some clowns breached cell block.

318
00:26:49,280 --> 00:26:50,640
但他们哪儿也去不了
But they won't get anywhere.

319
00:26:50,650 --> 00:26:52,210
两头的门都被我们锁上了
We always have locked doors on either end.

320
00:26:52,220 --> 00:26:55,160
没有什么可担心的
There's nothing to worry about.

321
00:26:55,420 --> 00:26:58,390
婊子养的
Son of a bitch.

322
00:27:00,450 --> 00:27:04,480
A区的又一部分被突破
Additional sectors of A-Wing have been compromised.

323
00:27:19,920 --> 00:27:23,080
乖乖
I'll be damned!

324
00:27:23,090 --> 00:27:27,940
一个菜鸟狱警 圣诞节还没到呢
A rookie CO, and it ain't even Christmas!

325
00:27:27,950 --> 00:27:31,890
帮我把手铐打开
Take the cuffs off. Give me the key.

326
00:27:33,200 --> 00:27:36,770
到别的地方去 T-Bag
Get out of here, T-Bag.

327
00:27:36,780 --> 00:27:39,580
哦  我懂 是你先发现他的  谁发现是谁的?
Oh, I see. You found him first.Finders keepers.

328
00:27:39,590 --> 00:27:43,370
我也同意那样做  不过
You know, I respect that. I do.

329
00:27:43,380 --> 00:27:46,070
凡事好商量
But I think we can work something out.

330
00:27:46,080 --> 00:27:47,330
你想怎样?
What you got?

331
00:27:47,340 --> 00:27:51,430
我可以使你在地球上剩下的几周非常  非常的快活
Oh, I can make your last few weeks on Earth quite, quite enjoyable.

332
00:27:51,440 --> 00:27:53,740
给你些粉儿  或是
Get you some Demerol, some X.

333
00:27:53,750 --> 00:27:57,440
足够使你忘掉那个大电椅
You know, Make you forget about that big bad chair.

334
00:27:57,450 --> 00:27:59,770
不行
No deal.

335
00:27:59,880 --> 00:28:02,900
你得多学学谈判的艺术
You gotta learn that art of negotiating.

336
00:28:02,910 --> 00:28:08,120
首先: 明确自己的地位
Lesson one -bargaining position.

337
00:28:08,130 --> 00:28:11,050
你的地位刚好变了
Rules just changed.  Get the pig!

338
00:28:13,770 --> 00:28:16,570
-你想干什么?  -我要逃出去
-What are you doing?  -I gotta get out of here.

339
00:28:16,580 --> 00:28:17,910
看看周围  你跑不掉的
Look around,You're not gonna make it.

340
00:28:17,920 --> 00:28:21,280
不会见血的 大水缸
No blood needs to spill, Sink.

341
00:28:21,290 --> 00:28:23,590
那还不走开
Then walk away.

342
00:28:23,600 --> 00:28:25,740
咱们都知道这是不可能的
We both know that ain't gonna happen.

343
00:28:25,750 --> 00:28:28,100
没错
Yeah?

344
00:28:44,370 --> 00:28:46,540
混凝土好厚啊
That's one big pile of concrete.

345
00:28:46,550 --> 00:28:49,730
你怎么知道管道在那儿
How do you know where the pipe is?

346
00:28:50,620 --> 00:28:53,210
我请来了帮手
We've got someone to show us where it is.

347
00:28:53,220 --> 00:28:56,750
真的? 是谁?
Oh, really? Who?

348
00:29:06,530 --> 00:29:07,890
感染的不太严重
infection's not so bad.

349
00:29:07,900 --> 00:29:10,250
但为了以防万一我还是要给你打针青霉素  好么?
but I'm going to give you a shot of penicillin just to make sure, okay?

350
00:29:10,260 --> 00:29:12,840
多谢了  医生
Thanks, Doc.

351
00:29:21,530 --> 00:29:24,170
这里是Rizzo 有人需要支援么  完毕
This is Rizzo.Does anyone need back up, over?

352
00:29:24,180 --> 00:29:26,850
不用了 A区已经撤离并关闭
Negative. A-Wing is evacuating and locked down.

353
00:29:26,860 --> 00:29:29,400
待在B区
Remain in B-Wing.

354
00:29:40,150 --> 00:29:42,840
你好啊  医生?
What's up, Doc?

355
00:30:01,000 --> 00:30:05,190
来吧  医生
Come on, Doc.

356
00:30:05,470 --> 00:30:08,670
你不要这样
You don't wanna do this.

357
00:30:22,000 --> 00:30:27,620
很抱歉  这条线遇到了技术故障
We're sorry. This line is experiencing technical difficulties.

358
00:30:33,330 --> 00:30:35,170
你有没有看过狩猎节目
You ever see one of them safari shows

359
00:30:35,180 --> 00:30:39,030
一群猎豹冲向一只羚羊
where a bunch of cheetahs jump up on an antelope?

360
00:30:39,030 --> 00:30:42,190
想想你是哪个?
Guess which one you are.

361
00:31:07,610 --> 00:31:10,890
难缠的小猩猩  对吧?
Tough little gorilla, ain't he?

362
00:31:18,000 --> 00:31:21,000
虽然我一直相信恶魔具有某种邪恶的力量
I was raised to believe the devil's got some crazy power,

363
00:31:21,010 --> 00:31:24,020
但还是不会认为他能帮咱们把这堵墙推倒
but I don't think shining him on this wall is gonna bring it down.

364
00:31:24,030 --> 00:31:26,450
除非他再有个大锤
Not unless he's got a sledgehammer.

365
00:31:26,460 --> 00:31:29,620
没必要用大锤
We don't need a sledgehammer.

366
00:31:34,580 --> 00:31:37,770
我用这个能干个鸟?
What the hell am I supposed to do with this?

367
00:31:40,650 --> 00:31:42,290
医务室  请回答!
Sick Bay, report.

368
00:31:42,300 --> 00:31:45,030
医务室  请回答!
Sick Bay, please report.

369
00:31:45,040 --> 00:31:49,540
Rizzo,你那里还好吧?
Rizzo, is everything OK?

370
00:31:55,430 --> 00:31:58,580
医务室一切正常  完毕!
All clear in Sick Bay. Over.

371
00:31:58,590 --> 00:32:01,600
收到
Roger that.

372
00:32:05,280 --> 00:32:07,370
让狱警们去平息暴乱吧
Let the bulls worry about the noise.

373
00:32:07,380 --> 00:32:10,460
你应该知道怎么打通这面六英尺厚的混凝土墙
You worry about how you're gonna drill through a six-inch concrete wall

374
00:32:10,470 --> 00:32:12,450
竟然用这么一个捣蛋器
with what used to be an egg beater.

375
00:32:12,460 --> 00:32:14,180
只要几个小洞就行
We just need a few small holes.

376
00:32:14,190 --> 00:32:15,970
我们能从小洞中钻出去么?
How can we fit through small holes?

377
00:32:15,980 --> 00:32:18,080
听说过抗拉强度么?
Ever hear of tensile strength?

378
00:32:18,090 --> 00:32:20,230
胡克弹性定律?
Hooke's Law of elasticity?

379
00:32:20,240 --> 00:32:21,610
你是怎么想的?
 What do you think?

380
00:32:21,620 --> 00:32:23,380
我们只需在几个重点位置打好孔
If we drill holes in strategic locations,

381
00:32:23,390 --> 00:32:26,780
这样就破坏掉了墙的承载力
we compromise the load-carrying capacity of the wall.

382
00:32:26,790 --> 00:32:28,440
说点我听得懂的成么?
How about speaking English?

383
00:32:28,450 --> 00:32:31,470
我们就打通了盖住管道口的墙
We'll be able to break through the part of the wall that covers the pip

384
00:32:31,480 --> 00:32:33,700
把那个给我
Give me that.

385
00:32:33,710 --> 00:32:36,900
我们在每个角尖  眼睛
We go in through the tip of each horn,the eyes,

386
00:32:36,910 --> 00:32:38,070
鼻子末端
 the end of the nose,

387
00:32:38,080 --> 00:32:40,610
牙齿的尽头  头发的末端
the bottom of the fangs, and end of the braids.

388
00:32:40,620 --> 00:32:43,190
(连起来)就像是个"X"
It makes a kind of X.

389
00:32:43,200 --> 00:32:46,420
我们开始吧
Let's get to it.

390
00:32:54,890 --> 00:32:59,000
如果我们使用政府下发的新式武器
If I can get DIRT in there with some of the newer firepower...

391
00:32:59,010 --> 00:33:02,370
没错 我们今天就会结束暴乱 然后为他们再举行个葬礼了
Oh, yeah, so we can end the riots today and start funerals tomorrow?

392
00:33:02,380 --> 00:33:03,610
我可以控制住(局势)的
I can contain this.sir

393
00:33:03,620 --> 00:33:05,620
-有个电话找您  -现在不行
-Warden, I got a call for you.  -Not now.

394
00:33:05,630 --> 00:33:09,190
我想您还是接一下吧  是州长
I think you should take it. It's the governor.

395
00:33:09,200 --> 00:33:11,420
-长官  -我女儿在哪儿?
-Governor.  -Where's my daughter?

396
00:33:11,430 --> 00:33:12,600
不必担心  她很好
Not to worry, sir. She's fine.

397
00:33:12,610 --> 00:33:14,380
她在B区的医务室
She's in Sick Bay in B-Wing.

398
00:33:14,390 --> 00:33:16,400
和A区完全不同的一区
It's a completely different part of the facility,

399
00:33:16,410 --> 00:33:18,890
那里和骚动区完全隔离
It's, uh, totally locked off from the disturbance.

400
00:33:18,900 --> 00:33:21,050
骚动?  你就是这么称暴乱的么?
Disturbance? That's what you're calling a riot nowadays?

401
00:33:21,050 --> 00:33:23,440
那些畜生有没有可能接触到我女儿?
Can these animals get to her?

402
00:33:23,450 --> 00:33:27,490
先生  任何人都不可能从A区到达医务室的
Sir, it's impossible for anyone from A-Wing to get into Sick Bay.

403
00:33:27,500 --> 00:33:29,490
警卫已经确认一切正常
A guard there assures us that everything is fine.

404
00:33:29,500 --> 00:33:31,340
一切都在我们的控制中  长官
We have everything under control.Governor

405
00:33:31,350 --> 00:33:35,760
为了你自己  你最好那样
For your sake, you'd better hope you do.

406
00:33:46,190 --> 00:33:49,070
我要和你跳舞  医生!
I'm gonna dance with you, Doc!

407
00:33:49,320 --> 00:33:50,240
一直跳到天亮!
We are going to dance till the sun come up!

408
00:33:50,740 --> 00:33:53,240
过来  医生  把门打开
Come on, Doc!Open the door!

409
00:34:01,560 --> 00:34:03,150
换你来
All right. It's your turn.

410
00:34:03,160 --> 00:34:05,140
我不能惊动恶魔  伙计
No. I ain't messing with no diablo.

411
00:34:05,150 --> 00:34:06,870
我们不能停下来
man, We can't afford downtime.

412
00:34:06,880 --> 00:34:08,080
必须轮流钻
We have to switch off drilling.

413
00:34:08,090 --> 00:34:09,710
这可不是什么好兆头  伙计 你开玩笑呢?
It's bad mojo.bro Are you kidding me?

414
00:34:09,720 --> 00:34:11,210
我惊动了他  你在他上面钻孔
I mess with him,you drill into him,

415
00:34:11,220 --> 00:34:13,090
他就会被激怒  然后会怎样?
he gets pissed.and then what?

416
00:34:13,100 --> 00:34:16,680
我的敌人已经够多的了
I got enough enemies already, papi. OK?

417
00:34:16,690 --> 00:34:19,230
你信上帝  对么?
You believe in God, right?

418
00:34:19,240 --> 00:34:20,570
你知道我信
You know I do.

419
00:34:20,580 --> 00:34:22,930
所以你是受上帝保护的
So you're protected.

420
00:34:22,940 --> 00:34:27,220
他会保护你的
He'll protect you.From him.

421
00:35:00,560 --> 00:35:04,240
我向你们保证 一旦我和鲍勃无法达成一致...
I assure you, once Bob and I are don't getting acquainte...

422
00:35:04,250 --> 00:35:06,340
我们千刀万剐了他
We blaze him!

423
00:35:06,350 --> 00:35:09,790
谁都有机会
...everyone else will get their turn.

424
00:35:09,800 --> 00:35:15,440
好啊!
yeah

425
00:35:19,360 --> 00:35:21,460
咱们去玩点好玩的
We're gonna have a little fun, Bobby.

426
00:35:21,460 --> 00:35:23,600
不用担心
Don't worry.

427
00:35:23,610 --> 00:35:25,650
我不脏
I don't got the blickey.

428
00:35:25,660 --> 00:35:28,540
我的那儿很干净
My pipes are clean.

429
00:35:30,390 --> 00:35:33,600
你现在又想去哪儿  菜鸟?
Where are you going, rookie?

430
00:35:35,890 --> 00:35:39,990
不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no.

431
00:35:40,000 --> 00:35:45,660
他们总认为自己能够跑掉
They always think they can run away.

432
00:36:00,160 --> 00:36:03,430
我有个问题想问你  菜鸟
Got a question for you, fish.

433
00:36:04,660 --> 00:36:07,840
咱们打通这堵墙后 却发现管道在十英尺外怎么办?
What if we do all this work and the pipe is ten feet that way?

434
00:36:07,850 --> 00:36:11,020
-不会的  -你会X光透视?
-It won't be.  -you got X-ray vision?

435
00:36:11,030 --> 00:36:13,030
我计算过钻孔点的坐标
I calculated the drill point coordinates,

436
00:36:13,040 --> 00:36:16,420
把他们标在我的纹身里 然后在把他们的位置还原到墙上
hid them in my tattoo and then projected them onto the wall.

437
00:36:16,430 --> 00:36:19,540
所有的点都经过计算 图像会表示出正确的位置
Everything's been worked out so the image hits the right spot.

438
00:36:19,550 --> 00:36:20,680
只不过是数学问题罢了
It's just math.

439
00:36:20,690 --> 00:36:23,440
你要是计算错了呢?
What if your math is wrong?

440
00:36:23,450 --> 00:36:26,540
你会钻到墙那边的某根煤气管道里
You'll drill into one of a dozen gas lines behind the wall.

441
00:36:26,550 --> 00:36:30,340
然后会爆炸  我们将活活的被烧死
There'll be an explosion and we'll be burned alive.

442
00:36:33,450 --> 00:36:36,920
你数学学的不错  对吧?
But you're good at math, right?

443
00:37:08,970 --> 00:37:11,800
他们想越狱
They're breaking out.

444
00:37:19,000 --> 00:37:25,960
-他们要  -嘘
-They're breaking...  -Shh.

445
00:37:49,280 --> 00:37:53,750
你来,你胳膊比我长
Yo, Stroke.You got longer arms than me, man.

446
00:37:57,040 --> 00:38:00,470
噢! 婊子
Agh! Son of a...

447
00:38:05,520 --> 00:38:08,440
那婊子戳我
That bitch stuck me.

448
00:38:23,050 --> 00:38:25,990
他们还不嫌热么?我要切断所有的水源
You think it's hot now?I want all the water shut off.

449
00:38:26,000 --> 00:38:30,270
-我去处理  -麦克尔 这事交给你了
-I'll call it in.  -Mack, you take care of it.

450
00:38:30,320 --> 00:38:32,690
遵命
Yes, sir.

451
00:38:42,730 --> 00:38:45,810
-我们现在遇到点问题   -噢 说的没错
-Yeah, we... we have a problem.   -That's right.

452
00:38:45,820 --> 00:38:49,610
鲍勃看到这个洞了 应该干掉他
Yeah, Bob here's seen the hole. He's gotta go away.

453
00:38:53,350 --> 00:38:56,820
-谁也不能死  -他看到洞了
-No one's going anywhere.  -He's seen the hole.

454
00:38:56,830 --> 00:38:59,730
你也看到了
So have you.

455
00:38:59,740 --> 00:39:03,350
看来戒严的主意还不够好  是吧?
Looks like your lockdown idea didn't work out too good, huh?

456
00:39:03,360 --> 00:39:07,070
我有个女儿  求你们了
I have a daughter. Please.

457
00:39:08,310 --> 00:39:09,670
我们得干掉他
We gotta kill him.

458
00:39:09,680 --> 00:39:12,640
警察就在外面
The cops are right outside.

459
00:39:12,740 --> 00:39:14,820
他们会一直守在那里
And they'll stay outside.

460
00:39:14,830 --> 00:39:17,000
只要他们知道我们还让他活着
As long as they know we're keeping him alive.

461
00:39:17,010 --> 00:39:18,040
他毕竟是个警卫
But he's a guard.

462
00:39:18,040 --> 00:39:19,430
他会出卖我们的
He's gonna squeal.

463
00:39:19,430 --> 00:39:23,370
他干什么关你卵事?
What the hell does this have to do with you anyway?

464
00:39:23,380 --> 00:39:27,680
这用不着你操心
This is not any of your concern.

465
00:39:31,280 --> 00:39:35,680
看  现在鲍勃知道了咱们的秘密
See, Bob here knows about our secret.

466
00:39:35,690 --> 00:39:40,100
他知道了咱们要越狱
He knows about our escape.

467
00:39:40,350 --> 00:39:44,960
所以这是事关大家的事  不是么?
So it's all of our concern now, isn't it?

468
00:40:01,130 --> 00:40:04,200
没事的  大块头  是我
Easy, big fella. It's just me.

469
00:40:04,210 --> 00:40:07,280
看来你伤得不轻啊
Looks like you took a pretty good hit.

470
00:40:09,990 --> 00:40:12,600
他们把警卫弄到牢房里了
Cons got that rook guard in Gen Pop.

471
00:40:12,610 --> 00:40:15,110
那孩子可能已经死了 宁愿他已经死了
Kid's probably dead already, or wishing he was.

472
00:40:15,120 --> 00:40:16,350
斯科菲尔德在哪儿?
Where's Scofield?

473
00:40:16,360 --> 00:40:18,030
自从开始闹事我就没见到他
Haven't seen him since things jumped off.

474
00:40:18,040 --> 00:40:19,050
我得去找他
I gotta find him.

475
00:40:19,050 --> 00:40:21,120
你在找斯科菲尔德?
You looking for Scofield?

476
00:40:21,130 --> 00:40:22,430
是的 
Yeah, Turk.

477
00:40:22,440 --> 00:40:24,730
跟我来
Come on.

478
00:40:34,070 --> 00:40:35,710
你差点坏了事  你这个疯子
You got things backwards, pervert.

479
00:40:35,720 --> 00:40:38,400
你的处境和他差不多了  明白么?
You're in as much trouble as he is. You understand?

480
00:40:38,410 --> 00:40:41,650
来啊   来啊  接着打  接着打
Go ahead. Go ahead. Stick me, stick me.

481
00:40:41,660 --> 00:40:43,750
看看在被你打死前
Let's see how many times I can shout out

482
00:40:43,750 --> 00:40:45,840
我能喊出多少声  比赛不?
about your little hole in there before I bleed out, huh?

483
00:40:45,850 --> 00:40:48,550
到时候你们的逃跑将变成众人皆知的秘密
'Cause every con in here is gonna know about your little escape

484
00:40:48,560 --> 00:40:51,810
在我第一滴血滴到地上前
before one drip of my blood hits the floor.

485
00:40:51,820 --> 00:40:53,950
不信你就试试吧  朋友
So you see, friends,

486
00:40:53,960 --> 00:40:55,760
要么咱们一起穿过那个洞
either I'm through that hole with you

487
00:40:55,770 --> 00:40:59,500
要么我像强尼·卡什一样歌唱(Johnny Cash－美国传奇乡村音乐人)
or I'm gonna sing like Johnny Cash.

488
00:41:25,130 --> 00:41:29,560
嘿  伙计 斯卓克就快抓住医生了!
Hey, yo! Check it!Stroke is about to get the doc.

489
00:41:43,860 --> 00:41:45,980
苏克雷  我需要你完成刚才的工作
Sucre, I need you to finish what we started.

490
00:41:45,990 --> 00:41:47,040
出什么事了  伙计? 你要去哪儿?
Where are you going,man?Where you going?

491
00:41:47,050 --> 00:41:48,000
医务室
Sick Bay.

492
00:41:48,010 --> 00:41:50,740
嘿  根本到不了B区 我们被堵死了
Hey There's no way to B-Wing. We're all locked out.

493
00:41:50,750 --> 00:41:54,310
我不这么认为  谁也不许动狱警
I'm not. No one touches the CO.

494
00:41:54,320 --> 00:41:56,600
谁也不行
No one.

495
00:42:03,390 --> 00:42:07,340
加我一个吧  老哥?
You gonna clue me in, paisano?

496
00:42:10,920 --> 00:42:14,190
从这边走能快点
It's faster if we cut through here.

497
00:42:14,910 --> 00:42:18,700
布伦斯死定了
Burrows is as good as dead.

498
00:36:02,350 --> 00:36:05,750
就一点点时间而已
Just give me the time.

