1
00:00:03,700 --> 00:00:05,700
知道我们队伍里危机四伏吧
You got a couple foxes in your hen house, right

2
00:00:05,800 --> 00:00:07,100
他们都想出去
They both want out of here.

3
00:00:07,200 --> 00:00:08,300
在出去前他们不会惹麻烦的
They'll behave until then.

4
00:00:08,400 --> 00:00:09,400
听着 情况就是这样严峻
Look, this is it, man.

5
00:00:09,500 --> 00:00:10,900
这次根本没有推翻重来的机会
Ain't no do-overs this time.

6
00:00:11,100 --> 00:00:11,900
我们今晚就越狱
We break out tonight

7
00:00:12,500 --> 00:00:13,600
要不然就永远出不去了
or we ain't never getting out

8
00:00:16,600 --> 00:00:18,400
这都是斯科菲尔德一手策划的吧
Brains of the outfit, huh, Scofield

9
00:00:20,100 --> 00:00:22,000
他正引领你们走向深渊
He's leading you off a cliff, boys

10
00:00:22,400 --> 00:00:24,700
听上去你还是这儿的负责人
Now you're acting like you still in charge.

11
00:00:25,000 --> 00:00:25,900
就当我不在场
Pretend I ain't here.

12
00:00:26,000 --> 00:00:28,100
是啊 也可以假装你不会用对讲机报警
Yeah, you and the radio.

13
00:00:32,300 --> 00:00:33,900
有件事情我还没搞清楚
The thing I can't quite figure is

14
00:00:34,000 --> 00:00:36,800
事情现在闹得这么大
with the crap storm this thing's become

15
00:00:37,300 --> 00:00:38,900
他们为什么还没有杀了你
why they haven't killed you.

16
00:00:39,300 --> 00:00:41,500
我们有个员工表现不怎么的
We have an employee. She's not working out.

17
00:00:42,300 --> 00:00:42,900
我们炒了她鱿鱼
We fire her.

18
00:00:43,800 --> 00:00:44,800
就应该处理地这么简单
It needs to be that simple.

19
00:00:44,900 --> 00:00:47,100
她毕竟是美利坚合众国的副总统啊
She's the Vice President of the United States.

20
00:00:47,200 --> 00:00:48,600
她当不了多久了 吉姆
And that's all she'll ever be, Jim.

21
00:00:49,000 --> 00:00:49,800
你要对我怎么样?
What's going on?

22
00:00:50,200 --> 00:00:51,600
去布莱克福特把斯蒂德曼找出来
You get to Blackfoot, you find Steadman.

23
00:00:52,500 --> 00:00:53,700
就请你再给我次机会
Just give me a chance.

24
00:00:54,100 --> 00:00:54,700
不要!
No!

25
00:00:55,100 --> 00:00:55,800
律师在哪里?
Where's the lawyer?

26
00:01:03,200 --> 00:01:03,900
我们成功了
We're through.

27
00:01:23,900 --> 00:01:24,800
老家伙 你还撑的住吗
You okay, old man

28
00:01:25,000 --> 00:01:25,600
我不行了
No!

29
00:01:27,000 --> 00:01:27,500
天哪
Oh, my God!

30
00:01:29,400 --> 00:01:30,100
快拉警报
Sound the alarm.

31
00:01:30,300 --> 00:01:31,100
快啊 迈克尔
Come on Michael!

32
00:01:31,500 --> 00:01:32,300
快拉警报
Sound the alarm!

33
00:01:32,700 --> 00:01:33,200
快啊
Come on!

34
00:01:35,800 --> 00:01:36,400
再加把劲
Come on!

35
00:01:40,600 --> 00:01:42,000
迈克尔 用力爬啊
Michael come on move it!

36
00:01:46,800 --> 00:01:47,700
抓住我的手
Michael grab my hand!

37
00:01:49,400 --> 00:01:50,300
抓住我的手...
Grab my hand.

38
00:02:21,600 --> 00:02:22,400
求求你 别开枪!
Don't shoot please!

39
00:02:24,600 --> 00:02:25,300
别开枪
Don't shoot!

40
00:02:25,400 --> 00:02:25,900
我们抓住了一个逃犯
We got a 10-98! Inmates over the wall!

41
00:02:26,000 --> 00:02:26,900
其他同伙都翻出墙跑了
Inmates over the wall!

42
00:02:29,000 --> 00:02:31,200
还有谁
Who was with you? Who was with you?

43
00:02:31,300 --> 00:02:32,100
没有了
Nobody!

44
00:02:32,500 --> 00:02:33,500
-没有人 是吧?  -没有人
-Nobody huh?   -No.

45
00:02:34,400 --> 00:02:35,500
快招 不然我对天发誓
Talk or I swear to God 

46
00:02:35,600 --> 00:02:36,500
我现在就把你脑袋拧下来
I'll snap your neck right here!

47
00:02:37,900 --> 00:02:38,600
我真的不知道
I don't know! I don't know!

48
00:02:39,900 --> 00:02:41,500
快报上其他人的姓名
Names. I want names.

49
00:02:43,400 --> 00:02:44,500
斯科菲尔德
Scofield...

50
00:02:45,700 --> 00:02:48,500
布伦斯 苏克雷
Burrows Sucre.

51
00:02:48,600 --> 00:02:49,900
还有那个小毛贼
And that Vanilla Ice kid.

52
00:02:50,300 --> 00:02:51,000
还有谁
Who else?

53
00:02:53,300 --> 00:02:54,500
博格威尔
Bagwell man.

54
00:02:55,300 --> 00:02:56,300
希诺特
C-Note.

55
00:02:56,900 --> 00:02:57,800
阿布鲁奇
Abruzzi.

56
00:02:58,700 --> 00:03:00,500
还有那个神经病
And that bug-eyed J-Cat...

57
00:03:00,900 --> 00:03:02,100
还有谁
Was there anybody else?

58
00:03:03,800 --> 00:03:05,300
快说还有谁
Was there anybody else?

59
00:03:08,600 --> 00:03:09,800
韦斯特莫兰德
Westmoreland.

60
00:03:18,000 --> 00:03:19,100
报告 有人越狱跑了
We got inmates over the wall. Repeat.

61
00:03:19,900 --> 00:03:20,600
多少人
How many?

62
00:03:20,700 --> 00:03:21,200
八个
Eight

63
00:04:26,900 --> 00:04:27,400
报告狱长
Warden

64
00:04:28,200 --> 00:04:29,100
刚刚找到贝利克了
they just found Bellick.

65
00:04:35,000 --> 00:04:36,100
把霰弹枪给我
Get me my shotgun.

66
00:04:36,200 --> 00:04:38,000
珀尔已经给所有的狱警布置任务了
Pope's already given orders for all the COs to hit the streets.

67
00:04:38,100 --> 00:04:39,200
你聋了吗
Did I stutter

68
00:04:40,000 --> 00:04:41,500
把霰弹枪给我
Get me my shotgun!

69
00:04:45,100 --> 00:04:45,800
这帮兔崽子
Those piles of crap 

70
00:04:45,900 --> 00:04:47,100
这么对待我
doing what they just did 

71
00:04:47,300 --> 00:04:48,700
他们死定了
they just signed their death warrant.

72
00:04:51,600 --> 00:04:52,800
谁都别想跑
Every last one of them.

73
00:05:00,700 --> 00:05:01,900
那些逃犯翻墙出去的时候
When those men went over the wall 

74
00:05:02,000 --> 00:05:03,100
已经做出了选择
they made a choice.

75
00:05:04,700 --> 00:05:07,400
这个选择使他们再次成为社会安定的威胁
That choice makes them a threat to society once again.

76
00:05:08,100 --> 00:05:09,100
正如你们所知道的那样
Now as many of you know 

77
00:05:09,500 --> 00:05:11,500
他们中的有些人已经被判杀人罪
some of those men are convicted killers.

78
00:05:12,500 --> 00:05:14,600
我们现在要站出来
Now our job

79
00:05:14,900 --> 00:05:17,500
确保整个社会的安稳
is to protect and ensure the safety of the general population

80
00:05:18,900 --> 00:05:22,100
意味着如果需要击毙他们来确保社会安全
That means if we have to bring them down to ensure that safety 

81
00:05:22,200 --> 00:05:23,900
看在上帝的份上那就那么做吧!
by God we will do it!

82
00:05:25,100 --> 00:05:26,900
同志们 这次我们可是来真的了
This time we're playing for keeps gentlemen

83
00:05:28,200 --> 00:05:29,600
现在离他们翻墙而出
Now it's been at least 12 minutes

84
00:05:29,700 --> 00:05:30,700
至少有12分钟了
since they went over that wall.

85
00:05:31,500 --> 00:05:33,600
他们徒步最多逃到一英里外
That's one mile on foot at best.

86
00:05:33,900 --> 00:05:35,200
如果有车子帮忙的话
If they've got their hands on a vehicle 

87
00:05:35,300 --> 00:05:37,000
可能已经逃到十英里开外了
they could be 10 miles from here.

88
00:05:37,600 --> 00:05:39,700
所以大家马上行动起来
So let's get moving!

89
00:06:08,200 --> 00:06:08,700
兄弟 抓紧时间
Yo come on man 

90
00:06:08,800 --> 00:06:09,800
我们得动起来
we gotta roll.

91
00:06:10,500 --> 00:06:12,700
我们什么也不用做就等在这儿
We don't got to do anything but wait right here

92
00:06:13,200 --> 00:06:14,700
让他们赶在我们前头好了
and let them get ahead of us.

93
00:06:14,800 --> 00:06:16,300
我不知道这样我们还有机会逃成功吗
I don't know if we're gonna get a chance papi.

94
00:06:18,000 --> 00:06:19,900
靠 有警犬
Dogs. Son of a bitch.

95
00:06:20,200 --> 00:06:21,300
他们正朝我们过来
They're coming right for us.

96
00:06:21,400 --> 00:06:22,400
都不要动
Nobody move.

97
00:06:30,900 --> 00:06:31,900
他们闻不到我们
They can't smell us.

98
00:06:35,000 --> 00:06:36,200
但是他们能看到我们
But they can see us.

99
00:07:37,700 --> 00:07:39,400
你好 我现在有事不能接听你的电话
Hey this is Nick. Can't get to the phone.

100
00:07:39,500 --> 00:07:40,200
请留言
Leave a message.

101
00:07:41,100 --> 00:07:42,200
尼克 是我啊
Hey Nick it's me.

102
00:07:42,300 --> 00:07:43,600
听着 我刚刚抵达蒙大拿
Look I just landed in Montana.

103
00:07:43,700 --> 00:07:45,400
现在我正在去布莱克福特的路上
I'm about an hour outside of Blackfoot.

104
00:07:45,500 --> 00:07:46,700
那幢房子
And this house 

105
00:07:46,800 --> 00:07:48,700
肯定和特伦斯·斯蒂德曼凶杀案有关
it's got something to do with Terrence Steadman's murder 

106
00:07:48,800 --> 00:07:49,500
我确定
I know it.

107
00:07:50,000 --> 00:07:51,800
如果在这儿能发现任何线索证明林肯的清白
And if whatever's here can help free Lincoln 

108
00:07:52,000 --> 00:07:54,400
我想对你说声谢谢
then I wanted to say thank you.

109
00:07:59,100 --> 00:08:01,400
有钱能使鬼推磨
Soft money makes the world go round.

110
00:08:01,500 --> 00:08:03,000
你知我知
You know it and I know it.

111
00:08:03,100 --> 00:08:04,100
你削减了我的竞选经费
You cut my funding

112
00:08:04,200 --> 00:08:06,900
我就没办法很好地参与竞选
and I can't run a proper campaign without it.

113
00:08:07,000 --> 00:08:09,300
相信我 公司内部对竞选款争议颇多
There was a lot of internal debate trust me.

114
00:08:09,400 --> 00:08:12,100
你完全可以凭借演说辞竞选成功
And there's every chance that you can still win with your message 

115
00:08:12,200 --> 00:08:15,400
-那样这笔钱就白白浪费了...  -噢 别再废话连篇了
-and it would certainly be our loss...  -Oh cut the crap.

116
00:08:16,000 --> 00:08:18,000
你还有什么想告诉我的吗
Is there anything else you want to tell me 

117
00:08:18,500 --> 00:08:22,100
还是说 你来这里是只是想落井下石
or did you just come here to twist the knife you stuck in my back?

118
00:08:22,200 --> 00:08:23,000
好吧 事实上
Well actually 

119
00:08:23,200 --> 00:08:25,600
我来这儿是为了致谢
I came here to express our gratitude

120
00:08:25,700 --> 00:08:27,700
感谢这些年来你为我们所作出的贡献
for all that you've done for us over the years.

121
00:08:28,200 --> 00:08:30,000
你要明白这不是私人间的致谢
And to let you know that this isn't personal.

122
00:08:30,600 --> 00:08:32,900
-当然你在政界摸爬滚打多年肯定能明白  -听着
-Surely you've been in politics long enough to know that.  -Look 

123
00:08:34,400 --> 00:08:35,900
是不是因为能源法令的原故?
is this about the energy bill?

124
00:08:36,300 --> 00:08:38,200
和能源法 毫不相关
The energy bill has nothing to do with it.

125
00:08:38,600 --> 00:08:41,400
为什么我觉得那么难以置信呢?
Why am I finding that so tough to believe?

126
00:08:44,000 --> 00:08:45,100
我是成年人
I'm a grown woman.

127
00:08:46,300 --> 00:08:48,300
不如你直截了当地挑明吧
How about you give it to me straight?

128
00:08:48,900 --> 00:08:49,600
好啊
All right.

129
00:08:51,400 --> 00:08:52,200
好啊
All right.

130
00:08:53,300 --> 00:08:54,000
根本问题是
The bottom line 

131
00:08:54,100 --> 00:08:55,300
副总统女士
Madam Vice President 

132
00:08:55,400 --> 00:08:58,600
根本问题是你对白宫没有影响力
is that you can't effect change in the Oval Office.

133
00:08:59,300 --> 00:09:01,200
而那正是我们最迫切需要的
And that is what we need the most.

134
00:09:01,400 --> 00:09:02,200
发言人
Certitude.

135
00:09:03,600 --> 00:09:04,400
简单地说
Simply put

136
00:09:05,800 --> 00:09:07,100
你能力有限
you can't get things done.

137
00:09:10,600 --> 00:09:12,600
或许你对我还不够了解
Well maybe you don't know me so well.

138
00:09:19,200 --> 00:09:22,000
我强烈建议在接下去的几周里
I highly suggest that in the coming weeks 

139
00:09:22,200 --> 00:09:25,100
随着竞选越来越激烈 候选人开始逐一退出...
as the race narrows and the candidates start falling out 

140
00:09:26,400 --> 00:09:27,300
你也能够退出竞选
that you walk away 

141
00:09:27,600 --> 00:09:28,400
非常安静地退出
quietly 

142
00:09:28,700 --> 00:09:29,800
自意地退出
of your own volition.

143
00:09:31,000 --> 00:09:32,500
不然的话 或许
Otherwise maybe

144
00:09:33,700 --> 00:09:35,000
公司会强迫你退出
it'll be of The Company's volition.

145
00:09:51,300 --> 00:09:52,500
你把衣服脱掉
Hey hey take the suit off.

146
00:09:52,700 --> 00:09:53,400
在夜色中 你特别显眼
You're practically glowing in the dark.

147
00:09:53,500 --> 00:09:55,500
-我里面只穿了内衣  -快脱掉!
-I only got my Skivvies on underneath.  -Take the suit off!

148
00:09:55,600 --> 00:09:56,300
我会冻死的
I'll freeze to death!

149
00:09:56,400 --> 00:09:57,900
抓紧
Hurry up.

150
00:09:58,400 --> 00:09:59,800
-我们必须对那疯子采取点行动  -你说得对
-We got to do something about that freak.  -You got it dude.

151
00:09:59,900 --> 00:10:01,700
快 动作快点 抓紧时间
Come on. Come on hurry up. Hurry up.

152
00:10:14,000 --> 00:10:14,700
车在哪
Where the hell is the van?

153
00:10:16,800 --> 00:10:19,300
车到底在哪
Eyetie where in the hell is the van?

154
00:10:19,400 --> 00:10:21,400
给我点信任好不好
Ye of little faith.

155
00:10:28,700 --> 00:10:29,300
来 来吧
Come on come on.

156
00:10:37,200 --> 00:10:39,000
看 在那 我告诉过你
I told you. I told you.

157
00:10:40,500 --> 00:10:42,100
你来开车 克鲁马努人
Behind the wheel Cro-Magnon.

158
00:10:42,200 --> 00:10:43,100
别闹
Hey hey hey

159
00:10:51,700 --> 00:10:52,400
你在那干嘛
What the hell are you doing

160
00:10:53,100 --> 00:10:54,300
我在让我们不易察觉
I'm getting us invisible.

161
00:11:06,300 --> 00:11:07,300
约翰 车钥匙呢
John where are the keys

162
00:11:07,400 --> 00:11:08,600
-什么  -我问你钥匙在哪里
-What  -The keys where are they

163
00:11:08,700 --> 00:11:11,600
我告诉过你 在树旁垃圾筒内的塑料袋里
I told you in the garbage can by the trees in a plastic bag.

164
00:11:11,900 --> 00:11:12,400
那你还等什么
What are you waiting for

165
00:11:12,500 --> 00:11:15,500
去 快去找钥匙
Come on come on.

166
00:11:37,700 --> 00:11:40,300
不 不
No! No no no!

167
00:11:41,400 --> 00:11:42,600
不!
No!

168
00:11:48,000 --> 00:11:50,200
我们对55和80号高速实行全程监控
We got the on-ramps to 55 and 80 being monitored.

169
00:11:50,300 --> 00:11:53,600
在171 6和53号路口设置了检查站
We've got traffic checks on 171 6 and 53.

170
00:11:53,700 --> 00:11:57,100
在奥海尔和中途都有特别部门监控来往过客的名单
Special Services has secured a watch on passenger lists at O'Hare and Midway.

171
00:11:57,200 --> 00:11:58,400
电话监控安排了没有?
How are we doing with the wiretaps?

172
00:11:58,500 --> 00:12:01,200
所有越狱者家里都安装了窃听器
They're being set up on all the family members of the escapees as we speak.

173
00:12:01,300 --> 00:12:04,000
监控小组也正在住所外围布控
Surveillance teams are being established outside the residences as well.

174
00:12:04,100 --> 00:12:04,600
谢谢
Thank you.

175
00:12:06,100 --> 00:12:06,600
你发现了什么线索?
What do you got?

176
00:12:07,100 --> 00:12:08,400
门不是被撬开的
Door wasn't forced.

177
00:12:08,700 --> 00:12:09,900
锁也没有被凿过
Lock wasn't picked.

178
00:12:11,100 --> 00:12:11,900
就目前情况来看
As far as I can tell 

179
00:12:12,000 --> 00:12:13,400
他们基本上就是走进去的
they basically just walked right in.

180
00:12:13,600 --> 00:12:14,500
我不明白这怎么可能
I don't see how that's possible.

181
00:12:14,600 --> 00:12:16,800
这门每天下班后都是锁上的
These doors are locked down every night when we leave

182
00:12:16,900 --> 00:12:18,100
这是第一要务
It's priority number one.

183
00:12:18,500 --> 00:12:19,900
我唯一能想到的就是
Only thing I can think is...

184
00:12:20,800 --> 00:12:21,300
是什么?
What?

185
00:12:21,900 --> 00:12:23,400
有人故意不锁为他们开着
Someone left it open for them.

186
00:12:35,400 --> 00:12:36,900
约翰 我不得不问你
Hey John I've got to ask you

187
00:12:37,500 --> 00:12:39,400
你为什么这么坚持林肯来开车
why you were so intent on Lincoln driving here

188
00:12:39,500 --> 00:12:41,900
还有你为什么挑了这么个特别的位置?
and you taking that particular seat?

189
00:12:48,100 --> 00:12:50,800
你座位下到底有什么东西?
Now what is it exactly you got up underneath there huh?

190
00:12:53,200 --> 00:12:54,300
你他妈的在干嘛
What the hell are you doing

191
00:12:54,400 --> 00:12:56,400
你认为这么做就能让我停手?
You think that will stop me huh?

192
00:12:56,800 --> 00:12:59,700
好好再想想吧
Think twice Johnny boy.

193
00:13:00,200 --> 00:13:00,900
你杀了我
You shoot me pretty here

194
00:13:01,300 --> 00:13:04,400
那他就要拖着170磅的尸体做伴了
pretty here will be dragging around 170 pounds of dead Alabama flesh with him.

195
00:13:04,600 --> 00:13:05,100
你想想
And considering

196
00:13:05,200 --> 00:13:08,500
他对你完成复仇菲波纳奇有多重要...
how much you need him to get this little Fibonacci vendetta of yours...

197
00:13:09,700 --> 00:13:11,500
所以你最好不要扣动扳机
So I just don't think you're gonna be pulling that trigger.

198
00:13:16,200 --> 00:13:16,700
不吗
No?

199
00:13:24,500 --> 00:13:26,900
快把手铐的钥匙给我 死变态 
You're gonna give me the key to those cuffs T-bag.

200
00:13:29,000 --> 00:13:30,200
你这狗娘养的
you son of a bitch.

201
00:13:30,500 --> 00:13:32,000
找找看
Get it get it. Get it.

202
00:13:32,100 --> 00:13:33,400
你在找这个吗
You looking for this?

203
00:13:38,300 --> 00:13:39,400
-吐出来!  -快吐出来!
-Come on. Spit it out!  -Spit it out!

204
00:13:40,000 --> 00:13:41,000
快啊
Come on.

205
00:13:54,000 --> 00:13:54,900
他们喝下这个
They drink this 

206
00:13:55,600 --> 00:13:57,200
只要几分钟就要了命
it's only a matter of minutes.

207
00:13:59,000 --> 00:14:02,600
蛤蚌毒素配糖混合制剂在血液中立刻起作用
This glycoside saxitoxin hybrid goes to work in the blood stream instantly.

208
00:14:04,700 --> 00:14:06,950
体质再好 心肌再强
Five minutes is the outside limit even

209
00:14:06,950 --> 00:14:09,200
的人也撑不过五分钟
the strongest cardiac muscles can continue to function.

210
00:14:09,500 --> 00:14:10,100
再然后
After that 

211
00:14:11,100 --> 00:14:14,100
就算神仙也回天乏术了
massive cardiac arrest with no chance of survival.

212
00:14:15,000 --> 00:14:16,600
能通过毒素测试吗
What about toxicology tests?

213
00:14:17,900 --> 00:14:19,100
放心 什么也检查不出来
Well they'll reveal nothing.

214
00:14:20,100 --> 00:14:22,100
死因只能归咎为自然疾病
Death will appear to be from natural causes.

215
00:14:25,600 --> 00:14:26,800
这可是很重的叛国罪
This is high treason.

216
00:14:27,200 --> 00:14:28,200
你不会不知道吧
You know that don't you?

217
00:14:46,300 --> 00:14:47,000
血迹未干 长官
It's fresh boss.

218
00:14:47,400 --> 00:14:47,900
是今晚留下的?
From tonight.

219
00:14:48,200 --> 00:14:49,500
不会超过一小时
Can't be more than an hour old.

220
00:14:49,700 --> 00:14:50,500
让警犬闻过气味了吗
Dogs get the scent?

221
00:14:51,100 --> 00:14:51,700
已经闻过了
Already have

222
00:14:54,100 --> 00:14:55,100
长官 来看看这个
Hey boss check this out.

223
00:15:01,500 --> 00:15:02,000
队长
Captain 

224
00:15:04,100 --> 00:15:05,200
这人就住在路边
this guy lives up the road.

225
00:15:05,900 --> 00:15:07,300
白天在这工作
Works on the property during the day.

226
00:15:07,500 --> 00:15:08,800
你看到一辆车停在这?
You see a vehicle parked here?

227
00:15:09,000 --> 00:15:10,500
对 是的
I think so yeah.

228
00:15:11,200 --> 00:15:12,000
什么样的车?
What did it look like?

229
00:15:12,300 --> 00:15:14,600
像部厢式货车
Like a... Like a van.

230
00:15:15,100 --> 00:15:15,800
蓝色的厢式货车
A blue van.

231
00:15:16,300 --> 00:15:18,400
你就没有想过向当局报案?
And you didn't think to report it to the authorities?

232
00:15:20,000 --> 00:15:21,100
一辆停着的车?
A parked car?

233
00:15:32,900 --> 00:15:36,700
如果你觉得我不会亲手把你肠子割断取出钥匙
If you think I won't gut you myself to get that key 

234
00:15:36,700 --> 00:15:38,400
那就看看会给你什么惊喜吧
you're in for a big surprise.

235
00:15:38,400 --> 00:15:41,700
我建议你回想一下上次你冲我动刀的情形
I encourage you to remember the last time you came at me with a knife.

236
00:15:41,700 --> 00:15:42,600
闭嘴!
Shut up!

237
00:15:42,600 --> 00:15:43,600
快闭嘴!
Shut up!

238
00:15:43,600 --> 00:15:45,400
你们两个都给我闭嘴!
Both of you!

239
00:15:45,400 --> 00:15:47,000
你们可以到墨西哥后再作个了断
You can settle this in Mexico.

240
00:15:47,000 --> 00:15:48,900
离飞机跑道还有多远?
How far to the airstrip?

241
00:15:48,900 --> 00:15:50,700
大概还有5英里
I guess five miles maybe.

242
00:15:55,300 --> 00:15:58,200
黑老大 你的飞机最好在那停着
You know your jet better be there Mr. Mafia.

243
00:15:58,200 --> 00:15:59,500
你明白我的意思吗
You feel me?

244
00:15:59,500 --> 00:16:01,100
确保飞机在那儿
It better be there.

245
00:16:11,800 --> 00:16:13,800
警犬布置完毕
Canine unit being deployed.

246
00:16:13,800 --> 00:16:15,000
收到
Roger that.

247
00:16:16,000 --> 00:16:19,500
尽量缩小搜查范围
Push past the search perimeter before we can pick up track. Over.

248
00:16:19,500 --> 00:16:21,200
周围到处都是警察
They're everywhere out there.

249
00:16:21,200 --> 00:16:23,000
还用你来说
Tell me something I don' t know.

250
00:16:30,400 --> 00:16:33,000
你是说你对此一无所知?
You're saying you don't know anything about this?

251
00:16:33,000 --> 00:16:34,700
我真的不知道
Honestly I don't.

252
00:16:34,700 --> 00:16:36,400
门没有上锁 卡蒂
The door was left open Katie.

253
00:16:36,400 --> 00:16:37,400
不是我干的
It wasn't me.

254
00:16:37,400 --> 00:16:38,100
那是谁?
Well then who was it?

255
00:16:38,100 --> 00:16:40,700
只有你和唐克雷蒂医生在晚上离开那儿
Only you and Dr. Tancredi were left at the end of the night.

256
00:16:40,700 --> 00:16:42,000
值班人员确认过这件事
The orderly confirmed that.

257
00:16:42,000 --> 00:16:43,600
不是我
It wasn't me.

258
00:16:43,600 --> 00:16:45,000
那你就是说唐克雷蒂医生干的?
Then you're telling me it was Dr. Tancredi?

259
00:16:45,000 --> 00:16:45,900
不
No...

260
00:16:49,500 --> 00:16:51,900
我知道你觉察到什么了 卡蒂
I know you know something Katie.

261
00:16:51,900 --> 00:16:52,800
把任何你知道的事情
And anything you know 

262
00:16:52,800 --> 00:16:53,900
统统告诉我
you have got to tell me.

263
00:16:53,900 --> 00:16:54,400
如果不告诉我的话
If you don't 

264
00:16:54,400 --> 00:16:57,500
你失去的将不仅仅是工作
you are gonna lose a lot more than your job.

265
00:16:57,500 --> 00:16:59,600
知情不报会让你成为同谋犯
Withholding information makes you an accessory.

266
00:16:59,600 --> 00:17:02,500
如果你再不说的话我就按铃报警了!
And I will press that button if you don't start talking!

267
00:17:07,200 --> 00:17:08,300
莎拉
Sara

268
00:17:08,300 --> 00:17:09,800
莎拉怎么了
What about Sarah

269
00:17:11,600 --> 00:17:14,500
莎拉喜欢斯科菲尔德
Sara had a thing for Scofield.

270
00:17:19,600 --> 00:17:20,900
谢谢你 卡蒂
Thank you Katie.

271
00:17:27,300 --> 00:17:29,500
我只想摸摸她的肚子
All I want to do is touch her belly 

272
00:17:31,000 --> 00:17:32,700
感受一下小生命的存在
feel that he's in there.

273
00:17:35,500 --> 00:17:36,800
这之后
After that 

274
00:17:38,100 --> 00:17:39,000
随便让我干什么
whatever I got to do I'll figure it out.

275
00:17:39,000 --> 00:17:40,700
我都愿意去做
I'll figure it out.

276
00:17:42,200 --> 00:17:44,300
我就是想摸摸她的肚子
I just want to touch her belly.

277
00:17:45,100 --> 00:17:46,500
我们快到了 帕皮
We're close papi.

278
00:17:47,600 --> 00:17:48,900
糟了 有麻烦了
We got trouble.

279
00:18:07,000 --> 00:18:08,100
这太疯狂了
Yo dawg man this is bananas.

280
00:18:08,100 --> 00:18:09,500
我们必须离开这条道
We got to get off this road.

281
00:18:09,500 --> 00:18:10,500
还有其他路可以到机场吗
Any other way to the airstrip

282
00:18:10,500 --> 00:18:11,400
就只有这条路
This is the only road.

283
00:18:11,400 --> 00:18:12,800
那我们就跑吧
Then let's just run this bitch.

284
00:18:12,800 --> 00:18:14,100
谁让他闭嘴
Somebody shut him up 

285
00:18:14,100 --> 00:18:15,300
还是我自己来
or I will.

286
00:18:15,300 --> 00:18:16,000
我们能回去吗
Can we go back

287
00:18:16,000 --> 00:18:18,300
那对我们没有任何好处
That won't do us any good.

288
00:18:18,300 --> 00:18:20,300
这只会让我们越来越远离目的地
It'll only get us farther from where we need to be.

289
00:18:20,300 --> 00:18:22,600
那意味着我们必须冲过那个路障
Which means we got to bust that roadblock.

290
00:18:22,600 --> 00:18:24,200
或许不用
Maybe not.

291
00:18:24,200 --> 00:18:25,900
我们可以试着绕路走
We've got to try and go around.

292
00:18:26,700 --> 00:18:27,700
来吧
Come on.

293
00:18:35,900 --> 00:18:38,300
我们会从你这拿到钥匙的
We're gonna get that key from you.

294
00:18:38,300 --> 00:18:41,000
我才不管你是用拉出来还是什么的
I don't care if you got to crap it out.

295
00:18:41,000 --> 00:18:43,700
你有时候嘴很臭 小子
You got a foul mouth sometimes pretty.

296
00:18:49,400 --> 00:18:50,500
怎么了?
What?

297
00:18:53,000 --> 00:18:54,700
靠 轮胎陷进去了!
Son of a bitch we're stuck!

298
00:18:54,700 --> 00:18:57,500
大家都出去
Everybody out. Everybody out.

299
00:19:05,300 --> 00:19:06,800
这是为今晚演讲准备的吗
This for the speech tonight

300
00:19:07,500 --> 00:19:08,800
出示证件
Need some ID.

301
00:19:10,300 --> 00:19:11,700
特工部门
Secret Service.

302
00:19:12,600 --> 00:19:13,900
好的
Have at it.

303
00:19:20,400 --> 00:19:21,500
用力
Come on!

304
00:19:24,200 --> 00:19:25,300
这车没指望了
This thing ain't going nowhere!

305
00:19:25,300 --> 00:19:26,400
离机场还有多远?
How far is the airstrip?

306
00:19:26,400 --> 00:19:27,300
徒步?
On foot?

307
00:19:27,300 --> 00:19:28,200
或许2英里
Maybe two miles.

308
00:19:28,200 --> 00:19:29,400
那我们还等什么?
What the hell are we waiting for?

309
00:19:29,400 --> 00:19:30,100
赶紧跑啊
Let's move.

310
00:19:30,100 --> 00:19:32,400
三只脚竞走可跑不快啊
Three-legged race over here ain't going to make it 10 feet.

311
00:19:32,400 --> 00:19:33,700
我们行的 不是吗?
We'll manage won't we?

312
00:19:33,700 --> 00:19:35,100
那当然
Sure pretty.

313
00:19:35,100 --> 00:19:36,200
我们是队友
We're teammates.

314
00:19:36,200 --> 00:19:37,400
永远的队友
Teammates till the end.

315
00:19:37,400 --> 00:19:38,100
让我们离开这
Let's get out of here!

316
00:19:38,100 --> 00:19:39,100
出发
Let's go!

317
00:19:39,100 --> 00:19:39,900
走了
Let's go.

318
00:19:39,900 --> 00:19:40,900
走
Let's go. Come on.

319
00:19:42,000 --> 00:19:43,700
你就只能跟到这了
This is as far as you go my friend.

320
00:19:43,700 --> 00:19:44,900
什么
What

321
00:19:44,900 --> 00:19:46,700
不行 你不能在这丢下我 不该这样的
No man you can't leave me out here not like this.

322
00:19:46,700 --> 00:19:48,300
我们说好了 记得吗
We had a deal remember

323
00:19:50,600 --> 00:19:51,600
对 但是别这样 好兄弟
Yeah but come on bro.

324
00:19:51,600 --> 00:19:53,100
你和我
You and I 

325
00:19:53,100 --> 00:19:54,700
我们可不是什么兄弟
we're not bros.

326
00:19:55,300 --> 00:19:57,900
要不要我通知他们你和警察的事情
And I don't think you want me telling the guys what I know.

327
00:20:01,600 --> 00:20:02,900
滚开
Now walk.

328
00:20:08,900 --> 00:20:10,900
我们有麻烦了
We got trouble pretty.

329
00:20:17,100 --> 00:20:18,200
走 快走
Go! Go!

330
00:20:18,200 --> 00:20:19,300
跟上
Come on!

331
00:20:36,400 --> 00:20:37,800
天呐
Oh my God!

332
00:20:39,700 --> 00:20:41,000
现在怎么办
Now what?

333
00:20:41,000 --> 00:20:41,800
走不了了
What do we do now Michael?

334
00:20:41,800 --> 00:20:42,300
我真不敢相信
I don't believe this.

335
00:20:42,300 --> 00:20:43,700
怎么办
What now

336
00:21:10,000 --> 00:21:12,200
长官 检查完毕 未发现目标
This area clear. Negative contact.

337
00:21:22,300 --> 00:21:24,800
又回来了 又回来了
It's coming back y'all it's coming back!

338
00:21:28,900 --> 00:21:30,600
注意隐蔽
Make yourself small.

339
00:21:36,000 --> 00:21:39,800
像这样我们根本走不了2英里
There's no way we are gonna make two miles like this.

340
00:21:41,200 --> 00:21:43,600
特别上面还有这么大只鸟
Especially with that bird up there.

341
00:21:52,100 --> 00:21:54,600
如果想想办法说不定可以
We are if I got something to do with it.

342
00:22:32,700 --> 00:22:33,800
打搅一下
Excuse me.

343
00:22:34,700 --> 00:22:36,200
有什么能帮你的吗
What can I do for you?

344
00:22:36,700 --> 00:22:39,100
我正想问同样的问题呢
Sort of was gonna ask you the same question.

345
00:22:39,100 --> 00:22:40,600
我白天负责瞭望塔
I run the tower during the day.

346
00:22:40,600 --> 00:22:42,600
日落后这儿就不许通航了
There's no traffic allowed here after sundown.

347
00:22:42,600 --> 00:22:44,200
飞机出了机械故障
Had some mechanical problems.

348
00:22:44,200 --> 00:22:45,600
需要我帮忙看看吗
You need me to take a look at anything?

349
00:22:45,600 --> 00:22:47,200
不 不用 我们自己能解决
No no we got it.

350
00:22:48,500 --> 00:22:49,900
不用麻烦你了
Don't trouble yourself.

351
00:22:49,900 --> 00:22:51,300
我们马上就离开
We'll be on our way in no time.

352
00:22:51,300 --> 00:22:52,500
你肯定吗
You sure?

353
00:22:52,500 --> 00:22:53,800
绝对
Positive.

354
00:22:55,300 --> 00:22:56,400
好吧
Okay.

355
00:22:56,400 --> 00:22:57,800
老兄 祝你晚安
Have a good night hey buddy?

356
00:22:57,800 --> 00:22:58,800
同祝晚安
Yeah you too.

357
00:23:05,500 --> 00:23:07,200
那些家伙最好抓紧时间
Those guys better hurry up.

358
00:23:13,400 --> 00:23:14,200
是我
Hey it's me.

359
00:23:14,200 --> 00:23:16,500
我在高斯公园发现一不明身份飞机
I've got an unidentified aircraft here at Goose Park.

360
00:23:16,500 --> 00:23:18,100
最好你们来看看
I think you better have a look at it.

361
00:23:18,100 --> 00:23:21,600
尾翼号码是986D
Tail number's 986-Delta.

362
00:23:25,200 --> 00:23:26,400
动作快点
Hurry up

363
00:23:26,400 --> 00:23:27,600
大水缸
Tranquilo

364
00:23:27,600 --> 00:23:30,100
就让我用小魔力来安心干活 好不好?
Just let papi work a little bit of his magic okay?

365
00:23:30,100 --> 00:23:31,400
你知道你在干吗
You know what you're doing?

366
00:23:31,400 --> 00:23:32,500
你在笑话我?
Are you kidding me?

367
00:23:32,500 --> 00:23:35,000
捣鼓这个对我来说就像摆弄烤箱
Hot-wiring this thing is like hot-wiring a toaster.

368
00:23:35,000 --> 00:23:36,200
当然 如果这中间还有什么插曲
Now if it were to be an Acura 

369
00:23:36,200 --> 00:23:37,400
或者是中国车
or one of those Chinese cars 

370
00:23:37,400 --> 00:23:39,400
那就完全不同了
that's a whole different story.

371
00:23:39,400 --> 00:23:41,300
电子点火装置
Electronic ignition 

372
00:23:41,300 --> 00:23:43,000
电脑芯片 统统不考虑
computer chips forget about it.

373
00:23:43,000 --> 00:23:44,100
不管怎样 我们快成功了
But no we're good.

374
00:23:45,300 --> 00:23:48,100
直升机马上会回来的 所以动作快点
Well that chopper's gonna be coming back again so hurry up.

375
00:24:01,600 --> 00:24:04,000
墨西哥怎么样
Hey yo. What they got in Mexico anyhow

376
00:24:04,700 --> 00:24:06,500
你从没有去过
You never been there

377
00:24:06,500 --> 00:24:10,100
除了伊拉克 唐人街和Fox River监狱
Ain't never been nowhere

378
00:24:10,100 --> 00:24:12,100
我哪儿都没有去过
except for Iraq Chi-Town and Fox River.

379
00:24:12,900 --> 00:24:14,500
你看什么看?
What you looking at?

380
00:24:17,600 --> 00:24:19,100
听着
Look man 

381
00:24:21,400 --> 00:24:23,700
有没有个地方可以容你安个家?
is it a good place where you can have a family?

382
00:24:25,900 --> 00:24:27,800
那儿有很多家庭
Lots of families down there 

383
00:24:27,800 --> 00:24:28,900
据我所知
so I hear.

384
00:24:28,900 --> 00:24:31,100
你知道我在说什么吗
Man you know what I'm talking about.

385
00:24:31,100 --> 00:24:32,100
能给一个黑人
For a black man 

386
00:24:33,500 --> 00:24:36,400
给一个美国人安家
an American man with a family.

387
00:24:36,400 --> 00:24:37,900
这就是你计划?
So that's the plan huh?

388
00:24:38,600 --> 00:24:40,700
让他们去墨西哥找你?
They're gonna meet you down in Mexico?

389
00:24:41,900 --> 00:24:44,300
是啊 比不见他们更糟糕
Yeah it's worse to not see them.

390
00:24:44,300 --> 00:24:46,500
我再也不能这么下去了
And I can't do that no more.

391
00:24:46,500 --> 00:24:49,000
对他们来说这根本不算什么生活
Not much of a life for them.

392
00:24:49,000 --> 00:24:50,700
但起码也算得上是过日子
But it'll be a life.

393
00:24:52,600 --> 00:24:56,700
日子肯定会比过去的两年好
More than what me and them have been having for the last two years man.

394
00:25:00,200 --> 00:25:02,100
他们是我的家人
They're family snowflake.

395
00:25:03,600 --> 00:25:06,100
我不可能撇下他们不管
Ain't no way in hell I'm leaving them behind.

396
00:25:09,000 --> 00:25:10,100
差不多成了
We're good.

397
00:25:10,900 --> 00:25:12,800
对付这我绰绰有余
I must have done this a thousand times.

398
00:25:12,800 --> 00:25:15,100
我觉得你更适合武装抢劫
Man I thought you got busted for armed robbery.

399
00:25:16,100 --> 00:25:17,900
那就是他们逮捕我的原因
That's what they caught me for.

400
00:25:19,300 --> 00:25:20,800
红色的是火线
Red's the juice 

401
00:25:20,800 --> 00:25:22,200
白色的是地线
white is the ground.

402
00:25:22,200 --> 00:25:23,900
把他们接到一块
You strike them together

403
00:25:23,900 --> 00:25:26,000
这样我们就能离开这
and we blow this town.

404
00:25:26,100 --> 00:25:27,100
怎么了?
What?

405
00:25:27,700 --> 00:25:28,600
到底怎么了?
What?

406
00:25:28,600 --> 00:25:29,900
居然发动不起来
I don't get it.

407
00:25:38,700 --> 00:25:39,300
太糟糕了
Great.

408
00:25:39,300 --> 00:25:40,900
真他妈地见鬼
That's just great.

409
00:26:17,600 --> 00:26:18,700
对不起了
Sorry.

410
00:26:28,300 --> 00:26:29,300
发动机还是温的
Engine's still warm 

411
00:26:29,300 --> 00:26:31,600
我在这没有发现其他的轮胎痕迹
and I don't see any other tire tracks out here.

412
00:26:31,600 --> 00:26:32,900
我们肯定改步行了
They're on foot 

413
00:26:32,900 --> 00:26:35,100
通过对发动机热度的判断
and judging by how hot this engine is 

414
00:26:35,100 --> 00:26:36,400
他们还没有跑远
they haven't gone far.

415
00:26:36,400 --> 00:26:38,500
最多在我们前面5到10分钟
Five ten minutes ahead of us at the most.

416
00:26:38,500 --> 00:26:39,400
你在哪里?
Where are you?

417
00:26:39,400 --> 00:26:40,600
瑞文奇大道?
Renwick road?

418
00:26:40,600 --> 00:26:43,300
在瑞文奇和韦伯大道交界以西四分之一英里处
A quarter mile west of Weber on Renwick.

419
00:26:43,300 --> 00:26:45,700
行了 瑞文奇大道在南面
Okay we've got Renwick on the south 

420
00:26:45,700 --> 00:26:46,400
韦伯大道在东面
Weber on the east 

421
00:26:46,400 --> 00:26:49,000
143大街在北面
143rd Street on the north

422
00:26:49,000 --> 00:26:51,200
55大街在西面
and 55 on the west.

423
00:26:51,200 --> 00:26:53,200
这些路段沿线都布控了
Units are in place along all those roads.

424
00:26:53,200 --> 00:26:54,900
而且更多增援正在赶过来
And I've got a dozen more coming.

425
00:26:54,900 --> 00:26:59,000
布拉德 这可比我们想像中快得多
Brad this could be over quicker than we thought.

426
00:26:59,000 --> 00:27:00,900
我们已经把他们包围起来了
We've got them boxed in.

427
00:27:03,800 --> 00:27:06,000
长官 我们有唐克雷蒂医生的最新消息
Sir we've got an update on Dr. Tancredi.

428
00:27:06,000 --> 00:27:07,000
告诉我
Tell me.

429
00:27:07,000 --> 00:27:09,300
没有任何一名员工和她有过接触
None of the staff had any interaction with her.

430
00:27:09,300 --> 00:27:11,800
下午早些时候她就突然离开工作岗位了
She left work suddenly in the early afternoon 

431
00:27:11,800 --> 00:27:12,800
回来了大约一个小时
returned for maybe an hour 

432
00:27:12,800 --> 00:27:13,800
又走了
then left again.

433
00:27:13,800 --> 00:27:15,400
所有这些都很反常
All of it's very erratic.

434
00:27:15,400 --> 00:27:16,800
有人能联系上她吗
Has anyone been able to reach her?

435
00:27:16,800 --> 00:27:17,900
家里没装电话
Doesn't have a home line 

436
00:27:17,900 --> 00:27:19,600
手机也关机
cell phone seems to be shut off.

437
00:27:19,600 --> 00:27:22,600
警察局方面证实她的车就在住所外面
Chicago PD identified her car outside her residence.

438
00:27:22,600 --> 00:27:25,100
他们正在申请 突发事件许可 准备进门调查
They're getting an emergency warrant to go in.

439
00:27:27,100 --> 00:27:28,700
长官 虽然这和我无关
Sir it's none of my business 

440
00:27:28,700 --> 00:27:30,700
但是我想提醒你是否应给州长打电话?
but are you gonna call the Governor?

441
00:27:31,400 --> 00:27:33,700
我们在谈论的是她的女儿
This is his daughter we're talking about.

442
00:27:38,600 --> 00:27:40,300
队长 警犬发现了行踪
Captain the dogs picked up a trail.

443
00:27:40,300 --> 00:27:41,000
哪条路?
Which way?

444
00:27:41,000 --> 00:27:42,800
那条还有那条路
That way and that way.

445
00:27:42,800 --> 00:27:43,600
他们分兵两路了?
They split up?

446
00:27:43,600 --> 00:27:44,400
看上去是的
Looks like it.

447
00:27:44,400 --> 00:27:46,100
那我们还等什么?
What the hell we waiting for?

448
00:29:26,800 --> 00:29:30,300
很明显我们的政策非常有成效
I think it's pretty clear that our policies have been effective.

449
00:29:30,300 --> 00:29:36,200
已经实现了连续14个季度GDP增长超过三个百分点
We've had 14 consecutive quarters of GDP growth above 3%.

450
00:29:36,200 --> 00:29:38,300
减税政策正在起作用
The tax cuts are working.

451
00:29:38,300 --> 00:29:40,000
副总统女士!
Madame Vice President!

452
00:29:40,000 --> 00:29:41,200
彼得
Peter.

453
00:29:41,200 --> 00:29:42,100
副总统女士
Madame Vice President 

454
00:29:42,100 --> 00:29:46,200
有很多人质疑减少石油工业税收的明智性
a lot of people question the wisdom of granting tax cuts to the oil industry 

455
00:29:46,200 --> 00:29:48,600
根据就在于他们看到了盈利记录
in light of the fact that they're seeing record profits.

456
00:29:48,600 --> 00:29:50,100
你对此有何见解?
Do you have thoughts on that?

457
00:29:50,100 --> 00:29:53,100
我们奉行的是市场推动型经济 彼得
We're a market-driven economy Peter.

458
00:29:53,100 --> 00:29:55,900
对那些业务模式良好的公司课以重税
Punishing companies for being a good business model

459
00:29:55,900 --> 00:29:59,100
与我们的监管政策完全不符
doesn't make a whole lot of sense to this administration.

460
00:29:59,100 --> 00:30:00,700
副总统女士
Madame Vice President!

461
00:30:00,700 --> 00:30:01,500
瑞贝卡
Yeah Rebecca.

462
00:30:01,500 --> 00:30:02,000
谢谢
Thank you.

463
00:30:02,000 --> 00:30:02,900
副总统女士
Madame Vice President 

464
00:30:02,900 --> 00:30:04,500
你的意思是否是说
are you saying...

465
00:30:06,900 --> 00:30:09,200
如果你竟选成功就会
...if you're elected president?

466
00:30:09,200 --> 00:30:13,700
如果减税政策能够带来经济增长的话 那就是的
If those tax breaks result in growth yes.

467
00:30:15,800 --> 00:30:16,700
对不起
Excuse me.

468
00:30:16,700 --> 00:30:18,900
对不起 那位先生?
Excuse me. Sir? Yes.

469
00:30:18,900 --> 00:30:21,100
那位先生 我能
Sir can I...

470
00:30:44,050 --> 00:30:45,550
他们在哪?
Where are they?

471
00:30:45,670 --> 00:30:48,180
他们就在我们后面
They were way the hell back there.

472
00:30:49,510 --> 00:30:51,280
可不能再让他们连体下去
This ain't gonna work like this.

473
00:30:51,360 --> 00:30:53,030
我们得采取点行动
We've got to do something.

474
00:30:57,560 --> 00:30:58,960
这边
This way.

475
00:31:01,400 --> 00:31:03,120
快
Come on.

476
00:31:07,620 --> 00:31:10,180
怎么了 发生什么了
What's going on? What's going on?

477
00:31:13,450 --> 00:31:17,170
你想干吗 你到底想干吗
Guys what are you doing? What the hell you doing?

478
00:31:20,210 --> 00:31:21,650
我对天发誓
I swear to God.

479
00:31:21,730 --> 00:31:23,690
你发誓个屁
You swear what

480
00:31:29,510 --> 00:31:33,040
我猜这可能是注定的 伙计们?
I guess it was just meant to be hey now fellas?

481
00:31:52,800 --> 00:31:56,770
他很幸运我没有砍到他的头
He's lucky I didn't take this to his head.

482
00:31:58,180 --> 00:31:59,430
你砍了他的
You cut his...

483
00:31:59,960 --> 00:32:01,670
你砍断了他的
You cut his...

484
00:32:01,800 --> 00:32:04,610
你 你砍断了他的
You cut his...

485
00:32:04,680 --> 00:32:06,700
苏克雷 闭嘴
Sucre shut up.

486
00:32:09,670 --> 00:32:11,530
有人吗
Hello.

487
00:32:14,270 --> 00:32:16,180
里面有人吗
Hello!

488
00:32:30,260 --> 00:32:32,250
快 我们走
Come on let's go.

489
00:32:33,360 --> 00:32:35,100
我们不能就这样把他丢下...
We can't leave him to just like...

490
00:32:35,220 --> 00:32:37,650
你想留在这儿 随便你
You want to stay here? Be my guest.

491
00:33:49,390 --> 00:33:53,190
我是狐狸河监狱的狱长亨利·珀尔
Yes this is Warden Henry Pope at Fox River Penitentiary.

492
00:33:53,250 --> 00:33:55,400
我需要和州长谈谈
I need to speak with the Governor.

493
00:33:57,010 --> 00:33:58,450
什么事?
Yes?

494
00:33:58,520 --> 00:34:00,730
州长 我很抱歉来打搅你 但是 
Governor I'm sorry to bother you 

495
00:34:00,810 --> 00:34:03,590
-发生了件事...  -你在收看这个吗?
-but there's been an...  -Are you watching this?

496
00:34:03,670 --> 00:34:05,380
看什么?
Watching what?

497
00:34:05,460 --> 00:34:08,760
我建议你现在打开电视 狱长
I suggest you turn on your TV Warden.

498
00:34:12,870 --> 00:34:15,040
在华盛顿医疗中心的医生已经证实
Doctors at Washington Medical Center have corroborated

499
00:34:15,160 --> 00:34:17,830
米尔斯总统45分钟前已被紧急监护起来
that President Mills was admitted into emergency care here a little more than 45 minutes ago.

500
00:34:17,910 --> 00:34:21,940
据主治医生介绍 米尔斯总统突发严重心肌梗塞
In the chief surgeon's words President Mills suffered massive cardiac arrest

501
00:34:22,010 --> 00:34:24,180
医生虽尽力抢救但还是无法回天
doctors were unable to revive him.

502
00:34:24,290 --> 00:34:26,850
华盛顿医疗中心的消息是官方消息
The news out of Washington Medical Center is official now.

503
00:34:28,930 --> 00:34:32,540
现任美国总统 理查德·米尔斯已经辞世
The President of the United States Richard Mills is dead.

504
00:34:32,640 --> 00:34:35,680
根据宪法 副总统雷诺兹
And keeping with protocol Vice President Reynolds

505
00:34:35,720 --> 00:34:39,340
正在一保密地方宣誓就任美国第46任总统
is in an undisclosed location being sworn in as the 46th president...

506
00:34:39,410 --> 00:34:43,560
我会忠实地履行美国总统一职
"I will faithfully execute the office of President of the United States "

507
00:34:43,590 --> 00:34:47,400
尽我所能 保持 保护
"and will to the best of my ability preserve protect"

508
00:34:47,470 --> 00:34:51,010
并捍卫美利坚合众国宪法
"and defend the Constitution of the United States."

509
00:34:51,080 --> 00:34:56,150
我宣布你继任为美国第46任总统
I hereby recognize you as the 46th president of this country.

510
00:34:56,870 --> 00:35:01,620
请原谅 今晚我还有很多工作要做
And now if you'll excuse me I have a lot to attend to tonight.

511
00:35:01,740 --> 00:35:04,000
谢谢大家
Thank you all.

512
00:35:13,170 --> 00:35:17,320
你不是说我搞不定吗
And you said I couldn't get things done.

513
00:35:17,770 --> 00:35:21,390
副总统女士 或许我们可以坐下来谈谈如何进一步发展
Madam Vice President perhaps we could get together and discuss how to move...

514
00:35:21,460 --> 00:35:23,660
请注意 现在是"总统"了
It is "President" now madam 

515
00:35:23,710 --> 00:35:28,160
你得先和我的秘书谈谈我的档期一下子排满了
and you're going to have to talk to my organizers. My schedule is suddenly quite full.

516
00:35:28,200 --> 00:35:30,790
我想你肯定能理解
I'm sure you'll understand.

517
00:35:36,630 --> 00:35:38,200
莎拉·唐克雷蒂!
Sara Tancredi!

518
00:35:38,310 --> 00:35:41,580
我们是警察 我们有入室搜查的许可证
It's the police. We have a warrant to come in.

519
00:35:42,180 --> 00:35:46,310
你把门打开 不然我们就闯进来了
It's easier if you just open the door. Otherwise we're gonna come on in.

520
00:36:04,500 --> 00:36:08,380
报告呼叫中心 发现目标昏迷在家
Dispatch this is 15 David on scene. Roll a bus to 1616 Vanlear Drive.

521
00:36:08,380 --> 00:36:14,260
很可能是吸食吗啡过量
Apartment 236. Possible overdose. Likely DOA.

522
00:37:01,900 --> 00:37:04,620
飞机跑道在空地另一端
The airstrip's on the other side of that field.

523
00:37:04,720 --> 00:37:07,300
还有500码然后咱们就彻底消失了
Just 500 yards and this whole thing's over.

524
00:37:08,600 --> 00:37:09,960
警车没有开走的迹象
He's not moving.

525
00:37:10,040 --> 00:37:14,140
我们在这每多呆一秒 就增加了他们发现飞机的机会 我们必须立刻行动
Every second we stay here is another chance for them to find the plane. We gotta go now.

526
00:37:14,180 --> 00:37:15,550
等等 再等等
Wait wait.

527
00:37:24,510 --> 00:37:26,730
好了 我们走
All right let's go. Let's go.

528
00:37:27,830 --> 00:37:29,050
迈克尔
Michael

529
00:37:29,160 --> 00:37:32,280
如果我们跑不掉的话 我想让你知道 我...
If this doesn't work out I want you to know...

530
00:37:32,400 --> 00:37:33,200
我知道
I know.

531
00:37:33,330 --> 00:37:35,120
我能明白
I know.

532
00:37:46,810 --> 00:37:49,360
别动 不许动
Freeze. Don't move.

533
00:37:52,500 --> 00:37:54,360
我们不得不离开的时候 我会告诉你的
I'll tell you when we got to go.

534
00:37:54,400 --> 00:37:56,200
不行 我们必须要走了
No man. I mean we got to go.

535
00:37:59,720 --> 00:38:01,780
发动飞机
Fire her up

536
00:38:11,600 --> 00:38:16,870
现在宣判 被告谋杀特伦斯·斯蒂德曼罪名成立
We find the defendant charged of murdering Terrence Steadman guilty.

537
00:38:19,000 --> 00:38:23,670
林肯辩护律师想出来的这个拖延时间的把戏...
This stunt by Lincoln Burrows' defense counsel

538
00:38:23,790 --> 00:38:27,090
是对我死去的弟弟的公开侮辱
is an affront to the memory of my brother.

539
00:38:31,190 --> 00:38:33,650
我们给死者的牙齿做了齿印
We made an imprint of the deceased's teeth 

540
00:38:33,730 --> 00:38:37,260
通过和特伦斯·斯蒂德曼牙医记录的比对
and compared them to the dental records of Terrence Steadman.

541
00:38:37,340 --> 00:38:39,510
他们完全一致
They were a perfect match.

542
00:38:40,690 --> 00:38:43,000
谁杀了特伦斯·斯蒂德曼
Who killed Terrence Steadman

543
00:38:44,250 --> 00:38:46,220
没有人
Nobody.

544
00:38:53,370 --> 00:38:55,530
你好 特伦斯
Hello Terrence.

545
00:39:14,180 --> 00:39:15,850
我已经看到飞机了
I can see it.

546
00:39:29,680 --> 00:39:35,460
继续前进 快快 警察就在我们屁股后面紧追不放
Faster. Come on let's go. Oh God.

547
00:39:54,760 --> 00:39:57,240
快 快跑
We're almost there.

548
00:40:59,680 --> 00:41:09,070
不 不要
No! No!

549
00:41:17,760 --> 00:41:19,640
我们现在怎么办?
What do we do now?

550
00:41:25,810 --> 00:41:27,510
跑吧
We run.

551
00:41:28,190 --> 00:41:30,840
这边
This way this way.

