[Script Info]
; // The sub is created by AssToolkit
; // AssToolkit is an ASS Converter designed by David C.
Title:YYeTs
Original Script:YYeTs
Synch Point:0
ScriptType:v4.00+
Collisions:Normal
Timer:100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Actor, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:00.20,0:00:03.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,《行尸走肉》前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.64,0:00:05.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们是能做成事的人
Dialogue: 0,0:00:05.75,0:00:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能找到战胜他们的方法
Dialogue: 0,0:00:08.86,0:00:11.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔拉  你在外面比我们走得都远
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.43,0:00:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,至少你能告诉我们别去哪找
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.26,0:00:14.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.44,0:00:15.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.89,0:00:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别这样做
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.19,0:00:19.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要等待合适的时机
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.97,0:00:21.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,枪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.35,0:00:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很多枪
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.08,0:00:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿到后我们会加入你的战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.95,0:00:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.99,0:00:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达成协议了
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.73,0:01:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你昨晚守夜
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.73,0:01:27.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我喜欢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.36,0:01:33.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今晚你来守吧
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.51,0:01:39.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们今天会有收获吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.73,0:01:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会的
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.66,0:01:44.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们也需要给那个对讲机找电池
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.37,0:01:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让它重新开始工作
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.65,0:02:25.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  笑什么
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.78,0:02:30.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们出来几天了  结果只找到
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.21,0:02:31.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多两把枪  几个压扁的豆子罐头
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.81,0:02:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和几件球衣
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.13,0:02:34.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差不多吧
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.68,0:02:38.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在抗争
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.74,0:02:40.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样更好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.58,0:02:52.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,早上好
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.65,0:02:56.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我再听见关于肥乔的一个字
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.12,0:02:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就要打碎某人的牙齿
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.88,0:02:59.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看是甩掉了累赘
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.10,0:03:01.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总算没什么狗屁吉祥物了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.33,0:03:11.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们对椒盐脆饼的品位不错
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.98,0:03:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有电池
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.99,0:03:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,两天了  我们得回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.38,0:03:26.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.76,0:03:30.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再过一天半  今天和明天
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.97,0:03:35.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以再出来  我们应该回去了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.54,0:03:37.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再转会儿
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.46,0:03:39.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没事
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.80,0:03:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们没必要现在就找到武器
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.99,0:03:45.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.14,0:03:48.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再转转吧
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.19,0:03:55.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.47,0:03:57.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.40,0:04:48.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第七季  第十二集』
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.40,0:04:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\fs16\bord0\shad0\blur5\t(0,500,\blur0)\b1\c&HECB000&\pos(99,242)}原创翻译  双语字幕
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.90,0:04:57.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(0,500)\fn方正准圆_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs17\pos(235.108,242)\K40}最新连载海外影视剧下载\N{\fs19\K30}请登陆 {\c&H26F4FF&\fn方正综艺_GBK\K30}www.YYeTs.com\N{\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs15\c&HFFFFFF&\K60}仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.97,0:04:59.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我正想来拆线
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.63,0:05:04.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}翻译     冰蓝 Reginamoon CS小明漫画家
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.24,0:05:01.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹妮斯教过我
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.21,0:05:05.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我弄完了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.63,0:05:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}翻译     小酸奶 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.48,0:05:08.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.98,0:05:09.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没什么
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.63,0:05:14.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}校对     送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.67,0:05:12.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.63,0:05:19.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(27,235)}时间轴     加森  涛涛
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.87,0:05:15.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会解决的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.31,0:05:19.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是什么意思  塔拉
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.63,0:05:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}后期     送小哥  拉图
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.91,0:05:21.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,意思是我们现在有足够的人手去战斗了
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.34,0:05:22.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只用找一些枪
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.95,0:05:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我们今天能在哪找到这么多枪吗
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.63,0:05:29.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,500)\bord0\shad0\fs18\pos(35,235)}总监     送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.23,0:05:28.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这周呢  今年呢
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.27,0:05:32.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.62,0:05:35.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能就这样等着
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.40,0:05:39.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道你  但我不行
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.89,0:05:44.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会找到枪的  好吗  我们会战斗的
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.87,0:05:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这肯定不容易
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.03,0:05:48.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不像上次哨站那样
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.47,0:05:54.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许你可以省点脾气跟他们打
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.96,0:06:00.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.89,0:06:03.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能帮你的伤疤愈合
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.98,0:06:09.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你留着吧
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.96,0:06:12.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要枪
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.62,0:06:13.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去找
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.47,0:07:25.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.70,0:07:27.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.11,0:07:29.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一头鹿
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.79,0:07:32.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我欠你一头鹿
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.03,0:07:35.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之前那次
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.80,0:07:37.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当时他们在门外
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.54,0:07:39.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.24,0:07:51.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看见了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.86,0:07:55.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.86,0:08:28.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这种枪就是我们出来要找的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.30,0:08:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这里发生了惨剧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.92,0:09:02.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很久以前
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.17,0:09:05.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊  这些子弹很不错
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.03,0:09:08.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许这里也有好枪
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.02,0:09:18.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们上去瞧瞧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.75,0:09:19.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.75,0:10:31.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.37,0:10:39.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,注意脚下
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.03,0:10:42.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我们不该在这里待太久
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.41,0:10:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去看看有什么吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.66,0:11:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,士兵  平民  这些子弹
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.38,0:11:09.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,曾有一场恶战
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.22,0:11:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是行尸
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.49,0:11:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是别的人
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.93,0:11:16.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们还背着枪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.46,0:11:20.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得就是这里了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.44,0:11:22.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也这么想
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.00,0:11:26.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,觉得我们可以搞定吗
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.31,0:12:00.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.79,0:12:30.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.56,0:12:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.60,0:12:33.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.50,0:12:38.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是个预兆  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.73,0:12:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  肯定是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.67,0:12:47.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,的确是
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.86,0:12:54.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}即食口粮
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.48,0:12:54.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们是即食的
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.22,0:12:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们吃吧
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.30,0:13:28.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没找到枪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.71,0:13:30.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想知道的话
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.81,0:13:34.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在外面找了一整天  一把都没找到
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.50,0:13:36.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一把真枪都没找到
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.22,0:13:40.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题是  我之前有一把枪
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.72,0:13:44.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来打算用它杀了尼根
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.42,0:13:45.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我都已经准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.45,0:13:48.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如我当时按计划做了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.98,0:13:50.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今尼根已经死了
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.13,0:13:54.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  也许我也会死  但谁他妈在乎
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.47,0:13:58.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那样的话尤金就不会被抓走
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.80,0:14:02.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,奥利维亚会活着
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.86,0:14:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯宾塞也会活着
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.56,0:14:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如今他们都不在了  我却还在
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.99,0:14:12.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为我愚蠢地听信了你的话
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.26,0:14:14.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你听了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.57,0:14:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也照做了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.22,0:14:25.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就站在那里对别人指手画脚
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.13,0:14:29.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只对那些来这里的人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.86,0:14:32.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,比如你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.91,0:14:34.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像现在
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.98,0:14:37.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你什么都不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.80,0:14:40.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.46,0:14:43.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的确不懂
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.24,0:14:48.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我说过你不应该去送死
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.06,0:14:52.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不应该去做那件你计划要做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.72,0:14:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们需要你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.88,0:14:57.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们如今依然需要
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.32,0:15:01.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像我这样的傻瓜都能看清那一点
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.59,0:15:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,死了的确更容易些
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.48,0:15:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如你还活着是我的错的话
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.85,0:15:07.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我只能背负着这个错误了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.62,0:15:10.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当时决定要插手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.04,0:15:13.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我做的是我认为正确的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.76,0:15:17.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也知道这事风险很大
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.00,0:15:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你当然可以因为自己还活着而指责我
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.15,0:15:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但之后呢  你要怎么办
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.67,0:15:28.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要如何促成那些必须发生的事
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.06,0:15:33.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你心跳停止之前  一切皆有可能
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.90,0:15:39.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能做的绝不仅仅是冲着个傻子大吼
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.61,0:16:06.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}美国政府财产  严禁转售获利
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.54,0:16:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}即食口粮  \N7号菜单\N牛腩配肉汁
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.71,0:16:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}火鸡胸肉
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.80,0:16:15.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.56,0:16:24.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如何
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.32,0:16:27.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,棒极了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.13,0:16:35.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以  明天...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.42,0:16:37.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们出去  把武器抢回来  对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.97,0:16:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后让简迪斯和她的人跟我们一起战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.47,0:16:43.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们杀死尼根
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.70,0:16:45.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以及其他该杀之人  来赢得战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.53,0:16:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在那之后呢
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.44,0:16:53.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后  我们继续生活
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.11,0:16:55.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  但是
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.91,0:16:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根用他的方法统治世界
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.90,0:17:03.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他死之后  我们应该建立新秩序  对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.92,0:17:07.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所有社区
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.99,0:17:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以一起想办法  讨论如何继续生活
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.82,0:17:14.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  但总得有人促成这事
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.94,0:17:17.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总得有人负责  对吗
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.81,0:17:20.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人应该是你
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.11,0:17:27.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不是我  -为什么
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.58,0:17:29.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以胜任的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.91,0:17:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你会做得很好
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.09,0:17:34.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你想做的话
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.43,0:17:38.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想做  也不愿意做
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.48,0:17:46.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果是咱们俩  你和我
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.01,0:17:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一起重建秩序
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.11,0:17:54.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我愿意
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.08,0:17:58.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如你也愿意的话...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.22,0:18:03.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愿意
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.59,0:18:25.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要再吃五包这个  好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.17,0:18:29.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.94,0:18:33.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们用不着明天就搞定
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.35,0:18:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以悠闲点
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.19,0:18:39.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过一两天再走也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.97,0:18:43.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是说  这地方没危险
Dialogue: 0,0:18:44.46,0:18:46.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,严严实实的
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.51,0:18:51.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只有一条路能进来  所以
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.20,0:18:55.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该回去
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.52,0:18:59.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,既然能拿到枪
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.74,0:19:01.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多费点时间也没关系
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.61,0:19:04.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等  我一直
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.86,0:19:06.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在等着给你看这个
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.08,0:19:13.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这可是  辣椒  奶酪意面
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.98,0:19:16.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大杂烩
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.96,0:19:17.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,试试吧
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.17,0:20:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.73,0:20:23.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在思考
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.78,0:20:30.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  你要这个
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.41,0:20:33.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,恭喜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.05,0:20:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,归你了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.42,0:20:38.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是别人送我的  曾经帮助过我的某人
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.47,0:20:41.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她为我不顾一切
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.82,0:20:44.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她救了我的命  知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.33,0:20:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她本来不用做  但却做了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.33,0:20:50.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如今这是有意义的  毋庸置疑
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.21,0:20:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要是我说了  知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.82,0:20:58.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿不到枪  瑞克是不会离开那里的
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.74,0:21:00.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算我们能成功接近那里
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.35,0:21:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们也会开火  我们会反击
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.48,0:21:10.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们应该跟我们并肩战斗的
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.19,0:21:12.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救世军杀了她们的父亲
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.86,0:21:14.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,儿子和兄弟
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.41,0:21:18.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但她们不想和我们并肩战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.92,0:21:20.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们只想藏起来
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.03,0:21:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以她们只能和我们战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.82,0:21:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我告诉大家海边旅馆的事  就会这样
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.74,0:21:41.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凭什么我们的命比他们的更珍贵
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.92,0:21:46.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就因为我们想阻止
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.95,0:21:48.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些伤害我们的人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.47,0:21:52.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那些会伤害别人的人吗
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.29,0:22:05.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.56,0:22:41.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.54,0:22:45.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行尸在外游荡  没有被关起来
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.49,0:22:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.56,0:22:50.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得干掉外面的这些
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.54,0:22:53.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把缺口堵上  然后再慢慢干掉剩下的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.57,0:22:58.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,七  八...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.72,0:23:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,九
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.88,0:23:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能用那辆车堵上
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.18,0:23:07.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能干掉挡路的那一个
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.46,0:23:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把剩下的引开
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.62,0:23:12.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你给我留了八个
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.95,0:23:16.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以朝它们开枪
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.12,0:23:17.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但这样会引来其余的行尸
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.89,0:23:20.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得悄悄行动  用剑
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.88,0:23:24.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,八个对你来说不是问题
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.62,0:25:07.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你已经干掉八个行尸了  我推得动
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.40,0:25:08.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也行
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.91,0:25:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你只要负责把车开到缺口就行
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.40,0:25:16.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.36,0:25:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,刹车坏了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.11,0:25:45.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米琼恩  你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.86,0:25:46.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.97,0:25:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.22,0:25:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.56,0:25:54.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们开过头了
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.22,0:25:57.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得还是你确定
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.14,0:26:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确定
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.57,0:26:06.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过这是个好计划
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.57,0:26:08.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这个计划超棒
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.94,0:26:39.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在这里吧
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.96,0:26:40.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.36,0:26:46.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死  这拦不住它们
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.05,0:26:53.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.84,0:27:36.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们散开  减少它们的数量
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.03,0:27:38.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,栅栏也许能挡住
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.84,0:27:40.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去滑梯  我去摩天轮
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.11,0:27:42.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或者我们可以直接逃
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.88,0:27:45.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你想逃吗  -不  我们能搞定
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.19,0:27:46.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道我们能
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.81,0:28:47.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你那边如何
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.69,0:28:48.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还剩八个
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.63,0:28:50.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.68,0:28:55.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十个
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.28,0:29:55.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.13,0:30:15.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.20,0:31:24.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米琼恩
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.07,0:31:53.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我试过了  但我还欠你一头
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.84,0:33:55.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以在外面多待几天
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.01,0:33:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢那样
Dialogue: 0,0:34:08.59,0:34:10.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直没睡
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.29,0:34:17.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想着我们失去了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.07,0:34:22.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,想着我的朋友们
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.87,0:34:27.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格伦救过我
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.01,0:34:30.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在最开始的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.22,0:34:31.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我没能救他
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.25,0:34:35.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这很正常
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.51,0:34:38.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.08,0:34:41.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,无法释怀
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.59,0:34:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们经历了一些事
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.36,0:34:47.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,光这样是不能释怀的
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.26,0:34:50.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克  我很抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.50,0:34:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们要反抗他们
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.54,0:35:03.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是接下来会发生的事
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.01,0:35:07.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会失去一些人
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.18,0:35:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许是很多人  也许是对方
Dialogue: 0,0:35:14.99,0:35:19.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使那样  也值得
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.86,0:35:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我想到...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.00,0:35:30.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能失去你
Dialogue: 0,0:35:32.84,0:35:34.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你问过我
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.24,0:35:39.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放弃算怎么个活法
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.76,0:35:43.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那不是生活
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.73,0:35:47.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们在那里做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.55,0:35:50.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们现在做的事
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.72,0:35:54.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为朱迪思拼未来
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.22,0:35:55.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为格伦和玛姬的孩子拼未来
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.82,0:35:59.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,做出抗争  这才叫生活
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.15,0:36:01.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是你让我知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.77,0:36:04.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以失去我
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.52,0:36:06.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  -你可以
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.40,0:36:08.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也可以失去你
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.01,0:36:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以失去朋友  爱的人
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.89,0:36:17.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不再是关乎我们了
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.44,0:36:19.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是关乎未来
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.00,0:36:23.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我没能活下来
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.54,0:36:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你就必须带领其他人前行
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.72,0:36:27.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你有这能力
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.48,0:36:32.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.97,0:36:35.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你怎么知道
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.01,0:36:39.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.21,0:36:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你带我走到了这里
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.70,0:36:54.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都能用吗
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.23,0:36:56.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,据我说知能
Dialogue: 0,0:36:57.89,0:37:01.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能需要清理一下  我们找到了物资
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.89,0:37:03.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要我们清理吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.83,0:37:06.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们清理了一部分  上了油
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.12,0:37:08.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,剩下的你们来  我们是合作关系
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.33,0:37:10.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的  但能用吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.82,0:37:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以开几枪试试  如果你想的话
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.47,0:37:15.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-多少把  -63把
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.73,0:37:17.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们做了清单
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.62,0:37:18.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.36,0:37:21.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说不要清单吗
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.94,0:37:25.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不够  -你说什么
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.24,0:37:27.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要很多枪  这就是很多枪
Dialogue: 0,0:37:27.60,0:37:30.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要为你战斗  我们需要两倍的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.06,0:37:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要两倍的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.37,0:37:33.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们浪费够多时间了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.64,0:37:35.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧  带上枪
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.03,0:37:36.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.43,0:37:39.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,枪是我们的  协议还没结束
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.70,0:37:45.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们不能全拿
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.64,0:37:48.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们留十把  为了找更多的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.19,0:37:50.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,五把
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.04,0:37:51.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-十把  -六把
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.20,0:37:52.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-十把  -九把
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.26,0:37:54.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且要归还猫
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.75,0:38:00.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,二十把  猫归我
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.54,0:38:03.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们给你找到枪  然后一起战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.84,0:38:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,说同意
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.62,0:38:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同意
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.59,0:38:13.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尽快拿来更多枪  我们就战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.28,0:38:40.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再多等几天
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.36,0:38:44.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,"接下来的事"就会发生
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.27,0:38:49.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再多等几天
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.79,0:38:50.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.48,0:38:53.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会找到更多枪  想办法解决
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.73,0:38:55.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很快的
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.15,0:38:58.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再多等几天
Dialogue: 0,0:39:26.84,0:39:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.97,0:39:32.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事  我只是...正准备去找你
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.35,0:39:33.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.89,0:39:35.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你见到罗西塔了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.23,0:39:37.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今早换岗她不在
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.68,0:39:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她大概出去找枪了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.18,0:39:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.51,0:39:48.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.33,0:39:50.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么找我
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.54,0:39:57.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要告诉你一些事
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.09,0:40:32.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你来这里是...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.80,0:40:34.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来这里是找你帮忙的
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.87,0:40:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有一个条件
Dialogue: 0,0:40:48.73,0:40:50.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,要由我杀他
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.47,0:40:55.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.45,0:41:02.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你带桥上的炸药了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.41,0:41:03.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我考虑过
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.77,0:41:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我不想被别人发现和阻止
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.68,0:41:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带了更好的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.68,0:41:25.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样你就能杀他了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:34.66,0:41:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克和米琼恩找到了枪
Dialogue: 0,0:41:41.38,0:41:42.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他们没准备好行动
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.44,0:41:43.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不能
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.24,0:41:46.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她们需要更多枪  更多人  更多时间
Dialogue: 0,0:41:47.38,0:41:48.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更多借口
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.69,0:41:53.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我记下了达里尔和卡尔给瑞克说的
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.48,0:41:55.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根基地内部情况
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.66,0:41:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,耶稣给我画了一张外围的地图
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.61,0:42:01.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,非常远  守卫森严
Dialogue: 0,0:42:02.10,0:42:04.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-只有我们两个人  -你要改主意吗
Dialogue: 0,0:42:04.15,0:42:05.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我准备好杀他了
Dialogue: 0,0:42:06.33,0:42:08.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我要确认你知道这意味着什么
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.86,0:42:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.37,0:42:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们不能活捉我们
Dialogue: 0,0:42:16.68,0:42:18.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果被抓住  就给了他们借口
Dialogue: 0,0:42:19.48,0:42:21.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们这是有去无回
Dialogue: 0,0:42:24.66,0:42:25.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如我们都去的话
Dialogue: 0,0:42:28.33,0:42:29.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都去
