[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Synch Point: 1
ScriptType: v4.00+
YCbCr Matrix: TV.601
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:03.06,0:00:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}竹芋
Dialogue: 0,0:00:07.07,0:00:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}荸薺
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.06,0:01:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\p1\bord0\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,200,\fscx206\fscy266\t(200,400,\fscx103\fscy133\t(29600,29800,\fscx206,fscy266\t(29800,30000,\fscx0\fscy0))))\c&H573E00&\pos(39.5,211)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10m -13 -14 l 13 -14 l 13 12 l -13 12 l -13 -14 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.06,0:01:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,200,\fscx206\fscy266\t(200,400,\fscx103\fscy133\t(29600,29800,\fscx206,fscy266\t(29800,30000,\fscx0\fscy0))))\c&HEBAE00&\bord0\shad0\fad(0,330)\pos(51.4,231.16)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.06,0:01:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,200,\fscx206\fscy266\t(200,400,\fscx103\fscy133\t(29600,29800,\fscx206,fscy266\t(29800,30000,\fscx0\fscy0))))\c&HEBAE00&\bord0\shad0\frz180\t(0,500,\clip(-1,0,386,289))\pos(27.7,188.26)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.06,0:01:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\alpha&B0\c&H000000&\t(0,200,\fscx2000\fscy600\t(200,400,\fscx2500\fscy300\t(29800,30200,\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\alpha&AA\fscy400\fscx400)))\move(158,211.2,46.5,211.2,29800,30200)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.06,0:01:18.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\fs16\fn方正大黑_GBK\move(-150,211,56,211,400,600)\clip(54.24,192,230.88,228.48)}本字幕首發于{\c&HEBAE00&}字幕組{\c&HFFFFFF&}網站\N{\c&H00C0FF&}www.ZiMuZu.tv {\c&HFFFFFF&}歡迎交流
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.06,0:01:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,301,227))}翻譯  冰藍 Reginamoon 33來了 CS小明漫畫家
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.06,0:01:28.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,291,227))}翻譯  自然卷 小酸奶 蘑菇 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.06,0:01:33.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\frx-630\t(0,500,\frx0\t(4500,5000,\clip(40,213,40,248)))\pos(57.12,210.56)}校對  冰藍 送小孩 君君
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.06,0:01:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,0)\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\move(57.12,210.56,400,210.56,4500,5000)\clip(54.24,193.92,284.24,228.48)}時間軸  加森 雪貴人 濤濤
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.06,0:01:43.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(300,300)\fn方正黑體_GBK\fs17\bord0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&HEDB425&\4c&H9EF6FF&\shad0\bord0\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))\pos(57.12,210.56)}后期 吉吉 拉圖  總監 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.06,0:01:48.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\an4\bord0\shad0\fs12\fn方正大黑_GBK\alpha&44\pos(70,211.2)}打開微信   掃描左側二維碼\N或搜索公眾號:{\c&HEBAE00&}    ustvboom\N{\c&HFFFFFF&}了解最新影視字幕發布信息
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.06,0:01:53.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fad(500,500)\an7\p3\bord0\shad0\fscx47\fscy60\alpha&H0\1c&H000000\pos(22.2,180.8)} m 350 100 l 350 110 l 360 110 l 360 100 m 360 100 m 200 130 l 200 140 l 210 140 l 210 130 m 210 130 m 100 320 l 100 330 l 110 330 l 110 320 m 110 320 m 230 80 l 230 90 l 240 90 l 240 80 m 240 80 m 240 110 l 240 120 l 250 120 l 250 110 m 250 110 m 220 230 l 220 240 l 230 240 l 230 230 m 230 230 m 120 90 l 120 100 l 130 100 l 130 90 m 130 90 m 360 60 l 360 70 l 370 70 l 370 60 m 370 60 m 140 110 l 140 120 l 150 120 l 150 110 m 150 110 m 190 340 l 190 350 l 200 350 l 200 340 m 200 340 m 180 50 l 180 60 l 190 60 l 190 50 m 190 50 m 290 190 l 290 200 l 300 200 l 300 190 m 300 190 m 170 240 l 170 250 l 180 250 l 180 240 m 180 240 m 300 160 l 300 170 l 310 170 l 310 160 m 310 160 m 330 210 l 330 220 l 340 220 l 340 210 m 340 210 m 70 60 l 70 70 l 80 70 l 80 60 m 80 60 m 240 360 l 240 370 l 250 370 l 250 360 m 250 360 m 230 170 l 230 180 l 240 180 l 240 170 m 240 170 m 210 170 l 210 180 l 220 180 l 220 170 m 220 170 m 350 250 l 350 260 l 360 260 l 360 250 m 360 250 m 240 180 l 240 190 l 250 190 l 250 180 m 250 180 m 220 140 l 220 150 l 230 150 l 230 140 m 230 140 m 270 230 l 270 240 l 280 240 l 280 230 m 280 230 m 250 190 l 250 200 l 260 200 l 260 190 m 260 190 m 120 160 l 120 170 l 130 170 l 130 160 m 130 160 m 360 290 l 360 300 l 370 300 l 370 290 m 370 290 m 260 160 l 260 170 l 270 170 l 270 160 m 270 160 m 270 130 l 270 140 l 280 140 l 280 130 m 280 130 m 120 220 l 120 230 l 130 230 l 130 220 m 130 220 m 150 190 l 150 200 l 160 200 l 160 190 m 160 190 m 160 120 l 160 130 l 170 130 l 170 120 m 170 120 m 170 170 l 170 180 l 180 180 l 180 170 m 180 170 m 40 180 l 40 190 l 50 190 l 50 180 m 50 180 m 310 100 l 310 110 l 320 110 l 320 100 m 320 100 m 60 160 l 60 170 l 70 170 l 70 160 m 70 160 m 330 80 l 330 90 l 340 90 l 340 80 m 340 80 m 70 210 l 70 220 l 80 220 l 80 210 m 80 210 m 100 180 l 100 190 l 110 190 l 110 180 m 110 180 m 110 190 l 110 200 l 120 200 l 120 190 m 120 190 m 350 220 l 350 230 l 360 230 l 360 220 m 360 220 m 220 90 l 220 100 l 230 100 l 230 90 m 230 90 m 100 360 l 100 370 l 110 370 l 110 360 m 110 360 m 250 120 l 250 130 l 260 130 l 260 120 m 260 120 m 210 280 l 210 290 l 220 290 l 220 280 m 220 280 m 260 110 l 260 120 l 270 120 l 270 110 m 270 110 m 140 130 l 140 140 l 150 140 l 150 130 m 150 130 m 120 290 l 120 300 l 130 300 l 130 290 m 130 290 m 280 320 l 280 330 l 290 330 l 290 320 m 290 320 m 180 230 l 180 240 l 190 240 l 190 230 m 190 230 m 140 230 l 140 240 l 150 240 l 150 230 m 150 230 m 190 140 l 190 150 l 200 150 l 200 140 m 200 140 m 150 300 l 150 310 l 160 310 l 160 300 m 160 300 m 300 340 l 300 350 l 310 350 l 310 340 m 310 340 m 40 90 l 40 100 l 50 100 l 50 90 m 50 90 m 280 60 l 280 70 l 290 70 l 290 60 m 290 60 m 310 350 l 310 360 l 320 360 l 320 350 m 320 350 m 50 40 l 50 50 l 60 50 l 60 40 m 60 40 m 80 150 l 80 160 l 90 160 l 90 150 m 90 150 m 320 280 l 320 290 l 330 290 l 330 280 m 330 280 m 90 140 l 90 150 l 100 150 l 100 140 m 100 140 m 100 50 l 100 60 l 110 60 l 110 50 m 110 50 m 340 60 l 340 70 l 350 70 l 350 60 m 350 60 m 230 310 l 230 320 l 240 320 l 240 310 m 240 310 m 350 310 l 350 320 l 360 320 l 360 310 m 360 310 m 100 310 l 100 320 l 110 320 l 110 310 m 110 310 m 230 50 l 230 60 l 240 60 l 240 50 m 240 50 m 360 270 l 360 280 l 370 280 l 370 270 m 370 270 m 220 260 l 220 270 l 230 270 l 230 260 m 230 260 m 160 360 l 160 370 l 170 370 l 170 360 m 170 360 m 120 40 l 120 50 l 130 50 l 130 40 m 130 40 m 140 300 l 140 310 l 150 310 l 150 300 m 150 300 m 40 320 l 40 330 l 50 330 l 50 320 m 50 320 m 160 240 l 160 250 l 170 250 l 170 240 m 170 240 m 310 240 l 310 250 l 320 250 l 320 240 m 320 240 m 170 290 l 170 300 l 180 300 l 180 290 m 180 290 m 320 270 l 320 280 l 330 280 l 330 270 m 330 270 m 60 340 l 60 350 l 70 350 l 70 340 m 70 340 m 300 70 l 300 80 l 310 80 l 310 70 m 310 70 m 330 260 l 330 270 l 340 270 l 340 260 m 340 260 m 80 280 l 80 290 l 90 290 l 90 280 m 90 280 m 230 360 l 230 370 l 240 370 l 240 360 m 240 360 m 350 40 l 350 50 l 360 50 l 360 40 m 360 40 m 100 220 l 100 230 l 110 230 l 110 220 m 110 220 m 260 210 l 260 220 l 270 220 l 270 210 m 270 210 m 270 240 l 270 250 l 280 250 l 280 240 m 280 240 m 250 80 l 250 90 l 260 90 l 260 80 m 260 80 m 120 110 l 120 120 l 130 120 l 130 110 m 130 110 m 360 80 l 360 90 l 370 90 l 370 80 m 370 80 m 260 150 l 260 160 l 270 160 l 270 150 m 270 150 m 190 280 l 190 290 l 200 290 l 200 280 m 200 280 m 280 200 l 280 210 l 290 210 l 290 200 m 290 200 m 180 110 l 180 120 l 190 120 l 190 110 m 190 110 m 160 230 l 160 240 l 170 240 l 170 230 m 170 230 m 50 220 l 50 230 l 60 230 l 60 220 m 60 220 m 170 220 l 170 230 l 180 230 l 180 220 m 180 220 m 300 140 l 300 150 l 310 150 l 310 140 m 310 140 m 70 80 l 70 90 l 80 90 l 80 80 m 80 80 m 320 80 l 320 90 l 330 90 l 330 80 m 330 80 m 350 130 l 350 140 l 360 140 l 360 130 m 360 130 m 90 100 l 90 110 l 100 110 l 100 100 m 100 100 m 330 130 l 330 140 l 340 140 l 340 130 m 340 130 m 210 70 l 210 80 l 220 80 l 220 70 m 220 70 m 350 270 l 350 280 l 360 280 l 360 270 m 360 270 m 90 360 l 90 370 l 100 370 l 100 360 m 100 360 m 240 120 l 240 130 l 250 130 l 250 120 m 250 120 m 220 120 l 220 130 l 230 130 l 230 120 m 230 120 m 270 150 l 270 160 l 280 160 l 280 150 m 280 150 m 130 210 l 130 220 l 140 220 l 140 210 m 140 210 m 180 180 l 180 190 l 190 190 l 190 180 m 190 180 m 290 260 l 290 270 l 300 270 l 300 260 m 300 260 m 190 190 l 190 200 l 200 200 l 200 190 m 200 190 m 170 150 l 170 160 l 180 160 l 180 150 m 180 150 m 40 40 l 40 50 l 50 50 l 50 40 m 50 40 m 310 280 l 310 290 l 320 290 l 320 280 m 320 280 m 50 170 l 50 180 l 60 180 l 60 170 m 60 170 m 80 180 l 80 190 l 90 190 l 90 180 m 90 180 m 320 70 l 320 80 l 330 80 l 330 70 m 330 70 m 60 140 l 60 150 l 70 150 l 70 140 m 70 140 m 330 60 l 330 70 l 340 70 l 340 60 m 340 60 m 70 230 l 70 240 l 80 240 l 80 230 m 80 230 m 100 160 l 100 170 l 110 170 l 110 160 m 110 160 m 340 290 l 340 300 l 350 300 l 350 290 m 350 290 m 110 130 l 110 140 l 120 140 l 120 130 m 120 130 m 240 270 l 240 280 l 250 280 l 250 270 m 250 270 m 200 350 l 200 360 l 210 360 l 210 350 m 210 350 m 250 260 l 250 270 l 260 270 l 260 260 m 260 260 m 210 340 l 210 350 l 220 350 l 220 340 m 220 340 m 260 90 l 260 100 l 270 100 l 270 90 m 270 90 m 220 330 l 220 340 l 230 340 l 230 330 m 230 330 m 270 40 l 270 50 l 280 50 l 280 40 m 280 40 m 360 120 l 360 130 l 370 130 l 370 120 m 370 120 m 130 300 l 130 310 l 140 310 l 140 300 m 140 300 m 280 340 l 280 350 l 290 350 l 290 340 m 290 340 m 180 210 l 180 220 l 190 220 l 190 210 m 190 210 m 190 240 l 190 250 l 200 250 l 200 240 m 200 240 m 320 360 l 320 370 l 330 370 l 330 360 m 330 360 m 300 320 l 300 330 l 310 330 l 310 320 m 310 320 m 160 350 l 160 360 l 170 360 l 170 350 m 170 350 m 50 100 l 50 110 l 60 110 l 60 100 m 60 100 m 320 300 l 320 310 l 330 310 l 330 300 m 330 300 m 300 100 l 300 110 l 310 110 l 310 100 m 310 100 m 330 310 l 330 320 l 340 320 l 340 310 m 340 310 m 340 40 l 340 50 l 350 50 l 350 40 m 350 40 m 230 330 l 230 340 l 240 340 l 240 330 m 240 330 m 300 360 l 300 370 l 310 370 l 310 360 m 310 360 m 240 340 l 240 350 l 250 350 l 250 340 m 250 340 m 200 260 l 200 270 l 210 270 l 210 260 m 210 260 m 250 350 l 250 360 l 260 360 l 260 350 m 260 350 m 230 70 l 230 80 l 240 80 l 240 70 m 240 70 m 210 270 l 210 280 l 220 280 l 220 270 m 220 270 m 260 320 l 260 330 l 270 330 l 270 320 m 270 320 m 220 240 l 220 250 l 230 250 l 230 240 m 230 240 m 270 290 l 270 300 l 280 300 l 280 290 m 280 290 m 130 70 l 130 80 l 140 80 l 140 70 m 140 70 m 180 280 l 180 290 l 190 290 l 190 280 m 190 280 m 140 280 l 140 290 l 150 290 l 150 280 m 150 280 m 150 250 l 150 260 l 160 260 l 160 250 m 160 250 m 40 340 l 40 350 l 50 350 l 50 340 m 50 340 m 180 60 l 180 70 l 190 70 l 190 60 m 190 60 m 160 260 l 160 270 l 170 270 l 170 260 m 170 260 m 170 270 l 170 280 l 180 280 l 180 270 m 180 270 m 60 320 l 60 330 l 70 330 l 70 320 m 70 320 m 300 50 l 300 60 l 310 60 l 310 50 m 310 50 m 330 240 l 330 250 l 340 250 l 340 240 m 340 240 m 310 160 l 310 170 l 320 170 l 320 160 m 320 160 m 80 300 l 80 310 l 90 310 l 90 300 m 90 300 m 320 190 l 320 200 l 330 200 l 330 190 m 330 190 m 100 200 l 100 210 l 110 210 l 110 200 m 110 200 m 250 280 l 250 290 l 260 290 l 260 280 m 260 280 m 80 360 l 80 370 l 90 370 l 90 360 m 90 360 m 210 120 l 210 130 l 220 130 l 220 120 m 220 120 m 110 250 l 110 260 l 120 260 l 120 250 m 120 250 m 220 190 l 220 200 l 230 200 l 230 190 m 230 190 m 270 260 l 270 270 l 280 270 l 280 260 m 280 260 m 250 60 l 250 70 l 260 70 l 260 60 m 260 60 m 360 100 l 360 110 l 370 110 l 370 100 m 370 100 m 260 130 l 260 140 l 270 140 l 270 130 m 270 130 m 130 80 l 130 90 l 140 90 l 140 80 m 140 80 m 270 160 l 270 170 l 280 170 l 280 160 m 280 160 m 140 70 l 140 80 l 150 80 l 150 70 m 150 70 m 190 300 l 190 310 l 200 310 l 200 300 m 200 300 m 40 250 l 40 260 l 50 260 l 50 250 m 50 250 m 50 200 l 50 210 l 60 210 l 60 200 m 60 200 m 290 230 l 290 240 l 300 240 l 300 230 m 300 230 m 190 40 l 190 50 l 200 50 l 200 40 m 200 40 m 170 200 l 170 210 l 180 210 l 180 200 m 180 200 m 60 270 l 60 280 l 70 280 l 70 270 m 70 270 m 300 120 l 300 130 l 310 130 l 310 120 m 310 120 m 40 150 l 40 160 l 50 160 l 50 150 m 50 150 m 70 100 l 70 110 l 80 110 l 80 100 m 80 100 m 320 100 l 320 110 l 330 110 l 330 100 m 330 100 m 200 80 l 200 90 l 210 90 l 210 80 m 210 80 m 240 140 l 240 150 l 250 150 l 250 140 m 250 140 m 220 100 l 220 110 l 230 110 l 230 100 m 230 100 m 140 360 l 140 370 l 150 370 l 150 360 m 150 360 m 130 170 l 130 180 l 140 180 l 140 170 m 140 170 m 270 90 l 270 100 l 280 100 l 280 90 m 280 90 m 140 140 l 140 150 l 150 150 l 150 140 m 150 140 m 120 260 l 120 270 l 130 270 l 130 260 m 130 260 m 280 290 l 280 300 l 290 300 l 290 290 m 290 290 m 150 290 l 150 300 l 160 300 l 160 290 m 160 290 m 40 60 l 40 70 l 50 70 l 50 60 m 50 60 m 70 190 l 70 200 l 80 200 l 80 190 m 80 190 m 80 120 l 80 130 l 90 130 l 90 120 m 90 120 m 320 330 l 320 340 l 330 340 l 330 330 m 330 330 m 90 170 l 90 180 l 100 180 l 100 170 m 100 170 m 330 40 l 330 50 l 340 50 l 340 40 m 340 40 m 70 250 l 70 260 l 80 260 l 80 250 m 80 250 m 290 360 l 290 370 l 300 370 l 300 360 m 300 360 m 100 60 l 100 70 l 110 70 l 110 60 m 110 60 m 230 260 l 230 270 l 240 270 l 240 260 m 240 260 m 220 50 l 220 60 l 230 60 l 230 50 m 230 50 m 200 210 l 200 220 l 210 220 l 210 210 m 210 210 m 360 240 l 360 250 l 370 250 l 370 240 m 370 240 m 260 310 l 260 320 l 270 320 l 270 310 m 270 310 m 180 270 l 180 280 l 190 280 l 190 270 m 190 270 m 140 350 l 140 360 l 150 360 l 150 350 m 150 350 m 300 300 l 300 310 l 310 310 l 310 300 m 310 300 m 280 100 l 280 110 l 290 110 l 290 100 m 290 100 m 170 320 l 170 330 l 180 330 l 180 320 m 180 320 m 320 240 l 320 250 l 330 250 l 330 240 m 330 240 m 60 70 l 60 80 l 70 80 l 70 70 m 70 70 m 300 80 l 300 90 l 310 90 l 310 80 m 310 80 m 70 300 l 70 310 l 80 310 l 80 300 m 80 300 m 310 130 l 310 140 l 320 140 l 320 130 m 320 130 m 100 90 l 100 100 l 110 100 l 110 90 m 110 90 m 340 100 l 340 110 l 350 110 l 350 100 m 350 100 m 80 330 l 80 340 l 90 340 l 90 330 m 90 330 m 90 200 l 90 210 l 100 210 l 100 200 m 100 200 m 240 280 l 240 290 l 250 290 l 250 280 m 250 280 m 70 360 l 70 370 l 80 370 l 80 360 m 80 360 m 200 120 l 200 130 l 210 130 l 210 120 m 210 120 m 100 350 l 100 360 l 110 360 l 110 350 m 110 350 m 250 330 l 250 340 l 260 340 l 260 330 m 260 330 m 260 220 l 260 230 l 270 230 l 270 220 m 270 220 m 240 100 l 240 110 l 250 110 l 250 100 m 250 100 m 250 110 l 250 120 l 260 120 l 260 110 m 260 110 m 120 80 l 120 90 l 130 90 l 130 80 m 130 80 m 360 50 l 360 60 l 370 60 l 370 50 m 370 50 m 180 340 l 180 350 l 190 350 l 190 340 m 190 340 m 140 100 l 140 110 l 150 110 l 150 100 m 150 100 m 190 350 l 190 360 l 200 360 l 200 350 m 200 350 m 40 200 l 40 210 l 50 210 l 50 200 m 50 200 m 280 170 l 280 180 l 290 180 l 290 170 m 290 170 m 180 40 l 180 50 l 190 50 l 190 40 m 190 40 m 290 120 l 290 130 l 300 130 l 300 120 m 300 120 m 190 90 l 190 100 l 200 100 l 200 90 m 200 90 m 60 300 l 60 310 l 70 310 l 70 300 m 70 300 m 300 190 l 300 200 l 310 200 l 310 190 m 310 190 m 330 220 l 330 230 l 340 230 l 340 220 m 340 220 m 70 70 l 70 80 l 80 80 l 80 70 m 80 70 m 310 180 l 310 190 l 320 190 l 320 180 m 320 180 m 340 130 l 340 140 l 350 140 l 350 130 m 350 130 m 80 80 l 80 90 l 90 90 l 90 80 m 90 80 m 350 160 l 350 170 l 360 170 l 360 160 m 360 160 m 330 160 l 330 170 l 340 170 l 340 160 m 340 160 m 200 190 l 200 200 l 210 200 l 210 190 m 210 190 m 100 260 l 100 270 l 110 270 l 110 260 m 110 260 m 260 250 l 260 260 l 270 260 l 270 250 m 270 250 m 240 170 l 240 180 l 250 180 l 250 170 m 250 170 m 220 170 l 220 180 l 230 180 l 230 170 m 230 170 m 120 150 l 120 160 l 130 160 l 130 150 m 130 150 m 130 140 l 130 150 l 140 150 l 140 140 m 140 140 m 270 180 l 270 190 l 280 190 l 280 180 m 280 180 m 290 210 l 290 220 l 300 220 l 300 210 m 300 210 m 60 250 l 60 260 l 70 260 l 70 250 m 70 250 m 80 70 l 80 80 l 90 80 l 90 70 m 90 70 m 320 40 l 320 50 l 330 50 l 330 40 m 330 40 m 280 360 l 280 370 l 290 370 l 290 360 m 290 360 m 200 100 l 200 110 l 210 110 l 210 100 m 210 100 m 230 230 l 230 240 l 240 240 l 240 230 m 240 230 m 210 110 l 210 120 l 220 120 l 220 110 m 220 110 m 240 240 l 240 250 l 250 250 l 250 240 m 250 240 m 200 320 l 200 330 l 210 330 l 210 320 m 210 320 m 250 130 l 250 140 l 260 140 l 260 130 m 260 130 m 210 290 l 210 300 l 220 300 l 220 290 m 220 290 m 260 100 l 260 110 l 270 110 l 270 100 m 270 100 m 140 120 l 140 130 l 150 130 l 150 120 m 150 120 m 280 310 l 280 320 l 290 320 l 290 310 m 290 310 m 180 220 l 180 230 l 190 230 l 190 220 m 190 220 m 160 100 l 160 110 l 170 110 l 170 100 m 170 100 m 140 220 l 140 230 l 150 230 l 150 220 m 150 220 m 190 150 l 190 160 l 200 160 l 200 150 m 200 150 m 150 310 l 150 320 l 160 320 l 160 310 m 160 310 m 40 80 l 40 90 l 50 90 l 50 80 m 50 80 m 280 50 l 280 60 l 290 60 l 290 50 m 290 50 m 310 320 l 310 330 l 320 330 l 320 320 m 320 320 m 60 100 l 60 110 l 70 110 l 70 100 m 70 100 m 330 340 l 330 350 l 340 350 l 340 340 m 340 340 m 70 270 l 70 280 l 80 280 l 80 270 m 80 270 m 100 40 l 100 50 l 110 50 l 110 40 m 110 40 m 340 330 l 340 340 l 350 340 l 350 330 m 350 330 m 80 200 l 80 210 l 90 210 l 90 200 m 90 200 m 60 360 l 60 370 l 70 370 l 70 360 m 70 360 m 350 280 l 350 290 l 360 290 l 360 280 m 360 280 m 240 230 l 240 240 l 250 240 l 250 230 m 250 230 m 200 230 l 200 240 l 210 240 l 210 230 m 210 230 m 100 300 l 100 310 l 110 310 l 110 300 m 110 300 m 250 220 l 250 230 l 260 230 l 260 220 m 260 220 m 210 220 l 210 230 l 220 230 l 220 220 m 220 220 m 360 160 l 360 170 l 370 170 l 370 160 m 370 160 m 140 330 l 140 340 l 150 340 l 150 330 m 150 330 m 170 40 l 170 50 l 180 50 l 180 40 m 180 40 m 150 200 l 150 210 l 160 210 l 160 200 m 160 200 m 300 280 l 300 290 l 310 290 l 310 280 m 310 280 m 40 310 l 40 320 l 50 320 l 50 310 m 50 310 m 280 120 l 280 130 l 290 130 l 290 120 m 290 120 m 310 250 l 310 260 l 320 260 l 320 250 m 320 250 m 50 300 l 50 310 l 60 310 l 60 300 m 60 300 m 320 260 l 320 270 l 330 270 l 330 260 m 330 260 m 300 60 l 300 70 l 310 70 l 310 60 m 310 60 m 70 320 l 70 330 l 80 330 l 80 320 m 80 320 m 340 80 l 340 90 l 350 90 l 350 80 m 350 80 m 240 300 l 240 310 l 250 310 l 250 300 m 250 300 m 100 330 l 100 340 l 110 340 l 110 330 m 110 330 m 230 110 l 230 120 l 240 120 l 240 110 m 240 110 m 120 360 l 120 370 l 130 370 l 130 360 m 130 360 m 260 200 l 260 210 l 270 210 l 270 200 m 270 200 m 270 250 l 270 260 l 280 260 l 280 250 m 280 250 m 250 90 l 250 100 l 260 100 l 260 90 m 260 90 m 120 100 l 120 110 l 130 110 l 130 100 m 130 100 m 360 70 l 360 80 l 370 80 l 370 70 m 370 70 m 180 320 l 180 330 l 190 330 l 190 320 m 190 320 m 190 290 l 190 300 l 200 300 l 200 290 m 200 290 m 40 220 l 40 230 l 50 230 l 50 220 m 50 220 m 280 190 l 280 200 l 290 200 l 290 190 m 290 190 m 180 100 l 180 110 l 190 110 l 190 100 m 190 100 m 160 220 l 160 230 l 170 230 l 170 220 m 170 220 m 290 180 l 290 190 l 300 190 l 300 180 m 300 180 m 40 120 l 40 130 l 50 130 l 50 120 m 50 120 m 330 200 l 330 210 l 340 210 l 340 200 m 340 200 m 310 40 l 310 50 l 320 50 l 320 40 m 320 40 m 80 100 l 80 110 l 90 110 l 90 100 m 90 100 m 350 180 l 350 190 l 360 190 l 360 180 m 360 180 m 330 140 l 330 150 l 340 150 l 340 140 m 340 140 m 200 50 l 200 60 l 210 60 l 210 50 m 210 50 m 100 240 l 100 250 l 110 250 l 110 240 m 110 240 m 340 210 l 340 220 l 350 220 l 350 210 m 350 210 m 110 210 l 110 220 l 120 220 l 120 210 m 120 210 m 270 220 l 270 230 l 280 230 l 280 220 m 280 220 m 250 180 l 250 190 l 260 190 l 260 180 m 260 180 m 120 170 l 120 180 l 130 180 l 130 170 m 130 170 m 270 120 l 270 130 l 280 130 l 280 120 m 280 120 m 140 190 l 140 200 l 150 200 l 150 190 m 150 190 m 180 130 l 180 140 l 190 140 l 190 130 m 190 130 m 160 130 l 160 140 l 170 140 l 170 130 m 170 130 m 290 270 l 290 280 l 300 280 l 300 270 m 300 270 m 170 160 l 170 170 l 180 170 l 180 160 m 180 160 m 300 240 l 300 250 l 310 250 l 310 240 m 310 240 m 70 140 l 70 150 l 80 150 l 80 140 m 80 140 m 50 180 l 50 190 l 60 190 l 60 180 m 60 180 m 80 170 l 80 180 l 90 180 l 90 170 m 90 170 m 320 60 l 320 70 l 330 70 l 330 60 m 330 60 m 90 40 l 90 50 l 100 50 l 100 40 m 100 40 m 330 70 l 330 80 l 340 80 l 340 70 m 340 70 m 70 200 l 70 210 l 80 210 l 80 200 m 80 200 m 50 360 l 50 370 l 60 370 l 60 360 m 60 360 m 230 250 l 230 260 l 240 260 l 240 250 m 240 250 m 210 90 l 210 100 l 220 100 l 220 90 m 220 90 m 350 330 l 350 340 l 360 340 l 360 330 m 360 330 m 220 60 l 220 70 l 230 70 l 230 60 m 230 60 m 250 270 l 250 280 l 260 280 l 260 270 m 260 270 m 210 350 l 210 360 l 220 360 l 220 350 m 220 350 m 260 80 l 260 90 l 270 90 l 270 80 m 270 80 m 120 300 l 120 310 l 130 310 l 130 300 m 130 300 m 150 110 l 150 120 l 160 120 l 160 110 m 160 110 m 130 310 l 130 320 l 140 320 l 140 310 m 140 310 m 280 330 l 280 340 l 290 340 l 290 330 m 290 330 m 290 280 l 290 290 l 300 290 l 300 280 m 300 280 m 170 90 l 170 100 l 180 100 l 180 90 m 180 90 m 150 330 l 150 340 l 160 340 l 160 330 m 160 330 m 300 350 l 300 360 l 310 360 l 310 350 m 310 350 m 40 100 l 40 110 l 50 110 l 50 100 m 50 100 m 310 340 l 310 350 l 320 350 l 320 340 m 320 340 m 320 290 l 320 300 l 330 300 l 330 290 m 330 290 m 60 80 l 60 90 l 70 90 l 70 80 m 70 80 m 330 320 l 330 330 l 340 330 l 340 320 m 340 320 m 100 100 l 100 110 l 110 110 l 110 100 m 110 100 m 340 70 l 340 80 l 350 80 l 350 70 m 350 70 m 350 300 l 350 310 l 360 310 l 360 300 m 360 300 m 240 330 l 240 340 l 250 340 l 250 330 m 250 330 m 200 250 l 200 260 l 210 260 l 210 250 m 210 250 m 100 280 l 100 290 l 110 290 l 110 280 m 110 280 m 250 200 l 250 210 l 260 210 l 260 200 m 260 200 m 210 200 l 210 210 l 220 210 l 220 200 m 220 200 m 260 350 l 260 360 l 270 360 l 270 350 m 270 350 m 270 340 l 270 350 l 280 350 l 280 340 m 280 340 m 130 320 l 130 330 l 140 330 l 140 320 m 140 320 m 190 220 l 190 230 l 200 230 l 200 220 m 200 220 m 40 330 l 40 340 l 50 340 l 50 330 m 50 330 m 280 140 l 280 150 l 290 150 l 290 140 m 290 140 m 160 250 l 160 260 l 170 260 l 170 250 m 170 250 m 310 270 l 310 280 l 320 280 l 320 270 m 320 270 m 50 280 l 50 290 l 60 290 l 60 280 m 60 280 m 290 150 l 290 160 l 300 160 l 300 150 m 300 150 m 170 280 l 170 290 l 180 290 l 180 280 m 180 280 m 320 200 l 320 210 l 330 210 l 330 200 m 330 200 m 300 40 l 300 50 l 310 50 l 310 40 m 310 40 m 70 340 l 70 350 l 80 350 l 80 340 m 80 340 m 310 170 l 310 180 l 320 180 l 320 170 m 320 170 m 200 160 l 200 170 l 210 170 l 210 160 m 210 160 m 250 290 l 250 300 l 260 300 l 260 290 m 260 290 m 210 130 l 210 140 l 220 140 l 220 130 m 220 130 m 260 260 l 260 270 l 270 270 l 270 260 m 270 260 m 240 60 l 240 70 l 250 70 l 250 60 m 250 60 m 220 180 l 220 190 l 230 190 l 230 180 m 230 180 m 250 70 l 250 80 l 260 80 l 260 70 m 260 70 m 120 120 l 120 130 l 130 130 l 130 120 m 130 120 m 360 90 l 360 100 l 370 100 l 370 90 m 370 90 m 260 120 l 260 130 l 270 130 l 270 120 m 270 120 m 130 90 l 130 100 l 140 100 l 140 90 m 140 90 m 190 310 l 190 320 l 200 320 l 200 310 m 200 310 m 150 150 l 150 160 l 160 160 l 160 150 m 160 150 m 40 240 l 40 250 l 50 250 l 50 240 m 50 240 m 50 210 l 50 220 l 60 220 l 60 210 m 60 210 m 290 160 l 290 170 l 300 170 l 300 160 m 300 160 m 170 210 l 170 220 l 180 220 l 180 210 m 180 210 m 60 260 l 60 270 l 70 270 l 70 260 m 70 260 m 40 140 l 40 150 l 50 150 l 50 140 m 50 140 m 50 150 l 50 160 l 60 160 l 60 150 m 60 150 m 80 40 l 80 50 l 90 50 l 90 40 m 90 40 m 40 360 l 40 370 l 50 370 l 50 360 m 50 360 m 330 120 l 330 130 l 340 130 l 340 120 m 340 120 m 200 70 l 200 80 l 210 80 l 210 70 m 210 70 m 100 140 l 100 150 l 110 150 l 110 140 m 110 140 m 210 60 l 210 70 l 220 70 l 220 60 m 220 60 m 110 230 l 110 240 l 120 240 l 120 230 m 120 230 m 350 260 l 350 270 l 360 270 l 360 260 m 360 260 m 240 130 l 240 140 l 250 140 l 250 130 m 250 130 m 220 130 l 220 140 l 230 140 l 230 130 m 230 130 m 200 290 l 200 300 l 210 300 l 210 290 m 210 290 m 360 320 l 360 330 l 370 330 l 370 320 m 370 320 m 260 70 l 260 80 l 270 80 l 270 70 m 270 70 m 130 180 l 130 190 l 140 190 l 140 180 m 140 180 m 270 140 l 270 150 l 280 150 l 280 140 m 280 140 m 140 170 l 140 180 l 150 180 l 150 170 m 150 170 m 120 250 l 120 260 l 130 260 l 130 250 m 130 250 m 280 280 l 280 290 l 290 290 l 290 280 m 290 280 m 140 270 l 140 280 l 150 280 l 150 270 m 150 270 m 190 180 l 190 190 l 200 190 l 200 180 m 200 180 m 170 140 l 170 150 l 180 150 l 180 140 m 180 140 m 300 220 l 300 230 l 310 230 l 310 220 m 310 220 m 40 50 l 40 60 l 50 60 l 50 50 m 50 50 m 320 320 l 320 330 l 330 330 l 330 320 m 330 320 m 60 150 l 60 160 l 70 160 l 70 150 m 70 150 m 90 180 l 90 190 l 100 190 l 100 180 m 100 180 m 340 340 l 340 350 l 350 350 l 350 340 m 350 340 m 80 250 l 80 260 l 90 260 l 90 250 m 90 250 m 230 270 l 230 280 l 240 280 l 240 270 m 240 270 m 110 120 l 110 130 l 120 130 l 120 120 m 120 120 m 260 360 l 260 370 l 270 370 l 270 360 m 270 360 m 240 200 l 240 210 l 250 210 l 250 200 m 250 200 m 200 200 l 200 210 l 210 210 l 210 200 m 210 200 m 220 300 l 220 310 l 230 310 l 230 300 m 230 300 m 120 320 l 120 330 l 130 330 l 130 320 m 130 320 m 360 130 l 360 140 l 370 140 l 370 130 m 370 130 m 130 290 l 130 300 l 140 300 l 140 290 m 140 290 m 280 350 l 280 360 l 290 360 l 290 350 m 290 350 m 180 260 l 180 270 l 190 270 l 190 260 m 190 260 m 160 60 l 160 70 l 170 70 l 170 60 m 170 60 m 300 330 l 300 340 l 310 340 l 310 330 m 310 330 m 40 280 l 40 290 l 50 290 l 50 280 m 50 280 m 280 90 l 280 100 l 290 100 l 290 90 m 290 90 m 160 280 l 160 290 l 170 290 l 170 280 m 170 280 m 170 330 l 170 340 l 180 340 l 180 330 m 180 330 m 320 310 l 320 320 l 330 320 l 330 310 m 330 310 m 60 60 l 60 70 l 70 70 l 70 60 m 70 60 m 330 300 l 330 310 l 340 310 l 340 300 m 340 300 m 210 360 l 210 370 l 220 370 l 220 360 m 220 360 m 100 80 l 100 90 l 110 90 l 110 80 m 110 80 m 80 320 l 80 330 l 90 330 l 90 320 m 90 320 m 230 320 l 230 330 l 240 330 l 240 320 m 240 320 m 90 210 l 90 220 l 100 220 l 100 210 m 100 210 m 100 340 l 100 350 l 110 350 l 110 340 m 110 340 m 230 60 l 230 70 l 240 70 l 240 60 m 240 60 m 240 90 l 240 100 l 250 100 l 250 90 m 250 90 m 120 70 l 120 80 l 130 80 l 130 70 m 130 70 m 360 40 l 360 50 l 370 50 l 370 40 m 370 40 m 130 60 l 130 70 l 140 70 l 140 60 m 140 60 m 180 290 l 180 300 l 190 300 l 190 290 m 190 290 m 190 320 l 190 330 l 200 330 l 200 320 m 200 320 m 150 240 l 150 250 l 160 250 l 160 240 m 160 240 m 40 350 l 40 360 l 50 360 l 50 350 m 50 350 m 280 160 l 280 170 l 290 170 l 290 160 m 290 160 m 160 270 l 160 280 l 170 280 l 170 270 m 170 270 m 170 260 l 170 270 l 180 270 l 180 260 m 180 260 m 60 330 l 60 340 l 70 340 l 70 330 m 70 330 m 70 40 l 70 50 l 80 50 l 80 40 m 80 40 m 320 120 l 320 130 l 330 130 l 330 120 m 330 120 m 360 360 l 360 370 l 370 370 l 370 360 m 370 360 m 90 300 l 90 310 l 100 310 l 100 300 m 100 300 m 210 190 l 210 200 l 220 200 l 220 190 m 220 190 m 110 240 l 110 250 l 120 250 l 120 240 m 120 240 m 270 210 l 270 220 l 280 220 l 280 210 m 280 210 m 260 180 l 260 190 l 270 190 l 270 180 m 270 180 m 270 190 l 270 200 l 280 200 l 280 190 m 280 190 m 120 200 l 120 210 l 130 210 l 130 200 m 130 200 m 180 140 l 180 150 l 190 150 l 190 140 m 190 140 m 160 180 l 160 190 l 170 190 l 170 180 m 170 180 m 60 240 l 60 250 l 70 250 l 70 240 m 70 240 m 40 160 l 40 170 l 50 170 l 50 160 m 50 160 m 50 130 l 50 140 l 60 140 l 60 130 m 60 130 m 80 60 l 80 70 l 90 70 l 90 60 m 90 60 m 60 180 l 60 190 l 70 190 l 70 180 m 70 180 m 350 140 l 350 150 l 360 150 l 360 140 m 360 140 m 330 100 l 330 110 l 340 110 l 340 100 m 340 100 m 100 120 l 100 130 l 110 130 l 110 120 m 110 120 m 250 360 l 250 370 l 260 370 l 260 360 m 260 360 m 230 200 l 230 210 l 240 210 l 240 200 m 240 200 m 350 200 l 350 210 l 360 210 l 360 200 m 360 200 m 240 150 l 240 160 l 250 160 l 250 150 m 250 150 m 200 310 l 200 320 l 210 320 l 210 310 m 210 310 m 140 150 l 140 160 l 150 160 l 150 150 m 150 150 m 120 270 l 120 280 l 130 280 l 130 270 m 130 270 m 150 60 l 150 70 l 160 70 l 160 60 m 160 60 m 130 260 l 130 270 l 140 270 l 140 260 m 140 260 m 280 300 l 280 310 l 290 310 l 290 300 m 290 300 m 180 170 l 180 180 l 190 180 l 190 170 m 190 170 m 190 120 l 190 130 l 200 130 l 200 120 m 200 120 m 170 120 l 170 130 l 180 130 l 180 120 m 180 120 m 150 280 l 150 290 l 160 290 l 160 280 m 160 280 m 300 200 l 300 210 l 310 210 l 310 200 m 310 200 m 40 70 l 40 80 l 50 80 l 50 70 m 50 70 m 280 40 l 280 50 l 290 50 l 290 40 m 290 40 m 80 130 l 80 140 l 90 140 l 90 130 m 90 130 m 320 340 l 320 350 l 330 350 l 330 340 m 330 340 m 60 130 l 60 140 l 70 140 l 70 130 m 70 130 m 100 70 l 100 80 l 110 80 l 110 70 m 110 70 m 240 220 l 240 230 l 250 230 l 250 220 m 250 220 m 200 220 l 200 230 l 210 230 l 210 220 m 210 220 m 250 230 l 250 240 l 260 240 l 260 230 m 260 230 m 210 230 l 210 240 l 220 240 l 220 230 m 220 230 m 220 280 l 220 290 l 230 290 l 230 280 m 230 280 m 270 330 l 270 340 l 280 340 l 280 330 m 280 330 m 360 150 l 360 160 l 370 160 l 370 150 m 370 150 m 180 240 l 180 250 l 190 250 l 190 240 m 190 240 m 290 320 l 290 330 l 300 330 l 300 320 m 300 320 m 190 210 l 190 220 l 200 220 l 200 210 m 200 210 m 170 50 l 170 60 l 180 60 l 180 50 m 180 50 m 150 210 l 150 220 l 160 220 l 160 210 m 160 210 m 40 300 l 40 310 l 50 310 l 50 300 m 50 300 m 280 110 l 280 120 l 290 120 l 290 110 m 290 110 m 160 300 l 160 310 l 170 310 l 170 300 m 170 300 m 170 310 l 170 320 l 180 320 l 180 310 m 180 310 m 60 40 l 60 50 l 70 50 l 70 40 m 70 40 m 300 90 l 300 100 l 310 100 l 310 90 m 310 90 m 330 280 l 330 290 l 340 290 l 340 280 m 340 280 m 70 330 l 70 340 l 80 340 l 80 330 m 80 330 m 310 120 l 310 130 l 320 130 l 320 120 m 320 120 m 80 340 l 80 350 l 90 350 l 90 340 m 90 340{\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.53,0:02:07.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-好啊  卡蘿爾  -托賓\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hey, Carol. - Tobin.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.54,0:02:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你該吃點餅干\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You deserve some cookies.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.62,0:02:12.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  孩子們還餓著呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, no, not with the kids as hungry--
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.59,0:02:16.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  有很多  我找到了很多橡子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, there's plenty. I foraged a lot of acorns.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.24,0:02:24.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-這是粉色的  -甜菜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- They're pink. - Beets.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.56,0:02:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-甜菜  -能讓它們更甜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Beets? - It's what makes them sweet.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.10,0:02:31.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不大喜歡吃甜菜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I never was much of a beet kind of guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.60,0:02:33.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你別廢話了直接吃行嗎  混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Will you just put it in your mouth, jerk.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.25,0:02:50.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是我吃過的最好吃的甜菜橡子餅干\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're the best beet and acorn cookies I've ever eaten.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.97,0:02:53.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在耍我嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you screwing with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.42,0:02:54.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.41,0:02:56.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Seriously.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.36,0:02:59.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,太好吃了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.60,0:03:00.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們回來了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're back!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.51,0:03:20.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去找奧利維亞\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get Olivia.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.09,0:03:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她該登記我們帶回來的東西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She should inventory what we have.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.65,0:03:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫她在儲藏室見我們\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll meet her at the pantry.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.16,0:03:26.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你們弄到了食物嗎  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You have food? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.72,0:03:28.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,足夠再撐一個月\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Enough for another month.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.04,0:03:32.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叫大家一小時內到教堂集合\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need everybody in the church in an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.49,0:03:33.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.94,0:03:35.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們一會兒說\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll talk about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.92,0:03:42.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rick, what's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.28,0:03:45.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們得戰斗了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna have to fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.64,0:04:23.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那事過后有一陣子了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's been a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.40,0:04:26.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幾周了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Weeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.94,0:04:29.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-什么事  -聊天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Since what? - Since we talked.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.51,0:04:32.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們在那牢房里只聊天了嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's what we did in that cell? We talked.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.48,0:04:39.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你為什么不告訴瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why didn't you tell Rick?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.72,0:04:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔拉  羅西塔  尤金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tara, Rosita, Eugene?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.72,0:04:46.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他們為什么沒有說  -我叫他們保密\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Why didn't they...? - I told them to keep quiet about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.07,0:04:48.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.96,0:04:52.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們能忘了這事  翻篇嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can we just forget it, move past it?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.71,0:04:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒必要背負那事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't have to carry that.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.52,0:04:57.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Carry what?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.73,0:04:59.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道我做了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.53,0:05:02.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不想告訴別人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't want to tell anyone, it--
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.85,0:05:07.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好像你也做了一樣\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's kind of like you did it, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.81,0:05:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, it's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.09,0:05:15.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just go.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.93,0:05:41.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}山姆·安德森
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.31,0:06:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs21}本藍光版外掛字幕由  {\c&H9B30FF&}風吹來的那片云{\c&HFFFFFF&}  用WEB版調軸
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.31,0:06:16.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第六季  第十二集』
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.88,0:06:21.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以跟山頂寨合作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And we can work with the Hilltop.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.43,0:06:24.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪姬談定了一筆交易\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maggie hammered out a deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.88,0:06:26.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們為我們提供食物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're getting food--
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.34,0:06:29.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雞蛋  黃油  新鮮蔬菜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Eggs, butter, fresh vegetables.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.04,0:06:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他們不是白送的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But they're not just giving it away.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.08,0:06:35.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這些救世軍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}These Saviors,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.91,0:06:39.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,差點在路上殺了薩沙  達里爾和亞伯拉罕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}they almost killed Sasha, Daryl, and Abraham on the road.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.04,0:06:41.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們遲早會找到我們\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, sooner or later, they would've found us,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.62,0:06:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就跟狼群一樣\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just like those Wolves did,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.66,0:06:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟耶穌一樣\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just like Jesus did.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.29,0:06:48.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們會殺死我們中的一個或幾個\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They would killed someone or some of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.99,0:06:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后他們會試圖支配我們\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And then they would try to own us.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.93,0:06:53.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而我們會試圖阻止他們\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And we would try to stop them.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.19,0:06:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但到了那個時候  在那種戰斗中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But by then, in that kind of fight,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.91,0:07:01.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們糧食短缺  可能會輸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}low on food, we could lose.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.00,0:07:03.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是唯一一種能盡可能地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is the only way to be sure,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.96,0:07:06.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,確保我們取勝的方式\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as sure as we can get, that we win.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.26,0:07:08.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們必須贏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And we have to win.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.71,0:07:12.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們只有幫山頂寨這個忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We do this for the Hilltop,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.58,0:07:15.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能保護這里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it's how we keep this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.02,0:07:17.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才能養活這里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's how we feed this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.73,0:07:20.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這件事得集體表決\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This needs to be a group decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.94,0:07:24.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如有人反對\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If anybody objects,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.35,0:07:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在就是你們發表意見的機會\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}here's your chance to say your piece.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.20,0:07:37.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你確定我們能取勝嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're sure we can do it?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.72,0:07:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以打敗他們嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can beat them?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.61,0:07:48.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,憑借我們做過的事  我們學到的東西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What this group has done, what we've learned,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.36,0:07:50.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們所成為的人  我們所有人...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}what we've become, all of us--
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.37,0:07:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯  我確定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I'm sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.59,0:07:54.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我們只用告訴他們這一點就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then all we have to do is just tell them that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.66,0:07:56.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們是不會妥協的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, they don't compromise.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.27,0:07:57.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這不是要他們妥協\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This isn't a compromise.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.26,0:08:01.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是給他們一個選擇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a choice you give them.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.66,0:08:04.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是一條出路  對他們和對我們都是如此\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a way out, for them and for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.87,0:08:06.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,假如我們試著去和救世軍談\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We try and talk to the Saviors,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.57,0:08:08.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我們就放棄了我們的先機和安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we give up our advantage, our safety.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.99,0:08:13.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  我們得在他們找上門之前搶先出擊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, we have to come for them before they come for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.85,0:08:16.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不能讓他們活著\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can't leave them alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.04,0:08:18.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要有生命  便有可能性\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where there's life, there's possibility.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.77,0:08:20.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有他們攻擊我們的可能性\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of them hitting us.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.10,0:08:21.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不是必須這樣做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're not trapped in this.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.93,0:08:23.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們沒有一個人必須這樣做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}None of you are trapped in this.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.71,0:08:27.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩根...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Morgan...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.37,0:08:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們總是會回來的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They always come back.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.98,0:08:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們死后也會回來的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come back when they're dead, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.53,0:08:34.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒錯  到時我們會阻止它們\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, we'll stop them.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.84,0:08:35.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們之前就阻止過\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have before.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.62,0:08:37.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我說的不是行尸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not talking about the walkers.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.80,0:08:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩根想要先和他們談談\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Morgan wants to talk to them first.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.84,0:08:45.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得那是個錯誤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think that would be a mistake,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.65,0:08:47.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但這不取決于我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but it's not up to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.38,0:08:49.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我會和那些待在家中的人談談\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll talk to the people still at home.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.26,0:08:51.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也會和現在正在放哨的人討論\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll discuss it with the people on guard now, too,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.58,0:08:54.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但這里還有沒有人想要先和救世軍接觸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but who else wants to approach the Saviors,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.91,0:08:56.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和他們談談\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}talk to them first?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.41,0:08:57.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這個地方發生過的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What happened here,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.21,0:09:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不會讓它再次發生了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we won't let that happen again.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.66,0:09:04.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I won't.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.91,0:09:19.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就定了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Looks like it's settled.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.29,0:09:23.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們很清楚這是怎么一回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We know exactly what this is.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.68,0:09:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不回避它  才能生存\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't shy from it, we live.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.08,0:09:30.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們要把他們殺光\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We kill them all.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.45,0:09:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是所有人都得動手殺人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't all have to kill.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.26,0:09:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但選擇留在這里的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But if people are gonna stay here...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.37,0:09:48.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,必須接受這一點\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}they do have to accept it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.94,0:10:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}瑞恩\N凱倫  大衛\N麗茲\N終點站/院子  3?\N蠟燭女  4\N狼群  7
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.65,0:10:30.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}共計18
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.83,0:10:42.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,需要有人在周邊放哨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need someone on the perimeter keeping watch.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.56,0:10:43.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That could be me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.99,0:10:46.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這樣才安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That would be safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.48,0:10:48.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,更安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Safer.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.53,0:10:55.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在再安全也不安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever safer looks like now.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.41,0:10:56.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.00,0:10:59.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交易是我談的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I made that deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.06,0:11:03.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雖然不是我的主意  但卻牽連了大家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It wasn't my idea, but I led us into this.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.96,0:11:08.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必須去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have to come.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.18,0:11:16.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那東西會要你的命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Those things'll kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.66,0:11:19.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有多余的嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got another one?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.02,0:11:22.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒你的份\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:22.84,0:11:24.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And why is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.56,0:11:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為你是混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'cause, asshole.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.98,0:11:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.43,0:11:31.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也睡不著嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Couldn't sleep either?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.04,0:11:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我什么時候睡著過\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I never could sleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.95,0:11:43.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很擔心明天的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Worried about tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.85,0:11:45.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你去嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You going?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.36,0:11:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.51,0:11:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是你要去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.81,0:11:56.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你做出的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can do things that--
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.31,0:12:00.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能把我嚇死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That just terrify me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:05.94,0:12:06.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.77,0:12:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你覺得我為什么做得到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How do you think I do those things?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.80,0:12:18.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是位母親\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're a mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.43,0:12:20.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以前是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.76,0:12:24.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在也是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.31,0:12:26.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It-- it--
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.22,0:12:31.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不是說餅干和微笑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not the cookies or the smiles.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.18,0:12:32.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's--
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.94,0:12:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,棘手的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's the hard stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.94,0:12:38.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可怕的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The scary stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.74,0:12:43.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你才做得到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's how you can do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.33,0:12:46.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是力量\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's strength.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.50,0:12:52.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在大多數人的心中  你是位母親\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're a mom to most of the people here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.56,0:12:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在你心中也是嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To you, too?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.77,0:13:04.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.91,0:13:09.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在我心中很特別\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're something else to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.90,0:13:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還沒到明天呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, it's not tomorrow yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.01,0:13:36.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就開始收拾了嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Packing your stilettos?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.26,0:13:38.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們只離開一個晚上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll only be gone a night.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.27,0:13:39.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm going.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.78,0:13:41.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也去  但是明天才去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am, too, but tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.29,0:13:45.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm leaving.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.31,0:13:55.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,為什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.41,0:13:56.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就這樣發生了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.67,0:14:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你當真要走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you serious?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.26,0:14:03.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是我所希望的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is how I want it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.86,0:14:08.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-為什么  -為什么紅果莓是棕色的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Why? - Why are dingleberries brown?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.71,0:14:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,哪有那么多狗屁理由\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just the way shit is.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.58,0:14:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  不  我們經歷了這么多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no. After everything we've been through,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.87,0:14:15.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不許一走了之  除非告訴我理由\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you are not walking out that door unless you can tell me why.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.70,0:14:16.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.52,0:14:19.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,告訴我理由\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me why!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.49,0:14:21.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,第一次見到你的時候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I first met you,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.50,0:14:23.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以為你是地球上最后一個女人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought you were the last woman on Earth.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.65,0:14:26.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.11,0:14:54.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你嘗過這個嗎  很有嚼頭\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You try one of these? They're chewy.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.44,0:14:56.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有點...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.82,0:14:59.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,勁道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}got some fight in them.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.21,0:15:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,描述一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Describe it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.37,0:15:10.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,長方形的建筑  頂部有個大接收器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rectangular building, big satellites on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.48,0:15:11.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有窗戶嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Any windows?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.20,0:15:13.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不記得了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't remember any.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.36,0:15:15.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想他們只給那地方留了一個入口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think they made it so there's only one way in.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.75,0:15:17.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,門口有守衛嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Guards outside?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.70,0:15:20.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有  至少兩個\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, two of them, at least.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.16,0:15:22.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不知道他們有多少人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And you don't know how many people they have?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.28,0:15:23.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.34,0:15:35.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}主門  院子
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.95,0:15:28.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不知道  我看到過一個儲存食物的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, no. I saw a place where they stored food.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:28.30,0:15:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面不大  所以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It wasn't that big, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.13,0:15:32.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你進去過嗎  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You've been inside? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.09,0:15:35.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們讓我們搬過一次補給品\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They had us load in supplies one time.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.83,0:15:37.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你記得什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.63,0:15:40.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你擔心嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you worried?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.79,0:15:42.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.76,0:15:46.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不擔心  只是...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, it's just...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.20,0:15:51.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我愛你  走之前我想說出來...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love you, and I just wanted to say it before...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.01,0:15:53.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不用回應我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you don't have to say it back.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.79,0:15:57.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那個...  -等你回來我再回應你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's...  - I'll say it when you come back.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.60,0:16:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,希斯和我還得再出去兩周\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Heath and I are still going on that two-weeker.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.45,0:16:01.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們就從那里出發\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna leave from there.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.58,0:16:05.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想一起走嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you want to come?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.59,0:16:08.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以改計劃  不用從基地走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, I can change it so we don't leave from the compound.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.28,0:16:10.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們可以回來  從這里走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We could come back and we could leave from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.75,0:16:13.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我們要拿些藥品  所以...  -我不能去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You know, we're gonna get meds, so... - I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.67,0:16:16.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我得留在這  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No, I didn't-- I'm-- I just-- I need to be here. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.11,0:16:17.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在我是唯一的醫生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm the only doctor now.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.19,0:16:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我不能去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.14,0:16:21.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.07,0:16:28.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我很想去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I want to.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.42,0:16:34.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等你回來我會回應你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll tell you when you come back.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.21,0:16:38.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.57,0:16:48.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你沒看到其他房間嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And you didn't see any other rooms?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.58,0:16:51.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒有  地方很大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, it's a big place.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.46,0:17:15.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}食品間
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.60,0:16:53.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是我看到的那條走廊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is the hallway I saw.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.80,0:16:55.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有更多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There is more.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.13,0:16:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,每次他們都讓你們把東西搬到這里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And every time, they had you bring things into here?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.99,0:17:00.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jesus.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.48,0:17:02.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們帶過一些長矛給他們\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We brought a couple spears for them.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.97,0:17:05.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,兩個救世軍沿著這條走廊把東西帶進去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Two of the Saviors took them down this hallway.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.40,0:17:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們一定是做了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, they must've done something with them
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.40,0:17:09.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為他們沒把東西帶回來\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because they didn't come back with them.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.06,0:17:11.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許是個武器柜  軍械庫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe a weapons locker, an armory.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.21,0:17:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.32,0:17:16.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們進去  守住軍械庫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We get in there, secure the armory,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.26,0:17:17.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就能終結戰斗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that's how we end it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.63,0:17:20.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,當時卡蘿爾在這里也是這么做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's how Carol ended it here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.90,0:17:25.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他們是否有軍械庫  \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But we don't know if they have an armory
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.93,0:17:27.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,甚至在哪我們都不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or where it even is.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.45,0:17:30.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們有很多可靠的推測\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, we've got a lot of good guesses.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.70,0:17:32.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,靠更少的情報我們都成功過\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We've done more with less.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.32,0:17:34.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們晚上趁他們睡覺時潛入\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We go in at night while they're sleeping.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.23,0:17:36.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,守衛不會睡覺的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The guards won't be sleeping.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.77,0:17:40.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,正如我說  我認為只有一條路進去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Like I said, I think there's only one way in
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.13,0:17:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒辦法在不吵醒其他人的情況下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and there's no way to bust through that door
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.68,0:17:42.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直接從那扇門突入\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}without waking up the rest of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.99,0:17:44.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用吵醒他們\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't need to.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.27,0:17:48.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們會開門讓我們進去的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're going to open it for us, let us walk right in.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.71,0:17:52.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們要格雷戈里的人頭  對吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They want Gregory's head, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.44,0:17:56.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們就給他們\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna give it to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.34,0:18:27.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亞倫  羅西塔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Aaron, Rosita.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.99,0:18:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們從這開始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You start here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.61,0:18:33.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們每四分之一英里就分頭行動\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll peel off every quarter mile,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.12,0:18:36.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,幾小時后來這會合\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}meet back here in a couple of hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.81,0:18:38.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看有什么收獲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See what we got.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.19,0:18:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在沒法回頭了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's no turning back now.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.90,0:18:47.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I could walk.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:48.42,0:18:50.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許能跑一小段  也許能跑很久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe run a little, maybe a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.77,0:18:53.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我哪都不去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not going anywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.88,0:18:56.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想學習  你教我是有原因的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanted to learn and you taught me for a reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.88,0:19:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你為什么還穿成這樣\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why are you still wearing that?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.31,0:19:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我覺得  我還是我自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's still who I was. I think.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.38,0:19:13.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且他們很難在黑暗中看到我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And it'll be harder for them to see me in the dark.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.46,0:19:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我差點就在會上跟大家說了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I almost told everyone at the meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.26,0:19:31.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不能告訴他們\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're not telling them.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.52,0:19:33.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摩根在教堂里站出來  \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Morgan stood up in that church
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.93,0:19:35.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,試圖說服我們不要這樣做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and tried to talk us out of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.65,0:19:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那又怎樣\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's wrong with that?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.40,0:19:39.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許他不知道他在說什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe that he didn't know what the hell he's talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.61,0:19:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們沒把他藏匿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That he should take the win
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.92,0:19:43.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個精神病的事抖出來  他就應該知足\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that we didn't kick his ass out for hiding that psychopath.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.86,0:19:44.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我們跟所有人說  \N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If we told everyone,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.80,0:19:47.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們也會知道丹妮斯的事  你知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}they'd find out about Denise, you know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.28,0:19:51.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那個婊子養的想站在那\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That hijo de puta tried to stand there
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.04,0:19:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,表現得好像我們不知道我們...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and act like we didn't know what we were--
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.90,0:19:54.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他不想殺人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He doesn't want to kill.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.04,0:19:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們也不想殺人  也不喜歡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't want to kill. We don't like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.78,0:19:59.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但就這樣發生了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.98,0:20:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不會跟人說的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not telling anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.41,0:20:51.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,覺得如何\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you think?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.12,0:20:53.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也許可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.40,0:20:57.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我們剪一下頭發\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If we, um, cut the hair...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.66,0:20:59.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,修一下胡子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}trim the beard.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.69,0:21:02.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果天黑了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If it's dark.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.04,0:21:09.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們要殺了那些人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna kill those people.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.67,0:21:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就今晚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.97,0:21:15.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直很幸運\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I've been lucky.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.86,0:21:17.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前都沒必要這樣做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I haven't had to do it before.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.14,0:21:20.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have you?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.25,0:21:22.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也一直很幸運\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've been lucky, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.28,0:21:25.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你緊張嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You nervous?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.85,0:21:31.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你經歷過那種...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have you ever seen something that, um...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.03,0:21:36.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,經歷過之后  你...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}afterwards, you--
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.09,0:21:38.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不想睡覺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you didn't want to sleep
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.95,0:21:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你根本不餓  因為當你閉上眼睛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you weren't hungry because when you close your eyes
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.55,0:21:44.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就會浮現在眼前的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you could see it?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.86,0:21:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-當你試圖去吃東西...  -有過\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- And when you try to eat-- - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.46,0:21:52.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Me, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.16,0:22:00.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺人肯定比這感覺糟多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Killing somebody has gotta be worse than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.11,0:22:02.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定更糟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It has to be.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.32,0:22:06.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以沒錯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, yeah...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.89,0:22:09.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很緊張\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm nervous.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.54,0:22:11.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對于這一切  伙計\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For the whole thing, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.48,0:22:14.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對于這一切都是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For the whole thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.35,0:22:31.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們要去四周看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna take a look around,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.26,0:22:34.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,摸清楚那里到底有多少人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}try to get a feel for how many people are in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.78,0:22:39.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我們覺得可行  就潛入\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We like how it looks, we go in.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.42,0:22:42.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,黎明前的那幾個小時\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A couple of hours before dawn.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.92,0:22:46.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面的守衛也倦了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The guards outside'll be tired.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.65,0:22:48.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,里面的人都在睡覺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everyone inside'll be sleeping.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.75,0:22:53.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果感覺形勢不對就撤退  重訂計劃\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't like what we see, we head back, make a new plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.15,0:22:55.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們不知道我們是誰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They don't know who we are.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.95,0:22:58.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們要讓耶穌躲在暗處\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll keep Jesus in the shadows.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.04,0:23:01.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是我們的生存方式\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is how we eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.57,0:23:05.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是我們的生存方式\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is how we eat.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.59,0:23:10.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們半夜出發\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We roll out at midnight.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.04,0:23:23.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑪姬怎么也來了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why is Maggie here?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.31,0:23:24.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她負責在周邊放哨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's guarding the perimeter.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.74,0:23:27.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  但她為什么會來\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, but why is she here?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.14,0:23:29.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因為這是她的選擇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause it's her choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.81,0:23:32.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想跟她一起待在外面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want to stay out there with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.54,0:23:34.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們必須率先奪取軍械庫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, this whole thing's a race to the armory.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.57,0:23:36.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們需要盡可能多的人一起進去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need as many people inside as we can get.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.57,0:23:37.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她不該一個人在外面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She shouldn't be out there alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.87,0:23:41.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她一開始就不該來\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She shouldn't be out here in the first place.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.84,0:23:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.98,0:23:48.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.53,0:23:55.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她把頭發弄好了嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's done with the hair?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.13,0:23:57.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,現在是什么情況\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What've we got?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.95,0:24:00.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那個  -就那個\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That one. - That's it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.20,0:24:03.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.70,0:24:07.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還好我們是晚上行動\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Though, it's probably good we're doing this at night.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.14,0:24:10.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有什么問題嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Something wrong with it?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.16,0:24:15.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鼻子  格雷戈里的鼻子形狀不一樣\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The nose. Gregory's is a different shape.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.43,0:24:26.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他反抗了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He fought back.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.74,0:24:29.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他打斷了你的手  對吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He broke your hand, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.46,0:24:32.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看來沒必要追究細節了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Guess there's no reason to be subtle about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.72,0:24:38.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.97,0:24:41.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,救世軍很可怕  但是...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The Saviors, they're scary, but ...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.94,0:24:43.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那幫混球跟你比差遠了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}those pricks got nothing on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.78,0:25:14.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,停在那\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stop right there!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.90,0:25:18.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,報上名來  混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Announce yourself, asshole!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.00,0:25:19.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是山頂寨的埃迪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's Eddie from Hilltop!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.83,0:25:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,任務已完成\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's done!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.99,0:25:23.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出來\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Step out!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.68,0:25:36.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是他的頭嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is that it?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.51,0:25:38.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.91,0:25:42.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿過來  蠢貨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bring it here, shit brain!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.35,0:25:59.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,從袋子里拿出來  小牙簽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't want the bag, needle dick.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.76,0:26:15.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看這狗東西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Will you look at this shit?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.58,0:26:18.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看這狗東西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Will you look at this shit?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.95,0:26:37.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他打斷了我的手  我打斷了他的鼻子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He broke my hand. I broke his nose.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.30,0:26:38.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以他看起來是這樣的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's why he looks that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.29,0:27:02.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小賤人打斷了我的鼻子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Little bitch broke my nose.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.06,0:27:15.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  看來你長教訓了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, looks like you learned.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.13,0:27:18.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我放了你的人  你回家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll get your guy, you'll go home,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.27,0:27:21.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,下周多帶點貢品過來  知道嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you bring us more stuff next week, hmm?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.88,0:28:08.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧誰來了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, well, well. Look who it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.83,0:28:14.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,沒事  沒事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's okay, it's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.42,0:28:16.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們帶你回家  帶你回家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're bringing you back. We're bringing you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:37.40,0:28:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,檢查門  找到軍械庫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Check the doors. Find the arsenal.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.15,0:28:41.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們去干掉他們\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We take them out.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:08.06,0:32:09.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你還是神父嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You still a priest?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.62,0:32:16.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克和卡爾教我用槍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rick and Carl taught me about guns,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.08,0:32:19.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,還有其他武器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}other weapons.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.02,0:32:22.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,教我怎么出一份力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How to contribute.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.88,0:32:29.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我還是神父\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm still a priest.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.14,0:32:38.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天早上我對我女朋友撒謊了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I lied to my girlfriend this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.39,0:32:44.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我...  她發現我在想事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I, um-- she caught me thinking about something,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.96,0:32:46.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我告訴她我愛她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so I told her that I loved her.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.35,0:32:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我第一次對她這樣說\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For the first time.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.74,0:32:54.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我這么對她說是為了隱瞞一些事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's how I told her, covering something up.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.40,0:33:00.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在隱瞞什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What were you covering?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.20,0:33:04.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以前做過這種事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That I'd done something like this before.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.72,0:33:07.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并不喜歡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That I didn't like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.75,0:33:11.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.88,0:33:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你愛她嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you love her?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.07,0:33:20.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.08,0:33:25.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你知道自己是為什么而戰了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, you know what you're fighting for.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.05,0:33:49.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,藏寶室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Honeypot.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:14.33,0:34:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們有麻煩了  待在這\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're in trouble. Stay here.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.79,0:34:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我和你一塊去  -我說了待在這\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm going with you. - I said stay here.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.40,0:34:18.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.32,0:34:19.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,該死  瑪姬\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damn it, Maggie.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.70,0:34:23.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我必須去  -不  你不必\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I have to. - No, you don't. You don't have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.06,0:34:24.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  我必須去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.15,0:34:25.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你到底來這里做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the hell are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.37,0:34:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我應該做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What am I supposed to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.42,0:34:29.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你應該做個母親\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're supposed to be someone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.17,0:34:35.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們需要我們的幫助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They need our help.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.80,0:34:50.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你必須留在這里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are staying here.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.27,0:35:03.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們得走了  送他們回山頂寨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need to go. Get them back to the Hilltop.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.15,0:35:06.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么  你們的人可能有危險\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What? Your people could be in trouble.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.09,0:35:08.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你帶他們回去  交易依然有效  對嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you get them back, the deal's still on, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.69,0:35:09.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,對嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.72,0:35:10.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他們能自己回去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If they get themselves back.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.93,0:35:12.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安迪  送他們回山頂寨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Andy, drive him back to the Hilltop.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.64,0:35:21.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,聽著  如果他們看到你  而我們沒成功\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, if they see you and we don't make it--
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.16,0:35:23.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們會成功的  他們不會看到我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna make it. And they're not gonna see me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.26,0:35:27.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是認真的嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you kidding?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.76,0:35:34.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.87,0:36:04.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是我們死  就是你們亡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If it wasn't us, it was gonna be you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.91,0:36:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,搞什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The hell?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.37,0:36:27.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這是上鎖的房間之一  我掩護你  上吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's one of the locked ones. I'm gonna cover you. Do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.71,0:36:43.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.90,0:38:14.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,這就是新世界\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, this is the next world.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.85,0:38:26.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放下槍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Drop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.86,0:38:28.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放下槍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Drop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.58,0:38:30.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You, uh--
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.09,0:38:33.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你會殺我嗎  神父\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You gonna kill me, Padre?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.32,0:38:37.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,神父\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Padre?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.31,0:38:41.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們心里不要憂愁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Let not your heart be troubled."
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.77,0:38:45.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跟我一樣死定了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're just as dead as me.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.54,0:38:49.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在我父的家里  有許多住處\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"In my father's house are many mansions.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.01,0:38:51.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,若是沒有  我就早已告訴你們了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If it were not so, I would've told you."
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.38,0:38:52.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們都死定了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're all dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.37,0:38:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}全部引自《約翰福音》
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.37,0:38:56.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我若去為你們預備了地方  -要見血了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- "I go prepare a place for you." - Blood's coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.05,0:39:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,阿門\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Amen.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.36,0:39:33.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想跟我們回家嗎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, you want to just come back with us?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.44,0:39:36.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,休息幾天  再和塔拉出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Take a couple days before you and Tara go out again?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.11,0:39:39.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不了老兄  我只想盡快離開這里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, man. I just want to get out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.08,0:41:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.58,0:41:04.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just--
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.77,0:41:08.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想知道他們中哪個是尼根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just want to know which one of them was Negan.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:14.77,0:41:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,狗雜種\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Son of a bitch!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:28.05,0:41:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是從哪里搞到摩托的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where'd you get the bike?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.57,0:41:32.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,殺了我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just do it!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.87,0:41:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就像你們殺了其他人一樣  對吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Like you did everyone else, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.47,0:41:39.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放下武器  混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lower your gun, prick.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.94,0:41:43.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拿著柯爾特蟒蛇左輪的那個\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You, with the Colt Python.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.03,0:41:46.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你們所有人  立刻放下武器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All of you, lower your weapons right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.67,0:41:56.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,出來\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on out.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:57.52,0:41:58.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們談談\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.89,0:42:02.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我們不會出來  但我們會談談\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're not coming out, but we will talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.95,0:42:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡蘿爾和瑪姬在我們手上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We've got a Carol and a Maggie.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.43,0:42:10.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你們應該想談談這個\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm thinking that's something you want to chat about.
