1
00:00:02,610 --> 00:00:04,890
上面說點火開關保險絲
It says the ignition switch fuse

2
00:00:04,890 --> 00:00:06,660
在27號位置
is found at location number 27.

3
00:00:06,660 --> 00:00:08,980
好吧  27號  我得知道那在哪
All right, 27. I need to know where that is.

4
00:00:10,280 --> 00:00:13,080
就在這里
Um, right here.

5
00:00:13,540 --> 00:00:15,440
好吧  這個壞了
Yeah, okay, this one's blown.

6
00:00:15,440 --> 00:00:17,000
這個紅色的是什么
What's this one, the red one?

7
00:00:21,600 --> 00:00:23,080
爸媽  我們得走了
Mom, Dad, we got to go.

8
00:00:23,080 --> 00:00:24,880
-快點  快點  -我們看見它們了
- Come on, come on. - We see them.

9
00:00:25,540 --> 00:00:27,670
我們得找到保險絲來發動車
Just need to find a fuse so we can start the car.

10
00:00:27,670 --> 00:00:29,530
就快找到了  親愛的  6號位置
Almost got it, honey. Location six.

11
00:00:29,530 --> 00:00:31,940
那里有轉向燈和剎車燈
That's turn signal lamps and stop lamps.

12
00:00:31,950 --> 00:00:34,180
沒有轉向燈也行
All right, we can live without turn signals.

13
00:00:34,850 --> 00:00:35,980
爸  它們來...
Dad, they're com--

14
00:02:47,850 --> 00:03:17,850
m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10m -13 -14 l 13 -14 l 13 12 l -13 12 l -13 -14

15
00:02:47,850 --> 00:03:17,850
m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10

16
00:02:47,850 --> 00:03:17,850
m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10

17
00:02:47,850 --> 00:03:27,850
■

18
00:02:47,850 --> 00:02:52,850
本字幕首發于字幕組網站
www.ZiMuZu.tv 歡迎交流

19
00:02:52,850 --> 00:02:57,850
翻譯  冰藍 Reginamoon 33來了 送小孩

20
00:02:57,850 --> 00:03:02,850
翻譯  小酸奶 自然卷 CS小明漫畫家

21
00:03:02,850 --> 00:03:07,850
校對 送小孩 冰藍

22
00:03:07,850 --> 00:03:12,850
時間軸  雪貴人 加森 濤濤 想念Gallifrey

23
00:03:12,850 --> 00:03:17,850
后期 送小哥 拉圖  總監 送小孩吃涼皮

24
00:03:17,850 --> 00:03:22,850
打開微信   掃描左側二維碼
或搜索公眾號:    ustvboom
了解最新影視字幕發布信息

25
00:03:17,850 --> 00:03:27,850
m 350 100 l 350 110 l 360 110 l 360 100 m 360 100 m 200 130 l 200 140 l 210 140 l 210 130 m 210 130 m 100 320 l 100 330 l 110 330 l 110 320 m 110 320 m 230 80 l 230 90 l 240 90 l 240 80 m 240 80 m 240 110 l 240 120 l 250 120 l 250 110 m 250 110 m 220 230 l 220 240 l 230 240 l 230 230 m 230 230 m 120 90 l 120 100 l 130 100 l 130 90 m 130 90 m 360 60 l 360 70 l 370 70 l 370 60 m 370 60 m 140 110 l 140 120 l 150 120 l 150 110 m 150 110 m 190 340 l 190 350 l 200 350 l 200 340 m 200 340 m 180 50 l 180 60 l 190 60 l 190 50 m 190 50 m 290 190 l 290 200 l 300 200 l 300 190 m 300 190 m 170 240 l 170 250 l 180 250 l 180 240 m 180 240 m 300 160 l 300 170 l 310 170 l 310 160 m 310 160 m 330 210 l 330 220 l 340 220 l 340 210 m 340 210 m 70 60 l 70 70 l 80 70 l 80 60 m 80 60 m 240 360 l 240 370 l 250 370 l 250 360 m 250 360 m 230 170 l 230 180 l 240 180 l 240 170 m 240 170 m 210 170 l 210 180 l 220 180 l 220 170 m 220 170 m 350 250 l 350 260 l 360 260 l 360 250 m 360 250 m 240 180 l 240 190 l 250 190 l 250 180 m 250 180 m 220 140 l 220 150 l 230 150 l 230 140 m 230 140 m 270 230 l 270 240 l 280 240 l 280 230 m 280 230 m 250 190 l 250 200 l 260 200 l 260 190 m 260 190 m 120 160 l 120 170 l 130 170 l 130 160 m 130 160 m 360 290 l 360 300 l 370 300 l 370 290 m 370 290 m 260 160 l 260 170 l 270 170 l 270 160 m 270 160 m 270 130 l 270 140 l 280 140 l 280 130 m 280 130 m 120 220 l 120 230 l 130 230 l 130 220 m 130 220 m 150 190 l 150 200 l 160 200 l 160 190 m 160 190 m 160 120 l 160 130 l 170 130 l 170 120 m 170 120 m 170 170 l 170 180 l 180 180 l 180 170 m 180 170 m 40 180 l 40 190 l 50 190 l 50 180 m 50 180 m 310 100 l 310 110 l 320 110 l 320 100 m 320 100 m 60 160 l 60 170 l 70 170 l 70 160 m 70 160 m 330 80 l 330 90 l 340 90 l 340 80 m 340 80 m 70 210 l 70 220 l 80 220 l 80 210 m 80 210 m 100 180 l 100 190 l 110 190 l 110 180 m 110 180 m 110 190 l 110 200 l 120 200 l 120 190 m 120 190 m 350 220 l 350 230 l 360 230 l 360 220 m 360 220 m 220 90 l 220 100 l 230 100 l 230 90 m 230 90 m 100 360 l 100 370 l 110 370 l 110 360 m 110 360 m 250 120 l 250 130 l 260 130 l 260 120 m 260 120 m 210 280 l 210 290 l 220 290 l 220 280 m 220 280 m 260 110 l 260 120 l 270 120 l 270 110 m 270 110 m 140 130 l 140 140 l 150 140 l 150 130 m 150 130 m 120 290 l 120 300 l 130 300 l 130 290 m 130 290 m 280 320 l 280 330 l 290 330 l 290 320 m 290 320 m 180 230 l 180 240 l 190 240 l 190 230 m 190 230 m 140 230 l 140 240 l 150 240 l 150 230 m 150 230 m 190 140 l 190 150 l 200 150 l 200 140 m 200 140 m 150 300 l 150 310 l 160 310 l 160 300 m 160 300 m 300 340 l 300 350 l 310 350 l 310 340 m 310 340 m 40 90 l 40 100 l 50 100 l 50 90 m 50 90 m 280 60 l 280 70 l 290 70 l 290 60 m 290 60 m 310 350 l 310 360 l 320 360 l 320 350 m 320 350 m 50 40 l 50 50 l 60 50 l 60 40 m 60 40 m 80 150 l 80 160 l 90 160 l 90 150 m 90 150 m 320 280 l 320 290 l 330 290 l 330 280 m 330 280 m 90 140 l 90 150 l 100 150 l 100 140 m 100 140 m 100 50 l 100 60 l 110 60 l 110 50 m 110 50 m 340 60 l 340 70 l 350 70 l 350 60 m 350 60 m 230 310 l 230 320 l 240 320 l 240 310 m 240 310 m 350 310 l 350 320 l 360 320 l 360 310 m 360 310 m 100 310 l 100 320 l 110 320 l 110 310 m 110 310 m 230 50 l 230 60 l 240 60 l 240 50 m 240 50 m 360 270 l 360 280 l 370 280 l 370 270 m 370 270 m 220 260 l 220 270 l 230 270 l 230 260 m 230 260 m 160 360 l 160 370 l 170 370 l 170 360 m 170 360 m 120 40 l 120 50 l 130 50 l 130 40 m 130 40 m 140 300 l 140 310 l 150 310 l 150 300 m 150 300 m 40 320 l 40 330 l 50 330 l 50 320 m 50 320 m 160 240 l 160 250 l 170 250 l 170 240 m 170 240 m 310 240 l 310 250 l 320 250 l 320 240 m 320 240 m 170 290 l 170 300 l 180 300 l 180 290 m 180 290 m 320 270 l 320 280 l 330 280 l 330 270 m 330 270 m 60 340 l 60 350 l 70 350 l 70 340 m 70 340 m 300 70 l 300 80 l 310 80 l 310 70 m 310 70 m 330 260 l 330 270 l 340 270 l 340 260 m 340 260 m 80 280 l 80 290 l 90 290 l 90 280 m 90 280 m 230 360 l 230 370 l 240 370 l 240 360 m 240 360 m 350 40 l 350 50 l 360 50 l 360 40 m 360 40 m 100 220 l 100 230 l 110 230 l 110 220 m 110 220 m 260 210 l 260 220 l 270 220 l 270 210 m 270 210 m 270 240 l 270 250 l 280 250 l 280 240 m 280 240 m 250 80 l 250 90 l 260 90 l 260 80 m 260 80 m 120 110 l 120 120 l 130 120 l 130 110 m 130 110 m 360 80 l 360 90 l 370 90 l 370 80 m 370 80 m 260 150 l 260 160 l 270 160 l 270 150 m 270 150 m 190 280 l 190 290 l 200 290 l 200 280 m 200 280 m 280 200 l 280 210 l 290 210 l 290 200 m 290 200 m 180 110 l 180 120 l 190 120 l 190 110 m 190 110 m 160 230 l 160 240 l 170 240 l 170 230 m 170 230 m 50 220 l 50 230 l 60 230 l 60 220 m 60 220 m 170 220 l 170 230 l 180 230 l 180 220 m 180 220 m 300 140 l 300 150 l 310 150 l 310 140 m 310 140 m 70 80 l 70 90 l 80 90 l 80 80 m 80 80 m 320 80 l 320 90 l 330 90 l 330 80 m 330 80 m 350 130 l 350 140 l 360 140 l 360 130 m 360 130 m 90 100 l 90 110 l 100 110 l 100 100 m 100 100 m 330 130 l 330 140 l 340 140 l 340 130 m 340 130 m 210 70 l 210 80 l 220 80 l 220 70 m 220 70 m 350 270 l 350 280 l 360 280 l 360 270 m 360 270 m 90 360 l 90 370 l 100 370 l 100 360 m 100 360 m 240 120 l 240 130 l 250 130 l 250 120 m 250 120 m 220 120 l 220 130 l 230 130 l 230 120 m 230 120 m 270 150 l 270 160 l 280 160 l 280 150 m 280 150 m 130 210 l 130 220 l 140 220 l 140 210 m 140 210 m 180 180 l 180 190 l 190 190 l 190 180 m 190 180 m 290 260 l 290 270 l 300 270 l 300 260 m 300 260 m 190 190 l 190 200 l 200 200 l 200 190 m 200 190 m 170 150 l 170 160 l 180 160 l 180 150 m 180 150 m 40 40 l 40 50 l 50 50 l 50 40 m 50 40 m 310 280 l 310 290 l 320 290 l 320 280 m 320 280 m 50 170 l 50 180 l 60 180 l 60 170 m 60 170 m 80 180 l 80 190 l 90 190 l 90 180 m 90 180 m 320 70 l 320 80 l 330 80 l 330 70 m 330 70 m 60 140 l 60 150 l 70 150 l 70 140 m 70 140 m 330 60 l 330 70 l 340 70 l 340 60 m 340 60 m 70 230 l 70 240 l 80 240 l 80 230 m 80 230 m 100 160 l 100 170 l 110 170 l 110 160 m 110 160 m 340 290 l 340 300 l 350 300 l 350 290 m 350 290 m 110 130 l 110 140 l 120 140 l 120 130 m 120 130 m 240 270 l 240 280 l 250 280 l 250 270 m 250 270 m 200 350 l 200 360 l 210 360 l 210 350 m 210 350 m 250 260 l 250 270 l 260 270 l 260 260 m 260 260 m 210 340 l 210 350 l 220 350 l 220 340 m 220 340 m 260 90 l 260 100 l 270 100 l 270 90 m 270 90 m 220 330 l 220 340 l 230 340 l 230 330 m 230 330 m 270 40 l 270 50 l 280 50 l 280 40 m 280 40 m 360 120 l 360 130 l 370 130 l 370 120 m 370 120 m 130 300 l 130 310 l 140 310 l 140 300 m 140 300 m 280 340 l 280 350 l 290 350 l 290 340 m 290 340 m 180 210 l 180 220 l 190 220 l 190 210 m 190 210 m 190 240 l 190 250 l 200 250 l 200 240 m 200 240 m 320 360 l 320 370 l 330 370 l 330 360 m 330 360 m 300 320 l 300 330 l 310 330 l 310 320 m 310 320 m 160 350 l 160 360 l 170 360 l 170 350 m 170 350 m 50 100 l 50 110 l 60 110 l 60 100 m 60 100 m 320 300 l 320 310 l 330 310 l 330 300 m 330 300 m 300 100 l 300 110 l 310 110 l 310 100 m 310 100 m 330 310 l 330 320 l 340 320 l 340 310 m 340 310 m 340 40 l 340 50 l 350 50 l 350 40 m 350 40 m 230 330 l 230 340 l 240 340 l 240 330 m 240 330 m 300 360 l 300 370 l 310 370 l 310 360 m 310 360 m 240 340 l 240 350 l 250 350 l 250 340 m 250 340 m 200 260 l 200 270 l 210 270 l 210 260 m 210 260 m 250 350 l 250 360 l 260 360 l 260 350 m 260 350 m 230 70 l 230 80 l 240 80 l 240 70 m 240 70 m 210 270 l 210 280 l 220 280 l 220 270 m 220 270 m 260 320 l 260 330 l 270 330 l 270 320 m 270 320 m 220 240 l 220 250 l 230 250 l 230 240 m 230 240 m 270 290 l 270 300 l 280 300 l 280 290 m 280 290 m 130 70 l 130 80 l 140 80 l 140 70 m 140 70 m 180 280 l 180 290 l 190 290 l 190 280 m 190 280 m 140 280 l 140 290 l 150 290 l 150 280 m 150 280 m 150 250 l 150 260 l 160 260 l 160 250 m 160 250 m 40 340 l 40 350 l 50 350 l 50 340 m 50 340 m 180 60 l 180 70 l 190 70 l 190 60 m 190 60 m 160 260 l 160 270 l 170 270 l 170 260 m 170 260 m 170 270 l 170 280 l 180 280 l 180 270 m 180 270 m 60 320 l 60 330 l 70 330 l 70 320 m 70 320 m 300 50 l 300 60 l 310 60 l 310 50 m 310 50 m 330 240 l 330 250 l 340 250 l 340 240 m 340 240 m 310 160 l 310 170 l 320 170 l 320 160 m 320 160 m 80 300 l 80 310 l 90 310 l 90 300 m 90 300 m 320 190 l 320 200 l 330 200 l 330 190 m 330 190 m 100 200 l 100 210 l 110 210 l 110 200 m 110 200 m 250 280 l 250 290 l 260 290 l 260 280 m 260 280 m 80 360 l 80 370 l 90 370 l 90 360 m 90 360 m 210 120 l 210 130 l 220 130 l 220 120 m 220 120 m 110 250 l 110 260 l 120 260 l 120 250 m 120 250 m 220 190 l 220 200 l 230 200 l 230 190 m 230 190 m 270 260 l 270 270 l 280 270 l 280 260 m 280 260 m 250 60 l 250 70 l 260 70 l 260 60 m 260 60 m 360 100 l 360 110 l 370 110 l 370 100 m 370 100 m 260 130 l 260 140 l 270 140 l 270 130 m 270 130 m 130 80 l 130 90 l 140 90 l 140 80 m 140 80 m 270 160 l 270 170 l 280 170 l 280 160 m 280 160 m 140 70 l 140 80 l 150 80 l 150 70 m 150 70 m 190 300 l 190 310 l 200 310 l 200 300 m 200 300 m 40 250 l 40 260 l 50 260 l 50 250 m 50 250 m 50 200 l 50 210 l 60 210 l 60 200 m 60 200 m 290 230 l 290 240 l 300 240 l 300 230 m 300 230 m 190 40 l 190 50 l 200 50 l 200 40 m 200 40 m 170 200 l 170 210 l 180 210 l 180 200 m 180 200 m 60 270 l 60 280 l 70 280 l 70 270 m 70 270 m 300 120 l 300 130 l 310 130 l 310 120 m 310 120 m 40 150 l 40 160 l 50 160 l 50 150 m 50 150 m 70 100 l 70 110 l 80 110 l 80 100 m 80 100 m 320 100 l 320 110 l 330 110 l 330 100 m 330 100 m 200 80 l 200 90 l 210 90 l 210 80 m 210 80 m 240 140 l 240 150 l 250 150 l 250 140 m 250 140 m 220 100 l 220 110 l 230 110 l 230 100 m 230 100 m 140 360 l 140 370 l 150 370 l 150 360 m 150 360 m 130 170 l 130 180 l 140 180 l 140 170 m 140 170 m 270 90 l 270 100 l 280 100 l 280 90 m 280 90 m 140 140 l 140 150 l 150 150 l 150 140 m 150 140 m 120 260 l 120 270 l 130 270 l 130 260 m 130 260 m 280 290 l 280 300 l 290 300 l 290 290 m 290 290 m 150 290 l 150 300 l 160 300 l 160 290 m 160 290 m 40 60 l 40 70 l 50 70 l 50 60 m 50 60 m 70 190 l 70 200 l 80 200 l 80 190 m 80 190 m 80 120 l 80 130 l 90 130 l 90 120 m 90 120 m 320 330 l 320 340 l 330 340 l 330 330 m 330 330 m 90 170 l 90 180 l 100 180 l 100 170 m 100 170 m 330 40 l 330 50 l 340 50 l 340 40 m 340 40 m 70 250 l 70 260 l 80 260 l 80 250 m 80 250 m 290 360 l 290 370 l 300 370 l 300 360 m 300 360 m 100 60 l 100 70 l 110 70 l 110 60 m 110 60 m 230 260 l 230 270 l 240 270 l 240 260 m 240 260 m 220 50 l 220 60 l 230 60 l 230 50 m 230 50 m 200 210 l 200 220 l 210 220 l 210 210 m 210 210 m 360 240 l 360 250 l 370 250 l 370 240 m 370 240 m 260 310 l 260 320 l 270 320 l 270 310 m 270 310 m 180 270 l 180 280 l 190 280 l 190 270 m 190 270 m 140 350 l 140 360 l 150 360 l 150 350 m 150 350 m 300 300 l 300 310 l 310 310 l 310 300 m 310 300 m 280 100 l 280 110 l 290 110 l 290 100 m 290 100 m 170 320 l 170 330 l 180 330 l 180 320 m 180 320 m 320 240 l 320 250 l 330 250 l 330 240 m 330 240 m 60 70 l 60 80 l 70 80 l 70 70 m 70 70 m 300 80 l 300 90 l 310 90 l 310 80 m 310 80 m 70 300 l 70 310 l 80 310 l 80 300 m 80 300 m 310 130 l 310 140 l 320 140 l 320 130 m 320 130 m 100 90 l 100 100 l 110 100 l 110 90 m 110 90 m 340 100 l 340 110 l 350 110 l 350 100 m 350 100 m 80 330 l 80 340 l 90 340 l 90 330 m 90 330 m 90 200 l 90 210 l 100 210 l 100 200 m 100 200 m 240 280 l 240 290 l 250 290 l 250 280 m 250 280 m 70 360 l 70 370 l 80 370 l 80 360 m 80 360 m 200 120 l 200 130 l 210 130 l 210 120 m 210 120 m 100 350 l 100 360 l 110 360 l 110 350 m 110 350 m 250 330 l 250 340 l 260 340 l 260 330 m 260 330 m 260 220 l 260 230 l 270 230 l 270 220 m 270 220 m 240 100 l 240 110 l 250 110 l 250 100 m 250 100 m 250 110 l 250 120 l 260 120 l 260 110 m 260 110 m 120 80 l 120 90 l 130 90 l 130 80 m 130 80 m 360 50 l 360 60 l 370 60 l 370 50 m 370 50 m 180 340 l 180 350 l 190 350 l 190 340 m 190 340 m 140 100 l 140 110 l 150 110 l 150 100 m 150 100 m 190 350 l 190 360 l 200 360 l 200 350 m 200 350 m 40 200 l 40 210 l 50 210 l 50 200 m 50 200 m 280 170 l 280 180 l 290 180 l 290 170 m 290 170 m 180 40 l 180 50 l 190 50 l 190 40 m 190 40 m 290 120 l 290 130 l 300 130 l 300 120 m 300 120 m 190 90 l 190 100 l 200 100 l 200 90 m 200 90 m 60 300 l 60 310 l 70 310 l 70 300 m 70 300 m 300 190 l 300 200 l 310 200 l 310 190 m 310 190 m 330 220 l 330 230 l 340 230 l 340 220 m 340 220 m 70 70 l 70 80 l 80 80 l 80 70 m 80 70 m 310 180 l 310 190 l 320 190 l 320 180 m 320 180 m 340 130 l 340 140 l 350 140 l 350 130 m 350 130 m 80 80 l 80 90 l 90 90 l 90 80 m 90 80 m 350 160 l 350 170 l 360 170 l 360 160 m 360 160 m 330 160 l 330 170 l 340 170 l 340 160 m 340 160 m 200 190 l 200 200 l 210 200 l 210 190 m 210 190 m 100 260 l 100 270 l 110 270 l 110 260 m 110 260 m 260 250 l 260 260 l 270 260 l 270 250 m 270 250 m 240 170 l 240 180 l 250 180 l 250 170 m 250 170 m 220 170 l 220 180 l 230 180 l 230 170 m 230 170 m 120 150 l 120 160 l 130 160 l 130 150 m 130 150 m 130 140 l 130 150 l 140 150 l 140 140 m 140 140 m 270 180 l 270 190 l 280 190 l 280 180 m 280 180 m 290 210 l 290 220 l 300 220 l 300 210 m 300 210 m 60 250 l 60 260 l 70 260 l 70 250 m 70 250 m 80 70 l 80 80 l 90 80 l 90 70 m 90 70 m 320 40 l 320 50 l 330 50 l 330 40 m 330 40 m 280 360 l 280 370 l 290 370 l 290 360 m 290 360 m 200 100 l 200 110 l 210 110 l 210 100 m 210 100 m 230 230 l 230 240 l 240 240 l 240 230 m 240 230 m 210 110 l 210 120 l 220 120 l 220 110 m 220 110 m 240 240 l 240 250 l 250 250 l 250 240 m 250 240 m 200 320 l 200 330 l 210 330 l 210 320 m 210 320 m 250 130 l 250 140 l 260 140 l 260 130 m 260 130 m 210 290 l 210 300 l 220 300 l 220 290 m 220 290 m 260 100 l 260 110 l 270 110 l 270 100 m 270 100 m 140 120 l 140 130 l 150 130 l 150 120 m 150 120 m 280 310 l 280 320 l 290 320 l 290 310 m 290 310 m 180 220 l 180 230 l 190 230 l 190 220 m 190 220 m 160 100 l 160 110 l 170 110 l 170 100 m 170 100 m 140 220 l 140 230 l 150 230 l 150 220 m 150 220 m 190 150 l 190 160 l 200 160 l 200 150 m 200 150 m 150 310 l 150 320 l 160 320 l 160 310 m 160 310 m 40 80 l 40 90 l 50 90 l 50 80 m 50 80 m 280 50 l 280 60 l 290 60 l 290 50 m 290 50 m 310 320 l 310 330 l 320 330 l 320 320 m 320 320 m 60 100 l 60 110 l 70 110 l 70 100 m 70 100 m 330 340 l 330 350 l 340 350 l 340 340 m 340 340 m 70 270 l 70 280 l 80 280 l 80 270 m 80 270 m 100 40 l 100 50 l 110 50 l 110 40 m 110 40 m 340 330 l 340 340 l 350 340 l 350 330 m 350 330 m 80 200 l 80 210 l 90 210 l 90 200 m 90 200 m 60 360 l 60 370 l 70 370 l 70 360 m 70 360 m 350 280 l 350 290 l 360 290 l 360 280 m 360 280 m 240 230 l 240 240 l 250 240 l 250 230 m 250 230 m 200 230 l 200 240 l 210 240 l 210 230 m 210 230 m 100 300 l 100 310 l 110 310 l 110 300 m 110 300 m 250 220 l 250 230 l 260 230 l 260 220 m 260 220 m 210 220 l 210 230 l 220 230 l 220 220 m 220 220 m 360 160 l 360 170 l 370 170 l 370 160 m 370 160 m 140 330 l 140 340 l 150 340 l 150 330 m 150 330 m 170 40 l 170 50 l 180 50 l 180 40 m 180 40 m 150 200 l 150 210 l 160 210 l 160 200 m 160 200 m 300 280 l 300 290 l 310 290 l 310 280 m 310 280 m 40 310 l 40 320 l 50 320 l 50 310 m 50 310 m 280 120 l 280 130 l 290 130 l 290 120 m 290 120 m 310 250 l 310 260 l 320 260 l 320 250 m 320 250 m 50 300 l 50 310 l 60 310 l 60 300 m 60 300 m 320 260 l 320 270 l 330 270 l 330 260 m 330 260 m 300 60 l 300 70 l 310 70 l 310 60 m 310 60 m 70 320 l 70 330 l 80 330 l 80 320 m 80 320 m 340 80 l 340 90 l 350 90 l 350 80 m 350 80 m 240 300 l 240 310 l 250 310 l 250 300 m 250 300 m 100 330 l 100 340 l 110 340 l 110 330 m 110 330 m 230 110 l 230 120 l 240 120 l 240 110 m 240 110 m 120 360 l 120 370 l 130 370 l 130 360 m 130 360 m 260 200 l 260 210 l 270 210 l 270 200 m 270 200 m 270 250 l 270 260 l 280 260 l 280 250 m 280 250 m 250 90 l 250 100 l 260 100 l 260 90 m 260 90 m 120 100 l 120 110 l 130 110 l 130 100 m 130 100 m 360 70 l 360 80 l 370 80 l 370 70 m 370 70 m 180 320 l 180 330 l 190 330 l 190 320 m 190 320 m 190 290 l 190 300 l 200 300 l 200 290 m 200 290 m 40 220 l 40 230 l 50 230 l 50 220 m 50 220 m 280 190 l 280 200 l 290 200 l 290 190 m 290 190 m 180 100 l 180 110 l 190 110 l 190 100 m 190 100 m 160 220 l 160 230 l 170 230 l 170 220 m 170 220 m 290 180 l 290 190 l 300 190 l 300 180 m 300 180 m 40 120 l 40 130 l 50 130 l 50 120 m 50 120 m 330 200 l 330 210 l 340 210 l 340 200 m 340 200 m 310 40 l 310 50 l 320 50 l 320 40 m 320 40 m 80 100 l 80 110 l 90 110 l 90 100 m 90 100 m 350 180 l 350 190 l 360 190 l 360 180 m 360 180 m 330 140 l 330 150 l 340 150 l 340 140 m 340 140 m 200 50 l 200 60 l 210 60 l 210 50 m 210 50 m 100 240 l 100 250 l 110 250 l 110 240 m 110 240 m 340 210 l 340 220 l 350 220 l 350 210 m 350 210 m 110 210 l 110 220 l 120 220 l 120 210 m 120 210 m 270 220 l 270 230 l 280 230 l 280 220 m 280 220 m 250 180 l 250 190 l 260 190 l 260 180 m 260 180 m 120 170 l 120 180 l 130 180 l 130 170 m 130 170 m 270 120 l 270 130 l 280 130 l 280 120 m 280 120 m 140 190 l 140 200 l 150 200 l 150 190 m 150 190 m 180 130 l 180 140 l 190 140 l 190 130 m 190 130 m 160 130 l 160 140 l 170 140 l 170 130 m 170 130 m 290 270 l 290 280 l 300 280 l 300 270 m 300 270 m 170 160 l 170 170 l 180 170 l 180 160 m 180 160 m 300 240 l 300 250 l 310 250 l 310 240 m 310 240 m 70 140 l 70 150 l 80 150 l 80 140 m 80 140 m 50 180 l 50 190 l 60 190 l 60 180 m 60 180 m 80 170 l 80 180 l 90 180 l 90 170 m 90 170 m 320 60 l 320 70 l 330 70 l 330 60 m 330 60 m 90 40 l 90 50 l 100 50 l 100 40 m 100 40 m 330 70 l 330 80 l 340 80 l 340 70 m 340 70 m 70 200 l 70 210 l 80 210 l 80 200 m 80 200 m 50 360 l 50 370 l 60 370 l 60 360 m 60 360 m 230 250 l 230 260 l 240 260 l 240 250 m 240 250 m 210 90 l 210 100 l 220 100 l 220 90 m 220 90 m 350 330 l 350 340 l 360 340 l 360 330 m 360 330 m 220 60 l 220 70 l 230 70 l 230 60 m 230 60 m 250 270 l 250 280 l 260 280 l 260 270 m 260 270 m 210 350 l 210 360 l 220 360 l 220 350 m 220 350 m 260 80 l 260 90 l 270 90 l 270 80 m 270 80 m 120 300 l 120 310 l 130 310 l 130 300 m 130 300 m 150 110 l 150 120 l 160 120 l 160 110 m 160 110 m 130 310 l 130 320 l 140 320 l 140 310 m 140 310 m 280 330 l 280 340 l 290 340 l 290 330 m 290 330 m 290 280 l 290 290 l 300 290 l 300 280 m 300 280 m 170 90 l 170 100 l 180 100 l 180 90 m 180 90 m 150 330 l 150 340 l 160 340 l 160 330 m 160 330 m 300 350 l 300 360 l 310 360 l 310 350 m 310 350 m 40 100 l 40 110 l 50 110 l 50 100 m 50 100 m 310 340 l 310 350 l 320 350 l 320 340 m 320 340 m 320 290 l 320 300 l 330 300 l 330 290 m 330 290 m 60 80 l 60 90 l 70 90 l 70 80 m 70 80 m 330 320 l 330 330 l 340 330 l 340 320 m 340 320 m 100 100 l 100 110 l 110 110 l 110 100 m 110 100 m 340 70 l 340 80 l 350 80 l 350 70 m 350 70 m 350 300 l 350 310 l 360 310 l 360 300 m 360 300 m 240 330 l 240 340 l 250 340 l 250 330 m 250 330 m 200 250 l 200 260 l 210 260 l 210 250 m 210 250 m 100 280 l 100 290 l 110 290 l 110 280 m 110 280 m 250 200 l 250 210 l 260 210 l 260 200 m 260 200 m 210 200 l 210 210 l 220 210 l 220 200 m 220 200 m 260 350 l 260 360 l 270 360 l 270 350 m 270 350 m 270 340 l 270 350 l 280 350 l 280 340 m 280 340 m 130 320 l 130 330 l 140 330 l 140 320 m 140 320 m 190 220 l 190 230 l 200 230 l 200 220 m 200 220 m 40 330 l 40 340 l 50 340 l 50 330 m 50 330 m 280 140 l 280 150 l 290 150 l 290 140 m 290 140 m 160 250 l 160 260 l 170 260 l 170 250 m 170 250 m 310 270 l 310 280 l 320 280 l 320 270 m 320 270 m 50 280 l 50 290 l 60 290 l 60 280 m 60 280 m 290 150 l 290 160 l 300 160 l 300 150 m 300 150 m 170 280 l 170 290 l 180 290 l 180 280 m 180 280 m 320 200 l 320 210 l 330 210 l 330 200 m 330 200 m 300 40 l 300 50 l 310 50 l 310 40 m 310 40 m 70 340 l 70 350 l 80 350 l 80 340 m 80 340 m 310 170 l 310 180 l 320 180 l 320 170 m 320 170 m 200 160 l 200 170 l 210 170 l 210 160 m 210 160 m 250 290 l 250 300 l 260 300 l 260 290 m 260 290 m 210 130 l 210 140 l 220 140 l 220 130 m 220 130 m 260 260 l 260 270 l 270 270 l 270 260 m 270 260 m 240 60 l 240 70 l 250 70 l 250 60 m 250 60 m 220 180 l 220 190 l 230 190 l 230 180 m 230 180 m 250 70 l 250 80 l 260 80 l 260 70 m 260 70 m 120 120 l 120 130 l 130 130 l 130 120 m 130 120 m 360 90 l 360 100 l 370 100 l 370 90 m 370 90 m 260 120 l 260 130 l 270 130 l 270 120 m 270 120 m 130 90 l 130 100 l 140 100 l 140 90 m 140 90 m 190 310 l 190 320 l 200 320 l 200 310 m 200 310 m 150 150 l 150 160 l 160 160 l 160 150 m 160 150 m 40 240 l 40 250 l 50 250 l 50 240 m 50 240 m 50 210 l 50 220 l 60 220 l 60 210 m 60 210 m 290 160 l 290 170 l 300 170 l 300 160 m 300 160 m 170 210 l 170 220 l 180 220 l 180 210 m 180 210 m 60 260 l 60 270 l 70 270 l 70 260 m 70 260 m 40 140 l 40 150 l 50 150 l 50 140 m 50 140 m 50 150 l 50 160 l 60 160 l 60 150 m 60 150 m 80 40 l 80 50 l 90 50 l 90 40 m 90 40 m 40 360 l 40 370 l 50 370 l 50 360 m 50 360 m 330 120 l 330 130 l 340 130 l 340 120 m 340 120 m 200 70 l 200 80 l 210 80 l 210 70 m 210 70 m 100 140 l 100 150 l 110 150 l 110 140 m 110 140 m 210 60 l 210 70 l 220 70 l 220 60 m 220 60 m 110 230 l 110 240 l 120 240 l 120 230 m 120 230 m 350 260 l 350 270 l 360 270 l 360 260 m 360 260 m 240 130 l 240 140 l 250 140 l 250 130 m 250 130 m 220 130 l 220 140 l 230 140 l 230 130 m 230 130 m 200 290 l 200 300 l 210 300 l 210 290 m 210 290 m 360 320 l 360 330 l 370 330 l 370 320 m 370 320 m 260 70 l 260 80 l 270 80 l 270 70 m 270 70 m 130 180 l 130 190 l 140 190 l 140 180 m 140 180 m 270 140 l 270 150 l 280 150 l 280 140 m 280 140 m 140 170 l 140 180 l 150 180 l 150 170 m 150 170 m 120 250 l 120 260 l 130 260 l 130 250 m 130 250 m 280 280 l 280 290 l 290 290 l 290 280 m 290 280 m 140 270 l 140 280 l 150 280 l 150 270 m 150 270 m 190 180 l 190 190 l 200 190 l 200 180 m 200 180 m 170 140 l 170 150 l 180 150 l 180 140 m 180 140 m 300 220 l 300 230 l 310 230 l 310 220 m 310 220 m 40 50 l 40 60 l 50 60 l 50 50 m 50 50 m 320 320 l 320 330 l 330 330 l 330 320 m 330 320 m 60 150 l 60 160 l 70 160 l 70 150 m 70 150 m 90 180 l 90 190 l 100 190 l 100 180 m 100 180 m 340 340 l 340 350 l 350 350 l 350 340 m 350 340 m 80 250 l 80 260 l 90 260 l 90 250 m 90 250 m 230 270 l 230 280 l 240 280 l 240 270 m 240 270 m 110 120 l 110 130 l 120 130 l 120 120 m 120 120 m 260 360 l 260 370 l 270 370 l 270 360 m 270 360 m 240 200 l 240 210 l 250 210 l 250 200 m 250 200 m 200 200 l 200 210 l 210 210 l 210 200 m 210 200 m 220 300 l 220 310 l 230 310 l 230 300 m 230 300 m 120 320 l 120 330 l 130 330 l 130 320 m 130 320 m 360 130 l 360 140 l 370 140 l 370 130 m 370 130 m 130 290 l 130 300 l 140 300 l 140 290 m 140 290 m 280 350 l 280 360 l 290 360 l 290 350 m 290 350 m 180 260 l 180 270 l 190 270 l 190 260 m 190 260 m 160 60 l 160 70 l 170 70 l 170 60 m 170 60 m 300 330 l 300 340 l 310 340 l 310 330 m 310 330 m 40 280 l 40 290 l 50 290 l 50 280 m 50 280 m 280 90 l 280 100 l 290 100 l 290 90 m 290 90 m 160 280 l 160 290 l 170 290 l 170 280 m 170 280 m 170 330 l 170 340 l 180 340 l 180 330 m 180 330 m 320 310 l 320 320 l 330 320 l 330 310 m 330 310 m 60 60 l 60 70 l 70 70 l 70 60 m 70 60 m 330 300 l 330 310 l 340 310 l 340 300 m 340 300 m 210 360 l 210 370 l 220 370 l 220 360 m 220 360 m 100 80 l 100 90 l 110 90 l 110 80 m 110 80 m 80 320 l 80 330 l 90 330 l 90 320 m 90 320 m 230 320 l 230 330 l 240 330 l 240 320 m 240 320 m 90 210 l 90 220 l 100 220 l 100 210 m 100 210 m 100 340 l 100 350 l 110 350 l 110 340 m 110 340 m 230 60 l 230 70 l 240 70 l 240 60 m 240 60 m 240 90 l 240 100 l 250 100 l 250 90 m 250 90 m 120 70 l 120 80 l 130 80 l 130 70 m 130 70 m 360 40 l 360 50 l 370 50 l 370 40 m 370 40 m 130 60 l 130 70 l 140 70 l 140 60 m 140 60 m 180 290 l 180 300 l 190 300 l 190 290 m 190 290 m 190 320 l 190 330 l 200 330 l 200 320 m 200 320 m 150 240 l 150 250 l 160 250 l 160 240 m 160 240 m 40 350 l 40 360 l 50 360 l 50 350 m 50 350 m 280 160 l 280 170 l 290 170 l 290 160 m 290 160 m 160 270 l 160 280 l 170 280 l 170 270 m 170 270 m 170 260 l 170 270 l 180 270 l 180 260 m 180 260 m 60 330 l 60 340 l 70 340 l 70 330 m 70 330 m 70 40 l 70 50 l 80 50 l 80 40 m 80 40 m 320 120 l 320 130 l 330 130 l 330 120 m 330 120 m 360 360 l 360 370 l 370 370 l 370 360 m 370 360 m 90 300 l 90 310 l 100 310 l 100 300 m 100 300 m 210 190 l 210 200 l 220 200 l 220 190 m 220 190 m 110 240 l 110 250 l 120 250 l 120 240 m 120 240 m 270 210 l 270 220 l 280 220 l 280 210 m 280 210 m 260 180 l 260 190 l 270 190 l 270 180 m 270 180 m 270 190 l 270 200 l 280 200 l 280 190 m 280 190 m 120 200 l 120 210 l 130 210 l 130 200 m 130 200 m 180 140 l 180 150 l 190 150 l 190 140 m 190 140 m 160 180 l 160 190 l 170 190 l 170 180 m 170 180 m 60 240 l 60 250 l 70 250 l 70 240 m 70 240 m 40 160 l 40 170 l 50 170 l 50 160 m 50 160 m 50 130 l 50 140 l 60 140 l 60 130 m 60 130 m 80 60 l 80 70 l 90 70 l 90 60 m 90 60 m 60 180 l 60 190 l 70 190 l 70 180 m 70 180 m 350 140 l 350 150 l 360 150 l 360 140 m 360 140 m 330 100 l 330 110 l 340 110 l 340 100 m 340 100 m 100 120 l 100 130 l 110 130 l 110 120 m 110 120 m 250 360 l 250 370 l 260 370 l 260 360 m 260 360 m 230 200 l 230 210 l 240 210 l 240 200 m 240 200 m 350 200 l 350 210 l 360 210 l 360 200 m 360 200 m 240 150 l 240 160 l 250 160 l 250 150 m 250 150 m 200 310 l 200 320 l 210 320 l 210 310 m 210 310 m 140 150 l 140 160 l 150 160 l 150 150 m 150 150 m 120 270 l 120 280 l 130 280 l 130 270 m 130 270 m 150 60 l 150 70 l 160 70 l 160 60 m 160 60 m 130 260 l 130 270 l 140 270 l 140 260 m 140 260 m 280 300 l 280 310 l 290 310 l 290 300 m 290 300 m 180 170 l 180 180 l 190 180 l 190 170 m 190 170 m 190 120 l 190 130 l 200 130 l 200 120 m 200 120 m 170 120 l 170 130 l 180 130 l 180 120 m 180 120 m 150 280 l 150 290 l 160 290 l 160 280 m 160 280 m 300 200 l 300 210 l 310 210 l 310 200 m 310 200 m 40 70 l 40 80 l 50 80 l 50 70 m 50 70 m 280 40 l 280 50 l 290 50 l 290 40 m 290 40 m 80 130 l 80 140 l 90 140 l 90 130 m 90 130 m 320 340 l 320 350 l 330 350 l 330 340 m 330 340 m 60 130 l 60 140 l 70 140 l 70 130 m 70 130 m 100 70 l 100 80 l 110 80 l 110 70 m 110 70 m 240 220 l 240 230 l 250 230 l 250 220 m 250 220 m 200 220 l 200 230 l 210 230 l 210 220 m 210 220 m 250 230 l 250 240 l 260 240 l 260 230 m 260 230 m 210 230 l 210 240 l 220 240 l 220 230 m 220 230 m 220 280 l 220 290 l 230 290 l 230 280 m 230 280 m 270 330 l 270 340 l 280 340 l 280 330 m 280 330 m 360 150 l 360 160 l 370 160 l 370 150 m 370 150 m 180 240 l 180 250 l 190 250 l 190 240 m 190 240 m 290 320 l 290 330 l 300 330 l 300 320 m 300 320 m 190 210 l 190 220 l 200 220 l 200 210 m 200 210 m 170 50 l 170 60 l 180 60 l 180 50 m 180 50 m 150 210 l 150 220 l 160 220 l 160 210 m 160 210 m 40 300 l 40 310 l 50 310 l 50 300 m 50 300 m 280 110 l 280 120 l 290 120 l 290 110 m 290 110 m 160 300 l 160 310 l 170 310 l 170 300 m 170 300 m 170 310 l 170 320 l 180 320 l 180 310 m 180 310 m 60 40 l 60 50 l 70 50 l 70 40 m 70 40 m 300 90 l 300 100 l 310 100 l 310 90 m 310 90 m 330 280 l 330 290 l 340 290 l 340 280 m 340 280 m 70 330 l 70 340 l 80 340 l 80 330 m 80 330 m 310 120 l 310 130 l 320 130 l 320 120 m 320 120 m 80 340 l 80 350 l 90 350 l 90 340 m 90 340

26
00:06:09,130 --> 00:06:13,340
本藍光版外掛字幕由  風吹來的那片云  用WEB版調軸

27
00:06:09,130 --> 00:06:13,340
行尸走肉
『第六季  第二集』

28
00:06:15,450 --> 00:06:16,600
西芹湯

29
00:06:16,960 --> 00:06:18,120
西芹湯
Celery soup.

30
00:06:18,540 --> 00:06:19,930
放在這里一直沒人要
It's been here since the start.

31
00:06:19,930 --> 00:06:21,550
你真勇敢
You're very brave.

32
00:06:22,090 --> 00:06:23,900
我希望辣椒粉能掩蓋
Well, I'm hoping the paprika will mask

33
00:06:23,900 --> 00:06:26,090
湯里的西芹味
the soup's celeryness.

34
00:06:26,090 --> 00:06:28,630
那你就會做出一碗辣椒粉湯
Then you'd be stuck with something that tastes like paprika.

35
00:06:29,360 --> 00:06:30,590
還是不要了
No, thank you.

36
00:06:30,590 --> 00:06:33,280
我只是想著既然我們的主食不多了
Well, I just figured since we're running low on staples,

37
00:06:33,280 --> 00:06:36,430
我想用一些沒人想要的東西
I'd try to use a few things nobody seems to want.

38
00:06:38,200 --> 00:06:41,000
我以前會給愛德做春季大掃蕩砂鍋菜
I used to make Ed these spring cleaning casseroles

39
00:06:41,000 --> 00:06:42,640
就是為了清空儲藏室
just to empty the pantry.

40
00:06:44,170 --> 00:06:46,920
我靠荸薺制造過奇跡
I made some miracles happen with water chestnuts.

41
00:06:46,970 --> 00:06:51,060
說到奇跡  可樂罐頭火腿的食譜真了不起
Talk about miracles, that recipe for cola canned ham.

42
00:06:52,610 --> 00:06:56,210
佩爾蒂埃太太  你真是個大英雄
Ms. Peletier, you are an honest to goodness hero.

43
00:07:00,650 --> 00:07:02,240
有什么問題嗎  謝莉
Something wrong, Shelly?

44
00:07:02,650 --> 00:07:05,190
只是一些老面條
It's just those old noodles.

45
00:07:05,630 --> 00:07:06,720
我跟你說
I mean, I tell you,

46
00:07:06,720 --> 00:07:09,150
如果有人給我找到一臺機器
if someone would just find me one of those machines,

47
00:07:09,150 --> 00:07:13,220
我發誓我們會大吃特吃意面
I swear we would all be eating like we were on a tour of Tuscany.

48
00:07:15,890 --> 00:07:17,180
小謝  我可以教你
You know, Shel, I could teach you

49
00:07:17,180 --> 00:07:19,470
怎么用雙手做意面
how to make pasta with your own two hands.

50
00:07:20,210 --> 00:07:22,720
但你得保證別在房子里抽煙
But you'd have to promise not to smoke in the house.

51
00:07:22,870 --> 00:07:24,700
那是個令人討厭的習慣
It's just a disgusting habit.

52
00:07:24,830 --> 00:07:26,050
而且會害死你
And it kills you.

53
00:07:27,030 --> 00:07:28,760
要我說  已經有太多
If you ask me, there are too many things

54
00:07:28,760 --> 00:07:30,880
想害死你的東西了  對吧
trying to do that already, right?

55
00:07:32,400 --> 00:07:33,390
對
Right.

56
00:07:40,800 --> 00:07:43,720
你爸爸以前打你  然后他被人殺了
Your dad used to hit you and then he got himself killed.

57
00:07:45,580 --> 00:07:48,130
這事發生了  別多想了
It happened. Now it's done.

58
00:07:49,260 --> 00:07:51,260
你要么接受這一點  要么被打垮
You live with it or it eats you up.

59
00:07:52,080 --> 00:07:53,040
回家吧
Go home.

60
00:08:12,870 --> 00:08:13,860
羅恩
Ron.

61
00:08:20,390 --> 00:08:21,350
羅恩
Ron.

62
00:08:22,520 --> 00:08:23,880
你能下來嗎
Can you come down here?

63
00:08:39,080 --> 00:08:40,010
不
No.

64
00:08:40,470 --> 00:08:42,500
-羅恩  -不  我不想剪頭發
- Ron. - No, I don't want a haircut.

65
00:08:44,090 --> 00:08:46,790
瞧  我剛給自己剪了  好嗎
Look, I just gave myself one. All right?

66
00:08:46,790 --> 00:08:48,940
東西都擺好了  別逼我下周再擺一次
It's all set up. Don't make me do it again next week.

67
00:08:49,620 --> 00:08:50,750
摘下你的帽子
Take off your hat.

68
00:08:50,900 --> 00:08:53,480
-這太扯了  -你說什么...
- This is bullshit. - What did you just--

69
00:08:53,480 --> 00:08:55,270
你不過是想和我談談
This is just you trying to talk to me.

70
00:08:57,610 --> 00:08:59,200
有些事情我們得談談了
There are things we need to talk about.

71
00:09:01,840 --> 00:09:03,230
有些事情你必須學
There are things that you need to learn.

72
00:09:03,230 --> 00:09:04,460
什么  你認真的嗎
What, are you serious?

73
00:09:06,970 --> 00:09:09,140
到底怎么了  你是...你是在怪我嗎
What is it? Do you-- do you blame me?

74
00:09:12,730 --> 00:09:14,320
你真的在怪我嗎
Do you actually blame me?

75
00:09:16,290 --> 00:09:18,080
把你的左臂舉過頭頂
Raise your left arm above your head.

76
00:09:21,540 --> 00:09:23,270
你做不到  告訴我為什么
You can't. Tell me why.

77
00:09:24,460 --> 00:09:25,350
不
No.

78
00:09:28,050 --> 00:09:29,900
你爸很危險
Your father was dangerous.

79
00:09:30,470 --> 00:09:32,410
瑞克很危險
Rick is dangerous.

80
00:09:32,410 --> 00:09:33,950
他和這件事沒關系
He doesn't have anything to do with this.

81
00:09:36,000 --> 00:09:37,190
怎么  他是你的朋友嗎
What, is he your friend?

82
00:09:39,580 --> 00:09:41,640
沒錯  他是我的朋友
Yeah, he's my friend.

83
00:09:54,220 --> 00:09:55,530
板子可以后搭
We got some panels to put up,

84
00:09:55,530 --> 00:09:57,720
但我們可以先種東西
but we don't have to wait to start growing things.

85
00:09:58,300 --> 00:10:00,670
你會累得腰酸腿疼
There will be some sore backs and tired feet.

86
00:10:01,620 --> 00:10:03,690
辛苦勞作就是這樣
That's how you know you've put in a hard day's work.

87
00:10:13,770 --> 00:10:16,650
他們在幾里外的一個育苗場里找到了好幾箱種子
They found crates of these at a nursery just a few miles out.

88
00:10:17,770 --> 00:10:20,270
西紅柿  胡蘿卜  什么都有
Tomatoes, carrots, you name it.

89
00:10:20,630 --> 00:10:22,060
我們可以在這里種
We can plant them right here.

90
00:10:23,290 --> 00:10:25,100
只需要完成擴張
Just need to finish the expansion

91
00:10:26,620 --> 00:10:28,360
并且把墻建起來
and the wall needs to go up.

92
00:10:30,310 --> 00:10:32,520
雷吉希望這個社區能壯大
Reg wanted this community to grow.

93
00:10:33,970 --> 00:10:35,000
你也是這么希望的
You did, too.

94
00:10:36,890 --> 00:10:37,980
現在改變主意了嗎
Has that changed?

95
00:10:43,440 --> 00:10:45,680
這里所有人都是因為你才在這里的
Everyone that's here is here because of you.

96
00:10:48,620 --> 00:10:50,310
你得讓他們看到你的心還在這里
You need to show them you're still here.

97
00:11:01,060 --> 00:11:02,850
我只是說那讓我爽歪歪
It hams my biscuits is all.

98
00:11:04,030 --> 00:11:05,070
而且根據體積計算
And going by cubic feet,

99
00:11:05,070 --> 00:11:06,400
那是擴張區中最大的一棟建筑物
the biggest building in the expansion

100
00:11:06,400 --> 00:11:08,060
而我們卻要把它浪費在一座教堂上
and we're gonna waste it on a church.

101
00:11:08,890 --> 00:11:09,430
把那些長椅拆掉
Take out the benches,

102
00:11:09,430 --> 00:11:10,510
那里就可以變成一間實驗室
that could be a lab,

103
00:11:10,510 --> 00:11:11,510
或者一個車間
a machine shop,

104
00:11:11,510 --> 00:11:13,510
至少可以變成一間超贊的游戲室
very least a sweet-ass game room.

105
00:11:13,510 --> 00:11:15,830
墻內房產在這里是非常珍貴的
Walled-in real estate is at a premium here.

106
00:11:15,890 --> 00:11:17,960
神棍不應該有優先權
Thumpers just shouldn't get dibs.

107
00:11:17,960 --> 00:11:20,540
也許我們可以共用教堂
Well, maybe we share the church, you know?

108
00:11:20,850 --> 00:11:22,730
每天做不同的用途
Do all that stuff on different days.

109
00:11:22,790 --> 00:11:23,620
讓你爽歪歪嗎
Hams my biscuits?

110
00:11:23,620 --> 00:11:27,120
爽歪歪  我只聽到了這個
Hams my biscuits. That's all I heard.

111
00:11:27,620 --> 00:11:30,160
我完全不知道你之后說了什么
I mean, I have no idea what you said after that.

112
00:11:30,220 --> 00:11:32,600
-我說根據體積...  -我開玩笑的
- Going by cubic feet... - I was kidding.

113
00:11:35,610 --> 00:11:36,810
你還好吧  丹娜
Are you okay, Dana?

114
00:11:36,810 --> 00:11:39,370
-我叫丹妮斯  -丹妮斯  不好意思
- It's Denise. - Denise, I'm sorry.

115
00:11:40,050 --> 00:11:41,130
沒關系
I'm okay.

116
00:11:42,340 --> 00:11:43,810
我是新任醫生
I'm the new doctor now.

117
00:11:45,000 --> 00:11:46,130
你拿阿司匹林做什么
What's the aspirin for?

118
00:11:46,130 --> 00:11:47,890
-你是醫生嗎  -那你是嗎
- You're a doctor? - Are you?

119
00:11:49,740 --> 00:11:51,840
抱歉  我...
I'm sorry. I, uh...

120
00:11:52,940 --> 00:11:54,320
之前聽說過你的事
heard that story.

121
00:11:52,940 --> 00:11:54,320
尤金曾聲稱自己是博士[醫生]

122
00:11:54,760 --> 00:11:55,680
黑得漂亮
Fair play.

123
00:11:55,950 --> 00:11:58,200
聽著  其實我有點緊張
Listen, I'm a little nervous here.

124
00:11:58,380 --> 00:11:59,940
我是心理醫生
I'm a psychiatrist.

125
00:11:59,970 --> 00:12:01,740
讀醫學院那會兒
I went to med school.

126
00:12:01,740 --> 00:12:03,160
我本打算當外科醫生
I was even gonna be a surgeon,

127
00:12:03,160 --> 00:12:04,780
但結果驚恐發作
but after the panic attacks,

128
00:12:04,790 --> 00:12:06,990
從此便對心理學感興趣了
I got really interested in psychology.

129
00:12:07,680 --> 00:12:08,770
其實...
And...

130
00:12:11,080 --> 00:12:14,030
我只想讓你們別對我抱太大期望
I think I'm really trying to lower expectations here.

131
00:12:14,040 --> 00:12:15,430
你到底行不行
Can you do this?

132
00:12:16,070 --> 00:12:18,840
尤金  閉嘴  她能行的
Eugene, shut up. She can do this.

133
00:12:18,840 --> 00:12:20,390
全鎮只有我一個人能上
I'm all this town's got.

134
00:12:21,110 --> 00:12:22,590
皮特不想我干這個
Pete didn't want me here.

135
00:12:23,360 --> 00:12:24,560
但我卻來了
But I'm here now

136
00:12:26,030 --> 00:12:28,130
不過還是會時不時想吐
and I only kind of want to throw up.

137
00:12:29,560 --> 00:12:31,000
那你拿阿司匹林做什么
So why the aspirin?

138
00:12:32,070 --> 00:12:35,040
我和尤金正在搭建另一座哨塔
Eugene and I were working on a platform for another guard tower.

139
00:12:35,040 --> 00:12:37,460
我有點頭暈  畢竟頭痛還沒有全好
I got a little dizzy. You know, I still get headaches.

140
00:12:37,460 --> 00:12:39,050
坐吧  我幫你看看
Sit down, I'll take a look.

141
00:12:46,090 --> 00:12:47,550
你是我的第一位患者
You're my first patient.

142
00:12:47,850 --> 00:12:51,620
這點小毛病  我保證醫不死你
And with that symptom, I'm pretty sure I can't kill you.

143
00:12:52,030 --> 00:12:53,470
除非有類似血腫什么的
I mean, it is possible if you miss,

144
00:12:53,470 --> 00:12:55,220
你沒有檢查出來
like, a hematoma or something.

145
00:13:19,150 --> 00:13:20,030
卡爾
Carl?

146
00:13:22,330 --> 00:13:23,310
干嘛
What?

147
00:13:25,230 --> 00:13:27,650
你知道我跟迪安娜告密了
You heard what I told Deanna about your group.

148
00:13:28,560 --> 00:13:29,680
你想干什么
What do you want?

149
00:13:30,170 --> 00:13:31,330
那怪我
It was about me,

150
00:13:32,420 --> 00:13:34,860
與你  和你們團隊無關
not you or your group.

151
00:13:36,190 --> 00:13:37,430
我如今醒悟了
I know that now.

152
00:13:39,360 --> 00:13:40,660
我想幫忙
I want to help.

153
00:13:41,840 --> 00:13:44,300
在教堂的時候  我不讓你教我
You tried to teach me back at my church.

154
00:13:45,430 --> 00:13:47,080
但現在我想學了
But I'm ready to learn now.

155
00:13:49,930 --> 00:13:51,530
你應該把這個想法告訴大家
I think you need to tell everybody.

156
00:13:56,400 --> 00:13:57,760
對  你說得沒錯
Yeah, I think you're right.

157
00:14:02,080 --> 00:14:03,600
三點左右過來吧
Come by around 3:00.

158
00:14:04,390 --> 00:14:05,740
我們先從砍刀學起
We'll start with the machete.

159
00:15:19,510 --> 00:15:22,560
理查茲  發生了什么事
Richards. What's going on in there?

160
00:15:27,030 --> 00:15:27,950
不
Oh, no.

161
00:15:28,510 --> 00:15:29,360
不
No.

162
00:15:40,260 --> 00:15:41,210
快走
Come on!

163
00:15:49,560 --> 00:15:50,280
我從樓上看到了
I saw from upstairs.

164
00:15:50,280 --> 00:15:51,180
他們正從四周突襲進來
They're coming in from all over.

165
00:15:51,180 --> 00:15:53,440
你必須留在這保護朱迪思
You have to stay here and keep Judith safe.

166
00:15:58,760 --> 00:16:01,440
-求你別走  -我必須去找羅恩
- Please don't go. - I have to go find Ron.

167
00:16:01,440 --> 00:16:02,390
求你了  別走
Please. Please don't go.

168
00:16:02,390 --> 00:16:04,970
-我馬上就回來  好嗎  -媽  不
- I'm gonna be right back, okay? - Mom, no.

169
00:16:04,970 --> 00:16:06,980
你藏到衣櫥里
You go put yourself in the closet

170
00:16:06,980 --> 00:16:09,160
鎖好門栓  就像我教你的那樣
and you close the latch just like I showed you.

171
00:17:02,630 --> 00:17:03,600
你好
Hi.

172
00:17:04,190 --> 00:17:05,800
你怎么不敲門
Why didn't you just knock?

173
00:17:06,310 --> 00:17:08,740
我有鑰匙  不想讓那些人拿到
I have these. Didn't want them to have them.

174
00:17:14,590 --> 00:17:16,150
我想跟你道別
And I wanted to say good-bye.

175
00:17:16,150 --> 00:17:18,190
看好后門  看到他們過來就告訴我
Okay, watch the back door. Tell me if you see them coming.

176
00:17:18,680 --> 00:17:20,910
-我要走了  -你不能走
- I'm not staying. - You're not going anywhere.

177
00:17:21,310 --> 00:17:23,570
坐下  幫我一起保護朱迪思
Sit down. You're helping me protect Judith.

178
00:17:23,880 --> 00:17:25,610
他們不能踏進這房子
They're not getting inside this house.

179
00:17:34,060 --> 00:17:35,250
我們不許
We're not gonna let them.

180
00:17:39,410 --> 00:17:40,430
看到他們了嗎
Did you see them?

181
00:17:42,410 --> 00:17:43,840
他們只不過是人
They're just people.

182
00:17:46,340 --> 00:17:48,620
這地方太大了  保護不了的
This place is too big to protect.

183
00:17:49,670 --> 00:17:51,430
盲點太多了
There are too many blind spots.

184
00:17:52,870 --> 00:17:54,250
所以我們才能...
That's how we were able to...

185
00:17:54,250 --> 00:17:57,380
墻沒攔住他們  但是他們會死的
They got in the walls, but they're gonna die.

186
00:17:59,750 --> 00:18:00,850
都會死
All of them.

187
00:18:05,220 --> 00:18:06,990
別跟我道別
Don't tell me good-bye.

188
00:18:15,670 --> 00:18:16,610
好吧
Okay.

189
00:18:20,960 --> 00:18:22,050
我不會的
I won't.

190
00:19:06,670 --> 00:19:08,630
不  請別這樣
No, please. Please don't.

191
00:19:08,630 --> 00:19:10,650
不  求你了  求你了
No, please. Please...

192
00:19:14,990 --> 00:19:16,050
走開
Go away!

193
00:19:17,630 --> 00:19:19,600
天啊
Oh, God.

194
00:20:06,310 --> 00:20:07,320
該死
Shit.

195
00:20:08,500 --> 00:20:10,990
快啊  快啊
Come on. Come on.

196
00:21:03,430 --> 00:21:04,390
霍莉
Holly!

197
00:21:04,950 --> 00:21:06,330
準備手術臺
We need the operating table prepped.

198
00:21:06,330 --> 00:21:08,930
她失血很多  快  快  快
She's lost a lot of blood. Come on, come on, come on.

199
00:21:08,930 --> 00:21:10,320
闖進來多少人
How many people are out there?

200
00:21:10,320 --> 00:21:11,730
我不知道  很多
I don't know, there's a lot.

201
00:21:11,730 --> 00:21:13,600
羅西塔  你知道怎么靜脈注射嗎
Rosita, you know how to stick an IV?

202
00:21:13,600 --> 00:21:16,000
我來  給我紗帶
I'm on it. Here, hand me tape.

203
00:21:16,000 --> 00:21:16,700
好
Got it.

204
00:21:16,700 --> 00:21:18,180
怎么響汽笛了  到底怎么回事
What about the air horn? What's happening?

205
00:21:18,180 --> 00:21:20,700
我不知道  我得去幫忙
I don't know. I need to help.

206
00:21:20,740 --> 00:21:22,740
-我必須試試  -我知道
- I need to try. - I know.

207
00:21:22,780 --> 00:21:25,250
丹妮斯  我也必須過去了
Denise, I'm gonna have to go, too.

208
00:21:27,680 --> 00:21:28,180
我也是
So do I.

209
00:21:28,190 --> 00:21:29,930
你揮舞錘子都會頭暈
You got dizzy swinging a hammer.

210
00:21:29,930 --> 00:21:31,110
必須有人看守住這個地方
Somebody's got to guard this place.

211
00:21:31,110 --> 00:21:32,770
-你能行的  -我不行
- You can handle it. - I can't!

212
00:21:32,770 --> 00:21:33,920
我認為此時此刻
I also believe my services

213
00:21:33,920 --> 00:21:35,290
我待在這里最有用
would be best rendered right very here.

214
00:21:35,290 --> 00:21:36,950
-什么  -我認為此時此刻...
- What? - I also believe my services--

215
00:21:36,950 --> 00:21:38,930
閉嘴  你在這很安全  走
Shut up! You're safe here. Come on.

216
00:22:14,910 --> 00:22:15,580
怎么回事
What happened?

217
00:22:15,580 --> 00:22:19,260
有一伙人  闖進了墻內
Someone, a group, they got inside the walls.

218
00:22:19,390 --> 00:22:20,640
他們在大肆屠殺
They're killing people.

219
00:22:20,660 --> 00:22:22,140
我們得進去
We need to get in there.

220
00:22:25,880 --> 00:22:26,690
你來嗎
You coming?

221
00:22:31,540 --> 00:22:32,440
躲起來
Hide.

222
00:22:54,730 --> 00:22:55,680
想快點死
Quick...

223
00:22:58,260 --> 00:22:59,240
還是慢點死
or slow?

224
00:23:01,850 --> 00:23:02,880
請你
Leave.

225
00:23:04,670 --> 00:23:05,690
離開
Please.

226
00:23:08,050 --> 00:23:09,190
那就是慢點死
Gonna be slow.

227
00:23:18,510 --> 00:23:19,560
我能阻止他的
I could have stopped him.

228
00:23:19,560 --> 00:23:21,390
-其他人回來了嗎  -沒有
- The others back? - No.

229
00:23:21,840 --> 00:23:23,850
-他們正在行動  -他們現在就動手了嗎
- It's happening out there. - They're doing it now?

230
00:23:23,850 --> 00:23:24,820
不得不動手
We had to.

231
00:23:25,900 --> 00:23:27,500
這些人沒有槍
These people don't have guns.

232
00:23:27,500 --> 00:23:28,850
我能阻止他的
I could have stopped him.

233
00:23:28,850 --> 00:23:30,470
他們要是有槍  就會用
If they had guns, they'd be using them.

234
00:23:30,470 --> 00:23:31,380
你聽到我的話了嗎
Did you hear me?

235
00:23:31,380 --> 00:23:33,530
我們得搶先到達軍械庫
We have to get to the armory before they do.

236
00:23:33,910 --> 00:23:36,290
要是我們快點  說不定能成功
If we keep moving, this might work.

237
00:23:36,300 --> 00:23:37,690
你沒必要殺人
You don't have to kill people.

238
00:23:37,690 --> 00:23:38,850
當然有必要了
Of course we do.

239
00:23:39,300 --> 00:23:40,180
卡蘿爾
Carol!

240
00:23:41,750 --> 00:23:43,070
你不喜歡這樣
You don't like it.

241
00:23:46,930 --> 00:23:49,590
我得趕到軍械庫  我需要你的幫助
I'm gonna get to the armory and I need your help.

242
00:23:55,250 --> 00:23:55,950
媽
Mom!

243
00:23:56,820 --> 00:23:58,990
天啊  斯賓塞
Oh, God. Spencer.

244
00:23:59,510 --> 00:24:00,490
感謝上帝
Thank God.

245
00:24:01,220 --> 00:24:02,250
感謝上帝
Thank God.

246
00:24:03,050 --> 00:24:04,350
我們得進去
We need to get inside.

247
00:24:04,820 --> 00:24:07,500
我不能進去  我沒有槍
I can't go in there. I don't have a gun.

248
00:24:07,670 --> 00:24:08,820
我不知道怎么戰斗
I don't know how to fight.

249
00:24:08,820 --> 00:24:10,200
要是我進去
If I go inside,

250
00:24:10,200 --> 00:24:12,530
只會變成你們的累贅
I'll just be another person who's got to be saved.

251
00:24:13,060 --> 00:24:16,640
現在我能為里面的人做的最好的事
The best thing that I can do for everyone in there

252
00:24:17,330 --> 00:24:18,790
就是待在外面
is to stay out here.

253
00:24:21,140 --> 00:24:22,900
-保護好她  -好的
- Keep her safe. - I will.

254
00:24:53,940 --> 00:24:55,140
她怎么了
What's happening with her?

255
00:24:55,830 --> 00:24:57,760
她在內出血
She's bleeding internally.

256
00:24:58,160 --> 00:25:00,690
也許切到了股動脈
Probably severed her femoral artery.

257
00:25:02,090 --> 00:25:02,980
她快死了
She's dying.

258
00:25:02,980 --> 00:25:05,320
好吧  切到了動脈  能治好嗎
Okay, so the artery's severed. Can it be fixed?

259
00:25:06,230 --> 00:25:07,880
外科醫生也許可以
Maybe by a surgeon.

260
00:25:07,880 --> 00:25:09,440
你本來要成為外科醫生的
You were gonna be a surgeon.

261
00:25:09,440 --> 00:25:10,920
但我不是
But I'm not.

262
00:25:10,920 --> 00:25:12,790
她保護著這個地方
She was protecting this place.

263
00:25:13,180 --> 00:25:14,200
她守護著我們
She was guarding us.

264
00:25:14,200 --> 00:25:16,140
這就是我們在這里的原因  照顧彼此
That's why we're here, for each other.

265
00:25:18,240 --> 00:25:19,580
你害怕了嗎
You're afraid?

266
00:25:20,500 --> 00:25:22,320
我不在乎  救救她
I don't care. Help her.

267
00:25:23,840 --> 00:25:24,870
試一下
Try!

268
00:25:25,580 --> 00:25:26,680
救她
Help her!

269
00:25:29,850 --> 00:25:31,640
你不想當一個懦夫的
You don't want to be a coward.

270
00:25:32,330 --> 00:25:33,280
我懂的
I know.

271
00:25:42,280 --> 00:25:43,470
我需要一根束腹帶
I need an abdominal binder.

272
00:25:43,470 --> 00:25:44,670
我們要把刀拔出來
We're gonna pull the knife.

273
00:25:44,670 --> 00:25:46,050
好的
Okay. Okay.

274
00:26:06,440 --> 00:26:07,320
媽的
Shit!

275
00:26:12,290 --> 00:26:13,160
求你了
Please, man.

276
00:26:13,600 --> 00:26:15,750
求你別殺我  求你了
Please don't kill me, man. Please.

277
00:26:15,910 --> 00:26:17,920
求你救救我  我的腿
Help me, please. My leg.

278
00:26:30,000 --> 00:26:31,040
回屋里
Come inside.

279
00:26:32,580 --> 00:26:33,830
我可以保護你
I can keep you safe.

280
00:26:40,330 --> 00:26:41,030
不
No.

281
00:26:42,460 --> 00:26:43,290
羅恩
Ron.

282
00:26:47,280 --> 00:26:48,550
卡爾  進來
Carl, come on!

283
00:27:00,410 --> 00:27:01,340
媽
Mom.

284
00:27:02,150 --> 00:27:03,310
媽  你在家嗎
Mom, you in?

285
00:27:12,230 --> 00:27:14,240
鎖起來  勇敢點
Lock it. Be brave.

286
00:27:33,160 --> 00:27:34,730
別進來  羅恩
Stay outside, Ron!

287
00:27:44,310 --> 00:27:45,250
不
No!

288
00:28:40,760 --> 00:28:41,960
干得好  蚜蟲
Good catch, Aphid.

289
00:28:45,640 --> 00:28:46,610
快走
Come on.

290
00:28:47,160 --> 00:28:48,970
-別管他了  -不
- Leave him. - No.

291
00:28:55,120 --> 00:28:57,060
蚜蟲  從哪拿的槍
Hey, Aphid, where'd you get the gun?

292
00:29:08,890 --> 00:29:10,300
你死定了
You're dead.

293
00:29:57,920 --> 00:29:59,300
求你別殺我
Please don't kill me.

294
00:30:02,120 --> 00:30:04,990
沒事的  還有人在這嗎
It's okay. Anybody else down here?

295
00:30:06,920 --> 00:30:08,660
-奧利維亞  -沒了
- Olivia! - No.

296
00:30:08,750 --> 00:30:10,100
沒了  就我一個
No, I'm the only one.

297
00:30:17,230 --> 00:30:17,970
過來
Come here.

298
00:30:18,760 --> 00:30:19,650
快點
Now.

299
00:30:22,990 --> 00:30:25,180
我一走你就守住我身后的門
You barricade that door behind me once I leave.

300
00:30:25,180 --> 00:30:26,460
知道怎么開槍嗎
Do you know how to shoot a gun?

301
00:30:27,550 --> 00:30:28,570
站在這
Stand here.

302
00:30:29,270 --> 00:30:31,480
手指扣扳機  對準那邊
Finger here. Aim there.

303
00:30:32,020 --> 00:30:33,210
有敵人進來
One of them comes through that door,

304
00:30:33,210 --> 00:30:35,760
就一直扣扳機  直到他們倒地
you squeeze and you don't stop till they're on the ground.

305
00:30:47,220 --> 00:30:48,730
你的招數是哪兒學的
How did you learn how to do that?

306
00:30:50,540 --> 00:30:51,960
一個做奶酪的人教我的
From a cheese maker.

307
00:30:59,160 --> 00:31:00,380
我們是在解放你們
We're freeing you.

308
00:31:01,340 --> 00:31:02,380
你們被困住了
You're trapped.

309
00:31:03,390 --> 00:31:07,290
你們得知道  人們不再屬于這里了
You need to know, people don't belong here anymore.

310
00:31:18,470 --> 00:31:20,080
-卡蘿爾  -瑪姬
- Carol? - Maggie!

311
00:31:25,280 --> 00:31:27,480
-給  -我...
- Here. - I--

312
00:31:28,290 --> 00:31:30,460
我不大會用槍  我...
I'm not very good with guns. I--

313
00:31:30,860 --> 00:31:31,920
我也是
Me neither.

314
00:32:30,800 --> 00:32:31,870
是你
You.

315
00:32:32,810 --> 00:32:34,290
你住在這里嗎
You live here?

316
00:32:43,760 --> 00:32:44,850
離開吧
Leave.

317
00:32:47,530 --> 00:32:49,900
我的伙伴有槍
My people have guns.

318
00:32:53,680 --> 00:32:54,900
你的伙伴沒有
Yours don't.

319
00:32:56,440 --> 00:32:59,480
他們可能正端著步槍瞄準你們
They may be aiming rifles at you right now.

320
00:33:01,070 --> 00:33:02,450
眼睛盯著瞄準具
Eyes at the scopes.

321
00:33:03,580 --> 00:33:04,960
手指扣著扳機
Fingers on the trigger.

322
00:33:06,570 --> 00:33:07,670
砰
Boom.

323
00:33:09,510 --> 00:33:10,820
他們隨時會開槍
It's gonna happen any second now

324
00:33:10,820 --> 00:33:13,480
除非你們離開這里  再也別回來
unless you get the hell out of here and you don't ever come back.

325
00:33:15,660 --> 00:33:17,440
你們繼續選擇這種生活
You keep choosing this life,

326
00:33:19,120 --> 00:33:20,500
遲早要送命的
you will die.

327
00:33:23,210 --> 00:33:24,630
不是我們選擇的
We didn't choose.

328
00:36:23,310 --> 00:36:24,680
醒醒啊  霍莉
Come on, Holly.

329
00:36:56,570 --> 00:36:58,040
丹妮斯  你盡力了
Denise, you tried.

330
00:36:58,500 --> 00:36:59,790
你是醫生
You are a doctor.

331
00:36:59,790 --> 00:37:03,110
去看看外面結束了沒有
Just go see if it's over out there

332
00:37:03,110 --> 00:37:04,660
如果...
and if...

333
00:37:07,180 --> 00:37:09,090
請你們都走吧
Please go, all of you.

334
00:37:09,490 --> 00:37:12,120
-好吧  但我只是  -好  走吧
- Okay, but I just-- - Good. Go.

335
00:37:23,020 --> 00:37:24,630
我只想說...
All I was gonna say is...

336
00:37:26,930 --> 00:37:28,750
記得破壞她的大腦
make sure you get her brain.

337
00:37:41,320 --> 00:37:42,740
今天發生的事
What happened today,

338
00:37:43,240 --> 00:37:44,950
外面就是這樣嗎
that's what it's like out there?

339
00:37:45,440 --> 00:37:46,550
差不多吧
Pretty much.

340
00:37:47,160 --> 00:37:48,110
你們怎么
How do you--

341
00:37:49,310 --> 00:37:52,450
你們知道世界是那樣的  還怎么活著啊
how do you just live knowing that's the world?

342
00:37:57,380 --> 00:37:58,530
為了這個團隊
This group,

343
00:38:00,040 --> 00:38:01,900
為了亞伯拉罕  還有這地方
Abraham, and this place.

344
00:38:04,790 --> 00:38:06,760
確保你有值得為之犧牲的東西
Make sure you got something worth dying for.

345
00:38:31,100 --> 00:38:32,310
我們還活著呢
We're still here.

346
00:38:34,180 --> 00:38:35,550
并非所有人
Not all of us.

347
00:38:52,570 --> 00:38:53,670
伊妮德
Enid?

348
00:38:55,860 --> 00:38:57,000
伊妮德
Enid?

349
00:39:07,140 --> 00:39:09,450
無論如何都要活下去[JSS]

350
00:41:06,450 --> 00:41:08,060
你狠不下心  對吧
You can't, can you?

351
00:41:12,800 --> 00:41:14,210
你該狠心的
You should've.

352
00:41:27,170 --> 00:41:28,480
抱歉
I'm sorry.

353
00:42:22,580 --> 00:42:30,580
■

354
00:42:22,580 --> 00:42:30,580
■

355
00:42:22,580 --> 00:42:30,580
最新美劇下載請登錄字幕組網站
www.ZiMuZu.tv
掃描左邊二維碼關注我們的微信號
或搜索微信號: ustvboom

356
00:42:22,580 --> 00:42:30,580
非常歡迎愛好者加入字幕組一起翻譯海外影視劇

357
00:42:22,580 --> 00:42:30,580
■

358
00:42:22,580 --> 00:42:30,580
m 350 100 l 350 110 l 360 110 l 360 100 m 360 100 m 200 130 l 200 140 l 210 140 l 210 130 m 210 130 m 100 320 l 100 330 l 110 330 l 110 320 m 110 320 m 230 80 l 230 90 l 240 90 l 240 80 m 240 80 m 240 110 l 240 120 l 250 120 l 250 110 m 250 110 m 220 230 l 220 240 l 230 240 l 230 230 m 230 230 m 120 90 l 120 100 l 130 100 l 130 90 m 130 90 m 360 60 l 360 70 l 370 70 l 370 60 m 370 60 m 140 110 l 140 120 l 150 120 l 150 110 m 150 110 m 190 340 l 190 350 l 200 350 l 200 340 m 200 340 m 180 50 l 180 60 l 190 60 l 190 50 m 190 50 m 290 190 l 290 200 l 300 200 l 300 190 m 300 190 m 170 240 l 170 250 l 180 250 l 180 240 m 180 240 m 300 160 l 300 170 l 310 170 l 310 160 m 310 160 m 330 210 l 330 220 l 340 220 l 340 210 m 340 210 m 70 60 l 70 70 l 80 70 l 80 60 m 80 60 m 240 360 l 240 370 l 250 370 l 250 360 m 250 360 m 230 170 l 230 180 l 240 180 l 240 170 m 240 170 m 210 170 l 210 180 l 220 180 l 220 170 m 220 170 m 350 250 l 350 260 l 360 260 l 360 250 m 360 250 m 240 180 l 240 190 l 250 190 l 250 180 m 250 180 m 220 140 l 220 150 l 230 150 l 230 140 m 230 140 m 270 230 l 270 240 l 280 240 l 280 230 m 280 230 m 250 190 l 250 200 l 260 200 l 260 190 m 260 190 m 120 160 l 120 170 l 130 170 l 130 160 m 130 160 m 360 290 l 360 300 l 370 300 l 370 290 m 370 290 m 260 160 l 260 170 l 270 170 l 270 160 m 270 160 m 270 130 l 270 140 l 280 140 l 280 130 m 280 130 m 120 220 l 120 230 l 130 230 l 130 220 m 130 220 m 150 190 l 150 200 l 160 200 l 160 190 m 160 190 m 160 120 l 160 130 l 170 130 l 170 120 m 170 120 m 170 170 l 170 180 l 180 180 l 180 170 m 180 170 m 40 180 l 40 190 l 50 190 l 50 180 m 50 180 m 310 100 l 310 110 l 320 110 l 320 100 m 320 100 m 60 160 l 60 170 l 70 170 l 70 160 m 70 160 m 330 80 l 330 90 l 340 90 l 340 80 m 340 80 m 70 210 l 70 220 l 80 220 l 80 210 m 80 210 m 100 180 l 100 190 l 110 190 l 110 180 m 110 180 m 110 190 l 110 200 l 120 200 l 120 190 m 120 190 m 350 220 l 350 230 l 360 230 l 360 220 m 360 220 m 220 90 l 220 100 l 230 100 l 230 90 m 230 90 m 100 360 l 100 370 l 110 370 l 110 360 m 110 360 m 250 120 l 250 130 l 260 130 l 260 120 m 260 120 m 210 280 l 210 290 l 220 290 l 220 280 m 220 280 m 260 110 l 260 120 l 270 120 l 270 110 m 270 110 m 140 130 l 140 140 l 150 140 l 150 130 m 150 130 m 120 290 l 120 300 l 130 300 l 130 290 m 130 290 m 280 320 l 280 330 l 290 330 l 290 320 m 290 320 m 180 230 l 180 240 l 190 240 l 190 230 m 190 230 m 140 230 l 140 240 l 150 240 l 150 230 m 150 230 m 190 140 l 190 150 l 200 150 l 200 140 m 200 140 m 150 300 l 150 310 l 160 310 l 160 300 m 160 300 m 300 340 l 300 350 l 310 350 l 310 340 m 310 340 m 40 90 l 40 100 l 50 100 l 50 90 m 50 90 m 280 60 l 280 70 l 290 70 l 290 60 m 290 60 m 310 350 l 310 360 l 320 360 l 320 350 m 320 350 m 50 40 l 50 50 l 60 50 l 60 40 m 60 40 m 80 150 l 80 160 l 90 160 l 90 150 m 90 150 m 320 280 l 320 290 l 330 290 l 330 280 m 330 280 m 90 140 l 90 150 l 100 150 l 100 140 m 100 140 m 100 50 l 100 60 l 110 60 l 110 50 m 110 50 m 340 60 l 340 70 l 350 70 l 350 60 m 350 60 m 230 310 l 230 320 l 240 320 l 240 310 m 240 310 m 350 310 l 350 320 l 360 320 l 360 310 m 360 310 m 100 310 l 100 320 l 110 320 l 110 310 m 110 310 m 230 50 l 230 60 l 240 60 l 240 50 m 240 50 m 360 270 l 360 280 l 370 280 l 370 270 m 370 270 m 220 260 l 220 270 l 230 270 l 230 260 m 230 260 m 160 360 l 160 370 l 170 370 l 170 360 m 170 360 m 120 40 l 120 50 l 130 50 l 130 40 m 130 40 m 140 300 l 140 310 l 150 310 l 150 300 m 150 300 m 40 320 l 40 330 l 50 330 l 50 320 m 50 320 m 160 240 l 160 250 l 170 250 l 170 240 m 170 240 m 310 240 l 310 250 l 320 250 l 320 240 m 320 240 m 170 290 l 170 300 l 180 300 l 180 290 m 180 290 m 320 270 l 320 280 l 330 280 l 330 270 m 330 270 m 60 340 l 60 350 l 70 350 l 70 340 m 70 340 m 300 70 l 300 80 l 310 80 l 310 70 m 310 70 m 330 260 l 330 270 l 340 270 l 340 260 m 340 260 m 80 280 l 80 290 l 90 290 l 90 280 m 90 280 m 230 360 l 230 370 l 240 370 l 240 360 m 240 360 m 350 40 l 350 50 l 360 50 l 360 40 m 360 40 m 100 220 l 100 230 l 110 230 l 110 220 m 110 220 m 260 210 l 260 220 l 270 220 l 270 210 m 270 210 m 270 240 l 270 250 l 280 250 l 280 240 m 280 240 m 250 80 l 250 90 l 260 90 l 260 80 m 260 80 m 120 110 l 120 120 l 130 120 l 130 110 m 130 110 m 360 80 l 360 90 l 370 90 l 370 80 m 370 80 m 260 150 l 260 160 l 270 160 l 270 150 m 270 150 m 190 280 l 190 290 l 200 290 l 200 280 m 200 280 m 280 200 l 280 210 l 290 210 l 290 200 m 290 200 m 180 110 l 180 120 l 190 120 l 190 110 m 190 110 m 160 230 l 160 240 l 170 240 l 170 230 m 170 230 m 50 220 l 50 230 l 60 230 l 60 220 m 60 220 m 170 220 l 170 230 l 180 230 l 180 220 m 180 220 m 300 140 l 300 150 l 310 150 l 310 140 m 310 140 m 70 80 l 70 90 l 80 90 l 80 80 m 80 80 m 320 80 l 320 90 l 330 90 l 330 80 m 330 80 m 350 130 l 350 140 l 360 140 l 360 130 m 360 130 m 90 100 l 90 110 l 100 110 l 100 100 m 100 100 m 330 130 l 330 140 l 340 140 l 340 130 m 340 130 m 210 70 l 210 80 l 220 80 l 220 70 m 220 70 m 350 270 l 350 280 l 360 280 l 360 270 m 360 270 m 90 360 l 90 370 l 100 370 l 100 360 m 100 360 m 240 120 l 240 130 l 250 130 l 250 120 m 250 120 m 220 120 l 220 130 l 230 130 l 230 120 m 230 120 m 270 150 l 270 160 l 280 160 l 280 150 m 280 150 m 130 210 l 130 220 l 140 220 l 140 210 m 140 210 m 180 180 l 180 190 l 190 190 l 190 180 m 190 180 m 290 260 l 290 270 l 300 270 l 300 260 m 300 260 m 190 190 l 190 200 l 200 200 l 200 190 m 200 190 m 170 150 l 170 160 l 180 160 l 180 150 m 180 150 m 40 40 l 40 50 l 50 50 l 50 40 m 50 40 m 310 280 l 310 290 l 320 290 l 320 280 m 320 280 m 50 170 l 50 180 l 60 180 l 60 170 m 60 170 m 80 180 l 80 190 l 90 190 l 90 180 m 90 180 m 320 70 l 320 80 l 330 80 l 330 70 m 330 70 m 60 140 l 60 150 l 70 150 l 70 140 m 70 140 m 330 60 l 330 70 l 340 70 l 340 60 m 340 60 m 70 230 l 70 240 l 80 240 l 80 230 m 80 230 m 100 160 l 100 170 l 110 170 l 110 160 m 110 160 m 340 290 l 340 300 l 350 300 l 350 290 m 350 290 m 110 130 l 110 140 l 120 140 l 120 130 m 120 130 m 240 270 l 240 280 l 250 280 l 250 270 m 250 270 m 200 350 l 200 360 l 210 360 l 210 350 m 210 350 m 250 260 l 250 270 l 260 270 l 260 260 m 260 260 m 210 340 l 210 350 l 220 350 l 220 340 m 220 340 m 260 90 l 260 100 l 270 100 l 270 90 m 270 90 m 220 330 l 220 340 l 230 340 l 230 330 m 230 330 m 270 40 l 270 50 l 280 50 l 280 40 m 280 40 m 360 120 l 360 130 l 370 130 l 370 120 m 370 120 m 130 300 l 130 310 l 140 310 l 140 300 m 140 300 m 280 340 l 280 350 l 290 350 l 290 340 m 290 340 m 180 210 l 180 220 l 190 220 l 190 210 m 190 210 m 190 240 l 190 250 l 200 250 l 200 240 m 200 240 m 320 360 l 320 370 l 330 370 l 330 360 m 330 360 m 300 320 l 300 330 l 310 330 l 310 320 m 310 320 m 160 350 l 160 360 l 170 360 l 170 350 m 170 350 m 50 100 l 50 110 l 60 110 l 60 100 m 60 100 m 320 300 l 320 310 l 330 310 l 330 300 m 330 300 m 300 100 l 300 110 l 310 110 l 310 100 m 310 100 m 330 310 l 330 320 l 340 320 l 340 310 m 340 310 m 340 40 l 340 50 l 350 50 l 350 40 m 350 40 m 230 330 l 230 340 l 240 340 l 240 330 m 240 330 m 300 360 l 300 370 l 310 370 l 310 360 m 310 360 m 240 340 l 240 350 l 250 350 l 250 340 m 250 340 m 200 260 l 200 270 l 210 270 l 210 260 m 210 260 m 250 350 l 250 360 l 260 360 l 260 350 m 260 350 m 230 70 l 230 80 l 240 80 l 240 70 m 240 70 m 210 270 l 210 280 l 220 280 l 220 270 m 220 270 m 260 320 l 260 330 l 270 330 l 270 320 m 270 320 m 220 240 l 220 250 l 230 250 l 230 240 m 230 240 m 270 290 l 270 300 l 280 300 l 280 290 m 280 290 m 130 70 l 130 80 l 140 80 l 140 70 m 140 70 m 180 280 l 180 290 l 190 290 l 190 280 m 190 280 m 140 280 l 140 290 l 150 290 l 150 280 m 150 280 m 150 250 l 150 260 l 160 260 l 160 250 m 160 250 m 40 340 l 40 350 l 50 350 l 50 340 m 50 340 m 180 60 l 180 70 l 190 70 l 190 60 m 190 60 m 160 260 l 160 270 l 170 270 l 170 260 m 170 260 m 170 270 l 170 280 l 180 280 l 180 270 m 180 270 m 60 320 l 60 330 l 70 330 l 70 320 m 70 320 m 300 50 l 300 60 l 310 60 l 310 50 m 310 50 m 330 240 l 330 250 l 340 250 l 340 240 m 340 240 m 310 160 l 310 170 l 320 170 l 320 160 m 320 160 m 80 300 l 80 310 l 90 310 l 90 300 m 90 300 m 320 190 l 320 200 l 330 200 l 330 190 m 330 190 m 100 200 l 100 210 l 110 210 l 110 200 m 110 200 m 250 280 l 250 290 l 260 290 l 260 280 m 260 280 m 80 360 l 80 370 l 90 370 l 90 360 m 90 360 m 210 120 l 210 130 l 220 130 l 220 120 m 220 120 m 110 250 l 110 260 l 120 260 l 120 250 m 120 250 m 220 190 l 220 200 l 230 200 l 230 190 m 230 190 m 270 260 l 270 270 l 280 270 l 280 260 m 280 260 m 250 60 l 250 70 l 260 70 l 260 60 m 260 60 m 360 100 l 360 110 l 370 110 l 370 100 m 370 100 m 260 130 l 260 140 l 270 140 l 270 130 m 270 130 m 130 80 l 130 90 l 140 90 l 140 80 m 140 80 m 270 160 l 270 170 l 280 170 l 280 160 m 280 160 m 140 70 l 140 80 l 150 80 l 150 70 m 150 70 m 190 300 l 190 310 l 200 310 l 200 300 m 200 300 m 40 250 l 40 260 l 50 260 l 50 250 m 50 250 m 50 200 l 50 210 l 60 210 l 60 200 m 60 200 m 290 230 l 290 240 l 300 240 l 300 230 m 300 230 m 190 40 l 190 50 l 200 50 l 200 40 m 200 40 m 170 200 l 170 210 l 180 210 l 180 200 m 180 200 m 60 270 l 60 280 l 70 280 l 70 270 m 70 270 m 300 120 l 300 130 l 310 130 l 310 120 m 310 120 m 40 150 l 40 160 l 50 160 l 50 150 m 50 150 m 70 100 l 70 110 l 80 110 l 80 100 m 80 100 m 320 100 l 320 110 l 330 110 l 330 100 m 330 100 m 200 80 l 200 90 l 210 90 l 210 80 m 210 80 m 240 140 l 240 150 l 250 150 l 250 140 m 250 140 m 220 100 l 220 110 l 230 110 l 230 100 m 230 100 m 140 360 l 140 370 l 150 370 l 150 360 m 150 360 m 130 170 l 130 180 l 140 180 l 140 170 m 140 170 m 270 90 l 270 100 l 280 100 l 280 90 m 280 90 m 140 140 l 140 150 l 150 150 l 150 140 m 150 140 m 120 260 l 120 270 l 130 270 l 130 260 m 130 260 m 280 290 l 280 300 l 290 300 l 290 290 m 290 290 m 150 290 l 150 300 l 160 300 l 160 290 m 160 290 m 40 60 l 40 70 l 50 70 l 50 60 m 50 60 m 70 190 l 70 200 l 80 200 l 80 190 m 80 190 m 80 120 l 80 130 l 90 130 l 90 120 m 90 120 m 320 330 l 320 340 l 330 340 l 330 330 m 330 330 m 90 170 l 90 180 l 100 180 l 100 170 m 100 170 m 330 40 l 330 50 l 340 50 l 340 40 m 340 40 m 70 250 l 70 260 l 80 260 l 80 250 m 80 250 m 290 360 l 290 370 l 300 370 l 300 360 m 300 360 m 100 60 l 100 70 l 110 70 l 110 60 m 110 60 m 230 260 l 230 270 l 240 270 l 240 260 m 240 260 m 220 50 l 220 60 l 230 60 l 230 50 m 230 50 m 200 210 l 200 220 l 210 220 l 210 210 m 210 210 m 360 240 l 360 250 l 370 250 l 370 240 m 370 240 m 260 310 l 260 320 l 270 320 l 270 310 m 270 310 m 180 270 l 180 280 l 190 280 l 190 270 m 190 270 m 140 350 l 140 360 l 150 360 l 150 350 m 150 350 m 300 300 l 300 310 l 310 310 l 310 300 m 310 300 m 280 100 l 280 110 l 290 110 l 290 100 m 290 100 m 170 320 l 170 330 l 180 330 l 180 320 m 180 320 m 320 240 l 320 250 l 330 250 l 330 240 m 330 240 m 60 70 l 60 80 l 70 80 l 70 70 m 70 70 m 300 80 l 300 90 l 310 90 l 310 80 m 310 80 m 70 300 l 70 310 l 80 310 l 80 300 m 80 300 m 310 130 l 310 140 l 320 140 l 320 130 m 320 130 m 100 90 l 100 100 l 110 100 l 110 90 m 110 90 m 340 100 l 340 110 l 350 110 l 350 100 m 350 100 m 80 330 l 80 340 l 90 340 l 90 330 m 90 330 m 90 200 l 90 210 l 100 210 l 100 200 m 100 200 m 240 280 l 240 290 l 250 290 l 250 280 m 250 280 m 70 360 l 70 370 l 80 370 l 80 360 m 80 360 m 200 120 l 200 130 l 210 130 l 210 120 m 210 120 m 100 350 l 100 360 l 110 360 l 110 350 m 110 350 m 250 330 l 250 340 l 260 340 l 260 330 m 260 330 m 260 220 l 260 230 l 270 230 l 270 220 m 270 220 m 240 100 l 240 110 l 250 110 l 250 100 m 250 100 m 250 110 l 250 120 l 260 120 l 260 110 m 260 110 m 120 80 l 120 90 l 130 90 l 130 80 m 130 80 m 360 50 l 360 60 l 370 60 l 370 50 m 370 50 m 180 340 l 180 350 l 190 350 l 190 340 m 190 340 m 140 100 l 140 110 l 150 110 l 150 100 m 150 100 m 190 350 l 190 360 l 200 360 l 200 350 m 200 350 m 40 200 l 40 210 l 50 210 l 50 200 m 50 200 m 280 170 l 280 180 l 290 180 l 290 170 m 290 170 m 180 40 l 180 50 l 190 50 l 190 40 m 190 40 m 290 120 l 290 130 l 300 130 l 300 120 m 300 120 m 190 90 l 190 100 l 200 100 l 200 90 m 200 90 m 60 300 l 60 310 l 70 310 l 70 300 m 70 300 m 300 190 l 300 200 l 310 200 l 310 190 m 310 190 m 330 220 l 330 230 l 340 230 l 340 220 m 340 220 m 70 70 l 70 80 l 80 80 l 80 70 m 80 70 m 310 180 l 310 190 l 320 190 l 320 180 m 320 180 m 340 130 l 340 140 l 350 140 l 350 130 m 350 130 m 80 80 l 80 90 l 90 90 l 90 80 m 90 80 m 350 160 l 350 170 l 360 170 l 360 160 m 360 160 m 330 160 l 330 170 l 340 170 l 340 160 m 340 160 m 200 190 l 200 200 l 210 200 l 210 190 m 210 190 m 100 260 l 100 270 l 110 270 l 110 260 m 110 260 m 260 250 l 260 260 l 270 260 l 270 250 m 270 250 m 240 170 l 240 180 l 250 180 l 250 170 m 250 170 m 220 170 l 220 180 l 230 180 l 230 170 m 230 170 m 120 150 l 120 160 l 130 160 l 130 150 m 130 150 m 130 140 l 130 150 l 140 150 l 140 140 m 140 140 m 270 180 l 270 190 l 280 190 l 280 180 m 280 180 m 290 210 l 290 220 l 300 220 l 300 210 m 300 210 m 60 250 l 60 260 l 70 260 l 70 250 m 70 250 m 80 70 l 80 80 l 90 80 l 90 70 m 90 70 m 320 40 l 320 50 l 330 50 l 330 40 m 330 40 m 280 360 l 280 370 l 290 370 l 290 360 m 290 360 m 200 100 l 200 110 l 210 110 l 210 100 m 210 100 m 230 230 l 230 240 l 240 240 l 240 230 m 240 230 m 210 110 l 210 120 l 220 120 l 220 110 m 220 110 m 240 240 l 240 250 l 250 250 l 250 240 m 250 240 m 200 320 l 200 330 l 210 330 l 210 320 m 210 320 m 250 130 l 250 140 l 260 140 l 260 130 m 260 130 m 210 290 l 210 300 l 220 300 l 220 290 m 220 290 m 260 100 l 260 110 l 270 110 l 270 100 m 270 100 m 140 120 l 140 130 l 150 130 l 150 120 m 150 120 m 280 310 l 280 320 l 290 320 l 290 310 m 290 310 m 180 220 l 180 230 l 190 230 l 190 220 m 190 220 m 160 100 l 160 110 l 170 110 l 170 100 m 170 100 m 140 220 l 140 230 l 150 230 l 150 220 m 150 220 m 190 150 l 190 160 l 200 160 l 200 150 m 200 150 m 150 310 l 150 320 l 160 320 l 160 310 m 160 310 m 40 80 l 40 90 l 50 90 l 50 80 m 50 80 m 280 50 l 280 60 l 290 60 l 290 50 m 290 50 m 310 320 l 310 330 l 320 330 l 320 320 m 320 320 m 60 100 l 60 110 l 70 110 l 70 100 m 70 100 m 330 340 l 330 350 l 340 350 l 340 340 m 340 340 m 70 270 l 70 280 l 80 280 l 80 270 m 80 270 m 100 40 l 100 50 l 110 50 l 110 40 m 110 40 m 340 330 l 340 340 l 350 340 l 350 330 m 350 330 m 80 200 l 80 210 l 90 210 l 90 200 m 90 200 m 60 360 l 60 370 l 70 370 l 70 360 m 70 360 m 350 280 l 350 290 l 360 290 l 360 280 m 360 280 m 240 230 l 240 240 l 250 240 l 250 230 m 250 230 m 200 230 l 200 240 l 210 240 l 210 230 m 210 230 m 100 300 l 100 310 l 110 310 l 110 300 m 110 300 m 250 220 l 250 230 l 260 230 l 260 220 m 260 220 m 210 220 l 210 230 l 220 230 l 220 220 m 220 220 m 360 160 l 360 170 l 370 170 l 370 160 m 370 160 m 140 330 l 140 340 l 150 340 l 150 330 m 150 330 m 170 40 l 170 50 l 180 50 l 180 40 m 180 40 m 150 200 l 150 210 l 160 210 l 160 200 m 160 200 m 300 280 l 300 290 l 310 290 l 310 280 m 310 280 m 40 310 l 40 320 l 50 320 l 50 310 m 50 310 m 280 120 l 280 130 l 290 130 l 290 120 m 290 120 m 310 250 l 310 260 l 320 260 l 320 250 m 320 250 m 50 300 l 50 310 l 60 310 l 60 300 m 60 300 m 320 260 l 320 270 l 330 270 l 330 260 m 330 260 m 300 60 l 300 70 l 310 70 l 310 60 m 310 60 m 70 320 l 70 330 l 80 330 l 80 320 m 80 320 m 340 80 l 340 90 l 350 90 l 350 80 m 350 80 m 240 300 l 240 310 l 250 310 l 250 300 m 250 300 m 100 330 l 100 340 l 110 340 l 110 330 m 110 330 m 230 110 l 230 120 l 240 120 l 240 110 m 240 110 m 120 360 l 120 370 l 130 370 l 130 360 m 130 360 m 260 200 l 260 210 l 270 210 l 270 200 m 270 200 m 270 250 l 270 260 l 280 260 l 280 250 m 280 250 m 250 90 l 250 100 l 260 100 l 260 90 m 260 90 m 120 100 l 120 110 l 130 110 l 130 100 m 130 100 m 360 70 l 360 80 l 370 80 l 370 70 m 370 70 m 180 320 l 180 330 l 190 330 l 190 320 m 190 320 m 190 290 l 190 300 l 200 300 l 200 290 m 200 290 m 40 220 l 40 230 l 50 230 l 50 220 m 50 220 m 280 190 l 280 200 l 290 200 l 290 190 m 290 190 m 180 100 l 180 110 l 190 110 l 190 100 m 190 100 m 160 220 l 160 230 l 170 230 l 170 220 m 170 220 m 290 180 l 290 190 l 300 190 l 300 180 m 300 180 m 40 120 l 40 130 l 50 130 l 50 120 m 50 120 m 330 200 l 330 210 l 340 210 l 340 200 m 340 200 m 310 40 l 310 50 l 320 50 l 320 40 m 320 40 m 80 100 l 80 110 l 90 110 l 90 100 m 90 100 m 350 180 l 350 190 l 360 190 l 360 180 m 360 180 m 330 140 l 330 150 l 340 150 l 340 140 m 340 140 m 200 50 l 200 60 l 210 60 l 210 50 m 210 50 m 100 240 l 100 250 l 110 250 l 110 240 m 110 240 m 340 210 l 340 220 l 350 220 l 350 210 m 350 210 m 110 210 l 110 220 l 120 220 l 120 210 m 120 210 m 270 220 l 270 230 l 280 230 l 280 220 m 280 220 m 250 180 l 250 190 l 260 190 l 260 180 m 260 180 m 120 170 l 120 180 l 130 180 l 130 170 m 130 170 m 270 120 l 270 130 l 280 130 l 280 120 m 280 120 m 140 190 l 140 200 l 150 200 l 150 190 m 150 190 m 180 130 l 180 140 l 190 140 l 190 130 m 190 130 m 160 130 l 160 140 l 170 140 l 170 130 m 170 130 m 290 270 l 290 280 l 300 280 l 300 270 m 300 270 m 170 160 l 170 170 l 180 170 l 180 160 m 180 160 m 300 240 l 300 250 l 310 250 l 310 240 m 310 240 m 70 140 l 70 150 l 80 150 l 80 140 m 80 140 m 50 180 l 50 190 l 60 190 l 60 180 m 60 180 m 80 170 l 80 180 l 90 180 l 90 170 m 90 170 m 320 60 l 320 70 l 330 70 l 330 60 m 330 60 m 90 40 l 90 50 l 100 50 l 100 40 m 100 40 m 330 70 l 330 80 l 340 80 l 340 70 m 340 70 m 70 200 l 70 210 l 80 210 l 80 200 m 80 200 m 50 360 l 50 370 l 60 370 l 60 360 m 60 360 m 230 250 l 230 260 l 240 260 l 240 250 m 240 250 m 210 90 l 210 100 l 220 100 l 220 90 m 220 90 m 350 330 l 350 340 l 360 340 l 360 330 m 360 330 m 220 60 l 220 70 l 230 70 l 230 60 m 230 60 m 250 270 l 250 280 l 260 280 l 260 270 m 260 270 m 210 350 l 210 360 l 220 360 l 220 350 m 220 350 m 260 80 l 260 90 l 270 90 l 270 80 m 270 80 m 120 300 l 120 310 l 130 310 l 130 300 m 130 300 m 150 110 l 150 120 l 160 120 l 160 110 m 160 110 m 130 310 l 130 320 l 140 320 l 140 310 m 140 310 m 280 330 l 280 340 l 290 340 l 290 330 m 290 330 m 290 280 l 290 290 l 300 290 l 300 280 m 300 280 m 170 90 l 170 100 l 180 100 l 180 90 m 180 90 m 150 330 l 150 340 l 160 340 l 160 330 m 160 330 m 300 350 l 300 360 l 310 360 l 310 350 m 310 350 m 40 100 l 40 110 l 50 110 l 50 100 m 50 100 m 310 340 l 310 350 l 320 350 l 320 340 m 320 340 m 320 290 l 320 300 l 330 300 l 330 290 m 330 290 m 60 80 l 60 90 l 70 90 l 70 80 m 70 80 m 330 320 l 330 330 l 340 330 l 340 320 m 340 320 m 100 100 l 100 110 l 110 110 l 110 100 m 110 100 m 340 70 l 340 80 l 350 80 l 350 70 m 350 70 m 350 300 l 350 310 l 360 310 l 360 300 m 360 300 m 240 330 l 240 340 l 250 340 l 250 330 m 250 330 m 200 250 l 200 260 l 210 260 l 210 250 m 210 250 m 100 280 l 100 290 l 110 290 l 110 280 m 110 280 m 250 200 l 250 210 l 260 210 l 260 200 m 260 200 m 210 200 l 210 210 l 220 210 l 220 200 m 220 200 m 260 350 l 260 360 l 270 360 l 270 350 m 270 350 m 270 340 l 270 350 l 280 350 l 280 340 m 280 340 m 130 320 l 130 330 l 140 330 l 140 320 m 140 320 m 190 220 l 190 230 l 200 230 l 200 220 m 200 220 m 40 330 l 40 340 l 50 340 l 50 330 m 50 330 m 280 140 l 280 150 l 290 150 l 290 140 m 290 140 m 160 250 l 160 260 l 170 260 l 170 250 m 170 250 m 310 270 l 310 280 l 320 280 l 320 270 m 320 270 m 50 280 l 50 290 l 60 290 l 60 280 m 60 280 m 290 150 l 290 160 l 300 160 l 300 150 m 300 150 m 170 280 l 170 290 l 180 290 l 180 280 m 180 280 m 320 200 l 320 210 l 330 210 l 330 200 m 330 200 m 300 40 l 300 50 l 310 50 l 310 40 m 310 40 m 70 340 l 70 350 l 80 350 l 80 340 m 80 340 m 310 170 l 310 180 l 320 180 l 320 170 m 320 170 m 200 160 l 200 170 l 210 170 l 210 160 m 210 160 m 250 290 l 250 300 l 260 300 l 260 290 m 260 290 m 210 130 l 210 140 l 220 140 l 220 130 m 220 130 m 260 260 l 260 270 l 270 270 l 270 260 m 270 260 m 240 60 l 240 70 l 250 70 l 250 60 m 250 60 m 220 180 l 220 190 l 230 190 l 230 180 m 230 180 m 250 70 l 250 80 l 260 80 l 260 70 m 260 70 m 120 120 l 120 130 l 130 130 l 130 120 m 130 120 m 360 90 l 360 100 l 370 100 l 370 90 m 370 90 m 260 120 l 260 130 l 270 130 l 270 120 m 270 120 m 130 90 l 130 100 l 140 100 l 140 90 m 140 90 m 190 310 l 190 320 l 200 320 l 200 310 m 200 310 m 150 150 l 150 160 l 160 160 l 160 150 m 160 150 m 40 240 l 40 250 l 50 250 l 50 240 m 50 240 m 50 210 l 50 220 l 60 220 l 60 210 m 60 210 m 290 160 l 290 170 l 300 170 l 300 160 m 300 160 m 170 210 l 170 220 l 180 220 l 180 210 m 180 210 m 60 260 l 60 270 l 70 270 l 70 260 m 70 260 m 40 140 l 40 150 l 50 150 l 50 140 m 50 140 m 50 150 l 50 160 l 60 160 l 60 150 m 60 150 m 80 40 l 80 50 l 90 50 l 90 40 m 90 40 m 40 360 l 40 370 l 50 370 l 50 360 m 50 360 m 330 120 l 330 130 l 340 130 l 340 120 m 340 120 m 200 70 l 200 80 l 210 80 l 210 70 m 210 70 m 100 140 l 100 150 l 110 150 l 110 140 m 110 140 m 210 60 l 210 70 l 220 70 l 220 60 m 220 60 m 110 230 l 110 240 l 120 240 l 120 230 m 120 230 m 350 260 l 350 270 l 360 270 l 360 260 m 360 260 m 240 130 l 240 140 l 250 140 l 250 130 m 250 130 m 220 130 l 220 140 l 230 140 l 230 130 m 230 130 m 200 290 l 200 300 l 210 300 l 210 290 m 210 290 m 360 320 l 360 330 l 370 330 l 370 320 m 370 320 m 260 70 l 260 80 l 270 80 l 270 70 m 270 70 m 130 180 l 130 190 l 140 190 l 140 180 m 140 180 m 270 140 l 270 150 l 280 150 l 280 140 m 280 140 m 140 170 l 140 180 l 150 180 l 150 170 m 150 170 m 120 250 l 120 260 l 130 260 l 130 250 m 130 250 m 280 280 l 280 290 l 290 290 l 290 280 m 290 280 m 140 270 l 140 280 l 150 280 l 150 270 m 150 270 m 190 180 l 190 190 l 200 190 l 200 180 m 200 180 m 170 140 l 170 150 l 180 150 l 180 140 m 180 140 m 300 220 l 300 230 l 310 230 l 310 220 m 310 220 m 40 50 l 40 60 l 50 60 l 50 50 m 50 50 m 320 320 l 320 330 l 330 330 l 330 320 m 330 320 m 60 150 l 60 160 l 70 160 l 70 150 m 70 150 m 90 180 l 90 190 l 100 190 l 100 180 m 100 180 m 340 340 l 340 350 l 350 350 l 350 340 m 350 340 m 80 250 l 80 260 l 90 260 l 90 250 m 90 250 m 230 270 l 230 280 l 240 280 l 240 270 m 240 270 m 110 120 l 110 130 l 120 130 l 120 120 m 120 120 m 260 360 l 260 370 l 270 370 l 270 360 m 270 360 m 240 200 l 240 210 l 250 210 l 250 200 m 250 200 m 200 200 l 200 210 l 210 210 l 210 200 m 210 200 m 220 300 l 220 310 l 230 310 l 230 300 m 230 300 m 120 320 l 120 330 l 130 330 l 130 320 m 130 320 m 360 130 l 360 140 l 370 140 l 370 130 m 370 130 m 130 290 l 130 300 l 140 300 l 140 290 m 140 290 m 280 350 l 280 360 l 290 360 l 290 350 m 290 350 m 180 260 l 180 270 l 190 270 l 190 260 m 190 260 m 160 60 l 160 70 l 170 70 l 170 60 m 170 60 m 300 330 l 300 340 l 310 340 l 310 330 m 310 330 m 40 280 l 40 290 l 50 290 l 50 280 m 50 280 m 280 90 l 280 100 l 290 100 l 290 90 m 290 90 m 160 280 l 160 290 l 170 290 l 170 280 m 170 280 m 170 330 l 170 340 l 180 340 l 180 330 m 180 330 m 320 310 l 320 320 l 330 320 l 330 310 m 330 310 m 60 60 l 60 70 l 70 70 l 70 60 m 70 60 m 330 300 l 330 310 l 340 310 l 340 300 m 340 300 m 210 360 l 210 370 l 220 370 l 220 360 m 220 360 m 100 80 l 100 90 l 110 90 l 110 80 m 110 80 m 80 320 l 80 330 l 90 330 l 90 320 m 90 320 m 230 320 l 230 330 l 240 330 l 240 320 m 240 320 m 90 210 l 90 220 l 100 220 l 100 210 m 100 210 m 100 340 l 100 350 l 110 350 l 110 340 m 110 340 m 230 60 l 230 70 l 240 70 l 240 60 m 240 60 m 240 90 l 240 100 l 250 100 l 250 90 m 250 90 m 120 70 l 120 80 l 130 80 l 130 70 m 130 70 m 360 40 l 360 50 l 370 50 l 370 40 m 370 40 m 130 60 l 130 70 l 140 70 l 140 60 m 140 60 m 180 290 l 180 300 l 190 300 l 190 290 m 190 290 m 190 320 l 190 330 l 200 330 l 200 320 m 200 320 m 150 240 l 150 250 l 160 250 l 160 240 m 160 240 m 40 350 l 40 360 l 50 360 l 50 350 m 50 350 m 280 160 l 280 170 l 290 170 l 290 160 m 290 160 m 160 270 l 160 280 l 170 280 l 170 270 m 170 270 m 170 260 l 170 270 l 180 270 l 180 260 m 180 260 m 60 330 l 60 340 l 70 340 l 70 330 m 70 330 m 70 40 l 70 50 l 80 50 l 80 40 m 80 40 m 320 120 l 320 130 l 330 130 l 330 120 m 330 120 m 360 360 l 360 370 l 370 370 l 370 360 m 370 360 m 90 300 l 90 310 l 100 310 l 100 300 m 100 300 m 210 190 l 210 200 l 220 200 l 220 190 m 220 190 m 110 240 l 110 250 l 120 250 l 120 240 m 120 240 m 270 210 l 270 220 l 280 220 l 280 210 m 280 210 m 260 180 l 260 190 l 270 190 l 270 180 m 270 180 m 270 190 l 270 200 l 280 200 l 280 190 m 280 190 m 120 200 l 120 210 l 130 210 l 130 200 m 130 200 m 180 140 l 180 150 l 190 150 l 190 140 m 190 140 m 160 180 l 160 190 l 170 190 l 170 180 m 170 180 m 60 240 l 60 250 l 70 250 l 70 240 m 70 240 m 40 160 l 40 170 l 50 170 l 50 160 m 50 160 m 50 130 l 50 140 l 60 140 l 60 130 m 60 130 m 80 60 l 80 70 l 90 70 l 90 60 m 90 60 m 60 180 l 60 190 l 70 190 l 70 180 m 70 180 m 350 140 l 350 150 l 360 150 l 360 140 m 360 140 m 330 100 l 330 110 l 340 110 l 340 100 m 340 100 m 100 120 l 100 130 l 110 130 l 110 120 m 110 120 m 250 360 l 250 370 l 260 370 l 260 360 m 260 360 m 230 200 l 230 210 l 240 210 l 240 200 m 240 200 m 350 200 l 350 210 l 360 210 l 360 200 m 360 200 m 240 150 l 240 160 l 250 160 l 250 150 m 250 150 m 200 310 l 200 320 l 210 320 l 210 310 m 210 310 m 140 150 l 140 160 l 150 160 l 150 150 m 150 150 m 120 270 l 120 280 l 130 280 l 130 270 m 130 270 m 150 60 l 150 70 l 160 70 l 160 60 m 160 60 m 130 260 l 130 270 l 140 270 l 140 260 m 140 260 m 280 300 l 280 310 l 290 310 l 290 300 m 290 300 m 180 170 l 180 180 l 190 180 l 190 170 m 190 170 m 190 120 l 190 130 l 200 130 l 200 120 m 200 120 m 170 120 l 170 130 l 180 130 l 180 120 m 180 120 m 150 280 l 150 290 l 160 290 l 160 280 m 160 280 m 300 200 l 300 210 l 310 210 l 310 200 m 310 200 m 40 70 l 40 80 l 50 80 l 50 70 m 50 70 m 280 40 l 280 50 l 290 50 l 290 40 m 290 40 m 80 130 l 80 140 l 90 140 l 90 130 m 90 130 m 320 340 l 320 350 l 330 350 l 330 340 m 330 340 m 60 130 l 60 140 l 70 140 l 70 130 m 70 130 m 100 70 l 100 80 l 110 80 l 110 70 m 110 70 m 240 220 l 240 230 l 250 230 l 250 220 m 250 220 m 200 220 l 200 230 l 210 230 l 210 220 m 210 220 m 250 230 l 250 240 l 260 240 l 260 230 m 260 230 m 210 230 l 210 240 l 220 240 l 220 230 m 220 230 m 220 280 l 220 290 l 230 290 l 230 280 m 230 280 m 270 330 l 270 340 l 280 340 l 280 330 m 280 330 m 360 150 l 360 160 l 370 160 l 370 150 m 370 150 m 180 240 l 180 250 l 190 250 l 190 240 m 190 240 m 290 320 l 290 330 l 300 330 l 300 320 m 300 320 m 190 210 l 190 220 l 200 220 l 200 210 m 200 210 m 170 50 l 170 60 l 180 60 l 180 50 m 180 50 m 150 210 l 150 220 l 160 220 l 160 210 m 160 210 m 40 300 l 40 310 l 50 310 l 50 300 m 50 300 m 280 110 l 280 120 l 290 120 l 290 110 m 290 110 m 160 300 l 160 310 l 170 310 l 170 300 m 170 300 m 170 310 l 170 320 l 180 320 l 180 310 m 180 310 m 60 40 l 60 50 l 70 50 l 70 40 m 70 40 m 300 90 l 300 100 l 310 100 l 310 90 m 310 90 m 330 280 l 330 290 l 340 290 l 340 280 m 340 280 m 70 330 l 70 340 l 80 340 l 80 330 m 80 330 m 310 120 l 310 130 l 320 130 l 320 120 m 320 120 m 80 340 l 80 350 l 90 350 l 90 340 m 90 340

