[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Subtitles
Original Script: Subtitles
website: www.zimuzu.tv
Sina Weibo: @zimuzu
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134
Style: LOGO,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.50,0:00:49.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有牙膏吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you have any toothpaste left?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.42,0:00:50.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.92,0:00:53.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为两周以来有个人每天都在借用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'cause someone's been borrowing it every day for two weeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.13,0:00:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Carl.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.35,0:00:59.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了  丹妮斯说是体育课\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What? Denise says it's PT.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.95,0:01:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我听不见  出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I can't hear you. Come on out.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.39,0:01:05.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.59,0:01:08.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹妮斯说是体育课\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Denise says this is PT.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.26,0:01:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你听见了  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You heard me. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.80,0:01:14.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该给你换绷带了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's time to change your bandage.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.55,0:01:16.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要借点牙膏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And I need to borrow some toothpaste.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.27,0:01:18.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  但我没牙膏了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, but I'm out of toothpaste.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.93,0:01:20.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-再见  爸爸  -回头见\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Bye, Dad. - I'll see you later.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.64,0:01:29.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.74,0:01:34.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你出去后会没事的  -我们看吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You be good out there. - Yeah, we'll see.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.28,0:01:37.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.45,0:01:41.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绿薄荷和小苏打  那是我最爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Spearmint and baking soda. That's my favorite.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.70,0:01:43.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等我拿到就给你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Soon as I get it, you will.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.22,0:01:56.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你好  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Hey. - Yes?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.67,0:01:57.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这底下的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This thing at the bottom right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.74,0:01:59.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是说饮料  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're talking about the drink, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.64,0:02:00.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I am, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.78,0:02:04.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不是药品\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's not medical.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.26,0:02:09.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错  我把重要的东西和那个划线分开了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I drew a line between the important stuff and that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.11,0:02:12.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是想着  如果你看见就带点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just figured, if you saw it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.95,0:02:13.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.97,0:02:16.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟药品有关的都是优先考虑的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Anything remotely medical is a priority.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.25,0:02:18.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有食物  也许比药更重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And food, maybe even food before medicine,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.15,0:02:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有汽油  电池  儿童书籍  衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and gas or batteries or books for the kids or clothes is just--
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.96,0:02:24.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你看见了  如果它碰巧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}if you see it, if it just happens to,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.37,0:02:27.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}you know, be right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.33,0:02:28.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你喜欢喝  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You like it, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.28,0:02:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不喝泡泡水\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I don't drink pop.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.08,0:02:31.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,泡泡水是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What the hell's pop?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.95,0:02:34.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来自俄亥俄州\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, I'm originally from Ohio.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.21,0:02:38.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么想要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why you want it?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.94,0:02:44.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,塔拉好像说梦话说到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Tara was talking about it in her sleep, I think.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.84,0:02:48.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要么喜欢  要么不喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Either she likes it or she doesn't,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.96,0:02:52.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但如果她喜欢  这会是个很棒的惊喜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but if she likes it, it'd be a really nice surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.86,0:02:55.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不擅长这种事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not good with that kind of stuff,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.07,0:02:57.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她和希斯要出去两周\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and she and Heath are going on that two-week run.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.91,0:03:00.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得这是个不错的临别礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just thought it'd be a nice going-away present.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.62,0:03:03.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用特别费心\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Just, uh, don't go out of your way.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.57,0:03:05.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这会给你带来麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}And if it gives you any trouble...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.22,0:03:06.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I won't.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.92,0:03:08.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  很好  因为这不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, good, 'cause it's not important.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.54,0:03:10.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我该说清楚的  而不是只划条线\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I should've said so instead of just drawing a line.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.39,0:03:14.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.31,0:03:24.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}铭记于心
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.58,0:03:45.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在地图上标出了一些农产品供给点\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mapped out some of the agricultural supply places in the area.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.66,0:03:47.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就算已经被清空了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Even if they've been cleaned out,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.70,0:03:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得高粱肯定没人碰\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}my bet is that the Sorghum would be untouched.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.01,0:03:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是一种严重被低估的粮食\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Now, that there is a criminally underrated grain
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.70,0:03:52.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以改变我们的生活\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}that could change the game
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.50,0:03:55.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让粮食储备从少得可怜变成满满当当\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}with our food situation from scary to hunky-dunky.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.31,0:04:03.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是在说它的生命力  耐旱性\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm talking standability, drought tolerance,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.37,0:04:06.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,转为秸秆的比例  都是谷物中最高的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}grain-to-stover ratio that is the envy of all corns.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.63,0:04:10.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,考虑一下吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Think about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.12,0:04:14.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢了  -不用\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Thanks. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.25,0:04:16.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.00,0:04:45.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天是个好日子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Today's the day.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.29,0:04:47.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会找到食物  也许还能找到一些人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're gonna find food, maybe some people.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.48,0:04:50.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,按概率来说也该遇到好事了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The law of averages has gotta catch up.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.16,0:04:55.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可不敢确定  我们几周都没碰到人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't know. We ain't seen nobody for weeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.34,0:04:58.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我们什么人也碰不到\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe we ain't gonna find nobody.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.49,0:04:59.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许那是件好事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe that's a good thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.36,0:05:09.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.40,0:05:11.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.50,0:05:12.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你别放\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Please don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.73,0:05:24.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,*把它们从家里引开*\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}*Draws 'em away from home!*
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.51,0:06:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第六季  第十集』
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.51,0:06:06.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs21}本蓝光版外挂字幕由  {\c&H9B30FF&}风吹来的那片云{\c&HFFFFFF&}  用WEB版调轴
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.22,0:06:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an7\p1\bord0\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,200,\fscx206\fscy266\t(200,400,\fscx103\fscy133\t(29600,29800,\fscx206,fscy266\t(29800,30000,\fscx0\fscy0))))\c&H573E00&\pos(39.5,211)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10m -13 -14 l 13 -14 l 13 12 l -13 12 l -13 -14 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.22,0:06:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,200,\fscx206\fscy266\t(200,400,\fscx103\fscy133\t(29600,29800,\fscx206,fscy266\t(29800,30000,\fscx0\fscy0))))\c&HEBAE00&\bord0\shad0\fad(0,330)\pos(51.4,231.16)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.22,0:06:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\p1\fscx0\fscy0\t(0,200,\fscx206\fscy266\t(200,400,\fscx103\fscy133\t(29600,29800,\fscx206,fscy266\t(29800,30000,\fscx0\fscy0))))\c&HEBAE00&\bord0\shad0\frz180\t(0,500,\clip(-1,0,386,289))\pos(27.7,188.26)}m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10 {\p0}
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.22,0:06:47.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\alpha&B0\c&H000000&\t(0,200,\fscx2000\fscy600\t(200,400,\fscx2500\fscy300\t(29800,30200,\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\alpha&AA\fscy400\fscx400)))\move(158,211.2,46.5,211.2,29800,30200)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.22,0:06:12.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\fs16\fn方正大黑_GBK\move(-150,211,56,211,400,600)\clip(54.24,192,230.88,228.48)}本字幕首发于{\c&HEBAE00&}字幕组{\c&HFFFFFF&}网站\N{\c&H00C0FF&}www.ZiMuZu.tv {\c&HFFFFFF&}欢迎交流
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.22,0:06:17.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,301,227))}翻译  冰蓝 Reginamoon CS小明漫画家 自然卷
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.22,0:06:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,291,227))}翻译  艾瑞卡 小酸奶 蘑菇 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.22,0:06:27.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\frx-630\t(0,500,\frx0\t(4500,5000,\clip(40,213,40,248)))\pos(57.12,210.56)}校对  冰蓝 君君 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.22,0:06:32.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,0)\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\move(57.12,210.56,400,210.56,4500,5000)\clip(54.24,193.92,284.24,228.48)}时间轴  加森 雪贵人 涛涛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.22,0:06:37.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(300,300)\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs17\bord0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&HEDB425&\4c&H9EF6FF&\shad0\bord0\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))\pos(57.12,210.56)}后期 吉吉 拉图  总监 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.17,0:07:05.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这段时间你到哪去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where have you been?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.32,0:07:08.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.98,0:07:10.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我一直没看见你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I never see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.76,0:07:12.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,大家这几周都在努力工作\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Everybody's been working for weeks
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.20,0:07:13.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,重建这地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}to get this place back together
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.44,0:07:14.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而你却不见人影\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you just disappear.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.64,0:07:19.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你整天都待在房间里吗  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Do you sit in your room all day? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.67,0:07:22.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你去哪里了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then where'd you go?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.09,0:07:23.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没去哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nowhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.60,0:07:28.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你帮格伦回家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You helped Glenn get home.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.58,0:07:31.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在那个哨岗上时你也帮了我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You helped me when I was up in that guard post.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.48,0:07:34.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.48,0:07:36.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以也许比起"没去哪里"\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So maybe there are better places
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.20,0:07:38.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有更好的去处\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for you to go than just nowhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.80,0:07:42.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我就在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm around.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.30,0:07:45.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可以来找我聊聊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come talk to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.29,0:08:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}高粱
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.49,0:08:44.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, hold up.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.53,0:08:46.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,小心为上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's best to be safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.64,0:08:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-掩护我  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- You cover it? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.61,0:08:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,安全\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, we're good.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.53,0:09:02.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再来一次吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}One more time?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.42,0:09:04.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没上锁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It ain't locked.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.08,0:09:18.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瞧瞧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, how about that?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.66,0:09:22.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,概率\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The law of averages.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.25,0:09:24.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.51,0:09:31.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把这车发动起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's get this thing going,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.82,0:09:34.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带上装备  晚点再回来取车\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}grab our gear, come back for the car later.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.00,0:09:36.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走另一条路回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Take another way back.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.25,0:09:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看能不能遇上什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See what we can see.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.03,0:09:41.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得这车能发动吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Think it'll start?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.37,0:09:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得能\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.39,0:09:45.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,高粱\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorghum.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.04,0:10:36.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,喂  过来帮个忙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yo, give me a hand with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.76,0:10:42.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把它翻过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's flip it over.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.86,0:10:52.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得我们翻不过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't think we got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.21,0:11:03.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我有个主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got an idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.10,0:11:27.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是汽水和糖果  要这么麻烦吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's soda and candy. Why the trouble?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.95,0:11:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一点也不麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It wasn't any trouble.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.23,0:11:42.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后退  马上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Back up! Now!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.42,0:11:43.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,举起手来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Keep 'em up!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.37,0:11:45.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放松点  伙计们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whoa, easy, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.81,0:11:47.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只是在躲行尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was just running from the dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.40,0:11:49.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有多少只\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How many?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.58,0:11:51.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,十只  也许更多\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}10, maybe more.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.99,0:11:53.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想冒险\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm not risking it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.17,0:11:55.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要到达两位数  我就会跑\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Once it gets to double digits, I start running.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.59,0:11:56.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.90,0:11:58.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,后面大约半英里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}About a half a mile back.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.98,0:12:00.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们正朝这边来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're headed this way.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.41,0:12:02.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们大概有十一分钟吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You probably have about 11 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.64,0:12:10.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧  谢谢你告诉我们\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay, thanks for letting us know.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.33,0:12:13.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.69,0:12:15.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们数量比我们多  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's more of them than us, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.75,0:12:16.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须团结起来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Gotta stick together.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.98,0:12:20.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.36,0:12:28.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们有营地吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have a camp?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.48,0:12:31.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.29,0:12:33.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.39,0:12:36.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.56,0:12:39.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,很抱歉撞到你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry for running into you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.21,0:12:41.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我得走了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna go now.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.78,0:12:44.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果这就是新世界  希望你们过得还好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If this is the next world, I hope it's good to you guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.63,0:12:48.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我是瑞克  这是达里尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm Rick. This is Daryl.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.03,0:12:50.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你叫什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's your name?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.07,0:12:56.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,保罗·罗维\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Paul Rovia.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.30,0:12:59.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但朋友们一般都叫我耶稣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But my friends used to call me Jesus.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.09,0:13:01.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们随意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your pick.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.90,0:13:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说你没有营地\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You said you didn't have a camp.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.85,0:13:04.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是独自一人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You on your own?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.97,0:13:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.71,0:13:10.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是  最好别打什么歪主意\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}But, still, best not to try anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.32,0:13:12.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也最好别做不自量力的威胁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Best not to make threats you can't keep, either.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.44,0:13:14.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Exactly.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.10,0:13:19.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你杀过多少...  -不  不要这家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- How many walkers... - No, not this guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.45,0:13:21.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀过多少行尸\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}How many walkers have you killed?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.27,0:13:23.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉  我得逃了  你们也应该快逃\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry, gotta run. You should, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.13,0:13:25.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们大概还有七分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Think you've got about seven minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.10,0:13:30.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你干嘛问他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What the hell was that?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.48,0:13:31.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他很干净\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He was clean.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.90,0:13:33.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他的胡子修过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}His beard, it was trimmed.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.43,0:13:36.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,肯定有名堂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's more going on there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.16,0:13:38.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他也没有枪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He didn't have a gun, either.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.64,0:13:40.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以跟踪他  观察一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We could track him, watch him for a while,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.01,0:13:42.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,多了解一些\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}get to know more.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.10,0:13:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看他是不是真的独自一人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See if he's really alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.90,0:13:46.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许带他回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe bring him back.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.67,0:13:49.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才不要  这家伙管自己叫耶稣\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nah, guy calls himself Jesus.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.09,0:14:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,鞭炮\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Firecrackers.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.75,0:14:07.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-该死  -妈的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Hell. - Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.30,0:14:08.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他把你的钥匙偷走了  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He swiped your keys, didn't he?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.14,0:14:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.43,0:14:12.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉啦\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sorry!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.67,0:14:26.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Shit.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.28,0:14:32.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.29,0:14:34.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.19,0:14:49.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got him.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.04,0:15:00.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你觉得我对付不了它吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You think I couldn't get it?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.21,0:15:02.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You could've.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.38,0:15:04.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我有刀\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have a sword.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.11,0:15:08.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在这干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you doing out here?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.09,0:15:11.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我站岗时看到有人进入了树林\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was on guard. I saw someone was in the woods.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.51,0:15:13.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你跑出来干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you doing out here?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.66,0:15:16.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我轮班结束后散散步\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I walk after my shifts.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.40,0:15:18.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我这样做已经有段时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been doing it for a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.23,0:15:22.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是第一个注意到的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're the first one to notice.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.48,0:15:26.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么带铲子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why the shovel?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.77,0:15:31.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我继续散步了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna keep walking now.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.27,0:15:33.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我陪你一起\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna come with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.53,0:15:34.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.01,0:15:40.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你妈妈曾要我搞清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Your mom told me I had to figure out what I want...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.06,0:15:43.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一辈子想要什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}for my whole life.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.37,0:15:50.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你搞清楚了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have you?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.34,0:15:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我还在努力\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm working up to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.14,0:15:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我只想知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Right now I just want to find out
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.74,0:15:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她儿子为什么要带着铲子在树林里游荡\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}why her son's wandering around the woods with a shovel.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.78,0:16:34.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.87,0:16:44.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,写的什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's it say?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.63,0:16:52.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全湿了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It got wet.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.65,0:16:54.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看不清了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's all gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.40,0:16:57.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.49,0:17:02.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看上去没那么旧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It doesn't look that old.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.19,0:17:02.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.50,0:17:05.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们虽然看不清写的是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I mean, we can't read what they wrote,but ...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.85,0:17:08.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是有人这样做  证明了一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}just by doing this, they're saying something.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.20,0:17:08.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.82,0:17:10.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们并不孤独\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}"We're not alone."
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.16,0:17:14.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们知道这一点  我们亲眼见过\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We knew that. We saw it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.90,0:17:17.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还死了人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}People died.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.25,0:17:23.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们为什么来这\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why are we coming out here?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.34,0:17:27.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我们是孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'Cause we're kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.74,0:17:29.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,孩子就喜欢到处玩\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's what they do.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.11,0:17:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不是孩子了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We're not kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.23,0:18:28.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是医生的特别要求\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This was a special request from the doctor.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.61,0:18:34.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她要什么都行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Whatever she wants.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.04,0:18:37.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她救了卡尔的命\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She saved Carl's life.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.73,0:18:41.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们之前不了解她  后来发现她还不错\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We didn't know her, and she turned out to be all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.56,0:18:45.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果外面还有人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If there's still people out here,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.60,0:18:47.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们还有人性的话\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and they're still people,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.61,0:18:49.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该把他们带回去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}we should bring 'em in.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.96,0:18:51.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,像那家伙吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What, like this guy?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.18,0:18:53.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  那家伙不行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, not this guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.23,0:19:01.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们还没跟丢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We still got a trail.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.68,0:19:05.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.09,0:19:35.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.45,0:19:57.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是米琼恩和斯宾塞而已\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It was just Michonne and Spencer.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.42,0:20:03.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What were they doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.36,0:20:07.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,散步吧  我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Walking. I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.46,0:20:20.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想再到外面来了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I don't want to come out here anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.64,0:20:37.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.25,0:21:10.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Carl.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.21,0:21:12.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米琼恩在外面  我不能放着不管\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Michonne's out here. I'm not leaving it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.23,0:21:29.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.32,0:21:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.17,0:21:34.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.56,0:21:35.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.15,0:21:38.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你在干什么  -你快走\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- What are you doing? - Just go.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.11,0:21:45.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们该杀了它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We should kill it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.03,0:21:46.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-回家去  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Go home. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.38,0:21:47.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-伊妮德  -这太胡闹了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Enid. - This is bullshit.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.99,0:21:49.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它该死掉才对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It should be dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.16,0:21:52.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-放开我  -你快走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Let go. - Just leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.48,0:22:00.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不能杀它\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're not killing it.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.46,0:22:03.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你有什么毛病\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What the hell is wrong with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.40,0:22:06.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不懂\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wouldn't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.41,0:22:13.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你自己说的你不想在外面\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You don't want to be out here. You said it.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.20,0:22:15.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就回家去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So go home.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.28,0:23:21.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不许动  或许我们不会伤害你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hold still and maybe we won't hurt you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.10,0:23:22.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Sure thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.24,0:23:35.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到此为止了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is done.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.67,0:23:43.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们有子弹吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Do you even have any ammo?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.01,0:23:49.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.78,0:23:53.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,为了个卡车就要崩了我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You gonna shoot me over a truck?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.59,0:23:55.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡车里有很多食物\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}There's a lot of food on that truck.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.73,0:23:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钥匙交出来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The keys, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.75,0:23:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你们知道我并不是坏人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think you know I'm not a bad guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.47,0:24:00.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.48,0:24:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你对我们又了解些什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What do you know about us?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.04,0:24:05.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,钥匙给我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Give me the keys.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.09,0:24:10.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最后一次警告\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}This is the last time I'm asking.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.00,0:24:18.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.52,0:24:23.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们准备丢下我不管吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're gonna leave me here like this?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.44,0:24:24.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们真的打算这么做吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You're really gonna do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.36,0:24:27.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,绳结不是很紧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The knots aren't that tight.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.02,0:24:29.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该可以挣脱开的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You should be able to get free...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.66,0:24:32.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不过那时我们已经走远了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}after we're long gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.74,0:24:37.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许我们应该谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe we should talk now.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.09,0:24:37.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,免了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Nah.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.66,0:24:39.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Here.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.49,0:24:42.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,以防你口渴\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}In case you get thirsty.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.07,0:25:10.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再见  混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So long, you prick!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.21,0:25:30.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,问题还是解决了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Still worked out.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.09,0:25:34.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天依旧是个好日子\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Today still is the day.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.30,0:25:44.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看那个\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Look at that.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.41,0:25:47.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是个谷仓\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, a barn.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.13,0:25:54.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你听到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You hear that?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.59,0:26:00.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我觉得那混蛋在车顶上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I think that son of a bitch is on the roof.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.20,0:26:02.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,坐稳了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.16,0:26:22.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-妈的  -达里尔  达里尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Mother-- - Daryl! Daryl!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.24,0:27:04.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们好不容易过个好日子  混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We came to a conclusion, asshole!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.46,0:27:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能抓住他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got him!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.35,0:27:16.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来  你这小混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come here, you little shit!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.85,0:27:28.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,蹲下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Duck.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.21,0:27:33.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.62,0:27:34.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是我的枪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's my gun!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.74,0:27:36.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come here!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.11,0:28:24.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.98,0:28:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.03,0:28:28.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,概率这事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Law of averages.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.89,0:28:30.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是胡扯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}That's bullshit, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.99,0:28:34.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去看看那些车  赶紧离开这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's go check them cars, get the hell out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.16,0:28:35.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这家伙怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What about the guy?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.13,0:28:37.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What about him?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:37.60,0:28:38.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他救了你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, he helped you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.38,0:28:42.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Maybe.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.63,0:28:47.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他拿枪威胁过你吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He ever pull a weapon on you?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.75,0:28:52.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.51,0:28:54.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们把他放树上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's put him up a tree.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.95,0:29:06.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为什么还在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Why are you still here?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:07.55,0:29:08.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我很喜欢你妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I liked your mom a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.34,0:29:12.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不希望看到你死\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I really don't want you to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.38,0:29:15.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.14,0:29:17.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-回家吧  -我的家人都死了  那不是我家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Let's go home. - My family's dead. That's not home.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.93,0:29:19.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只是我住的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's just where I live.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.76,0:29:20.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不止如此\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's more than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.82,0:29:22.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,够了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey, enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.37,0:29:24.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.35,0:29:30.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你在那儿有你的生活  也许我也会有\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've got a life back there, and maybe I will, too,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.42,0:29:33.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但在我考虑那件事之前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}but before I can even think about that,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.46,0:29:35.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我得先处理别的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I need to take care of something.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.12,0:29:43.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我总得试试\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I have to try.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.63,0:29:45.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那就让我帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So let me help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.62,0:29:52.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你帮不了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.48,0:30:04.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Carl?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.32,0:30:25.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我当晚就以为我看到了她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought I saw her that night.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.56,0:30:28.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为我看到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I thought I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.24,0:30:31.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我确实看到了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.77,0:31:18.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我来  我来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I got her. I got her.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.00,0:31:38.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这就是我出来的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So that's why I was out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.78,0:32:11.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她留给我一张纸条\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She left me a note.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.96,0:32:16.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她说我依然没有迷失方向\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She said I still knew my way.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.60,0:32:21.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我从来就不知道方向在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I never knew my way.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.60,0:32:23.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爱你的家人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You loved your family?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.31,0:32:26.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.21,0:32:28.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那你就知道方向\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then you know your way.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.37,0:32:30.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是家的方向\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's home.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.35,0:32:34.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们已经死了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}They're gone.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.52,0:32:40.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我追你走过了大半个树林\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I've been out here chasing you all over the woods.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.00,0:32:44.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有家人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You've still got family,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.04,0:32:47.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你还有家\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and you've still got a home.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.70,0:32:58.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:27.08,0:33:29.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他被重重击中了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He took a pretty hard hit.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.79,0:33:31.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得让丹妮斯检查一下\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Denise needs to look him over.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.94,0:33:32.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.85,0:33:35.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会那么狠心的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wouldn't have gone through with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.15,0:33:36.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会丢下他的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wouldn't have left him.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.25,0:33:38.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会的  放在树上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I would've, right up in a tree.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.80,0:33:41.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我会的  -你不会  我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- I would've. - No. I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.70,0:33:45.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一到亚历山大  你就明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Almost as soon as we got to Alexandria, you got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.22,0:33:46.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到... 你\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You saw-- You...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.95,0:33:50.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米琼恩  格伦  你们都试图说服我\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}and Michonne, Glenn, you all tried to tell me.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.68,0:33:53.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以别嘴硬了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}So shut up.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.72,0:33:59.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我终于肯听你们的了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}'Cause I'm finally listening.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:07.39,0:34:08.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看到那颗明星了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}See that bright one?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.25,0:34:11.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对  那是北极星\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, that's the North Star.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.07,0:34:15.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,位于小熊座的尾部\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's at the end of the Little Dipper.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.97,0:34:18.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.72,0:34:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你晚上迷路了  只要找到北极星就行\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}If you get lost at night, just find that star.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.56,0:34:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天过得好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You have a good day?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.45,0:34:36.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I guess so.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.66,0:34:40.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我把她抱进去\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I'm gonna take her in.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.52,0:34:42.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡尔\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Carl.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:51.75,0:34:53.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到你做了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I saw what you did.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.91,0:34:56.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对迪安娜\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}With Deanna.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.86,0:35:03.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.25,0:35:07.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你应该丢下她或者杀了她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You should've left her or killed her.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:12.68,0:35:14.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  那太蠢了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, that's stupid.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.19,0:35:18.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不用出去的时候待在外面才是蠢呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What's stupid is you being out there when you don't have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.20,0:35:19.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也一样  你不用...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You did the same thing. You didn't--
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.74,0:35:21.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你和斯宾塞不用出去的  但你还是去了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You and Spencer didn't have to go out there, but you did.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.96,0:35:23.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-那不一样  -一样的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- That's different. - It's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.31,0:35:26.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会把她那样留在外面的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I wasn't gonna leave her out there like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.63,0:35:27.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你也不会\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wouldn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.11,0:35:30.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不会的  我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wouldn't. I know it.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:31.39,0:35:32.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不能杀掉她\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I couldn't kill her.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:32.52,0:35:35.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-为什么不能  -因为...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Why not? - Because-- be--
Dialogue: 0,0:35:36.76,0:35:37.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你可以杀掉她的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You could've killed her.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.67,0:35:39.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我不能  我不想那么做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, I couldn't. I wouldn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.60,0:35:40.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你以为在外面是玩游戏吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Were you playing some sort of game out there?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.72,0:35:42.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-难道你以为...  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Did you think that-- - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.07,0:35:43.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Then why?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.14,0:35:44.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为应该由一个爱她的人来做\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Because it should be someone who loved her,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.58,0:35:47.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她的家人  我也会为你做同样的事\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}someone who's family, and I-- I'd do it for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.47,0:35:55.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I would.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.15,0:36:01.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,过来\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.35,0:36:08.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Me, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.27,0:36:24.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}欢迎来到亚历山大安全区\N迷途者的天堂  掠夺者的地狱
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.67,0:36:42.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗  我在想...\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You know, I was thinking...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.03,0:36:44.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们出发去采石场前\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}back before we went out to the quarry.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.17,0:36:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,雷吉和皮特那事之后的早上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}The morning after Reg and Pete.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.27,0:36:51.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说我们不应该再寻找人类了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You said we shouldn't be looking for people no more.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.74,0:36:53.95,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were right.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.52,0:36:56.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:57.69,0:36:59.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我错了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I was wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.60,0:37:00.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You were right.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:29.73,0:37:31.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-抱歉吵醒你们  -他是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Sorry to wake you up. - Who is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.87,0:37:33.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  他很沉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Come on, man, he's heavy.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.24,0:37:35.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你的饮料  泡汤了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh, that thing, uh, didn't work out.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.57,0:37:37.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是这个混蛋的错  抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's this asshole's fault. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:37.32,0:37:38.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,把他放在床上\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Lay him on the bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.36,0:37:39.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  检查一下他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}All right, take a look at him.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.81,0:37:41.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他不会久留\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}He ain't staying, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.86,0:38:02.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}你受伤了  我们带你来了这里\N你很安全  保重\N瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.85,0:38:04.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,再看看吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We'll see.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.11,0:38:10.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们俩出去确实挺蠢的  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It is pretty stupid of us to go out there, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.49,0:38:11.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.29,0:38:13.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-明天再来一次  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Do it again tomorrow? - Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.64,0:38:36.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让开\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Move.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.59,0:38:38.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.75,0:38:48.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她在睡梦中练习呢\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}She's practicing in her sleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.75,0:38:52.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:56.26,0:38:57.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家真好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's good to be home.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.33,0:39:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可不是么\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Yeah, you're telling me.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.23,0:39:04.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,达里尔在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Where's Daryl?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.90,0:39:06.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在看守一个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Watching over a guy
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.05,0:39:09.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,之后会有人接替他\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}till some other guy can take over.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.36,0:39:11.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们找到了一个人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You found a guy?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.75,0:39:16.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,疯狂的一天\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Crazy day.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.68,0:39:19.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想说说吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wanna talk about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:20.51,0:39:22.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在不想\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No, not right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.05,0:39:25.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我只想放松一会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}I just want to turn my brain off for a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.07,0:39:30.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你想跟我说说你的一天吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}You wanna tell me about your day?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.80,0:39:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.62,0:39:35.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我也一样\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Same thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.10,0:39:37.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么  你也找到人了\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}What, you found a guy?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.73,0:39:39.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不是人\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Not a guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.97,0:39:50.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Oh...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.38,0:39:57.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,给你带了样东西\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Got you something.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.62,0:40:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是牙膏的替代品吗\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Is this instead of the toothpaste?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.13,0:40:08.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Mm-hmm.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.87,0:40:12.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我本来给你搞了一箱牙膏\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Well, I do have a crate of toothpaste for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.18,0:40:14.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在沉到了湖底\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}It's currently at the bottom of a lake.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.67,0:40:19.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你今天过得真刺激  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}- Oh, so you had a day. - Yeah...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:20.62,0:40:23.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都是为了你的口腔卫生\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}all on account of your dental hygiene.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.24,0:40:25.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,吃你的薄荷糖吧\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Have your mints.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.43,0:41:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Wait-- wait a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:21.84,0:41:22.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:58.88,0:42:00.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:01.18,0:42:02.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克  醒醒\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}Rick, wake up.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:07.51,0:42:08.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑\fs14}We should talk.
