Script: spscriptorium
Synch: Bardamu
::Italian Subs Addicted::
[www.italiansubs.net]
Big Ring Slammer.
Comes with posable neck-smash grip.
That's pretty kewl.
Let's see...
Cock!
The Black Jackal.
Karate Kick Panel Force and bendable neck-
Asshole! Cock!
Asshole! Shit, shit! Cock!
Ma'am, is that your son over there?
Yes, I'm sorry.
My son has Tourette's Syndrome.
Tourette's Syndrome?
It's a neurological disorder.
He-he can't control what he says.
Oh!
Shiit! Dumb shiiit!
A-alright Thomas, maybe we should go?
All right Mom- Bitch! Ass bitch!
Here, let's buy you
a nice toy to take home.
Dude, that mom is kewl.
Cockbutt! Augh... Stupid shit!
Are you talkin' to me?!
No. Cocknose!
What's your problem, kid?!
Oh, a-I'm sorry.
My... son Thomas has Tourette's Syndrome.
What?
Mom, let's just go. Shhhit!
People with Tourette's can't control
certain tics. It's it's like a sneeze.
Asshole ASSHOLE.
Wait waitwait whoa whoa whoa.
You're telling me there's an illness
that makes you blurt out obscenities?
Mom, can we just go home, please?
It's okay, Thomas. They understand.
I want tuh go!
Poor kid!
Yeah!
All right, hold on just a second here:
Are you telling me that if you have
this Tourette's Syndrome
you can say whatever you want,
all the time, and never get in trouble?
It's a neurological disorder; he can't help it.
Yeah!
I've got a golden ticket.. I've got a golden
twinkle in my eye.
Hey don't you wanna buy that toy?
I don't need the toy!
I've found something better!
'Cause I've got a golden ticket!
I've got a golden change to make my way!
It started about four days ago, Doctor,
and every day he seems to get worse.
- Puh-Pussy!... Pussy! Cock! Shit!
- Oh dear!
I was checking out
the Internet and ih,
it almost seems like his symptoms are
like those in something called
"Tour, Tourette's Syndrome"?
Tourette's Syndrome?
What is that, Mommy?
Butthole! Titties! Balls!
That doesn't seem likely.
Tourette's is a hereditary disease;
it doesn't just suddenly start.
..Cocksucker!
On the other hand, Tourette's
does often develop later in a child's life,
getting progressively worse.
Oh wuh, well that's it!
Shithead! Asshole!
Mexican sticky balls!
Oh Doctor, can you help him?
We don't know very much
about Tourette's I'm afraid.
But we will give your son
all the help we can.
But what about school, Doctor?
The teachers and the principal, they won't
understand that I can't control what I say.
Don't worry, young man.
We'll make sure everyone understands your disease
and gives you the compassion you deserve.
Ohohh, that's awesome.
Thank you. Faggot!
Shit! Butthole!
Hey Wendy. DUMB BITCH! Uh, sorry.
Titties! Cock!
Ginger retard!
Asslicker dickface!
Dude, you'd better watch it.
The principal's right over there.
Uh, Good morning, Principal Victoria.
Shitballs!
Good morning, Eric.
Did Cartman just say "shitballs" to the principal?
Huhyou didn't hear?
Well Cartman has some, mental disease
called Tourette's Syndrome or somethin'.
What?
He's the luckiest kid in the world.
If I could say "shitballs" to
the principal I'd be sooo happy.
Uh excuse me, excuse me everyone I,
I guess you might have noticed my awkward tics.
Asshole! Pussy asshole!
Ach, augh, I just want you to know
that I can't control it.
It's okay, Eric. We all understand
and we think you're very brave.
He's faking.
Excuse me everyone, I need to have
a moment alonen with my good friend Kyle?
Asscheeks!
Kyle, apparently you missed
the school assembly yesterday,
but I've been diagnosed with a
very serious mental condition.
You do not have Tourette's Syndrome, fatass!
Oh, okay, you figured me out.
Bravo, Kyle, bravo.
Don't you see how awesome this is?
It's like, a magic cloak that makes
me impervious to getting in trouble.
- Who cares about saying whatever you-?
- Of course, if you want to be Sgt Buzzkill once again,
and spoil my fun because you're jealous you
didn't think of it first, well go right ahead, Kyle.
Grrhh, whatever.
Good morning, Mr. Mackey.
Asspussy!
If I could say "asspussy"
to the counselor I would be sooo happy.
Okay, so what do we get when
we multiply a negative number-?
Dicktits!
-when we multiply a negative
number by another negative-?
Shit! Asshole!
'Scuse me.
Ih if we apply what we've just learned,
we see that all negatives can-
Spooge balls bloody vaginal belch.
You guys, don't laugh.
It makes me feel insecure about my illness.
All right kids, let's just try to focus on learning, okay?
Now all you need to remember
here is that negative numbers
Tampon! Tampon DICKshit!
Will you knock it off already?!
Kyle, don't you think I wish I could?
I'd give anything to be normal like you.
Kike!
Don't push me, asshole!
Kyle, watch your language!
If I could yell "tampon dickshit"
in the classroom I'd be sooo happy.
Principal Victoria, it's just that Eric has
become such a distraction I,
I don't think I can teach my class anymore.
I understand it's been difficult,
Mrs. Garrison, and so,
Mr. Donaldson has come
from the Tourette's Tolerance
and Understanding Foundation.
Hello Mrs. Garrison-
Ass. ASS!
I want to help your class better
understand this illness. PISS!
- No! Up yours, fatboy!
- Kyle please! I'm sorry!
Principal Victoria,
there's something you need to know!
Cartman's Tourette's isn't real! He's faking!
Faking?
You think people with Tourette's are faking?!
N-no, I'm just saying that I think-
Do you have any idea how horrible that is to say?
Ass! ASS!
We aren't "faking", young man. Trust me,
nobody wants this illness, ass. Piss!
PIISS!
That's right, Kyle.
Crap-filled vagina!
This is the kind of intolerance you teach
at this school, Principal Victoria?!
No.
This if you wouldn't mind,
I'd like to take this "bully"
to see that Tourette's is very real. Piss!
Kids, today during therapy class
we have a special visitor.
ASS!
I, I wanted him to meet all of you
so he could try to understand Tourette's
Tourette's is like a cough or a sneeze.
It isn't contagious like some people think.
A lot of people with Tourette's have different tics.
My tic...
is that I have to bend my neck and snap my fingers.
But a lot of people don't even notice it.
Aw shit! COCK!
Sometimes it can be embarrassing
to have Tourette's, but I... Boop!
I've learned I shouldn't be mad at myself.
You see? These kids
can't control their actions.
Ass! Piss iin the ass!
L-look, I was just suggesting that maybe
this one person could control what he said,
but just didn't, for fun.
Fun?
This really isn't all that fun. Brrrr!
Aw shit!
Boop!
Piss coming from my ass!
Yee-you wanna know about fun?
Going to public places knowing
you're going to make a fool of yourself.
Embarrass your parents. Aw shit!
My dad... finally couldn't take it anymore.
He... divorced my mom, s-said he'd still be around,
but I only see him at Christmastime now.
S-sh-shit! S-sh-shit!
The worst part is I know how lonely my mom is.
A lot of times I know
she'd be better off if I was dead.
Dude!
Your mom would not be better off
if you were dead, Thomas.
Even if people like Kyle here think so.
Aw, come on!
So then you apologize
for what you said before?
Ah I was just trying to...
just, just in one instance...
No. No, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Well, Mr. and Ms. Broflovski, I think your son has
learned a lot, and he appears to be honestly remorseful
for making fun of people with disabilities.
Piss. PISS!
Our son is a good kid.
He just didn't understand
Tourette's was a real disease.
Well, I think the only thing left now is
for your son to apologize to his little classmate.
Well Kyle?
I'm sorry.
Oh, what was that? I I couldn't
quite make that out, Kyle.
I'm sorry.
You're starry?
I, I don't get what you mean by that, Kyle.
You're starry because uh I don't want it?
I said I'm sorry, you piece of sh-
Oh, oh, no, don't worry about it, Kyle.
Now I understand.
I've learned to deal with intolerance.
Dumbshit douchebag!
And it means a lot that you're standing here
apologizing with your dad and lovely mother.
Fat Jew! Jew bitch!
Oh thank you Eric!
Thank you. Big-nosed kike!
Well I think we can all put this behind us now.
Piiiss out my aaass!
Yeah. Piss out your ass right onto
Kyle's mom's fat fucking Jew face!
Oh goodness, 'scuse me.
Jeez, that was a bad one.
Well, gotta run, everybody.
Got some big things in the works.
Isn't having Tourette's awesome?
Next week on Dateline NBC:
it's a Dateline special report.
I'm Chris Hansen
You probably know me from To Catch A Predator,
where we bust men looking for sex with children.
Go ahead and take a seat.
Take a seat right over there.
Oh God, Whoa no.
What are you doin' here?
I'm just' bein' stupid, I guess.
But now we're switching our focus
from pedophiles to Tourette's syndrome.
It all started when I received this touching letter
from a brave little boy in Colorado.
Dear Mr Hansen, I have Tourette's and
I want the world to understand what it's like.
Won't you do a special report on me,
so the world can learn
to ACCEPT us instead of just laugh?
Donkey Boner!!!
This Saturday on Dateline I'll
be bringing you Eric's story, live
and uncensored,
from his home in Colorado.
Livingn with Tourette's: The Eric Cartman Story.
This Saturday on Dateline NBC
Finally, my wish of going public
with my illness can come true.
Goddamn Jews!
Suck my ass barf!
Hello, Kyle. Dickhead!
What's this about you going
on live television on Saturday?!
Yes. It's all finally come to fruition.
The final cog in my... master plan.
This Saturday I will go
on national television, live.
I will say ...horrible things on the air.
Unspeakable things.
And people will call me brave.
Cartman, there are people in the world
who really have Tourette's Syndrome.
This isn't funny!
Not funny?
I have free rein to say anything I want
and you get into trouble if you try and stop me.
Care for a Scotch?
Scotch?
Kyle I've won!
No matter how you look at it!
I've managed not only to get away with saying whatever
I want at school, on the bus, at the dinner table,
but this Saturday I will actually say anything I want...
on national television.
I'm going to blast the Jews, Kyle.
I'm going to call them every name in the book,
and people wlll call it brilliant television.
They'll probably give me an Emmy.
You are not going to go on national television and
spew a bunch of hate speech about Jewish people!
I WON'T LET YOU DO IT, CARTMAN!
Then the game is on, Kyle.
It's not a game, you derelict!
And this isn't Scotch!
It's apple juice!
Do you have any idea how liberating
it is to say whatever comes to mind?
"Big titties! Buttmumch!"
There's no walls anymore! "Shit!"
Whatever enters my brain I can
just say without thinking about it.
"I wet my bed last night."
What did you say?
Uhh nuh-nothing...
You aren't gonna get away
with this you stupid asshole!
Hm. That was... weird.
We are here today
to congratulate a brave little boy.
Tonight, Eric Cartman will go on television
and become the spokesman
for Tourette's Syndrome.
Piiiss out my aaass!
The spokesman for Tourette's? Oh no...
Cock!
Thanks, everybody. Suck my balls!
You've all been so understanding
and supportive of my illness.
Jews bomber dick sneeze.
And it is because of you...
that I have the courage to go
on national television tonight.
Titty sprinkles.
If I could say "titty sprinkles" on national
television I would be sooo happy.
And I also just want to say that...
I'm making this all up!
Uh, I... I...'m making this all up to you,
for putting up with my mental disorder.
I cry at night because I don't have a dad.
What the hell is going on?
Uhit's okay, Eric.
We understand your illness, m'kay?
No hey ut what, what I meant
to say was "asslicker cumballs".
And I'm secretly in love with Patty Nelson.
I fantasize about kissing Patty Nelson!
Eewwww!
Uhuh, excuse me I, I need a toilet!
Bathroom! Bathroom!
Uh hey Eric!
Butters, do you think it's possible that you
can lose the ability to filter what you say?
I mean, if somebody got used to
saying whatever came to their mind,
could they start saying things
that they would normally never say?
Wuh who are you talking about?
Uh, my cousin.
My cousin one time
my cousin and I touched wieners.
You... you and your cousin
touched wieners?
I didn't say that YES I DID
BUT WHY? Oh! Stop it!
Excuse me! Excuse me,
I gotta go! I gotta run!
Is there a problem, sweetie?
No, no problem.
I just need to... Argh!
My cousin and I touched each other's-
I just... no I...
I just want to thank everyone for coming-
my cousin and I touched wiener-
we wiener we, weenter!
Winter is a cold time of year.
Ah, I need to be going now.
Well all right Eric.
Well good luck on Dateline tonight.
Dateline. Right.
I wet my b-AAA!
I touched my cousin's WEE-NUH!
This sure has been fun! G'bye!
Tonight, an inside look at Tourette's Syndrooome.
I'm Chris Hansen.
Ah, Mr. Hansen?
I'm afraid I can't do the show.
Why not?
My uh, my grandma just died,
so I have to go to Memphis-
That's not true. My grandma's fine.
Why don't you have a seat?
No I just need to get home.
I'm not doin' the show.
Go ahead and take a seat.
But I'm not gonna do the-
Take a seat, right over there.
What are you doing here?
I'm, I'm telling you that
I'm not doing the show?
But you are doing the show.
You don't understand!
All of a sudden, I can't control what I say.
Well of course you can't coontrol
what you say. You have Tourehhtte's.
No! My Tourette's has gotten worse!
Before I just blurted out cool stuff
about Jews being lame and stuff.
But now it's gotten really bad.
So ah I'm sorry, but I'm not doin'
the show, that's it. Goodbye.
Why don't you take a seat?
Oh, I don't wanna take a seat!
Have a seat.
No, I'm just gonna go-
Take a seat, right over there.
How does he do that?
You know, one tiiime, I was doin'
a show called "To Catch A Predator".
We almost caught this pedophile, but then he raaan
from us 'cause he didn't wanna be on Dateline.
So we tracked him down to his hoouuse.
And you know what he did?
He shot himself.
It'd be a shame if...
you didn't wanna go on Dateline.
Be a shame if we had to track you
down and you "shot" "yourself."
Live, from our satellite studio in Colorado.
This! ...is Dateline.
Tonight, an inside look at Tourette's Syndrome.
I'm Chris Hansen.
In a few minutes, you will
meet little Eric Cartman,
who wants the world
to understand his affliction.
Five minutes, kid.
Jesus Christ. How did I get myself into this?
God? Please uh, I know I screwed up.
I should have never pretended to have
Tourette's Syndrome, but see, ah I get it now.
You can't just walk around
saying whatever you want.
You gave us a filter because,
people don't wanna hear things like
"I touched penises with my cousin!"
Ahaab, ahaabuh!
And, and I learned, you especially can't
say whatever you want on national televison,
'cause, there could be kids watching.
Please, God, don't make me
embarrass myself on national television.
You... must see how this is all
somewhat your fault, right?
Please. I need a miracle.
Tango, this is Foxtrot.
Are you in position?
Copy Foxtrot. Tango in position.
Awww, shit!
You sure you don't wanna back out?
Nono, you were right.
The fat kid is faking it!
If he goes on TV, more people will think
that having Tourette's is fun.
Asshole shit!
All right, then we go with the plan.
Just like "To Catch A Predator."
The first guy is here.
This is probably HotForBoys219.
Hi, are you CuteBilly182?
Yeah. I was chatting
with you online. SHIT!
Oh God, I'm so turned on right now.
This is your house?
Your, your parents aren't home, are they?
N-no, it's cool. Go on inside.
I made brownies. SHIT!
I'm just gonna slip into something
more comf'table. COCK!
Okay. Cock! Don't take too long.
So now let's meet a child who
haaas Tourette's Syndrooome,
and who must fi-
Ho, whoa, wait a minute.
This ain't no house.
What are you doing?!
Chris Hansen?!
Oh no, it's a setup! I knew it!
Sir, why don't you take
a seat, right over there.
Now everyone's gonna know I'm a perv!
Aw, not again.
Kyle?
Surprise, fatass!
Kyle, what are you doing?
I went online posing as a boy
who would have sex with older men,
and told them to meet me here.
My plan worked perfectly!
Hey, I brought you some Wendy's.
Yeah yeah, go on in.
There's a hot tub inside. STUPID SHIT!
Score!
Oh no, it's Chris Hansen!
What the hell is going on?!
Wait a minute.
Oh God, it's Chris Hansen!
Chris Hansen!
Dateline?!
I knew it!
There aren't really brownies!
Hey! Do you have something to do with this?
Answer meee!
Stupid shit! Cock!
What?! Nobody talks to me like that!
Why don't you take a seat?
Take a seat, right over there.
Suck it! Asshole licker dickfart!
Fine, you lil- I'll, I'll tell on you!
Wow, you're the coolest kid in the world.
If I could call Chris Hansen an asshole-licking
dickfart to his face, I would be sooo happy.
You would?
Could I just like, hang out with you sometime?
Like, do your laundry maybe?
Take a look, fatass! I beat you!
You aren't going on Dateline;
what have you got to say now?!
Oh thank you! Thank you Kyle!
What?
I asked God to send someone
to help me, and you came, Kyle!
I love you man!
No ah I beat you!
You totally saved my ass, Kyle.
You must... really care about me.
See you Kyle!
I gotta get to a psychiatrist
and learn to control what I say!
I got a golden ticket! Thanks to Kyle!
I got a golden twinkle in my eye!
Aww, shit!
www.tvsubtitles.net