1
00:00:29,010 --> 00:00:37,380
你還活著

2
00:00:45,140 --> 00:00:46,280
伙計
Hey, boy.

3
00:00:50,190 --> 00:00:51,400
你沒事的
Oh, you're fine.

4
00:00:55,110 --> 00:00:56,620
你沒事
You are fine.

5
00:00:59,580 --> 00:01:00,720
過來
Hey, come here.

6
00:01:02,240 --> 00:01:05,760
你還活著
You... are alive.

7
00:01:06,070 --> 00:01:11,080
m 330 133 l 343 133 l 343 125 l 330 125 m 330 122 l 343 122 l 343 115 l 330 115 m 330 112 l 343 112 l 343 104 l 330 104 m 322 136 l 322 133 l 327 133 l 327 101 l 346 101 l 346 133 l 350 133 l 350 136 m 316 121 b 316 121 316 121 316 121 b 316 121 320 121 323 121 b 323 121 323 123 323 123 b 318 124 315 124 311 125 l 311 122 b 311 122 317 114 317 114 b 317 114 317 114 317 114 b 316 113 310 115 310 115 l 310 112 b 310 112 317 99 317 99 l 320 100 b 317 105 316 107 314 112 b 313 112 314 112 313 112 b 320 112 322 105 322 105 l 325 107 b 325 107 316 121 316 121 m 310 131 b 313 131 318 130 324 129 l 324 131 b 319 132 315 133 310 134 m 296 126 b 296 125 293 124 293 123 l 288 123 l 288 126 m 281 123 b 280 123 277 126 277 126 l 285 126 l 285 123 m 276 116 l 298 116 l 298 113 l 276 113 m 276 111 l 298 111 l 298 109 l 276 109 m 291 99 l 294 99 l 294 101 l 306 101 l 305 104 l 294 104 l 294 106 l 291 106 l 291 104 l 282 104 l 282 106 l 279 106 l 279 104 l 268 104 l 268 101 l 279 101 l 279 98 l 282 98 l 282 101 l 291 101 m 268 120 l 278 120 b 280 119 280 119 278 120 b 280 119 280 119 280 119 l 272 119 l 272 106 l 301 106 l 301 118 l 287 118 b 285 118 284 119 283 120 l 305 120 l 305 123 l 297 123 b 299 123 297 123 307 128 b 306 128 307 128 305 131 b 301 128 300 128 300 128 l 300 130 b 300 134 297 135 297 135 l 291 135 b 291 135 291 135 291 132 b 291 132 291 133 291 133 b 292 132 292 132 297 132 b 297 130 297 130 297 131 l 297 129 l 288 129 l 288 138 l 285 138 l 285 129 l 277 129 l 277 136 l 274 136 l 274 127 b 274 127 274 127 268 131 b 268 131 268 131 266 129 b 266 129 272 125 276 123 l 268 123 m 244 98 l 244 98 b 244 98 246 103 247 104 l 244 104 l 263 104 l 263 112 l 259 112 l 259 108 l 229 108 l 229 113 l 225 113 l 225 104 l 244 104 b 244 104 241 99 244 104 b 244 104 241 99 241 99 m 242 119 l 251 115 l 231 115 l 231 112 l 256 112 l 256 116 l 246 121 l 246 122 l 264 122 l 264 125 l 246 125 l 246 129 b 246 134 246 137 243 138 l 235 138 b 235 138 234 134 234 134 b 236 134 236 134 242 134 b 242 134 242 130 242 130 l 242 125 l 224 125 l 224 122 l 242 122 m 210 58 l 192 58 l 192 54 l 210 54 m 225 55 l 239 56 l 261 28 l 245 28 l 225 53 b 224 49 221 45 216 46 l 178 46 l 178 66 l 193 66 l 193 77 l 189 77 l 191 68 l 178 68 l 174 87 l 188 87 l 190 81 l 193 87 l 209 87 l 209 66 l 225 66 m 192 19 l 210 19 l 210 21 l 192 21 m 192 9 l 210 9 l 210 12 l 192 12 m 228 34 l 210 34 l 209 31 l 226 31 l 226 27 l 238 27 l 261 0 l 244 0 l 226 22 l 225 22 l 225 6 b 225 3 224 0 217 0 l 177 0 l 176 30 l 193 30 l 193 34 l 174 34 l 174 43 l 227 43 m 246 57 l 226 79 l 224 69 l 212 69 l 215 85 l 223 84 l 222 87 l 238 87 l 261 57 m 336 77 l 336 59 l 329 58 l 329 14 l 315 14 l 315 49 l 291 87 l 306 87 l 324 58 l 324 87 l 346 87 l 350 77 m 310 10 l 334 10 l 335 56 l 345 56 l 345 6 b 345 4 343 0 339 0 l 298 0 l 298 56 l 310 56 m 295 36 l 286 36 l 295 21 l 295 10 l 288 10 l 284 0 l 267 0 l 272 10 l 261 10 l 261 20 l 279 20 l 260 51 l 270 51 l 270 86 l 283 87 l 283 42 l 285 39 l 287 64 l 297 64 m 155 87 l 129 35 l 104 87 l 84 87 l 128 0 l 146 0 l 132 30 l 146 30 l 174 87 m 66 87 l 39 35 l 14 87 l -5 87 l 38 0 l 56 0 l 42 30 l 56 30 l 84 87 m 203 138 l 199 138 l 190 111 l 194 111 l 201 133 b 201 134 201 134 201 133 l 209 111 l 213 111 m 188 135 l 188 137 b 183 137 188 137 183 137 b 183 137 179 138 179 134 l 179 115 l 176 115 l 176 111 l 179 111 l 179 104 l 183 103 l 183 111 l 187 111 l 187 115 l 183 115 l 183 135 b 183 135 183 135 188 135 m 166 132 l 171 132 l 171 137 l 166 137 m 154 111 l 158 111 l 158 137 l 155 137 l 155 133 b 153 136 151 138 145 137 b 143 138 139 137 136 132 l 136 111 l 140 111 l 140 127 b 140 131 139 134 146 135 b 151 135 153 132 154 128 m 110 134 l 132 134 l 132 137 l 104 137 l 104 135 l 126 105 l 107 105 l 107 102 l 131 102 l 131 105 m 96 111 l 100 111 l 100 137 l 97 137 l 97 133 b 94 135 93 138 88 138 b 85 138 81 136 79 130 l 79 111 l 83 111 l 83 130 b 84 133 86 135 89 135 b 94 135 97 130 96 123 m 69 107 l 57 137 l 54 137 l 42 107 l 42 137 l 38 137 l 38 102 l 43 102 l 56 132 l 67 102 l 73 102 l 73 137 l 69 137 m 27 111 l 31 111 l 31 137 l 27 137 m 27 102 l 31 102 l 31 106 l 27 106 m 0 135 l 23 135 l 23 137 l -5 137 l -5 135 l 17 105 l -3 105 l -3 102 l 22 102 l 22 104

8
00:01:06,070 --> 00:01:11,080
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

9
00:01:06,070 --> 00:01:11,080
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

10
00:01:06,070 --> 00:01:11,080
m 195 227 l 228 227 l 149 147 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 180 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 l 163 71 m 134 164 l 195 227 l 228 227 l 150 148 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 177 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147

11
00:01:07,070 --> 00:01:11,080
僅供學習 禁止用于任何商業盈利行為
更多影視更新
請登陸www.ZiMuZu.tv

12
00:01:07,070 --> 00:01:11,080
■

13
00:01:07,070 --> 00:01:11,080
原創翻譯  雙語字幕

14
00:01:11,070 --> 00:01:16,070
翻譯：冰藍 Reginamoon 33來了 CS小明漫畫家

15
00:01:11,080 --> 00:01:46,070
■

16
00:01:11,080 --> 00:01:36,080
m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

17
00:01:11,080 --> 00:01:36,080
m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

18
00:01:11,080 --> 00:01:36,080
m 195 227 l 228 227 l 149 147 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 180 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147 l 163 71 m 134 164 l 195 227 l 228 227 l 150 148 m 149 86 l 134 100 l 241 210 l 241 177 m 195 71 l 89 180 l 89 210 l 89 210 l 225 71 m 134 71 l 89 117 l 89 147

19
00:01:16,070 --> 00:01:21,070
翻譯：自然卷  艾瑞卡 蘑菇 小十三 君君 送小孩

20
00:01:21,070 --> 00:01:26,070
校對：冰藍 君君 送小孩

21
00:01:34,370 --> 00:01:39,370
時間軸：濤濤 加森 吉吉

22
00:01:39,370 --> 00:01:44,370
后期：吉吉  拉圖   總監：塞滿了的送小孩

23
00:02:01,020 --> 00:02:03,400
格倫還沒回來  我得陪著瑪姬
Glenn's still not back. I need to be there for Maggie.

24
00:02:03,400 --> 00:02:05,630
-我說了不  -卡爾
- I said no. - Carl.

25
00:02:05,630 --> 00:02:07,370
你之前弄錯了
Look, you were wrong before.

26
00:02:07,370 --> 00:02:09,140
這地方不大  可以保護
This place isn't too big to protect.

27
00:02:09,140 --> 00:02:11,620
你得留下防守
And you need to stay back and help protect it.

28
00:02:11,620 --> 00:02:13,180
這里準備好了
This place is ready.

29
00:02:13,180 --> 00:02:15,610
我們大部分人都訓練過了  你知道的
Most of us have been trained, you know that.

30
00:02:15,620 --> 00:02:18,000
如果你擔心襲擊  你根本不會走
If you were worried about an attack, you wouldn't be leaving.

31
00:02:18,000 --> 00:02:19,940
你知道山頂寨有多遠嗎
You know how far the Hilltop is?

32
00:02:19,940 --> 00:02:21,600
你知道可能發生什么嗎
You know what could happen?

33
00:02:23,390 --> 00:02:25,340
救世軍就在外面
Those Saviors are out there.

34
00:02:26,090 --> 00:02:28,180
你知道他們對丹妮斯做了什么
You know what they did to Denise,

35
00:02:28,180 --> 00:02:32,060
他們想對瑪姬和卡蘿爾做什么
what they tried to do with Maggie and Carol,

36
00:02:32,060 --> 00:02:35,130
還有達里爾  羅西塔和尤金
to Daryl, to Rosita, to Eugene.

37
00:02:36,970 --> 00:02:39,010
你不能碰上這種事  好嗎
That's not happening to you, all right?

38
00:02:39,010 --> 00:02:40,340
我不允許
I'm not gonna let it.

39
00:02:53,060 --> 00:02:54,220
有什么變化嗎
Any change?

40
00:02:54,670 --> 00:02:56,140
她的情況在惡化
She's getting worse.

41
00:02:56,140 --> 00:02:57,510
車子選得不錯
Good call on the transport.

42
00:02:57,510 --> 00:02:59,190
我覺得她會更舒服
Well, I figured she'd be more comfortable.

43
00:02:59,190 --> 00:03:01,230
也意味著能坐更多人
It also means you got room for more.

44
00:03:01,670 --> 00:03:04,460
他們在外面  所以我要跟你去
They're out there, so I'm gonna be there with you.

45
00:03:06,000 --> 00:03:06,950
我們要去
We are.

46
00:03:07,760 --> 00:03:08,780
買一送一
Package deal.

47
00:03:11,330 --> 00:03:12,710
我也是送的
Uh, what she said.

48
00:03:17,450 --> 00:03:19,250
你想撞到他們  對嗎
You want to run into them, right?

49
00:03:22,440 --> 00:03:24,060
你希望他們會出現
You hope they show up.

50
00:03:27,230 --> 00:03:30,890
天啊  重點是讓瑪姬看醫生  不是...
Jesus, this is about getting Maggie to a doctor, not about...

51
00:03:32,920 --> 00:03:34,000
去你的  我要去
Screw you, I'm going.

52
00:03:34,000 --> 00:03:36,410
伊妮德  別  等等
Enid, stop. Just wait.

53
00:03:37,600 --> 00:03:39,810
聽著  路途遙遠  而你剛...
Look, it's a long trip, and you're just getting over--

54
00:03:39,810 --> 00:03:41,270
這只是表面擦傷
It's a superficial graze,

55
00:03:41,270 --> 00:03:42,060
蛋白質在結合
proteins are binding,

56
00:03:42,060 --> 00:03:43,840
而且我們得討論彈藥的生產
plus we need to discuss ammunition production

57
00:03:43,840 --> 00:03:45,780
和制造  所以走吧
and manufacture, so let's roll.

58
00:03:46,630 --> 00:03:49,580
我已經試過了  他得寸進尺
I already tried. Give him an inch, he's taking a mile.

59
00:03:49,580 --> 00:03:51,180
我只要求你給我點時間
I'm only asking for 23, give or take,

60
00:03:51,180 --> 00:03:52,570
根據路線來定
depending on the route.

61
00:03:52,950 --> 00:03:55,060
我知道我能幫忙
I know I can be of some help.

62
00:03:55,060 --> 00:03:56,980
就是此時此刻了
Now's the time and here's the place.

63
00:03:57,500 --> 00:03:58,630
別忽視我
Don't shine me.

64
00:03:59,120 --> 00:04:01,390
我來做你的軍師  我絕對會的
I'll be your anchorman. Yes, I damn will.

65
00:04:16,070 --> 00:04:17,300
為什么是這種表情
Why the face?

66
00:04:18,540 --> 00:04:20,390
希望你別怪罪我們
I hope you're not putting this on us.

67
00:04:21,760 --> 00:04:24,710
我們給你們指了明路
I mean, we showed your people the way forward.

68
00:04:24,710 --> 00:04:26,260
給你們定了規矩
We gave you rules.

69
00:04:26,550 --> 00:04:29,230
你們違反了規矩就得死
You broke the rules, so folks had to die.

70
00:04:30,620 --> 00:04:31,990
開第一槍的人
The one who fired the first shot,

71
00:04:32,000 --> 00:04:34,630
我們吊死了他  以儆效尤
we strung him up to make an example of him.

72
00:04:35,110 --> 00:04:36,680
事情本可以就此平息
It could've stopped there.

73
00:04:37,250 --> 00:04:40,350
但你們還是不聽
But you people still didn't listen.

74
00:04:41,320 --> 00:04:43,960
想抵抗我們
You wanted to fight us.

75
00:04:44,570 --> 00:04:47,570
所以只能這樣了
So this is how it has to be.

76
00:04:48,680 --> 00:04:50,080
別攔我
Get out of my way.

77
00:04:50,440 --> 00:04:51,380
卡爾
Carl!

78
00:04:54,070 --> 00:04:55,880
去櫥柜里拿幾把手槍吧
Just grab some pistols from the closet.

79
00:04:55,880 --> 00:04:57,740
但得快點  馬上就得出發了
But hurry. We've gotta go now.

80
00:05:10,350 --> 00:05:11,260
卡爾
Carl!

81
00:05:12,940 --> 00:05:13,730
該死的
Damn it!

82
00:05:13,730 --> 00:05:15,310
求你了  求你了
Please, please.

83
00:05:15,310 --> 00:05:17,520
不  不要  求你了  不要
No, no, please-- Oh! No!

84
00:05:18,300 --> 00:05:20,390
別打了  求你了
Please, don't. Oh! Please.

85
00:05:22,560 --> 00:05:23,340
求你了
Please!

86
00:05:23,350 --> 00:05:26,080
卡爾  卡爾
Carl! Carl!

87
00:05:30,420 --> 00:05:32,230
你要是回不來了怎么辦
What happens if you don't come back?

88
00:05:34,200 --> 00:05:36,140
我要怎樣繼續撐下去
How am I supposed to live with that?

89
00:05:36,140 --> 00:05:37,870
我到底該怎么辦啊
What the hell am I supposed to do?

90
00:05:41,040 --> 00:05:42,700
無論如何都要活下去[JSS]
Just survive somehow.

91
00:05:47,730 --> 00:05:49,690
我們做好保護這里的準備了
We're ready to protect this place

92
00:05:49,690 --> 00:05:51,090
而救世軍清楚這一點
and the Saviors know it.

93
00:05:51,560 --> 00:05:52,940
所以他們才會抓尤金
That's why they grabbed Eugene.

94
00:05:52,940 --> 00:05:55,450
聽著  這事沒有商量的余地
Look, it's not up for discussion.

95
00:05:57,520 --> 00:05:59,140
那你只能沖著我臉上來一拳
Then you're just gonna have to punch me in the face

96
00:05:59,140 --> 00:06:00,490
再把我綁起來一次
and tie me up again.

97
00:06:01,580 --> 00:06:03,330
因為只有那樣才能阻止我
'Cause that's what it's gonna take to stop me.

98
00:06:08,880 --> 00:06:09,880
上車吧
Go on.

99
00:06:16,460 --> 00:06:19,780
每個崗哨24小時都有人輪班
We have 24-hour shifts set up on each of the watchtowers,

100
00:06:19,780 --> 00:06:22,580
每個站崗的人都全副武裝  做好了準備
each one of them fully supplied and ready.

101
00:06:22,580 --> 00:06:23,810
萬一這里失守了
In the case that we're incurred upon,

102
00:06:23,810 --> 00:06:25,010
我們安排好了司機
we have drivers assigned,

103
00:06:25,010 --> 00:06:26,660
撤離以及牽制計劃
evacuation and distraction,

104
00:06:26,660 --> 00:06:28,460
集合點也商量好了
and the rendezvous we discussed.

105
00:06:29,390 --> 00:06:31,220
無論出現什么緊急情況
In the event of any emergency,

106
00:06:32,000 --> 00:06:34,010
我的首要任務都是保護朱迪斯
my first priority is Judith.

107
00:06:34,710 --> 00:06:36,010
我不會辜負你的
I will not fail you.

108
00:06:38,150 --> 00:06:41,350
你放心讓我負責亞歷山大的守衛嗎
Are you comfortable leaving me in charge of Alexandria's defense?

109
00:06:49,440 --> 00:06:50,450
放心
Yes.

110
00:06:51,800 --> 00:06:52,780
瑞克
Hey, Rick.

111
00:06:54,220 --> 00:06:56,280
假如救世軍真的攻過來了...
If the Saviors do show up...

112
00:06:57,970 --> 00:06:58,680
我也不知道
I don't know,

113
00:06:58,680 --> 00:07:00,810
我在想  假如尚有余地的話
I'm thinking, if it's not too late,

114
00:07:01,430 --> 00:07:03,400
我們要不要試圖和他們談判
should we try and make some kind of deal?

115
00:07:04,260 --> 00:07:05,750
讓他們等我回來
Tell them to wait for me.

116
00:07:06,530 --> 00:07:08,080
我跟他們好好談
I got a deal for them.

117
00:07:08,880 --> 00:07:09,870
出發吧
Let's go.

118
00:08:01,200 --> 00:08:02,090
卡蘿爾
Carol?

119
00:08:11,020 --> 00:08:12,650
我告訴過你別來了
I told you not to come.

120
00:08:13,810 --> 00:08:16,130
好像我會聽你的一樣
And I'm gonna start listening to you real soon.

121
00:08:22,260 --> 00:08:23,360
來  我看看
Here, let me see.

122
00:08:56,270 --> 00:08:57,330
這是做什么
What is this?

123
00:08:58,380 --> 00:09:02,550
這是我們準備拿你殺雞儆猴
This is us about to make an example out of you.

124
00:09:02,790 --> 00:09:04,010
給誰看
To who?

125
00:09:04,010 --> 00:09:05,130
我的人...
My people--

126
00:09:05,680 --> 00:09:07,590
圖書館里的所有人都死了
everyone at the library, they're dead.

127
00:10:00,480 --> 00:10:04,690
本藍光版外掛字幕由  風吹來的那片云  用WEB版調軸

128
00:10:00,480 --> 00:10:04,690
行尸走肉
『第六季  第十六集 本季終』

129
00:10:37,880 --> 00:10:39,140
我們會到的
We're gonna get there.

130
00:10:41,080 --> 00:10:42,840
山頂寨的醫生
The doctor at the Hilltop,

131
00:10:43,950 --> 00:10:45,670
他會讓你好轉的
he's gonna make things better.

132
00:10:55,070 --> 00:10:56,040
你怎么知道
How do you know?

133
00:10:57,260 --> 00:11:01,030
我們所經歷的一切  都是一起挺過來的
Everything we've done, we've done together.

134
00:11:02,070 --> 00:11:05,130
我們一起來到這里  如今大家也都還在
We got here together and we're still here.

135
00:11:07,800 --> 00:11:10,150
發生了許多事  但我們總能解決
Things have happened, but it's always worked out for us

136
00:11:10,150 --> 00:11:13,140
因為我們一直同舟共濟
'cause it's always been all of us.

137
00:11:13,140 --> 00:11:14,440
所以我知道
That's how I know.

138
00:11:17,580 --> 00:11:19,580
只要我們在一起
'Cause as long as it's all of us,

139
00:11:20,360 --> 00:11:22,190
就能戰勝一切
we can do anything.

140
00:11:43,640 --> 00:11:44,930
是行尸
It's a walker.

141
00:11:46,600 --> 00:11:47,920
它很難搞
It's hard to get.

142
00:11:48,160 --> 00:11:51,660
我本打算去殺它  但流血太多了
I was going to, but I was too busy bleeding.

143
00:11:56,200 --> 00:11:58,600
按住傷口會好些  但還是需要縫針
Pressure should help, but you need stitches,

144
00:11:59,130 --> 00:12:02,030
要用抗生素才不會感染
antibiotics to make sure you don't get an infection.

145
00:12:08,320 --> 00:12:10,030
馬上要天黑了
Be dark in a few hours.

146
00:12:11,770 --> 00:12:14,360
我四處檢查一下  確保能安全過夜
I'll walk the camp, make sure we're safe for the night.

147
00:12:15,510 --> 00:12:18,590
天一亮我們就往回走
And at dawn, we will head back,

148
00:12:18,590 --> 00:12:19,850
找人幫你縫針
get you some help.

149
00:12:21,110 --> 00:12:22,040
好嗎
Okay?

150
00:12:25,160 --> 00:12:26,100
不
No.

151
00:12:48,300 --> 00:12:49,730
他娘的
What the bitch?

152
00:12:57,780 --> 00:12:58,690
怎么了
What?

153
00:12:59,290 --> 00:13:00,470
有敵人
Enemy close.

154
00:13:08,120 --> 00:13:09,220
要上嗎
We doing this?

155
00:13:11,100 --> 00:13:12,060
不
No.

156
00:13:45,800 --> 00:13:49,560
這個人屬于一個不聽話的團隊
He's someone who was with a whole lot of someones who didn't listen.

157
00:13:53,790 --> 00:13:55,200
我們可以談交易
We can make a deal

158
00:13:56,250 --> 00:13:59,250
就在這兒  就現在
right here, right now.

159
00:13:59,250 --> 00:14:01,890
沒錯  是可以
That's right, we can.

160
00:14:03,430 --> 00:14:05,060
把所有東西都交出來
Give us all your stuff.

161
00:14:05,840 --> 00:14:07,300
我們可能得殺你們一個人
We'll probably have to kill one of you.

162
00:14:07,300 --> 00:14:08,700
這是規矩沒辦法
That's just the way it is,

163
00:14:08,700 --> 00:14:12,540
但之后我們可以開始談
but then we can start moving forward on business.

164
00:14:12,540 --> 00:14:14,830
只要你們乖乖聽話
All you have to do is listen.

165
00:14:16,710 --> 00:14:18,010
是啊...
Yeah...

166
00:14:21,020 --> 00:14:23,520
你的條件我們不接受
that deal's not gonna work for us.

167
00:14:24,630 --> 00:14:27,480
其實我還打算讓你們把東西都交出來
Fact is, I was about to ask for all of your stuff,

168
00:14:27,480 --> 00:14:30,090
但我不想殺你們中任何一人
only I'm thinking I don't have to kill any of you.

169
00:14:32,270 --> 00:14:34,660
不想再殺了
Any more of you.

170
00:15:01,240 --> 00:15:05,100
抱歉  必須按我說的辦
Sorry, my deal is the only deal.

171
00:15:06,040 --> 00:15:07,510
不講價
We don't negotiate.

172
00:15:12,430 --> 00:15:14,410
那我和我的人這就走
Me and my people are leaving.

173
00:15:18,670 --> 00:15:19,890
好吧  朋友
Okay, friend.

174
00:15:20,960 --> 00:15:23,510
去你們的目的地還不容易嗎
Plenty of ways to get to where you're going.

175
00:15:31,760 --> 00:15:34,380
你想讓今天變成你的死期嗎
You want to make today your last day on Earth?

176
00:15:37,230 --> 00:15:38,240
不想
No,

177
00:15:38,770 --> 00:15:41,140
但你提到了也好
but that is a good thing to bring up.

178
00:15:43,200 --> 00:15:44,380
想想吧
Think about it.

179
00:15:45,930 --> 00:15:48,470
萬一今天是你的死期呢
What if it's the last day on Earth for you?

180
00:15:50,160 --> 00:15:51,630
你所愛的人的死期
For someone you love?

181
00:15:52,420 --> 00:15:53,780
萬一真是這樣呢
What if that's true?

182
00:15:57,380 --> 00:16:01,040
或許你該對車上的人更好些
Maybe you should be extra nice to those people in that RV,

183
00:16:01,040 --> 00:16:02,430
因為誰知道呢...
'cause you never know...

184
00:16:03,370 --> 00:16:04,620
說沒就沒了
Just like that.

185
00:16:07,390 --> 00:16:08,920
對彼此好一點
Be kind to each other.

186
00:16:10,480 --> 00:16:11,700
就像你說的...
Like you said...

187
00:16:13,680 --> 00:16:15,620
把今天當成最后一天來過
like it was your last day on Earth.

188
00:16:21,100 --> 00:16:22,630
你也是
You do the same.

189
00:17:31,010 --> 00:17:33,360
你為什么不留在家里守著
Why didn't you stay back and help guard the place?

190
00:17:37,560 --> 00:17:38,620
我欠她的
I owe her.

191
00:17:41,630 --> 00:17:42,810
那你為什么來
Why did you come?

192
00:17:46,220 --> 00:17:47,350
我欠他們的
I owe them.

193
00:17:52,200 --> 00:17:54,150
羅格朗路比較近
Logrun Road's a straight shot.

194
00:17:54,150 --> 00:17:55,610
我們需要能見度
We want visibility.

195
00:17:59,800 --> 00:18:01,700
這里  希爾頓路符合條件
There, you got it on Shelton.

196
00:18:02,410 --> 00:18:05,190
高爾夫球場  鄉村俱樂部  坡地地形
Golf course, country clubs, sloping terrain.

197
00:18:05,190 --> 00:18:07,920
不會中埋伏  很遠就能發現敵人
No bum rush from the bogeyman. We'd see them from a good piece.

198
00:18:08,330 --> 00:18:09,780
這樣會多走三分之一的路
It is a longer trip by a third,

199
00:18:09,780 --> 00:18:13,550
但是周圍一覽無余  比較安全
but we'd get the scenic safety of clear-cut dingles and glens.

200
00:18:16,570 --> 00:18:18,220
你是認真的嗎
You're being serious, right?

201
00:18:18,220 --> 00:18:19,880
比惡疾還真
As coronary thrombosis.

202
00:18:20,760 --> 00:18:22,340
-選好路線了嗎  -是的
- You got a route? - Yeah.

203
00:18:25,140 --> 00:18:26,130
出發吧
Let's go.

204
00:18:45,610 --> 00:18:46,940
不只我一個人
Wasn't just me.

205
00:18:48,730 --> 00:18:50,380
瑞克也出來找你了
Rick came looking, too.

206
00:18:52,370 --> 00:18:55,210
達里爾  還有其他人
Daryl, some of the others...

207
00:18:57,040 --> 00:18:58,120
他們原本也會來的
They would've.

208
00:18:59,400 --> 00:19:01,860
他們在知道你的事之前就出去了
They were gone before they even knew about you.

209
00:19:02,770 --> 00:19:03,770
出去了
Gone?

210
00:19:03,770 --> 00:19:05,650
我們回去時  他們也該回去了
They'll be back by the time we are.

211
00:19:06,260 --> 00:19:09,120
也許已經回去了  等消息呢
Probably back already, wondering.

212
00:19:09,730 --> 00:19:11,770
你以為我是在胡鬧嗎
You think I'm being dramatic here?

213
00:19:14,510 --> 00:19:16,000
你真以為你找到這里
Do you really think you could just come here

214
00:19:16,000 --> 00:19:18,590
說讓我回去  事情就解決了嗎
and tell me to come back and that's how it'll go?

215
00:19:22,150 --> 00:19:23,740
他們  你的伙伴
Those people, your people,

216
00:19:26,150 --> 00:19:27,340
他們很在意你
they care about you.

217
00:19:27,340 --> 00:19:31,030
這我知道  我也很在意他們
I know they do. And I care about them.

218
00:19:31,030 --> 00:19:32,350
所以我才不能回去
That's why I can't be there.

219
00:19:32,350 --> 00:19:34,010
所以你才必須回去
That's why you have to be there.

220
00:19:38,140 --> 00:19:40,280
你真的不懂嗎
Do you really just not get it?

221
00:19:43,660 --> 00:19:45,610
在經歷了這么多事之后
After everything that's happened.

222
00:19:51,220 --> 00:19:54,540
如果你有在意的人  就會想保護他們
If you care about people, there are people to protect,

223
00:19:54,550 --> 00:19:58,070
為他們而殺戮
there are people that you will kill for.

224
00:19:59,630 --> 00:20:01,360
如果你不想殺戮
If you don't want to kill...

225
00:20:03,600 --> 00:20:05,410
或不能再殺戮下去
or if you can't...

226
00:20:07,250 --> 00:20:09,170
那就必須離開他們
then you have to get away from them.

227
00:20:10,320 --> 00:20:11,890
兩者不可兼得
You do not get both.

228
00:20:11,890 --> 00:20:13,980
你應該懂的
You...you should know that.

229
00:20:15,630 --> 00:20:17,430
不  人才是最重要的
No, everything's about people.

230
00:20:19,280 --> 00:20:21,490
沒了人的人生一文不值
Everything in this life that's worth a damn,

231
00:20:21,490 --> 00:20:22,670
這就是我所知道的
that's what I know.

232
00:20:26,420 --> 00:20:27,930
你獨自出走
And out here on your own...

233
00:20:30,720 --> 00:20:31,780
必死無疑
you'll die.

234
00:20:34,290 --> 00:20:35,250
那就讓我死吧
Then let me die.

235
00:20:35,250 --> 00:20:36,680
不  我不能那么做
No, I can't do that.

236
00:20:38,490 --> 00:20:40,630
這可不是你說了算  快走吧
It's not your decision. Just go.

237
00:20:43,030 --> 00:20:44,510
我不會離開你的
I'm not leaving you.

238
00:20:47,370 --> 00:20:49,180
我讓你走
I said go.

239
00:21:01,500 --> 00:21:02,740
求你了  走吧
Please, just go.

240
00:21:11,530 --> 00:21:15,430
如果你有在意的人
If you care about anyone...

241
00:21:17,660 --> 00:21:21,080
那就有代價  摩根  你要付出代價的
There is a price, Morgan, and you're gonna pay it.

242
00:21:22,840 --> 00:21:25,220
我付過  今后付不起了
I have, and I can't anymore.

243
00:21:48,320 --> 00:21:49,300
你覺得我們能做到嗎
Think we could do it?

244
00:21:50,710 --> 00:21:51,480
什么事
What?

245
00:21:53,330 --> 00:21:56,610
格倫和瑪姬做的事
What they did, Glenn and Maggie?

246
00:22:01,880 --> 00:22:04,100
只想問問你能做到嗎
Just asking if you could do that.

247
00:22:06,960 --> 00:22:08,770
如果你在做那樣的大事
If you're doing something as big as that...

248
00:22:11,750 --> 00:22:12,800
如果那就是生活
if that's living.

249
00:22:16,000 --> 00:22:16,850
你能嗎
Could you?

250
00:22:21,850 --> 00:22:22,690
能
Yeah.

251
00:22:25,690 --> 00:22:26,650
我能
I could.

252
00:22:31,240 --> 00:22:32,100
就現在
Now.

253
00:22:45,980 --> 00:22:47,160
就想讓你知道
Just so you know.

254
00:22:54,190 --> 00:22:55,350
賤瘋子
Bitch nuts.

255
00:23:09,330 --> 00:23:10,750
我們要抵抗嗎
We making our stand?

256
00:23:14,090 --> 00:23:16,520
是的  了結他們
Yeah, we end it.

257
00:23:20,220 --> 00:23:22,570
不  現在不要
No, not now.

258
00:23:23,220 --> 00:23:25,300
他們是以逸待勞  早做好了準備
They've been waiting. They're ready.

259
00:23:25,650 --> 00:23:27,130
我們一個人開車的情況下
With one of us behind the wheel,

260
00:23:27,130 --> 00:23:30,320
是5對16
that's five on 16.

261
00:23:31,840 --> 00:23:34,460
我們要按對我們有利的方法來
We're gonna play it our way, how we want it.

262
00:23:35,810 --> 00:23:36,640
對吧
Right?

263
00:23:38,690 --> 00:23:39,490
對
Right.

264
00:23:42,370 --> 00:23:43,650
好  慢點退
All right, go slow.

265
00:26:12,580 --> 00:26:13,350
卡蘿爾
Carol?

266
00:26:24,250 --> 00:26:25,170
卡蘿爾
Carol?

267
00:26:29,740 --> 00:26:30,540
卡蘿爾
Carol?

268
00:26:48,140 --> 00:26:48,980
走吧
Let's go.

269
00:27:15,750 --> 00:27:17,260
還有多少油
How are we on gas?

270
00:27:17,640 --> 00:27:18,800
一半
Half a tank.

271
00:27:19,230 --> 00:27:21,270
走之前我還多裝了幾罐
I pulled some more cans before we left.

272
00:27:21,360 --> 00:27:23,920
剛剛那些不是第一次攔路的人
Those weren't the same men who blocked the road the first time.

273
00:27:24,690 --> 00:27:27,080
同樣的裝備  不同的戰士
Same outfit, different soldiers.

274
00:27:29,880 --> 00:27:31,100
他們人多
They got numbers.

275
00:27:32,740 --> 00:27:35,330
我們繼續開  送她到那里
We keep driving, we get her there.

276
00:27:36,230 --> 00:27:37,120
肯定會到的
We will.

277
00:27:37,920 --> 00:27:40,880
就算不得不滅掉他們所有人  也要送到
If we have to shove each and every one of them up their own asses.

278
00:27:58,180 --> 00:27:59,710
我們不能開過去
We can't go through it.

279
00:28:00,180 --> 00:28:01,980
不能拿房車冒險
Can't risk the RV.

280
00:28:02,540 --> 00:28:04,880
你坐在駕駛座上  以防萬一
You stay behind the wheel, just in case.

281
00:28:07,790 --> 00:28:08,760
我們來開路
We'll clear it.

282
00:28:33,140 --> 00:28:36,220
讓它們這樣手拉手要很多人才能完成
Putting together a red rover like that takes people.

283
00:28:38,770 --> 00:28:39,800
很多很多人
A lot of them.

284
00:28:53,860 --> 00:28:55,500
來吧  動手吧
Come on, let's do this.

285
00:28:56,050 --> 00:28:56,890
爸
Dad.

286
00:28:58,120 --> 00:28:59,400
那是米瓊恩的
That's Michonne's.

287
00:29:11,250 --> 00:29:12,600
那是達里爾的
That's Daryl's.

288
00:29:49,510 --> 00:29:52,190
回房車  快
Get back to the RV! Go!

289
00:30:13,110 --> 00:30:14,310
發動
Start it up!

290
00:30:49,610 --> 00:30:50,680
那什么聲音
What's that sound?

291
00:30:51,350 --> 00:30:53,080
車底盤可能中彈了
Undercarriage could've caught a bullet.

292
00:30:53,080 --> 00:30:55,200
或者是變速器出問題了  也可能沒事
Or could be transmission. It could be nothing.

293
00:30:56,590 --> 00:30:58,650
他們剛剛是朝我們的腳開槍
They were firing at our feet.

294
00:31:00,810 --> 00:31:02,720
他們封住了路  但并沒有想攔住我們
They blocked the road, but they weren't trying to stop us.

295
00:31:02,720 --> 00:31:05,240
他們希望我們走這個方向
They want us in this direction.

296
00:31:05,800 --> 00:31:07,330
巴頓路是向北的
Barton Road takes us north,

297
00:31:07,330 --> 00:31:08,850
但他們得知道我們想去北面
but they gotta know we wanna go north.

298
00:31:08,850 --> 00:31:09,730
走米多斯路
Meadows.

299
00:31:09,910 --> 00:31:10,940
稍微偏東一點
Could take us east a piece,

300
00:31:10,940 --> 00:31:12,870
但我們可以繞回到梅休路
but we can get back on track on Mayhew.

301
00:31:12,870 --> 00:31:13,760
我們還剩下三分之一的油
We're down to a third of a tank.

302
00:31:13,760 --> 00:31:15,290
到下一站我們可以加油
We could top off at the next stop,

303
00:31:15,290 --> 00:31:17,170
-但之后就沒油了  -好
- but no refills after that. - All right.

304
00:31:19,110 --> 00:31:20,560
她在發燒
She's burning up.

305
00:31:31,520 --> 00:31:32,450
瑞克
Rick.

306
00:31:49,560 --> 00:31:50,620
調頭
Go back.

307
00:31:52,540 --> 00:31:53,390
去哪
Where?

308
00:32:46,020 --> 00:32:46,940
走
Come on.

309
00:33:40,230 --> 00:33:42,390
不要  走開
No, get away.

310
00:34:15,880 --> 00:34:16,580
不
No.

311
00:34:30,220 --> 00:34:33,270
呼吸變得越來越困難
Each breath is getting harder.

312
00:34:35,020 --> 00:34:36,990
我估計也快不行了
I probably don't have too many more in me.

313
00:34:39,510 --> 00:34:41,500
所以我要好好利用每一口呼吸
So I'm gonna make each one count.

314
00:34:43,340 --> 00:34:45,100
接下來會這樣
So, here's how it's gonna go.

315
00:34:47,230 --> 00:34:52,200
你躺在那  我會看著你慢慢死去
You're gonna lie there and I'm gonna watch you die slow,

316
00:34:52,300 --> 00:34:55,040
就像之前在公路上我的朋友們那樣
just like my friends did back on that road.

317
00:34:56,750 --> 00:34:58,130
我也會這樣
Just like I'm gonna.

318
00:35:00,310 --> 00:35:02,700
看看誰會贏  賤人
Let's see who wins, bitch.

319
00:35:09,940 --> 00:35:11,110
看到了嗎
You see that?

320
00:35:11,920 --> 00:35:13,860
這樣開頭不錯吧
That's a pretty good start, huh?

321
00:35:39,510 --> 00:35:40,850
我們快到了嗎
Are we close?

322
00:35:41,140 --> 00:35:43,520
是的  馬上就到了
Yeah, we're-- we're getting there.

323
00:35:44,630 --> 00:35:47,550
剛才  我聽到了槍聲
Were there-- I heard shots.

324
00:35:48,140 --> 00:35:51,570
是的  是救世軍  不過他們都走了
Yeah, the Saviors, but they're gone.

325
00:35:52,180 --> 00:35:53,040
是我們走了
We are.

326
00:35:53,630 --> 00:35:54,970
我們會把你送到的
We're gonna get you there.

327
00:35:57,220 --> 00:35:58,150
我知道
I know.

328
00:35:59,920 --> 00:36:01,420
你會沒事的
You're gonna be okay.

329
00:36:02,050 --> 00:36:03,510
孩子會沒事的
The baby's gonna be okay.

330
00:36:03,510 --> 00:36:05,890
現在還沒到頭  沒有結束
This isn't it. This isn't it.

331
00:36:06,310 --> 00:36:07,280
你還有很多日子呢
There's more.

332
00:36:08,620 --> 00:36:10,000
你會好好活下去的
There's gonna be more.

333
00:36:12,100 --> 00:36:13,910
我相信你  瑞克
I believe in you, Rick.

334
00:36:31,240 --> 00:36:33,530
你笑什么  賤人
What do you got to smile about, bitch?

335
00:36:35,100 --> 00:36:36,870
你什么毛病
What the hell's wrong with you?

336
00:36:38,270 --> 00:36:41,030
我沒有毛病
There's nothing wrong with me.

337
00:36:42,740 --> 00:36:44,960
我就要死了  所以
I'm gonna die, so...

338
00:36:45,420 --> 00:36:47,700
我不會有任何毛病了
there's nothing wrong with me anymore.

339
00:37:04,120 --> 00:37:06,990
你覺得你苦受夠了嗎
You think you've suffered enough now?

340
00:37:09,980 --> 00:37:12,690
不  估計還沒有
No, probably not.

341
00:37:14,290 --> 00:37:16,220
老天
Oh, God.

342
00:37:26,150 --> 00:37:27,350
怎么  就這么完事了嗎
What, are you done?

343
00:37:29,130 --> 00:37:32,340
除非你現在殺了我  不然我不會死
Unless you kill me now, I'm not gonna die!

344
00:37:35,810 --> 00:37:37,530
你快做決定
You decide!

345
00:37:40,900 --> 00:37:44,730
世界不會做決定  只能你自己決定
The world doesn't decide! You decide!

346
00:37:45,730 --> 00:37:47,760
你不能說走就走
You don't get to walk away

347
00:37:48,250 --> 00:37:50,380
還能得償所愿
and get what you want!

348
00:37:58,330 --> 00:37:59,200
住手
Stop.

349
00:38:03,860 --> 00:38:04,820
放下槍
Drop it.

350
00:38:07,930 --> 00:38:09,480
你能活著離開
You can survive this.

351
00:38:10,460 --> 00:38:11,360
你可以的
You can.

352
00:38:14,100 --> 00:38:15,040
放下槍
Drop it.

353
00:38:18,800 --> 00:38:19,870
拜托
Please.

354
00:38:21,390 --> 00:38:22,320
不
No.

355
00:38:41,290 --> 00:38:44,890
你能讓我好好死嗎
Would you please just let me go?

356
00:38:44,890 --> 00:38:47,250
你還不能死
It's not your time.

357
00:38:48,890 --> 00:38:50,930
你會熬過去的
You are gonna come back from this.

358
00:39:01,570 --> 00:39:02,670
發生什么事了
What happened here?

359
00:39:09,900 --> 00:39:11,420
我找到你的馬了
I found your horse.

360
00:39:14,310 --> 00:39:15,700
也找到我的朋友了
Found my friend, too.

361
00:39:17,990 --> 00:39:19,400
她需要幫助
She needs help.

362
00:39:26,130 --> 00:39:27,610
那就讓我們來幫你
Then let's get you some help.

363
00:39:50,470 --> 00:39:51,760
這些蹤跡
These tracks...

364
00:39:52,940 --> 00:39:54,570
說明他們不光人多
they would indicate they not only have people,

365
00:39:54,570 --> 00:39:56,490
還有大型武器裝備
but some big-ass toys and capabilities.

366
00:39:56,490 --> 00:39:59,720
表明我們陷在齊脖深的屎坑里
What it indicates is we are neck-deep up shit creek

367
00:39:59,720 --> 00:40:02,150
嘴還都大張著
with our mouths wide open.

368
00:40:08,820 --> 00:40:11,350
-別開槍  -我可以試著打斷鏈子
- Don't. - I can try and break the chain.

369
00:40:11,730 --> 00:40:12,980
沒用的
It won't work.

370
00:40:12,980 --> 00:40:14,900
-我可以試試  -沒用的
- I can try. - It won't work.

371
00:40:19,710 --> 00:40:21,250
我們需要保留子彈
And we need the bullets.

372
00:40:58,170 --> 00:41:00,390
你有好好對待你的人吧
You're treating your people good, right?

373
00:41:01,770 --> 00:41:03,650
把今天當成最后一天來過
Like it was your last day on Earth?

374
00:41:04,750 --> 00:41:06,440
或者是他們中某人的最后一天
Or maybe one of theirs?

375
00:41:09,460 --> 00:41:10,610
你最好快走
You better go.

376
00:41:11,430 --> 00:41:12,610
這里會很熱的
It's gonna get hot.

377
00:41:13,410 --> 00:41:15,340
去你們的目的地吧
You go get where you're going.

378
00:41:16,360 --> 00:41:18,340
走吧  快走
Go, go.

379
00:41:25,880 --> 00:41:26,740
上車
Get on.

380
00:41:57,090 --> 00:41:58,250
我們怎么辦
So, what's the play?

381
00:42:00,400 --> 00:42:02,040
她需要醫生
She needs a doctor.

382
00:42:03,420 --> 00:42:05,450
北邊還有兩條路
There are two more routes north from here.

383
00:42:07,240 --> 00:42:09,350
他們可能已經在路上等著我們了
They're probably waiting for us right now.

384
00:42:14,320 --> 00:42:17,350
那他們就是在我們的前面  或者后面
So, they're ahead of us, probably behind us.

385
00:42:18,800 --> 00:42:21,220
但他們其實并不是在等我們
But they're not waiting on us, per se,

386
00:42:22,340 --> 00:42:24,030
他們在等這輛破車
they're waiting on this rust bucket.

387
00:42:25,610 --> 00:42:26,750
但他們并不知道
And they don't know

388
00:42:26,750 --> 00:42:29,940
這輛破車里實時的人數
the moment-to-moment occupancy of said rust-bucket.

389
00:42:30,810 --> 00:42:32,350
而且太陽馬上下山了
And the sun sets soon.

390
00:42:53,090 --> 00:42:54,520
這是最后一桶了
That's the last of it.

391
00:42:55,760 --> 00:42:58,480
如果路上遇到車  就吸出汽油
If you see a car, try to siphon the gas.

392
00:42:58,480 --> 00:43:01,010
除此之外  保持前進
Other than that, you keep moving.

393
00:43:01,010 --> 00:43:02,990
我要讓他們以為我們在配合著玩他們的游戲
I'll have them thinking we're playing their game.

394
00:43:03,290 --> 00:43:05,570
一關接著一關  一級接著一級
All phases of the turn, level after level,

395
00:43:05,790 --> 00:43:07,860
一步接著一步  我會騙得他們團團轉
move after move, I'll keep them spun.

396
00:43:07,930 --> 00:43:09,470
我向你保證  我會做到的
I assure you, I will.

397
00:43:11,960 --> 00:43:13,520
我有東西要給你
I got something for you.

398
00:43:14,870 --> 00:43:18,180
是個配方  不是西班牙凍湯的
It's a recipe, and it ain't gazpacho.

399
00:43:21,860 --> 00:43:23,730
如何從零開始制造子彈
How to Build Bullets 101.

400
00:43:24,860 --> 00:43:27,280
亞伯拉罕可以帶你去那個地方  以防萬一
Abraham can show you where, just in case.

401
00:43:33,170 --> 00:43:35,600
謝謝你
Thank you for this.

402
00:43:37,120 --> 00:43:38,980
謝謝你做的一切
For all of it.

403
00:43:41,490 --> 00:43:43,070
有你在我們很幸運
We're lucky you're here.

404
00:43:44,300 --> 00:43:45,900
我就勉強同意你這話吧
I won't argue with that.

405
00:43:52,200 --> 00:43:53,890
踩油門穩一點
You go steady on the pedal.

406
00:43:54,170 --> 00:43:55,820
別開得太猛
You don't make that thing gulp.

407
00:43:57,910 --> 00:43:59,960
你怎么從來都沒有讓我開過卡車呢
How come you never let me drive the truck?

408
00:44:05,400 --> 00:44:07,030
我以為你不會開車
I didn't think you could do it.

409
00:44:11,490 --> 00:44:12,610
我錯了
I was wrong.

410
00:44:14,020 --> 00:44:15,590
你是個生存者
You're a survivor.

411
00:44:17,550 --> 00:44:18,850
你一直都是
You always were.

412
00:44:20,700 --> 00:44:22,320
我們只是以前不知道罷了
We just didn't know it.

413
00:44:25,820 --> 00:44:27,420
我和你都沒意識到
Me and you both.

414
00:44:57,600 --> 00:44:58,970
謝謝你
Thank you.

415
00:46:14,670 --> 00:46:16,510
亞倫  求你了
Aaron, please.

416
00:46:17,180 --> 00:46:18,770
讓我走路吧
Just let me walk it.

417
00:46:19,140 --> 00:46:20,290
放松
Relax.

418
00:46:21,040 --> 00:46:22,580
還有幾英里就到了
Just a few more miles.

419
00:46:25,290 --> 00:46:28,290
我聽見我們走的時候你和她說的話了
I heard what you told her when we were leaving.

420
00:46:31,490 --> 00:46:32,950
我們的確可以戰勝一切
We can do anything,

421
00:46:33,220 --> 00:46:35,370
因為我們會做一切必要的事
'cause we'll do anything we need to do.

422
00:46:36,140 --> 00:46:39,210
以前是  以后也是
We have and we will.

423
00:46:43,290 --> 00:46:44,780
丹妮斯身上發生的事
What happened to Denise,

424
00:46:45,300 --> 00:46:47,920
我不允許再發生在任何人身上
I'm not gonna let anybody die like that again.

425
00:46:50,450 --> 00:46:52,800
-兒子...  -怎么了
- Son... - What?

426
00:47:07,300 --> 00:47:08,940
走  快走
Go! Go!

427
00:48:47,540 --> 00:48:48,880
很好
Good.

428
00:48:50,460 --> 00:48:51,970
你們成功了
You made it.

429
00:48:53,360 --> 00:48:55,280
歡迎來到你們的目的地
Welcome to where you're going.

430
00:49:00,170 --> 00:49:01,850
我們要收走你們的武器
We'll take your weapons.

431
00:49:03,520 --> 00:49:04,710
就現在
Now.

432
00:49:09,460 --> 00:49:11,800
-我們可以談...  -不用談了
- We can talk about-- - We're done talking.

433
00:49:13,110 --> 00:49:14,720
該聽話了
Time to listen.

434
00:49:35,290 --> 00:49:36,690
這是你的  對吧
That's yours, right?

435
00:49:39,240 --> 00:49:43,140
沒錯  就是你的
Yeah, it's yours.

436
00:49:48,930 --> 00:49:50,220
好了
Okay.

437
00:49:51,680 --> 00:49:54,930
把她放下來  你們都跪下
Let's get her down and get you all on your knees.

438
00:49:56,350 --> 00:49:58,010
好多事要辦
Lots to cover.

439
00:49:58,990 --> 00:50:00,180
等下
Hold up.

440
00:50:00,740 --> 00:50:02,230
我們自己來
We got it.

441
00:50:02,830 --> 00:50:05,020
可以  可以
Sure, sure.

442
00:50:40,450 --> 00:50:42,650
你們得跪下
Gonna need you on your knees.

443
00:51:25,330 --> 00:51:28,210
再帶一個出來  立刻
Let's get you another one. Right now.

444
00:51:30,260 --> 00:51:32,170
-德懷特  -來了
- Dwight! - Yeah.

445
00:51:32,230 --> 00:51:33,530
快點
Chop-chop.

446
00:51:41,320 --> 00:51:42,670
來吧
Come on.

447
00:51:42,670 --> 00:51:44,230
帶你見見人
You got people to meet.

448
00:52:01,760 --> 00:52:03,180
瑪姬
Maggie?

449
00:52:04,440 --> 00:52:05,860
跪下
On your knees!

450
00:52:14,850 --> 00:52:16,140
好啊
All right!

451
00:52:16,690 --> 00:52:18,730
都到齊了
We got a full boat.

452
00:52:20,270 --> 00:52:21,840
見見我們頭兒
Let's meet the man.

453
00:52:40,960 --> 00:52:42,570
嚇尿褲子了嗎
Pissing our pants yet?

454
00:52:48,350 --> 00:52:52,230
好家伙  我覺得快了
Boy, do I have a feeling we're getting close.

455
00:52:59,360 --> 00:53:00,700
沒錯
Yep.

456
00:53:01,950 --> 00:53:05,560
馬上就要屁滾尿流了
It's gonna be pee-pee pants city here real soon.

457
00:53:08,490 --> 00:53:11,390
你們這些混蛋誰是頭兒
Which one of you pricks is the leader?

458
00:53:11,960 --> 00:53:13,360
是這人
It's this one.

459
00:53:15,460 --> 00:53:16,720
他是頭兒
He's the guy.

460
00:53:30,140 --> 00:53:31,570
你就是瑞克  對吧
You're Rick, right?

461
00:53:32,400 --> 00:53:33,860
我是尼根
I'm Negan.

462
00:53:35,070 --> 00:53:38,730
你殺了我的手下  我可不太高興
And I do not appreciate you killing my men.

463
00:53:39,800 --> 00:53:41,730
而且  我派人
Also, when I sent my people

464
00:53:41,730 --> 00:53:44,250
去替我的手下報仇
to kill your people for killing my people,

465
00:53:44,760 --> 00:53:47,180
你又殺了我更多手下
you killed more of my people.

466
00:53:49,010 --> 00:53:50,760
不厚道
Not cool.

467
00:53:52,000 --> 00:53:53,290
不厚道
Not cool.

468
00:53:53,670 --> 00:53:57,340
你都不知道
You have no idea

469
00:53:57,340 --> 00:53:59,470
你干的事兒有多不厚道
how not cool that shit is.

470
00:53:59,470 --> 00:54:03,290
不過我想你馬上就要知道了
But I think you're gonna be up to speed shortly.

471
00:54:06,270 --> 00:54:07,510
沒錯
Yeah.

472
00:54:09,550 --> 00:54:13,040
你馬上就會很后悔跟我作對
You are so gonna regret crossing me in a few minutes.

473
00:54:15,950 --> 00:54:17,240
你一定會的
Yes, you are.

474
00:54:20,360 --> 00:54:22,210
瑞克  無論你做什么
You see, Rick, whatever you do,

475
00:54:23,400 --> 00:54:24,720
無論什么情況  
no matter what,

476
00:54:24,720 --> 00:54:26,700
你都不該挑戰新世界的秩序
you don't mess with the new world order.

477
00:54:26,700 --> 00:54:27,940
我來告訴你新世界的秩序是什么  
And the new world order is this,

478
00:54:27,940 --> 00:54:29,740
非常非常簡單
and it's really very simple.

479
00:54:29,740 --> 00:54:33,320
所以即便你蠢  你也很可能確實蠢
So, even if you're stupid, which you very may well be,

480
00:54:33,320 --> 00:54:35,190
你也能懂
you can understand it.

481
00:54:35,960 --> 00:54:37,360
準備好了嗎
You ready?

482
00:54:39,220 --> 00:54:41,170
開始了  注意聽
Here goes. Pay attention.

483
00:54:50,090 --> 00:54:51,730
把你的東西給我
Give me your shit...

484
00:54:53,090 --> 00:54:54,810
否則我就殺了你
or I will kill you.

485
00:54:59,630 --> 00:55:01,540
今天就像是自我介紹日啊
Today was career day.

486
00:55:03,060 --> 00:55:05,260
我們投入了很多
We invested a lot

487
00:55:05,260 --> 00:55:10,000
好讓你們知道我是誰  我能做出什么事
so you would know who I am and what I can do.

488
00:55:11,660 --> 00:55:13,350
你們現在都要替我工作了
You work for me now.

489
00:55:14,450 --> 00:55:17,660
你們得到任何東西  都要上交給我
You have shit, you give it to me.

490
00:55:17,660 --> 00:55:19,240
那就是你們的工作
That's your job.

491
00:55:21,420 --> 00:55:28,300
我知道你們一時間很難接受這事
Now, I know that is a mighty big, nasty pill to swallow,

492
00:55:28,550 --> 00:55:33,850
但你們最終一定會接受的
but swallow it you most certainly will.

493
00:55:38,060 --> 00:55:39,850
你稱霸一方
You ruled the roost.

494
00:55:40,030 --> 00:55:43,840
建造了安全窩
You built something.

495
00:55:45,780 --> 00:55:47,550
你們以為自己很安全
You thought you were safe.

496
00:55:48,120 --> 00:55:49,300
我理解的
I get it.

497
00:55:51,150 --> 00:55:54,660
但是世界已經失序
But the word is out.

498
00:55:56,320 --> 00:55:59,570
你們并不安全
You are not safe.

499
00:56:01,580 --> 00:56:03,620
一點都不安全
Not even close.

500
00:56:03,620 --> 00:56:05,660
實際上  你們已經完蛋了
In fact, you are pegged,

501
00:56:06,170 --> 00:56:08,170
如果你們不照我說的做  就更完蛋了
more pegged if you don't do what I want.

502
00:56:08,170 --> 00:56:10,890
我想要的  就是你們一半的東西
And what I want is half your shit.

503
00:56:10,890 --> 00:56:12,180
如果那太多了
And if that's too much,

504
00:56:12,180 --> 00:56:14,380
你們可以制造  搜尋或盜竊更多的
you can make, find, or steal more,

505
00:56:14,830 --> 00:56:17,080
遲早都得補上
and it'll even out sooner or later.

506
00:56:19,700 --> 00:56:22,500
這就是你們現在的生存方式了
This is your way of life now.

507
00:56:22,980 --> 00:56:26,940
你們越反抗  就越艱難
The more you fight back, the harder it will be.

508
00:56:28,190 --> 00:56:32,220
所以  如果有人敲你家的門
So, if someone knocks on your door...

509
00:56:35,360 --> 00:56:36,800
你就得讓我們進去
...you let us in.

510
00:56:36,800 --> 00:56:39,470
那扇門是屬于我們的
We own that door.

511
00:56:39,700 --> 00:56:42,000
你如果敢阻止我們
You try to stop us

512
00:56:42,000 --> 00:56:45,420
我們就把那扇門撞爛
and we will knock it down.

513
00:56:47,880 --> 00:56:50,040
聽明白了嗎
You understand?

514
00:56:53,210 --> 00:56:55,880
怎么  沒有答復嗎
What, no answer?

515
00:56:59,550 --> 00:57:02,720
你們不會真的以為  你們不接受懲罰
You don't really think that you were gonna get through this

516
00:57:02,720 --> 00:57:05,060
就能逃過這一劫吧
without being punished, now, did you?

517
00:57:07,060 --> 00:57:09,280
我并不想殺你們
I don't want to kill you people.

518
00:57:09,280 --> 00:57:11,780
我想從一開始就說清楚這一點
Just want to make that clear from the get-go.

519
00:57:12,900 --> 00:57:15,230
我要你們替我工作
I want you to work for me.

520
00:57:15,240 --> 00:57:19,240
如果你們死了  還怎么替我工作  對吧
You can't do that if you're dead, now, can you?

521
00:57:22,410 --> 00:57:24,610
我才不會去種菜園子
I'm not growing a garden.

522
00:57:28,330 --> 00:57:33,220
但是你們殺了我的人  殺了很多人
But you killed my people, a whole damn lot of them.

523
00:57:33,220 --> 00:57:34,750
多到我無法接受了
More than I'm comfortable with.

524
00:57:35,170 --> 00:57:38,960
因此  你們必須付出代價
And for that, for that you're gonna pay.

525
00:57:42,900 --> 00:57:44,180
所以現在...
So, now...

526
00:57:48,490 --> 00:57:52,750
我要打爆你們其中一個人
I'm gonna beat the holy hell outta one of you.

527
00:57:59,030 --> 00:58:00,440
這個...
This--

528
00:58:01,900 --> 00:58:03,510
名叫露西爾
this is Lucille,

529
00:58:04,080 --> 00:58:08,030
她非常厲害
and she is awesome.

530
00:58:14,090 --> 00:58:19,940
所有這一切  只是為了從你們當中
All this, all this is just so we can pick out

531
00:58:19,940 --> 00:58:23,220
挑出一個人來接受光榮的犧牲
which one of you gets the honor.

532
00:58:40,400 --> 00:58:42,320
我可得把胡子好好刮一下
Ugh, I gotta shave this shit.

533
00:58:49,210 --> 00:58:51,700
你拿走了我們的一把槍
You got one of our guns.

534
00:58:59,010 --> 00:59:00,960
你拿走了我們的很多槍
You got a lot of our guns.

535
00:59:04,680 --> 00:59:08,080
該死的  孩子  放松一點嘛
Shit, kid, lighten up.

536
00:59:10,270 --> 00:59:12,160
至少稍微哭一下嘛
At least cry a little.

537
00:59:30,840 --> 00:59:33,150
天啊
Jesus.

538
00:59:33,210 --> 00:59:35,830
你看上去糟透了
You look shitty.

539
00:59:37,330 --> 00:59:39,650
我現在就應該解脫你
I should just put you out of your misery right now.

540
00:59:39,650 --> 00:59:41,020
不  不
No! No!

541
00:59:41,170 --> 00:59:43,410
住手
Stop it!

542
00:59:45,210 --> 00:59:46,240
天啊
God--!

543
00:59:48,940 --> 00:59:49,790
不
Nope.

544
00:59:50,860 --> 00:59:52,800
-不  把他放回隊伍中  -不
- Nope, get him back in line. - No.

545
00:59:55,440 --> 00:59:56,490
不
No.

546
00:59:57,580 --> 00:59:58,650
不
No.

547
01:00:08,080 --> 01:00:09,320
別
Don't.

548
01:00:10,330 --> 01:00:11,460
別
Don't.

549
01:00:14,500 --> 01:00:16,010
好吧  聽著
All right, listen.

550
01:00:17,220 --> 01:00:21,200
永遠不準再那樣做
Don't any of you do that again.

551
01:00:21,200 --> 01:00:24,950
我會弄死你們  沒有例外
I will shut that shit down, no exceptions.

552
01:00:26,810 --> 01:00:28,080
第一次算了
First one's free.

553
01:00:28,080 --> 01:00:31,300
你們很緊張  我懂
It's an emotional moment, I get it.

554
01:00:47,250 --> 01:00:48,900
糟透了  不是嗎
Sucks, don't it?

555
01:00:49,780 --> 01:00:52,570
當你意識到自己屁都不知道的時候
The moment you realize you don't know shit.

556
01:01:08,560 --> 01:01:10,570
這是你兒子  對嗎
This is your kid, right?

557
01:01:15,640 --> 01:01:17,720
這肯定是你兒子
This is definitely your kid.

558
01:01:17,720 --> 01:01:19,670
-別這樣了  -嘿
- Just stop this! - Hey!

559
01:01:21,140 --> 01:01:25,100
別逼我殺了這個未來的連環殺手
Do not make me kill the little future serial killer.

560
01:01:25,100 --> 01:01:27,190
別給我動手的借口
Don't make it easy on me.

561
01:01:29,230 --> 01:01:31,180
我必須選個人
I gotta pick somebody.

562
01:01:32,060 --> 01:01:35,750
每個人都在餐桌上  供我享用
Everybody's at the table waiting for me to order.

563
01:01:54,610 --> 01:01:56,550
真是太難選了
I simply cannot decide.

564
01:02:04,160 --> 01:02:05,860
我有個主意
I got an idea.

565
01:02:14,450 --> 01:02:15,390
點
Eenie...

566
01:02:18,040 --> 01:02:19,400
兵
meenie...

567
01:02:19,990 --> 01:02:21,470
點
miney...

568
01:02:24,180 --> 01:02:25,400
將
mo...

569
01:02:27,760 --> 01:02:29,350
騎
catch...

570
01:02:30,720 --> 01:02:32,130
虎
a tiger...

571
01:02:33,350 --> 01:02:34,470
打
by...

572
01:02:36,110 --> 01:02:37,460
仗
his toe.

573
01:02:38,470 --> 01:02:39,800
點到
If...

574
01:02:40,480 --> 01:02:42,210
哪里
he hollers...

575
01:02:43,730 --> 01:02:44,740
哪里就上
let him go.

576
01:02:47,450 --> 01:02:48,980
頭
My mother...

577
01:02:49,620 --> 01:02:50,780
破
told me...

578
01:02:51,280 --> 01:02:52,420
血
to pick

579
01:02:52,420 --> 01:02:54,780
流 
the very...

580
01:02:54,780 --> 01:02:55,960
死
best one...

581
01:02:57,550 --> 01:02:58,980
在
and you...

582
01:03:01,120 --> 01:03:02,690
場
are...

583
01:03:11,010 --> 01:03:12,510
上
it.

584
01:03:13,390 --> 01:03:15,520
有人敢動或說話
Anybody moves, anybody says anything,

585
01:03:15,520 --> 01:03:18,190
就把那孩子的另一只眼睛挖出來喂他父親吃
cut the boy's other eye out and feed it to his father

586
01:03:18,190 --> 01:03:19,820
然后我們再開始
and then we'll start.

587
01:03:20,070 --> 01:03:21,600
你可以呼吸
You can breathe,

588
01:03:21,820 --> 01:03:23,290
你可以眨眼
you can blink,

589
01:03:23,580 --> 01:03:25,280
你可以哭泣
you can cry.

590
01:03:25,520 --> 01:03:28,360
見鬼  你們每個人都會那樣的
Hell, you're all gonna be doing that.

591
01:03:34,110 --> 01:03:36,600
看看
Look at that.

592
01:03:37,030 --> 01:03:39,220
真有種
Taking it like a champ!

593
01:03:43,440 --> 01:03:44,830
該死
Damn!

