1
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:03,600
Previously, on AMC's "The Walking Dead."

2
00:00:03,840 --> 00:00:06,480
We live. We kill them all.

3
00:00:15,360 --> 00:00:17,230
You wanna just come back with us?

4
00:00:17,230 --> 00:00:19,820
Take a couple days before you and Tara go out again.

5
00:00:20,100 --> 00:00:21,580
I just wanna get outta here.

6
00:00:23,130 --> 00:00:25,030
Heath and I are still going on that two-weeker.

7
00:00:25,030 --> 00:00:26,340
When we leave from there...

8
00:00:34,980 --> 00:00:35,890
It's gross.

9
00:00:35,890 --> 00:00:37,350
Just throw it back.

10
00:00:38,390 --> 00:00:39,740
It'll dry out.

11
00:00:40,930 --> 00:00:42,550
It smells terrible.

12
00:00:42,780 --> 00:00:44,240
We can empty it out,

13
00:00:44,240 --> 00:00:46,210
stuff it full of Miss Iris' sage,

14
00:00:46,330 --> 00:00:47,810
and some of the lavender, too.

15
00:00:48,010 --> 00:00:49,120
Then what?

16
00:00:49,300 --> 00:00:50,750
Then you have an awesome bear

17
00:00:50,750 --> 00:00:52,760
that survived the stormy sea, Rachel.

18
00:00:53,880 --> 00:00:55,540
I had one just like this when I was your age, and --

19
00:00:55,540 --> 00:00:57,090
Oh, shit! Look!

20
00:00:58,240 --> 00:00:59,470
Don't run!

21
00:01:03,640 --> 00:01:04,670
One hit.

22
00:01:05,660 --> 00:01:07,130
I didn't have to twice.

23
00:01:07,890 --> 00:01:09,070
Not bad, huh?

24
00:01:10,170 --> 00:01:11,050
Yeah.

25
00:01:13,430 --> 00:01:15,190
Look! Another one!

26
00:01:18,080 --> 00:01:19,960
Come on. Don't run!

27
00:01:35,580 --> 00:01:36,540
Wait!

28
00:01:45,140 --> 00:01:46,340
She's not a bobber.

29
00:01:51,920 --> 00:01:53,190
She's alive.

30
00:01:59,060 --> 00:02:00,630
We still gotta do it.

31
00:02:01,090 --> 00:02:01,940
No.

32
00:02:02,940 --> 00:02:04,290
We don't have to do it.

33
00:02:06,640 --> 00:02:07,790
Yes, we do.

34
00:02:08,070 --> 00:02:11,490
No, we don't, not if people don't find out.

35
00:02:17,070 --> 00:02:18,670
We're supposed to.

36
00:02:18,670 --> 00:02:20,160
I want to.

37
00:02:21,300 --> 00:02:22,530
I don't.

38
00:02:23,090 --> 00:02:24,330
So we won't.

39
00:02:27,610 --> 00:02:28,650
Are you gonna tell?

40
00:02:30,640 --> 00:02:32,370
Just tell me if you're gonna tell,

41
00:02:32,710 --> 00:02:33,880
if you're a snitch.

42
00:02:36,000 --> 00:02:37,760
I'm not a snitch.

43
00:02:38,950 --> 00:02:40,780
But I'm not going to help.

44
00:04:04,850 --> 00:04:06,680
Eight rusty cans of okra

45
00:04:07,380 --> 00:04:09,050
and a bottle of aspirin.

46
00:04:13,250 --> 00:04:15,630
That's what we got to show for our time out here...

47
00:04:17,790 --> 00:04:19,800
...other than the fact that we're still standin'.

48
00:04:20,910 --> 00:04:22,590
Rule number one of scavenging --

50
00:04:23,370 --> 00:04:25,700
there's nothing left in this world that isn't hidden.

51
00:04:26,000 --> 00:04:27,430
We just have to find it.

52
00:04:27,700 --> 00:04:28,780
Mm, good.

53
00:04:30,040 --> 00:04:31,430
We just have to find it.

54
00:04:31,860 --> 00:04:34,110
For a second there, I was worried.

55
00:04:35,930 --> 00:04:38,480
Listen, we went farther than we were supposed to.

56
00:04:39,450 --> 00:04:42,300
There's nothing left out here.

57
00:04:44,920 --> 00:04:46,510
We don't even have enough gas to keep looking

58
00:04:46,510 --> 00:04:48,490
even if we wanted to, okay?

59
00:04:48,490 --> 00:04:50,360
We said we'd be gone for two weeks.

60
00:04:50,360 --> 00:04:52,090
It's been two weeks.

61
00:04:52,090 --> 00:04:53,890
As long as the Hilltop keeps their side of the bargain,

62
00:04:53,890 --> 00:04:55,380
we have food at home.

63
00:04:55,850 --> 00:04:57,210
We need ammo.

64
00:04:57,610 --> 00:04:58,960
We need medicine.

65
00:05:01,270 --> 00:05:02,530
We can't go back like this.

66
00:05:02,530 --> 00:05:04,330
There's people counting on us.

67
00:05:04,680 --> 00:05:06,240
Why you acting like you don't know that?

68
00:05:06,240 --> 00:05:08,470
I'm not sure that means much to me anymore.

69
00:05:10,280 --> 00:05:13,950
What we did at the satellite station...

70
00:05:16,040 --> 00:05:18,520
all of those people that we killed...

71
00:05:20,890 --> 00:05:22,780
You didn't see it, okay?

72
00:05:22,780 --> 00:05:24,290
You just saw what was left.

73
00:05:24,290 --> 00:05:25,300
No.

74
00:05:26,710 --> 00:05:28,320
I had to do it, too.

75
00:05:28,320 --> 00:05:30,520
Yeah, we all had to...

76
00:05:31,440 --> 00:05:33,550
for some milk and some corn.

77
00:05:33,550 --> 00:05:35,330
That wasn't the only reason.

78
00:05:35,590 --> 00:05:37,030
And yeah, we did.

79
00:05:37,030 --> 00:05:38,110
You know we did.

80
00:05:38,110 --> 00:05:40,180
See, that's -- that's the thing.

81
00:05:41,040 --> 00:05:42,580
You saw how we were living back home

82
00:05:42,580 --> 00:05:44,020
before you guys got there.

83
00:05:44,640 --> 00:05:46,030
We didn't know shit.

84
00:05:47,650 --> 00:05:48,650
We thought...

85
00:05:49,360 --> 00:05:50,200
‭What?

86
00:05:51,530 --> 00:05:52,170
What?

87
00:05:52,170 --> 00:05:53,280
It doesn't matter.

88
00:05:57,270 --> 00:05:58,480
I get it now.

89
00:06:00,400 --> 00:06:04,430
If it's you or someone else, you choose you.

90
00:06:05,020 --> 00:06:08,680
You take what you can, you take out who you have to,

91
00:06:08,680 --> 00:06:10,570
and you get to keep going.

92
00:06:14,390 --> 00:06:16,560
Nobody's in this together, okay?

93
00:06:16,560 --> 00:06:17,670
Not anymore.

94
00:06:21,970 --> 00:06:23,860
It only hurts because you know what you just said

95
00:06:23,860 --> 00:06:25,340
is total bullshit.

96
00:06:26,320 --> 00:06:27,930
That's not you, Heath.

97
00:06:29,280 --> 00:06:30,190
Tara...

98
00:06:37,330 --> 00:06:38,310
that's me...

99
00:06:40,280 --> 00:06:41,290
that's you...

100
00:06:43,100 --> 00:06:46,810
and that's everybody who wants to stay alive.

101
00:06:49,230 --> 00:06:50,410
That's the truth.

102
00:06:54,640 --> 00:06:56,950
We can push towards the shore, but after today...

103
00:06:58,780 --> 00:06:59,800
we go back.

104
00:07:01,400 --> 00:07:03,710
Even if we just have those rusty cans.

105
00:11:29,950 --> 00:11:31,780
No, I got it. Thanks.

106
00:11:31,780 --> 00:11:33,890
Did they find anything out there yesterday?

107
00:11:34,150 --> 00:11:36,050
Ev said she reached the mouth.

108
00:11:36,060 --> 00:11:37,210
Are you serious?

109
00:11:37,330 --> 00:11:39,320
- What'd she see? - ‭Nothing.

110
00:11:39,930 --> 00:11:41,250
All the way down there.

111
00:11:41,250 --> 00:11:42,630
Not a damn thing.

112
00:14:33,850 --> 00:14:35,040
Go ahead.

113
00:14:53,150 --> 00:14:54,430
Doesn't matter.

114
00:14:54,430 --> 00:14:55,860
We're supposed to.

115
00:14:57,400 --> 00:14:59,960
Rachel...no.

116
00:15:14,050 --> 00:15:14,920
Hi.

117
00:15:16,880 --> 00:15:19,350
I just, uh... I didn't mean to.

118
00:15:22,110 --> 00:15:23,200
Look, I'm cool.

119
00:15:23,900 --> 00:15:25,360
I'm not here to hurt anyone.

120
00:15:26,820 --> 00:15:27,680
Rachel...

121
00:15:28,380 --> 00:15:30,670
everyone, just lower your guns.

122
00:15:30,680 --> 00:15:32,830
Cyndie, get away from her!

123
00:15:33,280 --> 00:15:34,710
She hasn't done anything wrong.

124
00:15:34,710 --> 00:15:36,250
That has nothing to do with it.

125
00:15:36,250 --> 00:15:37,220
Get away!

126
00:15:44,570 --> 00:15:45,420
I'm sorry.

127
00:15:45,420 --> 00:15:47,520
I just walked in -- crawled.

128
00:15:47,520 --> 00:15:49,130
I didn't even know I was in.

129
00:15:50,240 --> 00:15:51,200
I'm sorry.

130
00:15:52,540 --> 00:15:53,680
I can just go.

131
00:16:00,540 --> 00:16:01,350
Okay.

132
00:16:02,750 --> 00:16:04,220
This is cool, too.

133
00:16:05,310 --> 00:16:06,890
We just keep doing this.

134
00:16:38,440 --> 00:16:39,510
What do we think?

135
00:16:43,650 --> 00:16:45,340
Lotta blind spots down there.

136
00:18:03,400 --> 00:18:05,390
Let's check behind the tarps first.

137
00:18:20,140 --> 00:18:22,090
Looks like they had plans for something.

138
00:18:22,500 --> 00:18:24,490
Looks like they didn't get to finish.

139
00:18:31,850 --> 00:18:32,790
It's heavy.

140
00:18:33,370 --> 00:18:34,930
Could be something good in there.

141
00:18:41,310 --> 00:18:42,280
Tara.

142
00:18:43,190 --> 00:18:44,920
Hold on. Hold on!

143
00:19:20,530 --> 00:19:21,990
That way! Go!

144
00:19:28,820 --> 00:19:30,890
- Heath! - ‭Tara!

145
00:19:33,020 --> 00:19:33,980
Heath!

146
00:19:43,770 --> 00:19:45,720
We just need to hear what she has to say.

147
00:19:45,720 --> 00:19:46,890
No. The longer we wait,

149
00:19:46,890 --> 00:19:48,170
the more our community's at risk.

150
00:19:48,170 --> 00:19:50,060
We agreed to discuss this together as a group

151
00:19:50,060 --> 00:19:51,600
if someone ever got in.

152
00:19:51,830 --> 00:19:54,170
We made that decision a long time ago.

153
00:20:01,110 --> 00:20:04,190
Do you, uh, need to use the bathroom before we get started?

154
00:20:09,230 --> 00:20:11,610
No. Um, thank you.

155
00:20:13,060 --> 00:20:14,220
But maybe...

156
00:20:17,380 --> 00:20:18,560
I'm Natania.

157
00:20:18,560 --> 00:20:21,650
This is Kathy and Beatrice, 

158
00:20:21,650 --> 00:20:23,460
whom you've already met.

159
00:20:26,220 --> 00:20:28,330
Am I the only one hearing bells?

160
00:20:28,350 --> 00:20:29,220
They're ours.

161
00:20:29,220 --> 00:20:30,600
We have six of them --

162
00:20:30,710 --> 00:20:33,300
some nearby, some a couple of miles away.

163
00:20:33,300 --> 00:20:34,800
What about the air horn?

164
00:20:35,530 --> 00:20:37,730
We could only find so many bells.

165
00:20:38,150 --> 00:20:39,760
They are to redirect any of the dead

166
00:20:39,760 --> 00:20:41,760
that might have been drawn by it.

167
00:20:44,130 --> 00:20:45,160
Not bad.

168
00:20:45,970 --> 00:20:47,780
It helps sometimes.

169
00:20:48,310 --> 00:20:51,160
But a branch in the wind, leaves rustling...

170
00:20:51,280 --> 00:20:54,130
We're lucky this is a relatively clear area.

171
00:20:54,130 --> 00:20:56,420
The evacuations, the barges --

172
00:20:56,630 --> 00:20:58,200
if they were even real.

173
00:20:59,190 --> 00:21:00,160
So...

174
00:21:00,950 --> 00:21:02,290
where are you from?

175
00:21:04,670 --> 00:21:05,840
Atlanta...

176
00:21:07,520 --> 00:21:09,620
a long time ago.

177
00:21:10,690 --> 00:21:12,560
I just stayed on the move.

178
00:21:13,870 --> 00:21:15,190
My friend and I -- 

179
00:21:15,250 --> 00:21:16,310
we've been traveling around

180
00:21:16,310 --> 00:21:18,510
on our own for a couple years now.

181
00:21:19,290 --> 00:21:21,220
We used to work on a fishing boat.

182
00:21:21,220 --> 00:21:22,670
There's someone with you?

183
00:21:23,140 --> 00:21:24,250
There was.

184
00:21:24,780 --> 00:21:26,180
We got separated.

185
00:21:26,630 --> 00:21:28,690
What kind of fishing boat did you work on --

186
00:21:30,220 --> 00:21:32,720
trawler, seiner, larder?

187
00:21:32,940 --> 00:21:35,070
Oh, last one. You got it.

188
00:21:38,240 --> 00:21:40,080
What were you doing here?

189
00:21:41,170 --> 00:21:44,280
You must understand, we get nervous when people just find their way

190
00:21:44,280 --> 00:21:45,810
into our home.

191
00:21:46,560 --> 00:21:49,380
Yeah, I-I saw that.

192
00:21:49,380 --> 00:21:50,610
My friend and I -- 

193
00:21:50,610 --> 00:21:52,630
we found this settlement built on a bridge, 

194
00:21:52,630 --> 00:21:54,160
or what was left of it.

195
00:21:54,340 --> 00:21:55,030
We were scavenging,

196
00:21:55,030 --> 00:21:57,620
and we got attacked by walkers -- the dead.

197
00:21:58,230 --> 00:22:00,040
We were trying to get away from them,

198
00:22:00,300 --> 00:22:02,140
and I got knocked off a bridge.

199
00:22:02,620 --> 00:22:03,630
I fought the current, 

200
00:22:03,640 --> 00:22:05,110
wound up in the inlet.

201
00:22:06,520 --> 00:22:07,800
The estuary?

202
00:22:09,080 --> 00:22:10,050
The bay?

203
00:22:10,090 --> 00:22:11,760
Look, I'm not good with geography.

204
00:22:11,760 --> 00:22:14,830
I just thought I was dead out there.

205
00:22:15,280 --> 00:22:17,280
And I got to the shore, and I just passed out.

206
00:22:17,280 --> 00:22:18,680
It's the bridge on Windsor.

207
00:22:18,870 --> 00:22:20,520
You -- you know how to get there?

208
00:22:20,680 --> 00:22:21,650
We do.

209
00:22:21,880 --> 00:22:23,350
She didn't answer the question.

210
00:22:23,350 --> 00:22:24,370
I didn't?

211
00:22:24,490 --> 00:22:25,750
What was the question?

212
00:22:25,870 --> 00:22:27,490
What were you doing here?

213
00:22:27,750 --> 00:22:29,190
When that girl, Cyndie, brought me food,

214
00:22:29,190 --> 00:22:32,320
I just pretended like I was out and I followed her back.

215
00:22:32,320 --> 00:22:33,470
It seemed like she had a camp,

216
00:22:33,470 --> 00:22:35,170
and I wanted to see if I could get any help.

217
00:22:35,170 --> 00:22:37,160
Then why were you sneaking around?

218
00:22:37,630 --> 00:22:40,270
I wanted to see if it was safe.

219
00:22:40,600 --> 00:22:42,120
Still not sure.

220
00:22:43,010 --> 00:22:45,890
Look, I'm sorry that I freaked you out.

221
00:22:45,890 --> 00:22:46,890
Really.

222
00:22:47,050 --> 00:22:49,790
But if you just point me in the right direction, I'm gone.

223
00:22:49,790 --> 00:22:52,570
I need to get back to the bridge and look for my friend.

224
00:22:52,870 --> 00:22:54,310
If we let you go, 

225
00:22:54,320 --> 00:22:56,210
you have us at a disadvantage.

226
00:22:56,210 --> 00:22:58,680
You know a great deal about us now.

227
00:22:58,740 --> 00:23:01,240
- If you let me go? - Yes.

228
00:23:01,530 --> 00:23:04,050
You see, normally, we would've killed you already.

229
00:23:04,950 --> 00:23:09,130
We shoot strangers on sight if they come into our camp.

230
00:23:09,130 --> 00:23:11,670
But Beatrice said you spared her life,

231
00:23:11,670 --> 00:23:15,160
and my granddaughter almost lost hers trying to save you --

232
00:23:15,160 --> 00:23:17,260
"That girl," Cyndie.

233
00:23:18,810 --> 00:23:21,180
So it leaves us with the question still

234
00:23:21,180 --> 00:23:24,180
of what to do with you instead.

235
00:23:25,750 --> 00:23:26,710
Yeah.

236
00:23:27,850 --> 00:23:29,470
That's a pickle, all right.

237
00:23:32,540 --> 00:23:33,700
Why don't you rest up?

238
00:23:33,700 --> 00:23:35,250
We'll talk more later.

239
00:23:35,250 --> 00:23:37,940
Maybe one of us will have a brainstorm.

240
00:23:40,840 --> 00:23:41,800
Cool.

241
00:24:48,510 --> 00:24:50,210
Hope you like fish.

242
00:24:52,580 --> 00:24:53,900
the dried kind?

243
00:24:54,460 --> 00:24:56,570
She brought you salted perch.

244
00:24:57,640 --> 00:24:58,800
Did you like it?

245
00:24:59,470 --> 00:25:00,470
Sure.

246
00:25:01,410 --> 00:25:02,890
No, you didn't.

247
00:25:04,280 --> 00:25:05,810
Not so much.

248
00:25:06,270 --> 00:25:07,830
We're having stew.

249
00:25:09,990 --> 00:25:10,840
Oh, that's right --

250
00:25:10,840 --> 00:25:13,290
you two haven't formally met, have you?

251
00:25:13,370 --> 00:25:15,060
Tara, this is Cyndie.

252
00:25:17,100 --> 00:25:19,570
Uh, thank you for the beach and...

253
00:25:19,780 --> 00:25:21,140
everything out there.

254
00:25:22,330 --> 00:25:24,150
I mean, you saved my life.

255
00:25:26,050 --> 00:25:27,020
You did.

256
00:25:28,270 --> 00:25:30,980
I mean, I don't know if your grandma totally approves, but...

257
00:25:32,660 --> 00:25:33,970
My mom would've.

258
00:25:36,630 --> 00:25:38,070
She showed me the way.

259
00:25:39,430 --> 00:25:40,520
A way.

260
00:25:41,470 --> 00:25:42,990
I was trying to show Rachel.

261
00:25:43,600 --> 00:25:44,650
The little girl?

262
00:25:45,700 --> 00:25:46,880
Yeah.

263
00:25:47,900 --> 00:25:49,590
She hasn't had to do it yet.

264
00:25:50,740 --> 00:25:51,720
Have you?

265
00:25:58,870 --> 00:26:00,600
I'm a really good shot.

266
00:26:01,310 --> 00:26:02,770
Yes, you are.

267
00:26:04,230 --> 00:26:05,690
Okay, let's eat.

268
00:26:06,330 --> 00:26:07,620
Let's talk.

269
00:26:09,770 --> 00:26:10,710
Tara.

270
00:26:23,060 --> 00:26:24,410
When was the last time you ate?

271
00:26:24,410 --> 00:26:26,570
Do soy-sauce packets count as food?

272
00:26:26,860 --> 00:26:29,060
We have an endless supply of fish here --

273
00:26:29,060 --> 00:26:31,720
one of the perks of living so close to the ocean.

274
00:26:33,140 --> 00:26:35,040
You, um, you think, Tara,

275
00:26:35,040 --> 00:26:37,080
it's something you could get used to?

276
00:26:38,350 --> 00:26:40,530
I'm hoping to convince you to stay.

277
00:26:41,280 --> 00:26:42,310
Wait. What?

278
00:26:42,340 --> 00:26:43,320
Why not?

279
00:26:43,530 --> 00:26:46,140
It would be the perfect solution to our problem.

280
00:26:46,140 --> 00:26:48,010
We keep our village a secret,

281
00:26:48,010 --> 00:26:50,330
and you'd get to put down roots.

282
00:26:50,740 --> 00:26:53,390
You're a skilled fighter, Tara, and a good person.

283
00:26:53,390 --> 00:26:54,740
I can tell that.

284
00:26:55,270 --> 00:26:57,460
You wouldn't be leaving anything behind.

285
00:26:57,460 --> 00:27:00,260
And if you want, we can help you find your friend.

286
00:27:00,260 --> 00:27:03,030
And if he wants to stay, we'll offer him a home, too.

287
00:27:03,030 --> 00:27:04,560
He could stay here?

288
00:27:05,350 --> 00:27:06,890
Is there a reason why not?

289
00:27:07,620 --> 00:27:08,620
I mean...

290
00:27:11,300 --> 00:27:12,820
well, I never thought I'd be asking this,

291
00:27:12,820 --> 00:27:14,810
but where are all the men?

292
00:27:23,170 --> 00:27:24,450
All of them?

293
00:27:25,530 --> 00:27:28,420
We got into a skirmish with another group.

294
00:27:29,040 --> 00:27:30,500
None of them made it.

295
00:27:32,660 --> 00:27:34,500
And we lost others, too.

296
00:27:35,980 --> 00:27:39,610
Cyndie had an 11-year-old brother, my grandson,

297
00:27:40,290 --> 00:27:42,500
and their mother, too, my daughter.

298
00:27:49,890 --> 00:27:51,840
After that, we decided to protect ourselves, 

299
00:27:51,840 --> 00:27:53,110
no matter what.

300
00:27:53,750 --> 00:27:56,910
No matter who we crossed, we would kill on sight.

301
00:27:58,470 --> 00:28:01,840
We left our old home with just the clothes on our backs.

302
00:28:02,890 --> 00:28:04,890
And then we found this place.

303
00:28:06,520 --> 00:28:08,170
We would stay hidden.

304
00:28:13,770 --> 00:28:16,050
And we would stay alive.

305
00:28:17,490 --> 00:28:20,080
Tara, you could have hurt us, and you didn't.

306
00:28:20,350 --> 00:28:22,740
I-I know we must sound like monsters to you,

307
00:28:22,740 --> 00:28:23,810
but I had to be honest

308
00:28:23,810 --> 00:28:27,030
so maybe you could understand why we do it.

309
00:28:27,790 --> 00:28:29,200
Maybe you could...

310
00:28:29,460 --> 00:28:31,310
consider staying.

311
00:28:31,640 --> 00:28:34,230
And maybe you could be honest with us

312
00:28:34,230 --> 00:28:35,830
about where you're from.

313
00:28:36,270 --> 00:28:37,970
I was telling you the truth.

314
00:28:37,970 --> 00:28:38,960
Really?

315
00:28:39,480 --> 00:28:42,420
You said you worked on a fishing boat, a larder.

316
00:28:42,420 --> 00:28:43,500
That's right.

317
00:28:44,570 --> 00:28:47,480
Tara, a larder is a room used for storing meat.

318
00:28:47,480 --> 00:28:49,630
Yeah. I was lying.

319
00:29:00,560 --> 00:29:02,170
I come from a community.

320
00:29:02,750 --> 00:29:04,310
And that's really what it is.

321
00:29:04,900 --> 00:29:07,170
We live with each other. We help each other.

322
00:29:07,860 --> 00:29:09,380
We have walls, houses.

323
00:29:09,380 --> 00:29:11,490
I have a girlfriend I want to get back to.

324
00:29:13,260 --> 00:29:14,940
And we've done things...

325
00:29:15,560 --> 00:29:16,740
just like you.

326
00:29:22,300 --> 00:29:23,820
There were these people.

327
00:29:24,370 --> 00:29:26,010
They were threatening us.

328
00:29:26,250 --> 00:29:30,100
We found out they were using an old satellite station to operate out of.

329
00:29:30,570 --> 00:29:32,970
We went out there in the middle of the night, and we...

330
00:29:34,020 --> 00:29:37,830
took them out, every one of them.

331
00:29:39,370 --> 00:29:41,820
These people got what they deserved.

332
00:29:42,010 --> 00:29:44,590
They chose to kill and to terrorize people,

333
00:29:44,590 --> 00:29:47,050
but that's not why we killed them.

334
00:29:47,210 --> 00:29:49,310
We didn't do it to make the world a better place.

335
00:29:49,310 --> 00:29:53,360
We did it because we wanted to stay alive, just like you.

336
00:29:54,390 --> 00:29:56,200
And I know that you think that me staying

337
00:29:56,210 --> 00:29:57,950
is the only solution.

338
00:29:57,990 --> 00:29:59,300
Well, how's this for brainstorming --

339
00:29:59,300 --> 00:30:01,310
maybe our groups can start working together.

340
00:30:01,310 --> 00:30:02,060
We just told you

341
00:30:02,060 --> 00:30:04,250
that we don't want anyone to know about this place.

342
00:30:04,250 --> 00:30:06,040
You can't live like that forever.

343
00:30:06,230 --> 00:30:07,850
I think we can.

344
00:30:07,980 --> 00:30:11,120
Look, I -- I get why you're doing it,

345
00:30:11,270 --> 00:30:12,780
but if you keep seeing everyone as an enemy,

346
00:30:12,780 --> 00:30:14,150
then enemies are all you're gonna find.

347
00:30:14,150 --> 00:30:17,680
Sooner or later, you're gonna need a friend.

348
00:30:17,890 --> 00:30:19,660
We can protect each other.

349
00:30:20,410 --> 00:30:22,370
We'd be safer than we are --

350
00:30:31,380 --> 00:30:32,560
All right.

351
00:30:34,090 --> 00:30:36,370
We could send a guide out with her.

352
00:30:37,380 --> 00:30:39,190
Help her look for her friend,

353
00:30:39,730 --> 00:30:42,460
and then continue on to their community,

354
00:30:42,860 --> 00:30:46,440
just -- just to see what it's like.

355
00:30:48,840 --> 00:30:50,070
Yeah, I'll do it.

356
00:30:51,370 --> 00:30:52,220
I want to go with her.

357
00:30:52,220 --> 00:30:53,590
Absolutely not.

358
00:30:53,590 --> 00:30:55,730
You left without leaving a routing plan,

359
00:30:55,730 --> 00:30:57,310
without signing with the gate.

360
00:30:57,320 --> 00:30:59,810
Cyndie, I thought we were through with all this.

361
00:31:00,060 --> 00:31:01,220
We are.

362
00:31:01,230 --> 00:31:02,640
You will be staying behind the fence

363
00:31:02,640 --> 00:31:04,910
until you learn some responsibility.

364
00:31:04,910 --> 00:31:05,810
If this works out,

365
00:31:05,810 --> 00:31:08,090
there will be plenty of other chances.

366
00:31:10,040 --> 00:31:11,580
And if it doesn't...

367
00:31:12,310 --> 00:31:13,850
I don't want you there.

368
00:31:16,290 --> 00:31:18,200
There will be other chances.

369
00:31:24,330 --> 00:31:26,760
Are you sure there isn't a fishing boat called a larder?

370
00:31:26,760 --> 00:31:28,230
'Cause I'm, like, pretty sure that --

371
00:31:28,230 --> 00:31:31,470
- There isn't. - ‭Yeah. Fair enough.

372
00:31:34,960 --> 00:31:36,310
This is gonna get better --

373
00:31:36,820 --> 00:31:38,190
people getting together.

374
00:31:38,330 --> 00:31:40,250
That's how the world is gonna be the world again.

375
00:31:40,710 --> 00:31:42,280
I hope you're right.

376
00:31:43,260 --> 00:31:44,430
Be safe.

377
00:31:44,750 --> 00:31:45,780
Where's Cyndie?

378
00:31:46,810 --> 00:31:49,080
She's in the cabin, sulking.

379
00:31:49,680 --> 00:31:50,540
We wouldn't be doing this

380
00:31:50,550 --> 00:31:52,500
if it wasn't for her breaking all the rules.

382
00:31:55,420 --> 00:31:56,680
Good luck, Tara.

383
00:32:00,320 --> 00:32:01,260
Yeah.

384
00:32:01,910 --> 00:32:04,400
you know, we'll -- we'll work on that, Natania.

385
00:32:04,630 --> 00:32:05,610
Thank you.

386
00:32:06,100 --> 00:32:07,240
See you soon.

387
00:32:22,650 --> 00:32:24,100
See you later, Rachel.

388
00:32:52,130 --> 00:32:53,370
Hey, Beatrice.

389
00:32:53,900 --> 00:32:55,280
I'm sorry about the hit.

390
00:32:56,030 --> 00:32:57,470
Well, you got lucky.

391
00:32:59,200 --> 00:33:00,230
Yeah, I did.

392
00:33:01,420 --> 00:33:03,170
How far are we to the bridge?

393
00:33:03,740 --> 00:33:05,160
About halfway there.

394
00:33:06,370 --> 00:33:07,010
Stick close.

395
00:33:07,010 --> 00:33:08,440
It's pretty thick through here.

396
00:33:25,000 --> 00:33:25,970
I got it.

397
00:35:04,950 --> 00:35:06,030
Please.

398
00:35:09,000 --> 00:35:10,950
I could have killed you back in the village.

399
00:35:12,700 --> 00:35:13,810
Let me go.

400
00:35:15,010 --> 00:35:16,650
You don't have anything left.

401
00:35:17,950 --> 00:35:19,470
Your people are dead.

402
00:35:21,570 --> 00:35:22,820
The Saviors.

403
00:35:23,580 --> 00:35:25,660
That satellite post you took out --

404
00:35:27,180 --> 00:35:29,410
you have no idea what you started.

405
00:35:29,880 --> 00:35:30,850
We didn't start anything.

406
00:35:30,850 --> 00:35:32,470
We ended it. They're dead.

407
00:35:32,470 --> 00:35:33,760
You didn't stop them.

408
00:35:34,270 --> 00:35:35,870
You can't stop them.

409
00:35:37,030 --> 00:35:38,580
That was just an outpost.

410
00:35:39,300 --> 00:35:42,070
There are more -- more Saviors...

411
00:35:43,520 --> 00:35:44,900
more outposts.

412
00:35:46,340 --> 00:35:48,000
If they know about your friends...

413
00:35:49,350 --> 00:35:50,900
it's already too late for them.

414
00:35:52,210 --> 00:35:53,440
The Saviors...

415
00:35:55,950 --> 00:35:57,320
they did this to you?

416
00:35:58,190 --> 00:36:00,100
They're the ones that killed all your men?

417
00:36:04,110 --> 00:36:05,380
Every man...

418
00:36:06,910 --> 00:36:08,340
every boy over 10.

419
00:36:10,130 --> 00:36:12,110
They lined 'em up, shot 'em in the head.

420
00:36:15,140 --> 00:36:16,650
You see, we tried to fight...

421
00:36:17,340 --> 00:36:18,530
just like you.

422
00:36:20,700 --> 00:36:21,760
They won.

423
00:36:22,700 --> 00:36:24,590
And we were supposed to keep working for them.

424
00:36:25,210 --> 00:36:27,760
Then one night, we just left.

425
00:36:29,480 --> 00:36:31,500
We got away, okay?

426
00:36:31,500 --> 00:36:33,820
We are not gonna let you lead them back to us.

427
00:36:36,200 --> 00:36:37,530
They get what they want.

428
00:36:41,140 --> 00:36:43,610
I'm sorry you didn't get --

429
00:36:45,270 --> 00:36:46,890
Go! Run!

430
00:37:12,190 --> 00:37:13,140
Wait!

431
00:37:22,560 --> 00:37:23,990
You're not gonna shoot me.

432
00:37:24,940 --> 00:37:26,260
Because I saved you?

433
00:37:26,720 --> 00:37:27,930
Three times now.

434
00:37:28,560 --> 00:37:29,870
You're not gonna shoot me.

435
00:37:33,380 --> 00:37:34,620
You have to swear...

436
00:37:35,780 --> 00:37:37,280
that you'll never come back

437
00:37:37,870 --> 00:37:39,800
and you'll never tell anyone about us,

438
00:37:40,140 --> 00:37:41,640
not even your own people.

439
00:37:46,300 --> 00:37:49,400
Why...would I come back?

440
00:37:50,250 --> 00:37:53,050
Why would I tell anyone about this place?

441
00:37:53,060 --> 00:37:55,240
Because maybe you could get something out of it --

442
00:37:56,300 --> 00:37:57,510
anything.

443
00:37:59,040 --> 00:38:01,730
Why did we kill those two people who just came near us?

444
00:38:04,780 --> 00:38:08,880
Why did you kill all those people at that satellite station?

445
00:38:09,690 --> 00:38:11,610
Because you all thought you had to.

446
00:38:14,460 --> 00:38:16,260
But none of you had to.

447
00:38:18,680 --> 00:38:19,900
You just did.

448
00:38:23,210 --> 00:38:24,540
Nobody's evil.

449
00:38:25,930 --> 00:38:29,300
They just decide to forget who they are.

450
00:38:31,820 --> 00:38:33,700
You have to swear.

451
00:38:40,270 --> 00:38:42,380
Some people are evil, Cyndie.

452
00:38:43,910 --> 00:38:45,180
I've seen it.

453
00:38:46,970 --> 00:38:49,180
That's why I have to get back now.

454
00:38:50,240 --> 00:38:51,730
You have to swear.

455
00:39:02,810 --> 00:39:04,030
I swear.

456
00:39:10,950 --> 00:39:11,970
Here.

457
00:39:12,300 --> 00:39:13,600
Food and water.

458
00:39:15,430 --> 00:39:16,440
‭C'mon.

459
00:39:16,790 --> 00:39:18,170
I'll take you to the bridge.

460
00:39:18,690 --> 00:39:20,300
Try not to fall off this time.

461
00:39:32,030 --> 00:39:34,050
- There's more, right? - Yeah, a lot.

462
00:39:34,060 --> 00:39:36,460
I'll use the cars as cover until I can't anymore.

463
00:39:36,910 --> 00:39:38,030
Then what?

464
00:39:39,050 --> 00:39:40,200
I'll run.

465
00:39:40,830 --> 00:39:42,120
I love to run.

466
00:39:42,280 --> 00:39:43,550
It's my favorite thing.

467
00:39:44,420 --> 00:39:45,810
You'll never make it.

468
00:39:46,920 --> 00:39:48,490
Yeah, I will.

469
00:39:50,430 --> 00:39:51,410
Let me help you.

470
00:39:51,410 --> 00:39:52,900
You already did. You got me here.

471
00:39:52,900 --> 00:39:55,500
Just go back. Tell them that I attacked you.

472
00:39:55,570 --> 00:39:56,710
They know you, Tara.

473
00:39:56,710 --> 00:39:57,820
No, tell them you killed me.

474
00:39:57,820 --> 00:39:59,070
They know me.

475
00:40:00,120 --> 00:40:01,120
You know I'm not going anywhere

476
00:40:01,120 --> 00:40:04,240
until you get to the other side -- safe.

477
00:40:05,070 --> 00:40:07,160
I've got my rifle. I've got ammo.

478
00:40:09,000 --> 00:40:11,150
I didn't get you here just to watch you die.

479
00:40:13,270 --> 00:40:16,170
So let's just get this over with, okay?

480
00:40:17,390 --> 00:40:21,120
Kathy and Beatrice -- they know we were coming here.

481
00:40:21,530 --> 00:40:22,650
They're coming.

482
00:40:27,300 --> 00:40:28,420
Okay.

483
00:40:29,760 --> 00:40:31,340
Why aren't you like the rest of them,

484
00:40:33,800 --> 00:40:35,330
after everything that's happened?

485
00:40:39,910 --> 00:40:41,180
Why aren't you?

486
00:40:46,620 --> 00:40:47,800
Okay.

487
00:41:47,090 --> 00:41:48,250
Okay, up on that side.

488
00:41:48,300 --> 00:41:49,240
Go!

489
00:42:51,150 --> 00:42:52,170
Heath!

490
00:42:52,330 --> 00:42:53,360
Heath!

491
00:42:54,320 --> 00:42:55,350
Heath!

492
00:43:12,510 --> 00:43:13,740
Heath, I'm coming!

493
00:43:14,850 --> 00:43:15,950
I'm coming!

494
00:43:16,050 --> 00:43:18,770
No! Go! Go!

495
00:43:20,310 --> 00:43:21,660
We're in this together!

496
00:43:22,490 --> 00:43:23,600
I know.

497
00:44:46,790 --> 00:44:48,090
Maybe that was you.

498
00:44:56,950 --> 00:44:58,130
I hope that was you.

501
00:48:02,910 --> 00:48:04,130
I'm sorry, Tara.

502
00:48:09,570 --> 00:48:10,930
I'm sorry, too.

503
00:48:15,910 --> 00:48:17,940
We don't have to just sit here.

504
00:48:22,500 --> 00:48:25,290
Guns, ammunition...

505
00:48:26,680 --> 00:48:28,130
you don't have any leads?

506
00:48:32,800 --> 00:48:35,190
Anything, anywhere.

507
00:48:35,190 --> 00:48:37,370
I don't care how dangerous it looked.

508
00:48:37,370 --> 00:48:38,960
Tell me a place.

509
00:48:38,960 --> 00:48:40,130
I'll go.

510
00:48:44,830 --> 00:48:46,270
There's gotta be somewhere.

511
00:48:48,830 --> 00:48:50,820
We can square this.

512
00:48:53,770 --> 00:48:55,470
We can make this right.

513
00:48:56,840 --> 00:48:58,160
We have to.

514
00:49:01,630 --> 00:49:02,820
We can't.

515
00:49:06,730 --> 00:49:09,280
I didn't see anything like that out there.

