[Script Info]
; Script generated by Aegisub 3.2.2
; http://www.aegisub.org/
Title: Subtitles
Original Script: Subtitles
website: www.zimuzu.tv
Sina Weibo: @zimuzu
Synch Point: 0
ScriptType: v4.00+
Timer: 100.0000

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,2,134
Style: LOGO,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H006C3300,&H00000000,-1,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,5,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.30,0:00:21.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们为什么不出来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.80,0:00:23.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,到路上来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.75,0:00:25.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真好
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.70,0:00:27.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一开始就很顺利
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.82,0:00:30.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在第二步  交出你们的武器
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.94,0:00:32.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,凭什么
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.27,0:00:33.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为武器不是你们的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.22,0:00:35.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那是谁的
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.34,0:00:39.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们的财产
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.50,0:00:42.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在归尼根所有
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.11,0:00:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你们能搞到大卡车
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.20,0:00:55.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那我们就想跟你们认识认识
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.69,0:00:59.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,交出随身武器  好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.76,0:01:02.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.66,0:01:10.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.51,0:01:17.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.25,0:01:26.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你得吃屎
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.50,0:01:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,最好别细细品味
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.80,0:01:32.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咬  咀嚼  吞咽  重复
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.84,0:01:33.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这样更快
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.65,0:01:46.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.24,0:01:51.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们是什么人
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.16,0:01:53.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我明白你很好奇
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.87,0:01:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们也有问题
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.23,0:02:00.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,而且要由我们来问问题
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.32,0:02:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,同时我们要送你们回家
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.55,0:02:08.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看你们在哪儿挂帽子
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.47,0:02:12.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但先聊聊你们的储备
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.95,0:02:14.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你们有什么东西
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.46,0:02:15.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你刚拿走了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.33,0:02:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,拜托
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.92,0:02:22.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能别装了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.61,0:02:24.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有更多东西
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.40,0:02:27.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,总是有更多东西
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.49,0:02:33.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,T
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.03,0:02:36.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,带我的手下去卡车后面
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.82,0:02:39.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从后保险杠里开始
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.03,0:02:41.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一直搜到前面
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.31,0:02:43.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.42,0:02:50.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,咬  咀嚼  吞咽  重复
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.90,0:02:52.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,尼根是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.11,0:02:56.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,叮咚  地狱的钟声响起了
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.80,0:03:02.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一般情况下我们自我介绍的方式是
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.46,0:03:04.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开枪打死你们中的一人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.93,0:03:06.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但你们看起来像是讲理的人
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.95,0:03:10.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊  你还穿着海军制服呢
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.90,0:03:13.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如我所说  我们要送你们回家
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.93,0:03:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你知道这有多尴尬吗
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.23,0:03:18.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟一个你刚杀了他朋友的人拼车
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.39,0:03:23.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我跟你们说了  别问问题
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.72,0:03:26.58,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果这红毛做了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.86,0:03:29.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就这样了
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.62,0:03:32.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不想让你们误以为我软弱
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.22,0:03:34.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.52,0:03:39.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.81,0:03:43.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没必要这样做
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.00,0:03:47.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,闭嘴
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.43,0:03:50.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我在跟管事的说话
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.83,0:03:53.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  你没有
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.00,0:04:05.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不会杀了你们的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.76,0:04:14.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,等等
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.06,0:04:17.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,知道吗
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.26,0:04:20.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会的
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.77,0:04:50.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那混蛋比看起来要厉害
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.62,0:04:54.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他割伤你了吗  -有点
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.27,0:04:58.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真是一群畜生
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.96,0:05:01.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,回家去给你包扎
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.45,0:05:03.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,遵命
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.74,0:05:14.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,细细品味吧
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.52,0:05:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an9\fs65\shad0\bord0\c&H4C9AB9&\b1\pos(308.4,176.8)\fn方正大黑_GBK}行尸走肉\N{\b0\fs18}『第六季  第九集』
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.52,0:05:54.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\fs21}本蓝光版外挂字幕由  {\c&H9B30FF&}风吹来的那片云{\c&HFFFFFF&}  用WEB版调轴
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.23,0:06:35.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an5\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\fscx0\fscy0\alpha&B0\c&H000000&\t(0,200,\fscx2000\fscy600\t(200,400,\fscx2500\fscy300\t(29800,30200,\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&H000000&\alpha&AA\fscy400\fscx400)))\move(158,211.2,46.5,211.2,29800,30200)}■
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.23,0:06:00.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\bord0\shad0\fs16\fn方正大黑_GBK\move(-150,211,56,211,400,600)\clip(54.24,192,230.88,228.48)}本字幕首发于{\c&HEBAE00&}字幕组{\c&HFFFFFF&}网站\N{\c&H00C0FF&}www.ZiMuZu.tv {\c&HFFFFFF&}欢迎交流
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.23,0:06:05.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,281,227))}翻译  冰蓝 小十三  33来了 小酸奶
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.23,0:06:10.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(0,500)\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\pos(57.12,210.56)\clip(134,195,134,227)\t(0,500,\clip(54,195,291,227))}翻译  君君 艾瑞卡 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.23,0:06:15.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\frx-630\t(0,500,\frx0\t(4500,5000,\clip(40,213,40,248)))\pos(57.12,210.56)}校对  冰蓝 君君 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.23,0:06:20.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(500,0)\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs17\bord0\shad0\move(57.12,210.56,400,210.56,4500,5000)\clip(54.24,193.92,284.24,228.48)}时间轴  加森 雪贵人 涛涛
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.23,0:06:25.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an4\fad(300,300)\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs17\bord0\c&HFFFFFF&\3c&HEDB425&\4c&H9EF6FF&\shad0\bord0\blur20\t(0,500,\blur0\t(4500,5000,\fs30\blur20))\pos(57.12,210.56)}后期 吉吉 拉图  总监 送小孩
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.17,0:07:55.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好了  新计划
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.11,0:07:59.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,几把枪的照明弹还不够
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.70,0:08:01.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行尸太多  太分散了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.10,0:08:03.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不去武器库了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.12,0:08:07.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要采石场的车子
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.72,0:08:10.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都开车  把它们赶在一起
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.66,0:08:12.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们离开  然后回来
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.02,0:08:15.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.22,0:08:20.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是朱迪思
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.24,0:08:22.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去采石场然后回来  我...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.49,0:08:30.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我带着她
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.11,0:08:33.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让她安全待在我的教堂里
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.17,0:08:34.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,直到你们引开行尸
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.64,0:08:39.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能做到吗
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.88,0:08:42.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该做到
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.05,0:08:44.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我必须做到
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.21,0:08:48.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会做到的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.43,0:08:51.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.84,0:09:07.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-带上山姆  -不行
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.23,0:09:08.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,行  山姆  这样更安全
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.61,0:09:09.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不要离开你
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.01,0:09:11.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-山姆  -妈  我不要
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.49,0:09:14.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我能继续
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.47,0:09:17.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-山姆  -我能继续
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.28,0:09:21.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.17,0:09:26.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.31,0:09:30.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.07,0:09:33.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.52,0:09:41.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会保护好她
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.03,0:09:45.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.61,0:10:12.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他能做到的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.73,0:10:14.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吗
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.66,0:10:17.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我知道的
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.84,0:10:22.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.99,0:10:56.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得试试
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.99,0:10:59.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能出去  行尸太多了
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.08,0:11:00.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗西塔  他会杀了她的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.48,0:11:01.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们到不了她那里
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.80,0:11:03.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她需要我们
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.08,0:11:04.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会送命的
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.69,0:11:05.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,结果就会是这样
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.90,0:11:07.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们只有一把枪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.13,0:11:09.32,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,满街都是行尸
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.45,0:11:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个人需要她
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.46,0:11:14.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她是医生  他病了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.18,0:11:17.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们都见识过他的生存能力
Dialogue: 0,0:11:17.42,0:11:20.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但我们得确保卡萝尔和摩根无恙
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.70,0:11:21.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,然后再作打算
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.91,0:11:23.36,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们不能就这样走了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.15,0:11:25.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.56,0:11:27.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.57,0:11:35.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,罗西塔  我需要你的枪
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.08,0:11:37.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去褐石房那边检查一下
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.66,0:11:40.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,看看还有没有其他隐患
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.27,0:11:41.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他醒了
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.23,0:11:44.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,慢点
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.98,0:11:53.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.37,0:11:57.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹妮斯人呢
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.78,0:12:00.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他劫持了她  是吧
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.92,0:12:09.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们扶你起来
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.30,0:12:40.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他们搜刮这地方时漏掉了一些东西
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.72,0:12:45.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,只要搜刮者不是艾登或希斯的小队
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.30,0:12:47.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,放松
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.52,0:12:54.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,圣经也翻一下
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.89,0:12:56.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,可能在里面挖了洞
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.48,0:12:57.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,真的有可能吗
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.92,0:13:00.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们有两颗子弹
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.94,0:13:02.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,有人曾在这里避难
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.70,0:13:06.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们可能会藏枪和弹药
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.93,0:13:09.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或可以点火的东西
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.18,0:13:13.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天快要黑了  或许我们可以把它们引开
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.74,0:13:20.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}没有行动的信念是死的  雅各书  2.26
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.99,0:13:17.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要床单  绳子  毛巾
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.71,0:13:19.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,能帮玛姬从另一边爬下来的东西就行
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.51,0:13:32.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,风水轮流转啊
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.76,0:13:35.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊妮德
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.46,0:13:41.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想逃离的时候
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.02,0:13:48.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说过  你这样会失去别人
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.57,0:13:54.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,即使在他们死后
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.79,0:14:00.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这到底是什么意思
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.15,0:14:05.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你爱的人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.70,0:14:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们造就了你
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.48,0:14:11.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们依然是你的一部分
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.44,0:14:14.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果你放弃自己
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.97,0:14:19.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们在你身上留下的造就你的最后痕迹
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.97,0:14:21.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就会消失
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.15,0:14:26.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说这些人是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.76,0:14:28.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我父母
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.87,0:14:32.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个叫戴尔的人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.14,0:14:35.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬的父亲  赫谢尔
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.74,0:14:39.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一个叫安德莉亚的女人  一个叫泰尔西的男人
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.50,0:14:40.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对你来说这些人是谁
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.91,0:14:49.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我的父母
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.60,0:14:54.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那他们就还在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.21,0:14:56.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为你还在
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.11,0:15:04.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,一旦有缺口
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.27,0:15:07.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们就冲到塔里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.84,0:15:10.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不行  我会拖累你的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.51,0:15:11.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹妮斯
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.62,0:15:15.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹妮斯  你现在
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.73,0:15:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和我一起
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.13,0:15:20.20,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要你
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.96,0:15:24.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许我想要你在身边 
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.16,0:15:27.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为我好喜欢有你的陪伴
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.23,0:15:32.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你待在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.59,0:15:34.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,什么
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.79,0:15:35.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我希望你能回来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.83,0:15:37.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我可以应付的
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.33,0:15:37.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你说过你需要帮忙  -不  
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.96,0:15:40.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不希望你对这个地方失去信心
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.39,0:15:43.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对这些人失去信心  或是感到害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.42,0:15:44.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.66,0:15:49.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以我现在在这里
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.67,0:15:52.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要出去给你帮忙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.63,0:15:56.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得把她从高台上救下来
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.74,0:15:58.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她受伤了  需要我们的帮助才能翻过墙
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.97,0:16:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去爬门  你去引开它们
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.42,0:16:03.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们齐心协力
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.69,0:16:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,反正我无论如何都会跟着你
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.36,0:16:18.70,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你继续找那圣经里的手枪吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.72,0:16:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我去做个东西帮她爬下去
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.61,0:16:29.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好吧
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.27,0:16:35.02,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我喜欢你之前说的那句
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.87,0:16:38.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我并非生来如此
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.76,0:16:41.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说得对
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.85,0:16:44.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我变了
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.06,0:16:48.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在我要帮你改变
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.03,0:16:59.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你说对了
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.09,0:17:04.44,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们去救玛姬吧
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.01,0:17:08.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你就不能老实待这儿吗  -不能
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.87,0:17:13.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是上天赐予你的礼物  丹妮斯
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.43,0:17:16.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你总有一天会明白的
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.78,0:17:20.09,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许不会
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.39,0:18:45.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怪物会来抓你
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.60,0:18:48.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们来抓你时  你跑也跑不掉
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.79,0:18:51.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,外面那些怪物
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.90,0:18:53.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会把你撕个粉碎  
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.70,0:18:57.00,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,啃个精光  生吞活剥
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.27,0:19:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.95,0:19:06.73,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.45,0:19:09.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走  快走
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.60,0:19:11.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-宝贝  山姆  -你能行的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.94,0:19:13.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-你能行的  -你能行的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.73,0:19:15.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆  山姆  走了
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.04,0:19:19.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快走  山姆  -山姆
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.97,0:19:21.53,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-山姆  -山姆
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.90,0:19:23.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,嘿  你可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.94,0:19:25.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆  看着妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.81,0:19:26.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亲爱的  你可以的
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.17,0:19:28.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆  你会被...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.39,0:19:30.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆  亲爱的  你得跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.96,0:19:33.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-山姆  -你得跟我来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.25,0:19:35.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我也想  -你要坚强起来
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.55,0:19:36.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,山姆
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.07,0:19:38.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,妈妈
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.72,0:20:05.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-杰茜  -杰茜  杰茜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.17,0:20:07.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  -杰茜  杰茜
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.03,0:20:08.56,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我们走
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.73,0:20:12.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快  我们得走了
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.64,0:20:16.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.01,0:20:23.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.02,0:20:26.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.10,0:20:37.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.91,0:20:51.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.95,0:21:15.74,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.16,0:21:22.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.49,0:21:42.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,爸爸
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.16,0:21:46.03,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,卡尔
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.88,0:21:49.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.58,0:22:31.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们迟早会杀出一条血路出去
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.19,0:22:37.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我知道你心里非常清楚  -是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.30,0:22:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们会的
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.35,0:22:43.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但不包括你
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.01,0:22:46.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-在我看来...  -尤金
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.52,0:22:51.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,得了吧
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.68,0:23:07.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,它们正在往枪声的地方走
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.26,0:23:11.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那声尖叫
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.77,0:23:15.12,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我估计有些人还以为他们能抵抗一下呢
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.17,0:23:17.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想你们都是这么想的
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.69,0:23:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的确抵抗了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.16,0:23:22.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,所以你的朋友们都死了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.68,0:23:24.60,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是啊
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.42,0:23:29.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们应该再等一等  再观望一会儿
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.59,0:23:32.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我太自私了
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.92,0:23:36.19,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但也许如果我不那么自私
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.61,0:23:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就根本不会得到救治
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.85,0:23:46.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得找个缺口出去
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.08,0:23:49.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,登上那座哨塔  翻到墙的那一边
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.05,0:23:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你不用害怕
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.06,0:23:59.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去死吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.24,0:24:01.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你得知道
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.99,0:24:04.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,在外面远比里面安全
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.45,0:24:05.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.38,0:24:07.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,开始走
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.85,0:24:17.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,现在  直接走到那个护柱下面
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.01,0:24:19.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,千万别停
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.75,0:24:20.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走吧
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.79,0:24:22.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死的
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.79,0:24:49.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走  跟我一起
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.93,0:24:53.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你把我送到医务室  我可以救你的命
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.80,0:24:55.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我会救你的
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.24,0:25:47.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你曾经有个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.81,0:25:50.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,对吧
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.98,0:25:56.08,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,还有丈夫
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.73,0:26:06.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我之前并非有意伤害你  我只是不得不阻止你
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.80,0:26:10.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你救他是为了你自己  不是为了我们
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.62,0:26:14.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果是为了我们  你就会...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.03,0:26:25.92,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我应该杀了你的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.38,0:26:28.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我真该那么做的
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.34,0:26:39.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你杀不了
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.03,0:26:56.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,医务室就在巷子对面
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.61,0:26:58.51,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须立刻把你弄过去
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.10,0:27:05.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那个梯子周围没有行尸  我本可以爬上去的
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.87,0:27:07.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你为了我而回头
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.71,0:27:10.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是因为你需要医生
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.93,0:27:13.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,或许是因为你变了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.18,0:27:17.13,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你准备好了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.59,0:27:34.59,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走  快走
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.97,0:27:38.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,走  快走
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.37,0:27:40.67,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走啊
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.66,0:27:51.71,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快  进来
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.84,0:27:53.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你没事吧
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.01,0:27:55.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我没事  我的病人们怎么样了
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.61,0:27:57.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他们挺好的  我们把他们转移到楼上了以防万一
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.97,0:27:59.14,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,天啊
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.07,0:28:09.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是那个孩子
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.58,0:28:10.57,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他被咬了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.29,0:28:16.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,没有
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.86,0:28:18.23,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,怎么了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.23,0:28:19.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要绷带
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.73,0:28:21.55,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就在水槽边最高层的架子上
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.55,0:28:24.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,从冰箱里拿两支注射液  干净毛巾越多越好
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.39,0:28:25.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,亚伦  把轮床推过来
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.95,0:28:36.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是枪伤吗
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.35,0:28:38.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,手枪  近距离射击
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.02,0:28:42.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你救救他
Dialogue: 0,0:28:42.66,0:28:43.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.02,0:28:48.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,那会把行尸引过来的
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.21,0:28:49.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我需要光源
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.23,0:28:52.94,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米琼恩  拿毛巾来  准备好
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.44,0:28:54.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们需要压住伤口
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.40,0:28:57.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我探进去缝合撕裂处
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.44,0:28:59.72,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是这样  就那里
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.72,0:29:02.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,斯宾塞  我需要那个平盘
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.39,0:29:04.34,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就是托盘上的那个  很好
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.64,0:29:06.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要进行清洗和缝合
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.78,0:29:09.98,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,米琼恩  我弄到哪儿你就用毛巾跟着擦拭
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.03,0:29:27.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.88,0:29:29.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.20,0:29:32.49,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,瑞克
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.84,0:29:59.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-瑞克在外面  -坚持住
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.55,0:30:01.52,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-他需要我帮忙  -再缝一针
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.52,0:30:02.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但他在外面
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.45,0:30:05.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这是他儿子  给我点时间
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.05,0:30:05.99,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他在孤军奋战
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.99,0:30:07.84,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我们得去帮他  -什么
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.37,0:30:09.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们必须去
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.77,0:30:11.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-就看这一战了  -搞定了
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.13,0:31:09.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,击退它们  压制它们
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.28,0:31:17.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能打败它们
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.89,0:31:27.85,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,击退它们  就这样
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.13,0:31:29.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能一起做到
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.36,0:31:36.39,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能抱着她吗
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.24,0:31:40.31,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当然
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.47,0:31:42.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,跟我来  好的
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.69,0:31:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-谢谢你  -没事
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.68,0:31:50.79,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,加百利
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.85,0:31:54.15,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你要干什么
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.23,0:32:01.63,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们一直在一起祈祷
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.10,0:32:06.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,祈祷上帝能拯救我们的小镇
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.41,0:32:09.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们的祈祷应验了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.59,0:32:12.54,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,上帝会拯救亚历山大
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.77,0:32:17.87,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为上帝给予了我们拯救自己的勇气
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.36,0:32:30.11,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,前面的尸群散开了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:30.80,0:32:31.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们得离开这里
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.77,0:32:33.83,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-瑞克在进行抵抗  -怎么抵抗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.04,0:32:36.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,他正在外面与米琼恩他们一同战斗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.34,0:32:38.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,是时候了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.86,0:32:40.62,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我要去巷子里
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.44,0:32:42.88,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,丹妮斯很安全
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.08,0:32:44.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你看到她了吗
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.67,0:32:46.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,她撑到医务室了
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.23,0:32:49.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我去帮瑞克  -我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.54,0:32:51.40,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我跟你一起  -那好  我也去
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.64,0:32:54.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-我跟着你  -尤金  你不必这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.45,0:32:56.06,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这不对  我必须这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.72,0:32:58.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,今天没人能置身事外
Dialogue: 0,0:32:58.61,0:33:02.29,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死  今天的事将被载入史册
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.94,0:33:13.21,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边  快点
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.04,0:33:25.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,抱歉
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.66,0:33:33.77,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.66,0:33:38.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去帮她
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.02,0:33:40.22,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,去帮她
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.37,0:33:46.46,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来这边
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.50,0:33:49.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点  这边
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.57,0:33:53.18,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-来这边  -格伦
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.66,0:33:56.86,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  格伦
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.22,0:34:00.66,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-格伦  -过来  来这边  过来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.60,0:34:02.69,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,玛姬
Dialogue: 0,0:34:03.69,0:34:04.75,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,伊妮德
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.66,0:34:08.93,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,这边  这边  过来啊
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.88,0:34:14.90,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.85,0:34:17.48,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走  快翻过去
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.48,0:34:18.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-快走  -不
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.93,0:34:20.01,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快走
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.91,0:34:21.97,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,快点
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.56,0:34:29.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,该死
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.41,0:34:33.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,-不  格伦  -快走
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.28,0:34:35.47,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来这边
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.87,0:34:40.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格伦
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.30,0:34:44.82,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,格伦
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.99,0:34:54.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,你能把门打开吗
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.16,0:34:57.50,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,谢谢  伙计
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.80,0:35:08.43,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,来吧  我们拉你
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.87,0:35:18.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,发生了什么
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.10,0:35:19.33,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我不知道  我刚回来
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.57,0:35:21.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,听着
Dialogue: 0,0:35:22.41,0:35:24.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们可以引开一部分行尸
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.61,0:35:25.80,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是它们很分散
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.84,0:35:27.37,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不  我们一网打尽
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.56,0:35:28.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,不用引开它们
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.46,0:36:37.61,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,移动  后退
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.86,0:36:43.16,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,好  可以了
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.01,0:37:20.30,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,别松懈
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.33,0:39:37.64,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我错了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.02,0:39:45.25,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我以为在墙内生活了这么久
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.34,0:39:50.26,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,也许他们学不会了
Dialogue: 0,0:39:53.80,0:39:55.10,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,但是今天
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.73,0:39:58.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我看到了他们能做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.01,0:40:02.81,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们能做什么
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.05,0:40:05.65,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,如果我们一起合作
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.29,0:40:10.38,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就可以重建这些墙
Dialogue: 0,0:40:13.29,0:40:15.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,扩建这些墙
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.30,0:40:19.68,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,会有希望的  一定会有的
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.83,0:40:24.24,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,迪安娜说的一切
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.95,0:40:28.42,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,都有可能
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.06,0:40:32.89,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,全都有可能  我现在明白了
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.55,0:40:41.05,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当我在外面 
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.94,0:40:45.04,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,和他们在一起时
Dialogue: 0,0:40:47.77,0:40:49.35,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,当这一切结束
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.77,0:40:57.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我们重新夺回这个地方时
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.49,0:41:01.96,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我心中有一种感觉
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.76,0:41:09.45,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我花了一段时间
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.66,0:41:12.41,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,才想起来那感觉是什么
Dialogue: 0,0:41:14.26,0:41:16.07,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,因为自从我在医院醒来后
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.64,0:41:20.17,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,就再没有过那种感觉了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.95,0:41:28.27,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想让你看看新世界  卡尔
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.78,0:41:34.78,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,我想为你使之成为现实
Dialogue: 0,0:41:36.02,0:41:39.91,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  卡尔
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.96,0:41:45.28,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,让我给你看看吧
Dialogue: 0,0:41:45.28,0:41:48.76,*Default,NTP,0000,0000,0000,,求你了  儿子  别死
