1
00:00:20,300 --> 00:00:21,400
你們為什么不出來
Why don't you come on out,

2
00:00:21,800 --> 00:00:23,080
到路上來
join us on the road?

3
00:00:24,750 --> 00:00:25,670
真好
Yeah, that's great.

4
00:00:25,700 --> 00:00:27,270
一開始就很順利
It's going well right out of the gate.

5
00:00:27,820 --> 00:00:30,740
現在第二步  交出你們的武器
Now, step two-- hand over your weapons.

6
00:00:30,940 --> 00:00:32,000
憑什么
Why should we?

7
00:00:32,270 --> 00:00:33,800
因為武器不是你們的
Well, they're not yours.

8
00:00:34,220 --> 00:00:35,480
那是誰的
Whose are they?

9
00:00:38,340 --> 00:00:39,630
你們的財產
Your property...

10
00:00:40,500 --> 00:00:42,710
現在歸尼根所有
now belongs to Negan.

11
00:00:50,110 --> 00:00:52,140
如果你們能搞到大卡車
And if you can get your hands on a tanker,

12
00:00:53,200 --> 00:00:55,380
那我們就想跟你們認識認識
you're people our person wants to know.

13
00:00:57,690 --> 00:00:59,670
交出隨身武器  好嗎
So let's get those sidearms, shall we?

14
00:01:01,760 --> 00:01:02,550
快點
Right now.

15
00:01:09,660 --> 00:01:10,470
謝謝
Thank you.

16
00:01:16,510 --> 00:01:17,350
謝謝
Thank you.

17
00:01:25,250 --> 00:01:26,900
如果你得吃屎
If you have to eat shit,

18
00:01:27,500 --> 00:01:28,870
最好別細細品味
best not to nibble.

19
00:01:29,800 --> 00:01:32,230
咬  咀嚼  吞咽  重復
Bite, chew, swallow, repeat.

20
00:01:32,840 --> 00:01:33,870
這樣更快
It goes quicker.

21
00:01:45,650 --> 00:01:46,760
謝謝
Thank you.

22
00:01:50,240 --> 00:01:51,700
你們是什么人
Who are you people?

23
00:01:52,160 --> 00:01:53,910
我明白你很好奇
I get the curiosity,

24
00:01:54,870 --> 00:01:57,000
但我們也有問題
but we have questions ourselves.

25
00:01:58,230 --> 00:02:00,080
而且要由我們來問問題
And we'll be the ones asking them

26
00:02:01,320 --> 00:02:04,440
同時我們要送你們回家
while we drive you back to wherever it is you call home.

27
00:02:05,550 --> 00:02:08,110
看看你們在哪兒掛帽子
Take a gander at where you hang your hats.

28
00:02:09,470 --> 00:02:12,270
但先聊聊你們的儲備
First, though, your shit.

29
00:02:12,950 --> 00:02:14,200
你們有什么東西
What have you got for us?

30
00:02:14,460 --> 00:02:15,760
你剛拿走了
Yeah, you just took it.

31
00:02:19,330 --> 00:02:20,360
拜托
Come on.

32
00:02:20,920 --> 00:02:22,870
能別裝了嗎
I mean, can we not, okay?

33
00:02:23,610 --> 00:02:24,650
有更多東西
There's more.

34
00:02:25,400 --> 00:02:27,850
總是有更多東西
There is always more.

35
00:02:32,490 --> 00:02:33,290
T
T...

36
00:02:35,030 --> 00:02:36,980
帶我的手下去卡車后面
Take my man to the back of the truck,

37
00:02:37,820 --> 00:02:39,680
從后保險杠里開始
start inside the back bumper,

38
00:02:40,030 --> 00:02:41,530
一直搜到前面
Work your way to the front.

39
00:02:42,310 --> 00:02:43,100
快走
Go.

40
00:02:46,420 --> 00:02:50,650
咬  咀嚼  吞咽  重復
Bite, chew, swallow, repeat.

41
00:02:50,900 --> 00:02:52,140
尼根是誰
Who's Negan?

42
00:02:53,110 --> 00:02:56,770
叮咚  地獄的鐘聲響起了
Ding, dong, hell's bells.

43
00:02:59,800 --> 00:03:02,460
一般情況下我們自我介紹的方式是
You see, usually we introduce ourselves

44
00:03:02,460 --> 00:03:04,920
開槍打死你們中的一人
by just popping one of you right off the bat.

45
00:03:04,930 --> 00:03:06,880
但你們看起來像是講理的人
But you seem like reasonable people.

46
00:03:06,950 --> 00:03:10,580
天啊  你還穿著海軍制服呢
I mean, you're sportin' dress blues, for christ's sake.

47
00:03:10,900 --> 00:03:13,300
如我所說  我們要送你們回家
And, like I said, we're gonna drive you back to where you were.

48
00:03:13,930 --> 00:03:15,230
你知道這有多尷尬嗎
I mean, do you know how awkward it is

49
00:03:15,230 --> 00:03:18,290
跟一個你剛殺了他朋友的人拼車
carpooling with someone whose friend or friends you've just killed?

50
00:03:20,390 --> 00:03:23,880
但我跟你們說了  別問問題
But I told you not to ask any questions.

51
00:03:24,720 --> 00:03:26,580
結果這紅毛做了什么
And then what does this ginger do?

52
00:03:28,860 --> 00:03:29,940
就這樣了
So that's that.

53
00:03:30,620 --> 00:03:32,900
我不想讓你們誤以為我軟弱
I don't want you to get the wrong impression of me.

54
00:03:33,220 --> 00:03:34,040
等等
Wait.

55
00:03:38,520 --> 00:03:39,620
等等
Wait.

56
00:03:41,810 --> 00:03:43,390
你沒必要這樣做
You don't have to do this.

57
00:03:46,000 --> 00:03:47,000
閉嘴
Shut up.

58
00:03:47,430 --> 00:03:50,220
我在跟管事的說話
I am talking to the man.

59
00:03:50,830 --> 00:03:53,360
不  你沒有
No, you're not.

60
00:04:04,000 --> 00:04:05,730
我不會殺了你們的
I'm not gonna kill you.

61
00:04:11,760 --> 00:04:14,360
等等
Wait, wait.

62
00:04:17,060 --> 00:04:17,850
知道嗎
You know what?

63
00:04:19,260 --> 00:04:20,220
我會的
Yes, I am.

64
00:04:48,770 --> 00:04:50,640
那混蛋比看起來要厲害
Son of a bitch was tougher than he looked.

65
00:04:51,620 --> 00:04:54,370
-他割傷你了嗎  -有點
- Did he cut you? - A little.

66
00:04:57,270 --> 00:04:58,790
真是一群畜生
What a bunch of assholes.

67
00:04:59,960 --> 00:05:01,590
回家去給你包扎
Let's get you fixed up at home.

68
00:05:02,450 --> 00:05:03,560
遵命
Yes, ma'am.

69
00:05:12,740 --> 00:05:14,070
細細品味吧
Nibble on that.

70
00:05:50,520 --> 00:05:54,730
行尸走肉
『第六季  第九集』

71
00:05:50,520 --> 00:05:54,730
本藍光版外掛字幕由  風吹來的那片云  用WEB版調軸

72
00:05:55,230 --> 00:06:25,230
m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10m -13 -14 l 13 -14 l 13 12 l -13 12 l -13 -14

73
00:05:55,230 --> 00:06:25,230
m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10

74
00:05:55,230 --> 00:06:25,230
m -13 -10 l -13 -13 l 10 -13 l -6 3 l -8 1 l 3 -10 l -13 -10

75
00:05:55,230 --> 00:06:35,230
■

76
00:05:55,230 --> 00:06:00,230
本字幕首發于字幕組網站
www.ZiMuZu.tv 歡迎交流

77
00:06:00,230 --> 00:06:05,230
翻譯  冰藍 小十三  33來了 小酸奶

78
00:06:05,230 --> 00:06:10,230
翻譯  君君 艾瑞卡 送小孩

79
00:06:10,230 --> 00:06:15,230
校對  冰藍 君君 送小孩

80
00:06:15,230 --> 00:06:20,230
時間軸  加森 雪貴人 濤濤

81
00:06:20,230 --> 00:06:25,230
后期 吉吉 拉圖  總監 送小孩

82
00:07:53,170 --> 00:07:55,400
好了  新計劃
All right, new plan.

83
00:07:57,110 --> 00:07:59,650
幾把槍的照明彈還不夠
Flares from a few guns aren't enough.

84
00:07:59,700 --> 00:08:01,970
行尸太多  太分散了
Too many walkers, too spread out.

85
00:08:02,100 --> 00:08:03,870
我們不去武器庫了
We're not going to the armory.

86
00:08:05,120 --> 00:08:07,360
我們需要采石場的車子
We need our vehicles back at the quarry.

87
00:08:07,720 --> 00:08:10,620
我們都開車  把它們趕在一起
All of us drive. We'll need to round 'em up.

88
00:08:10,660 --> 00:08:12,850
我們離開  然后回來
We leave, we come back.

89
00:08:15,020 --> 00:08:15,850
好
Okay.

90
00:08:19,220 --> 00:08:20,340
但是朱迪思
But Judith...

91
00:08:21,240 --> 00:08:22,940
去采石場然后回來  我...
To the quarry and back, I...

92
00:08:29,490 --> 00:08:30,500
我帶著她
I'll take her.

93
00:08:32,110 --> 00:08:33,170
讓她安全待在我的教堂里
Keep her safe in my church

94
00:08:33,170 --> 00:08:34,860
直到你們引開行尸
until you all lead the walkers away.

95
00:08:38,640 --> 00:08:39,800
你能做到嗎
Can you do this?

96
00:08:41,880 --> 00:08:42,930
我應該做到
I'm supposed to.

97
00:08:44,050 --> 00:08:44,890
我必須做到
I have to.

98
00:08:47,210 --> 00:08:48,100
我會做到的
I will.

99
00:08:50,430 --> 00:08:51,230
好吧
All right.

100
00:09:05,840 --> 00:09:07,170
-帶上山姆  -不行
- Take Sam. - No.

101
00:09:07,230 --> 00:09:08,610
行  山姆  這樣更安全
Yes, Sam, it'll be safer.

102
00:09:08,610 --> 00:09:09,890
我不要離開你
I'm not leaving you.

103
00:09:10,010 --> 00:09:11,810
-山姆  -媽  我不要
- Sam-- - Mom, I'm not.

104
00:09:13,490 --> 00:09:14,850
我能繼續
I can keep going.

105
00:09:15,470 --> 00:09:17,400
-山姆  -我能繼續
- Sam-- - I can keep going.

106
00:09:20,280 --> 00:09:21,180
求你了
Please.

107
00:09:25,170 --> 00:09:26,030
求你了
Please.

108
00:09:29,310 --> 00:09:30,590
我們走吧
Let's just go.

109
00:09:33,070 --> 00:09:33,870
好
Okay.

110
00:09:39,520 --> 00:09:41,350
我會保護好她
I'm going to keep her safe.

111
00:09:45,030 --> 00:09:45,870
謝謝
Thank you.

112
00:10:11,610 --> 00:10:12,870
他能做到的
He's gonna make it.

113
00:10:13,730 --> 00:10:14,510
好嗎
Okay?

114
00:10:16,660 --> 00:10:17,590
我知道的
I know it.

115
00:10:21,840 --> 00:10:22,710
山姆
Sam.

116
00:10:55,990 --> 00:10:56,990
我們得試試
We have to try.

117
00:10:56,990 --> 00:10:59,080
我們不能出去  行尸太多了
We cannot go out there. There are too many of them.

118
00:10:59,080 --> 00:11:00,480
羅西塔  他會殺了她的
Rosita, he's gonna kill her.

119
00:11:00,480 --> 00:11:01,800
我們到不了她那里
We won't get to her.

120
00:11:01,800 --> 00:11:03,080
她需要我們
She needs us.

121
00:11:03,080 --> 00:11:04,020
我們會送命的
We'll die.

122
00:11:04,690 --> 00:11:05,900
結果就會是這樣
That is what will happen.

123
00:11:05,900 --> 00:11:07,130
我們只有一把槍
We have one gun,

124
00:11:07,130 --> 00:11:09,320
滿街都是行尸
and the streets are filled with those things.

125
00:11:10,450 --> 00:11:11,870
那個人需要她
That man needs her.

126
00:11:12,460 --> 00:11:14,700
她是醫生  他病了
Okay? She's a doctor. He is sick.

127
00:11:15,180 --> 00:11:17,410
我們都見識過他的生存能力
And I think we've seen that he knows how to survive.

128
00:11:17,420 --> 00:11:20,360
但我們得確保卡蘿爾和摩根無恙
But we need to make sure that Carol and Morgan are okay.

129
00:11:20,700 --> 00:11:21,910
然后再作打算
And then we make a plan.

130
00:11:21,910 --> 00:11:23,360
我們不能就這樣走了
We cannot just go.

131
00:11:25,150 --> 00:11:25,990
好吧
Okay.

132
00:11:26,560 --> 00:11:27,930
天啊
Oh, god.

133
00:11:33,570 --> 00:11:35,700
羅西塔  我需要你的槍
Rosita, gonna need your gun.

134
00:11:36,080 --> 00:11:37,660
我去褐石房那邊檢查一下
Gonna do a sweep of the brownstone.

135
00:11:37,660 --> 00:11:40,160
看看還有沒有其他隱患
I want to see what other surprises are in here.

136
00:11:40,270 --> 00:11:41,920
他醒了
Hey, he's waking up.

137
00:11:43,230 --> 00:11:44,170
慢點
Easy.

138
00:11:51,980 --> 00:11:53,130
他人呢
Where is he?

139
00:11:56,370 --> 00:11:57,480
丹妮斯人呢
Where's Denise?

140
00:11:57,780 --> 00:12:00,740
他劫持了她  是吧
He took her, didn't he?

141
00:12:07,920 --> 00:12:09,090
我們扶你起來
Let's get you up.

142
00:12:38,300 --> 00:12:40,490
也許他們搜刮這地方時漏掉了一些東西
Maybe when they searched this place, they missed something.

143
00:12:40,720 --> 00:12:45,000
只要搜刮者不是艾登或希斯的小隊
Depends if it was Aiden or Heath's group who went through it.

144
00:12:46,300 --> 00:12:47,210
放松
Easy.

145
00:12:53,520 --> 00:12:54,780
圣經也翻一下
Look in the bibles, too.

146
00:12:54,890 --> 00:12:56,440
可能在里面挖了洞
Could've hollowed out the pages.

147
00:12:56,480 --> 00:12:57,670
真的有可能嗎
Are you serious?

148
00:12:58,920 --> 00:13:00,210
我們有兩顆子彈
We have two bullets.

149
00:13:00,940 --> 00:13:02,420
有人曾在這里避難
People holed up in here.

150
00:13:04,700 --> 00:13:06,920
他們可能會藏槍和彈藥
People hide guns, ammo.

151
00:13:07,930 --> 00:13:09,510
或可以點火的東西
Maybe something to start a fire.

152
00:13:11,180 --> 00:13:13,410
天快要黑了  或許我們可以把它們引開
It's getting dark out soon. Maybe we can distract them.

153
00:13:14,740 --> 00:13:20,000
沒有行動的信念是死的  雅各書  2.26

154
00:13:14,990 --> 00:13:17,710
我們需要床單  繩子  毛巾
We need sheets, ropes, towels.

155
00:13:17,710 --> 00:13:19,920
能幫瑪姬從另一邊爬下來的東西就行
Anything Maggie can use to climb down the other side.

156
00:13:31,510 --> 00:13:32,870
風水輪流轉啊
How things turn.

157
00:13:34,760 --> 00:13:35,600
伊妮德
Enid.

158
00:13:39,460 --> 00:13:41,160
我想逃離的時候
When I wanted to run...

159
00:13:45,020 --> 00:13:48,170
你說過  你這樣會失去別人
You said, "That's how you lose people...

160
00:13:52,570 --> 00:13:54,140
即使在他們死后
even after they're gone."

161
00:13:58,790 --> 00:14:00,450
這到底是什么意思
What the hell does that mean?

162
00:14:04,150 --> 00:14:05,410
你愛的人
People you love...

163
00:14:07,700 --> 00:14:09,290
他們造就了你
They made you who you are.

164
00:14:10,480 --> 00:14:11,980
他們依然是你的一部分
They're still part of you.

165
00:14:13,440 --> 00:14:14,990
如果你放棄自己
If you stop being you,

166
00:14:15,970 --> 00:14:19,110
他們在你身上留下的造就你的最后痕跡
that last bit of them that's still around inside, who you are...

167
00:14:20,970 --> 00:14:21,750
就會消失
It's gone.

168
00:14:25,150 --> 00:14:26,770
對你來說這些人是誰
Who are those people to you?

169
00:14:27,760 --> 00:14:28,870
我父母
My parents.

170
00:14:30,870 --> 00:14:32,190
一個叫戴爾的人
A man named Dale.

171
00:14:34,140 --> 00:14:35,900
瑪姬的父親  赫謝爾
Maggie's father, Hershel.

172
00:14:36,740 --> 00:14:39,260
一個叫安德莉亞的女人  一個叫泰爾西的男人
A woman named Andrea. A man named Tyreese.

173
00:14:39,500 --> 00:14:40,740
對你來說這些人是誰
Who are they to you?

174
00:14:47,910 --> 00:14:49,130
我的父母
My parents.

175
00:14:52,600 --> 00:14:54,030
那他們就還在這里
Then they're still here...

176
00:14:55,210 --> 00:14:56,650
因為你還在
'cause you're still here.

177
00:15:03,110 --> 00:15:04,370
一旦有缺口
When there's an opening,

178
00:15:05,270 --> 00:15:07,380
我們就沖到塔里
we'll make a break for that tower.

179
00:15:08,840 --> 00:15:10,450
不行  我會拖累你的
No, I'll just slow you down.

180
00:15:10,510 --> 00:15:11,480
丹妮斯
Denise.

181
00:15:12,620 --> 00:15:15,790
丹妮斯  你現在
Denise, you're here...

182
00:15:16,730 --> 00:15:17,780
和我一起
With me.

183
00:15:19,130 --> 00:15:20,200
我需要你
I need you.

184
00:15:22,960 --> 00:15:24,830
也許我想要你在身邊 
Maybe I want you to stay

185
00:15:25,160 --> 00:15:27,420
因為我好喜歡有你的陪伴
'cause I'm enjoying your company so much.

186
00:15:31,230 --> 00:15:32,640
你待在這里
I want you to stay put.

187
00:15:33,590 --> 00:15:34,540
什么
What?

188
00:15:34,790 --> 00:15:35,830
我希望你能回來
I wanted you to come back.

189
00:15:35,830 --> 00:15:37,330
我可以應付的
I can handle myself.

190
00:15:37,330 --> 00:15:37,960
-你說過你需要幫忙  -不  
- You said you wanted help. - No,

191
00:15:37,960 --> 00:15:40,250
我不希望你對這個地方失去信心
I didn't want you to give up on this place,

192
00:15:40,390 --> 00:15:43,150
對這些人失去信心  或是感到害怕
On these people, to be afraid.

193
00:15:43,420 --> 00:15:44,520
你說得對
You were right.

194
00:15:47,660 --> 00:15:49,100
所以我現在在這里
So I'm here now.

195
00:15:49,670 --> 00:15:52,530
我要出去給你幫忙
And I'm going out there and I'm helping you.

196
00:15:54,630 --> 00:15:56,740
我們得把她從高臺上救下來
We have to get her off that platform.

197
00:15:56,740 --> 00:15:58,970
她受傷了  需要我們的幫助才能翻過墻
She's hurt. She needs help getting over the wall.

198
00:15:58,970 --> 00:16:01,630
我去爬門  你去引開它們
I can climb up the gate. You can distract them.

199
00:16:02,420 --> 00:16:03,670
我們齊心協力
We do it together.

200
00:16:06,690 --> 00:16:08,560
反正我無論如何都會跟著你
I'm just gonna follow you, anyway.

201
00:16:15,360 --> 00:16:18,700
你繼續找那圣經里的手槍吧
You keep looking for the Bible glock...

202
00:16:21,720 --> 00:16:23,500
我去做個東西幫她爬下去
I'll make her something to climb down.

203
00:16:28,610 --> 00:16:29,470
好吧
Okay.

204
00:16:33,270 --> 00:16:35,020
我喜歡你之前說的那句
I like what you said before.

205
00:16:36,870 --> 00:16:38,550
我并非生來如此
That I wasn't born this way.

206
00:16:40,760 --> 00:16:41,770
你說得對
You're right.

207
00:16:42,850 --> 00:16:44,290
我變了
I changed.

208
00:16:46,060 --> 00:16:48,620
現在我要幫你改變
And now I want to help you change.

209
00:16:59,030 --> 00:16:59,990
你說對了
You were right.

210
00:17:03,090 --> 00:17:04,440
我們去救瑪姬吧
Let's get Maggie.

211
00:17:06,010 --> 00:17:08,090
-你就不能老實待這兒嗎  -不能
- Can't you just stay here? - Nope.

212
00:17:10,870 --> 00:17:13,100
這是上天賜予你的禮物  丹妮斯
You've been given a gift, Denise.

213
00:17:15,430 --> 00:17:16,890
你總有一天會明白的
You'll see that one day.

214
00:17:18,780 --> 00:17:20,090
也許不會
Or maybe you won't.

215
00:18:43,390 --> 00:18:45,100
怪物會來抓你
The monsters will come,

216
00:18:45,600 --> 00:18:48,590
它們來抓你時  你跑也跑不掉
And you won't be able to run away when they come for you.

217
00:18:49,790 --> 00:18:51,080
外面那些怪物
The ones out there.

218
00:18:51,900 --> 00:18:53,640
會把你撕個粉碎  
And they will tear you apart

219
00:18:53,700 --> 00:18:57,000
啃個精光  生吞活剝
and eat you up all while you're still alive.

220
00:19:04,270 --> 00:19:05,050
山姆
Sam?

221
00:19:05,950 --> 00:19:06,730
山姆
Sam?

222
00:19:07,450 --> 00:19:09,030
快走  快走
Come on, come on.

223
00:19:09,600 --> 00:19:11,550
-寶貝  山姆  -你能行的
- Sweetheart? Sam?  - You can do it.

224
00:19:11,940 --> 00:19:13,310
-你能行的  -你能行的
- You can do it. - Yes, you can.

225
00:19:13,730 --> 00:19:15,940
山姆  山姆  走了
Sam. Sam, come on.

226
00:19:17,040 --> 00:19:19,120
-快走  山姆  -山姆
- Come on, Sam. - Sam.

227
00:19:19,970 --> 00:19:21,530
-山姆  -山姆
- Sam? - Sam...

228
00:19:21,900 --> 00:19:23,500
嘿  你可以的
Hey, you can do this.

229
00:19:23,940 --> 00:19:25,260
山姆  看著媽媽
Sam, just look at mom.

230
00:19:25,810 --> 00:19:26,990
親愛的  你可以的
Honey, you can do it.

231
00:19:27,170 --> 00:19:28,290
山姆  你會被...
Sam, you're gonna get--

232
00:19:29,390 --> 00:19:30,960
山姆  親愛的  你得跟我來
Sam, honey, I need you to come with me.

233
00:19:30,960 --> 00:19:33,250
-山姆  -你得跟我來
- Sam. - I need you to come with me.

234
00:19:33,250 --> 00:19:35,550
-我也想  -你要堅強起來
- I want to. - I need you to be strong.

235
00:19:35,550 --> 00:19:36,300
山姆
Sam-- -

236
00:19:37,070 --> 00:19:38,980
媽媽
Mom!

237
00:20:01,720 --> 00:20:05,170
-杰茜  -杰茜  杰茜
- Jessie? - Jessie. Jessie.

238
00:20:05,170 --> 00:20:07,030
-不  -杰茜  杰茜
- No. - Jessie. Jessie.

239
00:20:07,030 --> 00:20:08,560
跟我們走
Come with us.

240
00:20:10,730 --> 00:20:12,990
快  我們得走了
Come on. We have to go.

241
00:20:15,640 --> 00:20:16,370
不
No.

242
00:20:23,010 --> 00:20:23,940
不
No.

243
00:20:26,020 --> 00:20:26,860
不
No.

244
00:20:37,100 --> 00:20:37,910
爸爸
Dad.

245
00:20:50,910 --> 00:20:51,690
快走
Come on.

246
00:21:14,950 --> 00:21:15,740
你
You.

247
00:21:22,160 --> 00:21:22,900
你
You.

248
00:21:41,490 --> 00:21:42,210
爸爸
Dad?

249
00:21:45,160 --> 00:21:46,030
卡爾
Carl.

250
00:21:48,880 --> 00:21:49,830
不
No.

251
00:22:27,580 --> 00:22:31,790
我們遲早會殺出一條血路出去
Sooner or later, we're fighting our way out.

252
00:22:35,190 --> 00:22:37,850
-我知道你心里非常清楚  -是啊
- I know that you're fully aware that we will. - Yeah...

253
00:22:39,300 --> 00:22:40,310
我們會的
We will.

254
00:22:42,350 --> 00:22:43,410
但不包括你
Not you.

255
00:22:45,010 --> 00:22:46,840
-在我看來...  -尤金
- Well, by my reckoning-- - Eugene.

256
00:22:50,520 --> 00:22:51,910
得了吧
Come on.

257
00:23:05,680 --> 00:23:07,180
它們正在往槍聲的地方走
They're moving towards the gunfire.

258
00:23:10,260 --> 00:23:11,330
那聲尖叫
That shout.

259
00:23:12,770 --> 00:23:15,120
我估計有些人還以為他們能抵抗一下呢
I suppose someone thought they could put up a fight.

260
00:23:16,170 --> 00:23:17,690
我想你們都是這么想的
I guess you all thought that.

261
00:23:17,690 --> 00:23:19,490
我們的確抵抗了
We did put up a fight.

262
00:23:21,160 --> 00:23:22,880
所以你的朋友們都死了
That's why your friends are dead.

263
00:23:23,680 --> 00:23:24,600
是啊
Yeah.

264
00:23:26,420 --> 00:23:29,310
我們應該再等一等  再觀望一會兒
We should've waited and watched a little longer.

265
00:23:30,590 --> 00:23:32,010
我太自私了
I was selfish.

266
00:23:33,920 --> 00:23:36,190
但也許如果我不那么自私
But maybe if I wasn't so selfish,

267
00:23:36,610 --> 00:23:38,300
就根本不會得到救治
I wouldn't have got that IV.

268
00:23:43,850 --> 00:23:46,610
我們得找個缺口出去
We're gonna find a gap a go.

269
00:23:47,080 --> 00:23:49,780
登上那座哨塔  翻到墻的那一邊
Up that guard tower and over the wall.

270
00:23:53,050 --> 00:23:55,180
你不用害怕
You don't need to be afraid.

271
00:23:58,060 --> 00:23:59,260
去死吧
Go to hell.

272
00:24:00,240 --> 00:24:01,400
你得知道
You need to know

273
00:24:01,990 --> 00:24:04,300
在外面遠比里面安全
it's safer out there than it is in here.

274
00:24:04,450 --> 00:24:05,830
開始走吧
Start moving.

275
00:24:06,380 --> 00:24:07,640
開始走
Start moving.

276
00:24:13,850 --> 00:24:17,010
現在  直接走到那個護柱下面
Now, straight up that guard post

277
00:24:17,010 --> 00:24:19,610
千萬別停
and do not stop.

278
00:24:19,750 --> 00:24:20,510
走吧
Go.

279
00:24:21,790 --> 00:24:22,630
該死的
Shit!

280
00:24:47,790 --> 00:24:49,930
快走  跟我一起
Let's go. Come with me, now.

281
00:24:49,930 --> 00:24:53,050
你把我送到醫務室  我可以救你的命
You get me to the infirmary, I save your life.

282
00:24:53,800 --> 00:24:55,180
我會救你的
I'll save your life.

283
00:25:46,240 --> 00:25:47,800
你曾經有個孩子
You had a child.

284
00:25:49,810 --> 00:25:50,770
對吧
Right?

285
00:25:54,980 --> 00:25:56,080
還有丈夫
A husband?

286
00:26:03,730 --> 00:26:06,800
我之前并非有意傷害你  我只是不得不阻止你
I didn't want to hurt you, I just had to stop you.

287
00:26:06,800 --> 00:26:10,040
你救他是為了你自己  不是為了我們
You saved him for you, not us.

288
00:26:12,620 --> 00:26:14,470
如果是為了我們  你就會...
If it was for us, you would've...

289
00:26:24,030 --> 00:26:25,920
我應該殺了你的
I should've killed you.

290
00:26:27,380 --> 00:26:28,690
我真該那么做的
I should've.

291
00:26:38,340 --> 00:26:39,610
你殺不了
You can't.

292
00:26:55,030 --> 00:26:56,610
醫務室就在巷子對面
The infirmary's right across the alley.

293
00:26:56,610 --> 00:26:58,510
我們必須立刻把你弄過去
We need to get you there now.

294
00:27:03,100 --> 00:27:05,870
那個梯子周圍沒有行尸  我本可以爬上去的
The ladder was clear. Could've made it.

295
00:27:05,870 --> 00:27:07,400
你為了我而回頭
You turned back for me.

296
00:27:08,710 --> 00:27:10,760
或許是因為你需要醫生
Maybe it was because you needed a doctor,

297
00:27:11,930 --> 00:27:13,650
或許是因為你變了
or maybe you changed.

298
00:27:16,180 --> 00:27:17,130
你準備好了嗎
You ready?

299
00:27:32,590 --> 00:27:34,590
走  快走
Come on! Come on!

300
00:27:35,970 --> 00:27:38,300
走  快走
Go! Go!

301
00:27:39,370 --> 00:27:40,670
快走啊
Go!

302
00:27:50,660 --> 00:27:51,710
快  進來
Come on, come on.

303
00:27:51,840 --> 00:27:53,010
你沒事吧
You okay?

304
00:27:53,010 --> 00:27:55,460
我沒事  我的病人們怎么樣了
I'm fine. How are my patients?

305
00:27:55,610 --> 00:27:57,880
他們挺好的  我們把他們轉移到樓上了以防萬一
They're doing well. We moved them upstairs just in case.

306
00:27:57,970 --> 00:27:59,140
天啊
Oh, my god.

307
00:28:08,070 --> 00:28:09,150
是那個孩子
It's the kid.

308
00:28:09,580 --> 00:28:10,570
他被咬了嗎
Is he bit?

309
00:28:15,290 --> 00:28:16,390
沒有
Nope.

310
00:28:16,860 --> 00:28:18,230
怎么了
What?

311
00:28:18,230 --> 00:28:19,490
我需要繃帶
I need bandages.

312
00:28:19,730 --> 00:28:21,550
就在水槽邊最高層的架子上
Top shelf, next to the sink.

313
00:28:21,550 --> 00:28:24,390
從冰箱里拿兩支注射液  干凈毛巾越多越好
Two IVs from the fridge and all the clean towels you can find.

314
00:28:24,390 --> 00:28:25,980
亞倫  把輪床推過來
Aaron, grab the gurney.

315
00:28:34,950 --> 00:28:36,350
這是槍傷嗎
This is a gunshot?

316
00:28:36,350 --> 00:28:38,170
手槍  近距離射擊
Handgun. Close range.

317
00:28:41,020 --> 00:28:42,370
求你救救他
Please save him.

318
00:28:42,660 --> 00:28:43,890
求你了
Please.

319
00:28:47,020 --> 00:28:48,210
那會把行尸引過來的
That's gonna draw them here.

320
00:28:48,210 --> 00:28:49,490
我需要光源
I need light.

321
00:28:50,230 --> 00:28:52,940
米瓊恩  拿毛巾來  準備好
Michonne, towel. Hold it here.

322
00:28:53,440 --> 00:28:54,930
我們需要壓住傷口
We need to keep pressure on the wound.

323
00:28:55,400 --> 00:28:57,750
我探進去縫合撕裂處
I'll go in and sew up any lacerations.

324
00:28:58,440 --> 00:28:59,720
就是這樣  就那里
Just like that, right here.

325
00:28:59,720 --> 00:29:02,370
斯賓塞  我需要那個平盤
Now, Spencer, I need that pan.

326
00:29:02,390 --> 00:29:04,340
就是托盤上的那個  很好
That one on the tray. Good.

327
00:29:04,640 --> 00:29:06,780
我要進行清洗和縫合
I'm going to clean and close this.

328
00:29:06,780 --> 00:29:09,980
米瓊恩  我弄到哪兒你就用毛巾跟著擦拭
Michonne, keep following me with the towel.

329
00:29:26,030 --> 00:29:27,240
你要干什么
What-- what are you doing?

330
00:29:27,880 --> 00:29:29,010
瑞克
Rick!

331
00:29:31,200 --> 00:29:32,490
瑞克
Rick!

332
00:29:57,840 --> 00:29:59,330
-瑞克在外面  -堅持住
- Rick's out there. - Hold on.

333
00:29:59,550 --> 00:30:01,520
-他需要我幫忙  -再縫一針
- He needs my help. - Just one more suture.

334
00:30:01,520 --> 00:30:02,450
但他在外面
But he's out there.

335
00:30:02,450 --> 00:30:05,050
這是他兒子  給我點時間
This is his son. Give me a second.

336
00:30:05,050 --> 00:30:05,990
他在孤軍奮戰
He's taking them all on.

337
00:30:05,990 --> 00:30:07,840
-我們得去幫他  -什么
- We have to go get him. - What?

338
00:30:08,370 --> 00:30:09,310
我們必須去
We have to.

339
00:30:09,770 --> 00:30:11,870
-就看這一戰了  -搞定了
- This is it. - Okay, got it.

340
00:31:07,130 --> 00:31:09,180
擊退它們  壓制它們
Knock 'em away. Drive 'em down.

341
00:31:14,280 --> 00:31:17,780
我們能打敗它們
We can beat'em. We can beat'em!

342
00:31:25,890 --> 00:31:27,850
擊退它們  就這樣
Drive 'em back. That's it.

343
00:31:28,130 --> 00:31:29,870
我們能一起做到
We can do this together!

344
00:31:35,360 --> 00:31:36,390
你能抱著她嗎
Will you take her?

345
00:31:39,240 --> 00:31:40,310
當然
Of course.

346
00:31:40,470 --> 00:31:42,690
跟我來  好的
Come with me. Okay, okay.

347
00:31:42,690 --> 00:31:44,820
-謝謝你  -沒事
- Thank you. - It's okay.

348
00:31:49,680 --> 00:31:50,790
加百利
Gabriel.

349
00:31:52,850 --> 00:31:54,150
你要干什么
What are you doing?

350
00:31:58,230 --> 00:32:01,630
我們一直在一起祈禱
We've been praying... together.

351
00:32:03,100 --> 00:32:06,110
祈禱上帝能拯救我們的小鎮
Praying that god will save our town.

352
00:32:07,410 --> 00:32:09,290
我們的祈禱應驗了
Well, our prayers have been answered.

353
00:32:10,590 --> 00:32:12,540
上帝會拯救亞歷山大
God will save Alexandria...

354
00:32:14,770 --> 00:32:17,870
因為上帝給予了我們拯救自己的勇氣
because God has given us the courage to save it ourselves.

355
00:32:28,360 --> 00:32:30,110
前面的尸群散開了
Guys, it's thinning out there in front.

356
00:32:30,800 --> 00:32:31,770
我們得離開這里
We need to get out there.

357
00:32:31,770 --> 00:32:33,830
-瑞克在進行抵抗  -怎么抵抗
- Rick's making a stand. - How's that?

358
00:32:34,040 --> 00:32:36,780
他正在外面與米瓊恩他們一同戰斗
He's out there fighting them with Michonne and some others.

359
00:32:37,340 --> 00:32:38,280
是時候了
It's time.

360
00:32:38,860 --> 00:32:40,620
我要去巷子里
Up the alley. I'm going.

361
00:32:41,440 --> 00:32:42,880
丹妮斯很安全
Denise is safe.

362
00:32:43,080 --> 00:32:44,260
你看到她了嗎
Did you see her?

363
00:32:44,670 --> 00:32:46,820
她撐到醫務室了
Yeah, she made it to the infirmary.

364
00:32:47,230 --> 00:32:49,070
-我去幫瑞克  -我也去
- I'm gonna go help Rick. - I'm going, too.

365
00:32:49,540 --> 00:32:51,400
-我跟你一起  -那好  我也去
- I'm with you. - All right, me, too.

366
00:32:51,640 --> 00:32:54,450
-我跟著你  -尤金  你不必這么做
- Right behind you. - Eugene, you don't have to.

367
00:32:54,450 --> 00:32:56,060
這不對  我必須這么做
That's incorrect. I do.

368
00:32:56,720 --> 00:32:58,370
今天沒人能置身事外
No one gets to clock out today.

369
00:32:58,610 --> 00:33:02,290
該死  今天的事將被載入史冊
And, hell, this is a story people are gonna tell.

370
00:33:11,940 --> 00:33:13,210
這邊  快點
This way! Come on!

371
00:33:24,040 --> 00:33:25,270
抱歉
I'm sorry.

372
00:33:32,660 --> 00:33:33,770
不
No.

373
00:33:37,660 --> 00:33:38,690
去幫她
Go get her!

374
00:33:39,020 --> 00:33:40,220
去幫她
Go get her!

375
00:33:45,370 --> 00:33:46,460
來這邊
Over here!

376
00:33:48,500 --> 00:33:49,690
快點  這邊
Come on, here!

377
00:33:51,570 --> 00:33:53,180
-來這邊  -格倫
- Over here! - Glenn!

378
00:33:54,660 --> 00:33:56,860
不  格倫
No! Glenn!

379
00:33:58,220 --> 00:34:00,660
-格倫  -過來  來這邊  過來啊
- Glenn! - Come on! Over here, come on!

380
00:34:01,600 --> 00:34:02,690
瑪姬
Maggie!

381
00:34:03,690 --> 00:34:04,750
伊妮德
Enid!

382
00:34:06,660 --> 00:34:08,930
這邊  這邊  過來啊
Over here! Over here, come on.

383
00:34:13,880 --> 00:34:14,900
快點
Come on!

384
00:34:15,850 --> 00:34:17,480
快走  快翻過去
Just go! Just get over!

385
00:34:17,480 --> 00:34:18,780
-快走  -不
- Go! - No!

386
00:34:18,930 --> 00:34:20,010
快走
Go!

387
00:34:20,910 --> 00:34:21,970
快點
Come on!

388
00:34:28,560 --> 00:34:29,640
該死
Shit.

389
00:34:32,410 --> 00:34:33,820
-不  格倫  -快走
- No, Glenn! - Go!

390
00:34:34,280 --> 00:34:35,470
來這邊
Over here!

391
00:34:39,870 --> 00:34:40,960
格倫
Glenn!

392
00:34:42,300 --> 00:34:44,820
格倫
Glenn!

393
00:34:52,990 --> 00:34:54,240
你能把門打開嗎
Can you get the gate?

394
00:34:56,160 --> 00:34:57,500
謝謝  伙計
Appreciate it, pal.

395
00:35:06,800 --> 00:35:08,430
來吧  我們拉你
Come on, we got you.

396
00:35:16,870 --> 00:35:18,100
發生了什么
What the hell happened?

397
00:35:18,100 --> 00:35:19,330
我不知道  我剛回來
I don't know. I just got back.

398
00:35:20,570 --> 00:35:21,610
聽著
Listen...

399
00:35:22,410 --> 00:35:24,380
我們可以引開一部分行尸
We can-- we can lead some of them away,

400
00:35:24,610 --> 00:35:25,800
但是它們很分散
but they're scattered.

401
00:35:25,840 --> 00:35:27,370
不  我們一網打盡
No, we get 'em all together.

402
00:35:27,560 --> 00:35:28,890
不用引開它們
Won't have to lead 'em away.

403
00:36:35,460 --> 00:36:37,610
移動  后退
Move it! Back up!

404
00:36:41,860 --> 00:36:43,160
好  可以了
All right, that's it!

405
00:37:19,010 --> 00:37:20,300
別松懈
Don't let up!

406
00:39:36,330 --> 00:39:37,640
我錯了
I was wrong.

407
00:39:41,020 --> 00:39:45,250
我以為在墻內生活了這么久
I thought after living behind these walls for so long that...

408
00:39:48,340 --> 00:39:50,260
也許他們學不會了
Maybe they couldn't learn.

409
00:39:53,800 --> 00:39:55,100
但是今天
But today...

410
00:39:56,730 --> 00:39:58,780
我看到了他們能做什么
I saw what they could do,

411
00:40:00,010 --> 00:40:02,810
我們能做什么
What we could do,

412
00:40:04,050 --> 00:40:05,650
如果我們一起合作
If we work together.

413
00:40:08,290 --> 00:40:10,380
就可以重建這些墻
We'll rebuild the walls.

414
00:40:13,290 --> 00:40:15,270
擴建這些墻
We'll expand the walls.

415
00:40:17,300 --> 00:40:19,680
會有希望的  一定會有的
There will be more. There's gotta be more.

416
00:40:21,830 --> 00:40:24,240
迪安娜說的一切
Everything Deanna was talking about...

417
00:40:26,950 --> 00:40:28,420
都有可能
Is possible.

418
00:40:30,060 --> 00:40:32,890
全都有可能  我現在明白了
It's all possible. I see that now.

419
00:40:39,550 --> 00:40:41,050
當我在外面 
When I was out there...

420
00:40:43,940 --> 00:40:45,040
和他們在一起時
With them...

421
00:40:47,770 --> 00:40:49,350
當這一切結束
When it was over...

422
00:40:52,770 --> 00:40:57,410
我們重新奪回這個地方時
When I knew we had this place again...

423
00:41:00,490 --> 00:41:01,960
我心中有一種感覺
I had this feeling.

424
00:41:07,760 --> 00:41:09,450
我花了一段時間
It took me a while

425
00:41:10,660 --> 00:41:12,410
才想起來那感覺是什么
To remember what it was...

426
00:41:14,260 --> 00:41:16,070
因為自從我在醫院醒來后
Because I haven't felt it

427
00:41:16,640 --> 00:41:20,170
就再沒有過那種感覺了
Since before I woke up in that hospital bed.

428
00:41:23,950 --> 00:41:28,270
我想讓你看看新世界  卡爾
I want to show you the new world, Carl.

429
00:41:30,780 --> 00:41:34,780
我想為你使之成為現實
I want to make it a reality for you.

430
00:41:36,020 --> 00:41:39,910
求你了  卡爾
Please, Carl...

431
00:41:43,960 --> 00:41:45,280
讓我給你看看吧
Let me show you.

432
00:41:45,280 --> 00:41:48,760
求你了  兒子  別死
Plea-- please, son, don't die.

